Probably a vagrant
slept in the car
or just used it as a toilet.
Hey, man...
Are you gonna find
these guys, you know...
I mean, you got any
promising, uh, leads or...
Leads? Yeah, sure.
I'll just check with the boys
down at the crime lab.
They got four more detectives
working on the case.
They got us working in shifts.
Leads?
I hope the big Lebowski kills me
before the Germans
can cut my dick off.
That is just ridiculous, Dude.
No one'll cut your dick off.
- Thank you.
- Not if I have anything to say.
- That makes me feel secure.
- Dude.
- It makes me feel warm inside.
- Now, Dude.
This whole fuckin' thing.
I could be sitting here
with just pee stains on my rug.
- But, no, man, I gotta...
- Fucking Germans.
Nothing changes. Fucking Nazis.
They were Nazis, Dude?
Come on, Donny, they
were threatening castration.
- Are we gonna split hairs?
- No.
- Am I wrong?
- Well, he...
They were nihilists, man.
They kept saying
they believed in nothing.
Nihilists.
Fuck me.
Say what you want about the
tenets of national socialism,
at least it's an ethos.
And also,
let's not forget, Dude,
that keeping wildlife,
an amphibious rodent
for, you know, domestic...
within the city...
That ain't legal either.
- Are you a fucking park ranger?
- No, I'm just...
Who gives a shit
about the fucking marmot?
- We are sympathising, Dude.
- Fuck sympathy.
I don't need your fucking
sympathy. I need my johnson.
- What do you need that for?
- You've got to buck up!
You cannot drag this negative
energy into the tournament.
Fuck the tournament.
Fuck you, Walter.
Fuck the tournament?
OK, Dude. I can see you
don't want to be cheered up.
Come on, Donny.
Let's go get us a lane.
- Another Caucasian, Gary.
- Right, Dude.
Friends like these,
huh, Gary?
That's right, Dude.
Do you have a good Sarsaparilla?
Sioux City Sarsaparilla?
Yeah. That's a good one.
How you doin' there, Dude?
Not too good, man.
- One of those days, huh?
- Yeah.
Well...
A wiser fella than myself
once said,
"Sometimes you eat
the bar and..."
Much obliged.
"And sometimes the bar, well...
"he eats you."
That some kind of Eastern thing?
Far from it.
I like your style, Dude.
Hmm. Well...
I dig your style, too, man.
You got
a whole cowboy thing going.
Thankee.
- There's just one thing, Dude.
- What's that?
Do you have to use
so many cuss words?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
OK, Dude, have it your way.
Take her easy, Dude.
Yeah. Thanks, man.
Call for you, Dude.
Hello?
'Jeffrey, you have
not gone to the doctor.'
Uh, oh, yeah.
No... no, I haven't yet.
'I'd like to
see you immediately.'
Oh?
- So you're Lebowski.
- Yeah.
Maude has told me all about you.
She'll be back
in a minute. Sit down.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yeah, sure. White Russian.
The bar's over there.
- So what do you do, Lebowski?
- Who the fuck are you, man?
Just a friend of Maudie's.
The friend
with the cleft asshole?
What do you do?
Oh, nothing much.
Hello, Jeffrey.
Yeah, how are you?
Listen, Maude,
I got to, uh...
tender my resignation
or whatever.
It looks like your mother
really was kidnapped after all.
She most certainly was not.
Hey, man,
why don't you fucking...
listen occasionally?
You might learn something.
- Now, I got...
- Don't call her my mother.
She's the perpetrator
and not the victim.
I got pretty
definitive evidence...
- From who?
- From the main guy, Uli.
Uli Kunkel? Her co... star
in the beaver picture?
Beaver? You mean vagina...
I mean, you know the guy?
I might have introduced them
for all I know.
Do you remember Uli?
He's a musician.
Used to have a group, Autobahn.
They released
one album in the late 70s.
Their music is
sort of a... technopop.
So he's pretending
to be the abductor?
- Well, yeah.
- Look, Jeffrey,
you don't kidnap someone
you're acquainted with.
The idea is that the hostage
can't identify you
- after you've let them go.
- I know that.
What the fuck
is with this guy? Who is he?
Knox Harrington.
The video artist.
- So Uli has the money?
- Well...
No, not exactly...
This is a very
complicated case, Maude.
A lot of ins and outs
and what... have... yous...
A lot of strands
to keep in my head.
in old Duder's head.
Then who has the money?
It's Sandra, about the Biennale.
I have to take this. Do you
have that doctor's number?
- It's not bruised any more.
- Please, Jeffrey,
I don't want to be responsible
for any delayed after... effects.
After... effects?
Could you slide your shorts
down, Mr Lebowski, please?
No, man. She hit me right here.
I understand.
Could you slide
your shorts down, please?
He lives in North Hollywood,
on Radford,
near the In 'n' Out Burger.
The In 'n' Out Burger's
on Camrose.
- Near it.
- Those are good burgers.
Shut the fuck up, Donny.
The kid's in ninth grade,
and his father...
Are you ready for this? His
father is Arthur Digby Sellers.
Who the fuck is that?
Who the fuck is
Arthur Digby Sellers?
Ever heard of a show
called "Branded"?
"All but one man died
there at Bitter Creek"?
I know the fucking show.
So what?
Fucking Arthur Digby Sellers
wrote 156 episodes, Dude.
The bulk of the series.
- Not exactly a lightweight.
- No.
And yet his son
is a fucking dunce.
We'll go there
after the what... have... you,
we'll brace the kid.
We'll be near
the In 'n' Out Burger.
Shut the fuck up, Donny!
We'll brace the kid.
He should be a pushover.
We'll get that fucking
$1 million back...
If he hasn't spent it already.
A million fucking clams.
- Yes, we'll be near the, uh...
- In 'n' Out.
Some burgers, some beers,
a few laughs.
Our fucking troubles
are over, Dude.
Oh, fuck me, man!
That kid's already spent
all the money, man!
New 'vette? Hardly, Dude.
I'd say he still has
960, $970,000 left,
depending on the options.
Wait in the car, Donny.
- Yes?
- Pilar?
My name is Walter Sobchak.
This is my associate
Jeffrey Lebowski.
We came to talk about
little Larry. May we come in?
- Yes, yes.
- Thank you.
That's him, Dude.
And a good day to you, sir!
Sit down, please.
Larry, sweetie,
that man is here!
Is he... Does he still write?
Oh, no, no.
He has health problems.
Sir, I just want to say
that we're both,
on a personal level,
really enormous fans.
"Branded", especially
the early episodes,
was truly a source
of inspiration...
Sweetie, sit down!
This is the police.
Oh, no, ma'am,
we are not exactly the police.
We hope it won't
be necessary to call the police.
But that's up
to little Larry here.
Isn't it, Larry?
Is this your homework, Larry?
- Is this your homework?
- Look, man...
Dude, please.
Is this your homework, Larry?
Just ask him about the car.
- Is this your homework, Larry?
- Is that your car out front?
- We know it's his homework!
Where's the fucking money?
Look, Larry...
Have you heard of Vietnam?
You're entering
a world of pain, son.
We know that you stole the car.
- And the fucking money!
- And the fucking money.
We know that this
is your homework.
- We'll cut your dick off.
- You're killing your father.
All right. This is pointless.
OK? It's time for plan B.
You might want to watch out
that front window, Larry.
Son, this is what happens
when you fuck a stranger
in the ass!
Little language problem here.
The little prick's
stonewalling me.
Walter!
What... what are you doing, man?
What are you doing?
Here you go, Larry.
You see what happens?
You see what happens, Larry?
This is what happens
when you fuck a stranger
in the ass, Larry!
This is what happens, Larry!
You see what happens, Larry,
when you fuck a stranger
in the ass?
This is what happens.
You see what happens, Larry?
Do you see what happens, Larry,
when you fuck a stranger
in the ass?
This is what happens, Larry!
- No!
- This is what happens, Larry!
This is what happens
when you fuck a stranger...
What the fuck
are you doing? Stop it!
I just bought
that fucking car last week!
I'm gonna fuckin' kill you!
I just bought
the fucking car last week!
I'll kill your
fucking car, man!
No! That's not his... hey!
- God damn it!
- No! Oh, no!
Fuck you! You like that?
Fuck you!
I kill your fucking car!
I accept your apology.
No. I just... want to
handle it by myself from now on.
No, no, no.
That has nothing to do with it.
Yes, the car made it home.
You're calling me at home.
No, Walter, it did not look
like Larry was about to crack.
Well, that's your perception.
You know, Walter, you're right.
There is an unspoken message
here. It's "Fuck you"!
Leave me the fuck alone!
Yeah, I'll be at practice.
Pin your diapers on. Jackie
Treehorn wants to see you.
Jackie Treehorn knows
which Lebowski you are.
Jackie Treehorn wants to see
the deadbeat Lebowski.
You're not dealing with morons.
Hello, Dude. Thanks for coming.
I'm Jackie Treehorn.
This is quite a pad
you got here, man.
Completely unspoiled.
- What's your drink, Dude?
- White Russian. Thanks.
White Russian.
How's the smut business, Jackie?
I wouldn't know, Dude.
I deal in publishing,
entertainment,
political advocacy.
- Oh. Which one's "Logjammin"'?
- Yes, regrettably, it's true.
Standards have fallen
in adult entertainment.
It's video, Dude.
Now that we're
competing with amateurs,
we can't afford to invest
in extras, like story,
production value,
feelings.
You know, people forget
that the brain is
the biggest erogenous zone.
On you maybe.
You have to take
the good with the bad.
New technology permits us
to do exciting things
in interactive erotic software.
Wave of the future, Dude.
100% electronic.
Well...
I still jerk off manually.
Of course you do.
I can see you're anxious
for me to get to the point.
Well, here it is, Dude.
Where's Bunny?
- I thought you might know that.
- Why would I?
She ran off to get away from
that sizeable debt to me.
She didn't run off.
She's been...
I've heard that story.
I know you're
mixed up in this, Dude.
I don't care what you're
trying to get from the husband.
That's your business.
All I'm saying is...
- I want mine.
- Yeah, right, man.
There are a lot of...
facets to this,
a lot of interested parties.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Where's that?
All right.
Excuse me.
- Forgive me.
- No problemo, man.
So, uh...
If I, uh, can find your money...
What's in it for the Dude?
Of course, there's that
to discuss. Refill?
The Pope shit in the woods?
10% finder's fee.
That all right?
OK. Done, Jackie.
I dig the way
you do business, man.
Your money is being held
by a kid named Larry Sellers.
He lives in North Hollywood,
on Radford, uh...
by the In 'n' Out Burger.
A fuckin' brat,
but I'm sure
you can get it off him.
I mean, he's 15.
Flunking social studies.
So, if you could just, uh...
write me a cheque
for my 10% of half a million...
five grand...
I'll go out and mingle.
You mix a hell
of a Caucasian, Jackie.
A 15... year... old kid.
Is this some sort of a joke?
No, no joke.
No funny stuff, Jackie.
The kid's got it.
Hi, fellas.
The kid just wanted a car.
All the Dude ever wanted
was his rug back.
I'm not greedy.
It really...
tied the room together.
Darkness washed over the Dude.
Darker than
a black steer's tookus
on a moonless prairie night.
There was no bottom.
Branded!
Is this your only I. D?
I know my rights, man.
- You don't know shit, Lebowski.
- I want a fucking lawyer, man.
I want... Bill Kunstler, man...
or Ron Coobie.
Mr Treehorn tells us
that he had to eject you
from his garden party,
that you were drunk
and abusive.
Mr Treehorn treats objects
like women, man.
Mr Treehorn draws
a lot of water in this town.
You don't draw shit, Lebowski.
We got a nice quiet
little beach community here,
and I aim to keep it
nice and quiet.
So let me make something plain.
I don't like you sucking around,
bothering our citizens,
Lebowski.
I don't like your jerk... off name,
I don't like your jerk... off face,
I don't like
your jerk... off behaviour,
and I don't like you... Jerk... off.
Do I make myself clear?
I'm sorry. I wasn't listening.
Fucking fascist!
Stay out of Malibu, Lebowski!
Stay out of Malibu, deadbeat!
Keep your ugly goldbricking ass
out of my beach community.
Jesus... Man, could you
change the channel.
If you don't like my music,
get your own fucking cab!
I'll pull over
and kick your ass out.
I had a rough night,
and I hate the fucking Eagles.
Out of my fucking cab!
Out! Get...
Hey... man!
Man, hey!
Oh... Jesus.
Jeffrey.
Maude?
Love me.
Uh, that's my robe.
Tell me about yourself, Jeffrey.
Well, not much to tell.
I, um, I was one of the authors
of the Port Huron statement.
The original
Port Huron statement.
Not the compromised
second draft.
Uh, and then I, uh,
you ever hear of the Seattle 7?
That was me.
And, um, the six other guys.
Um... and then,
ah, music business briefly.
- Yeah, a roadie for Metallica.
- Oh.
- "Speed of Sound" tour.
- Mm... hmm.
Bunch of assholes.
Uh, and then, you know,
a little of this,
a little of that.
My career's slowed down
a little lately.
What do you do for recreation?
Oh, the usual.
Bowl, drive around.
The occasional acid flashback.
What happened to your house?
Oh, Jackie Treehorn
trashed the place.
He thought I had
your father's money.
He got me out of the way
while he looked for it.
- Cocktail?
- No, thanks.
It's not my father's money.
It's the Foundation's.
Why did he think you have it?
And who does?
Larry Sellers,
this high school kid.
Real fucking brat.
You know, this is a very
complicated case, Maude.
Lotta ins, lotta outs.
You know, fortunately,
I'm adhering
to a pretty strict...
drug regiment to keep
my mind, you know,
uh, limber, you know.
Very close
to your father's money.
It's the Foundation's money.
Father doesn't have any.
What are you talking about?
He's loaded.
No, no, the wealth
was all mother's.
No, he runs stuff, uh...
We did let him run a company,
but he didn't do very well.
- No, he's...
- He administers the charities,
and I give him
a reasonable allowance.
He has no money of his own.
I know how he presents himself.
Father's weakness is vanity.
- Hence, the slut.
- Uh, do you think he, uh...
What is that, yoga?
It increases
the chances of conception.
- Increases?
- Well, yes.
What did you think this
was about? Fun and games?
I want a child.
OK, yeah, OK, but let me...
Let me explain
something about the Dude.
Look, Jeffrey,
I don't want a partner.
I don't want the father
to be someone I have to see,
or who has any interest
in raising the child himself.
Oh, so that doctor...
Exactly.
Now, what happened to your face?
Did Jackie Treehorn
do that as well?
No, uh, it was
the Chief of Police of Malibu.
A real reactionary.
So, your father...
- Yeah, I get it. Yeah, yeah.
- What?
Oh, man, my thinking
about this case
had become very uptight.
Yeah, your father.
Jeffrey,
what are you talking about?
Jeffrey!
Walter, if you're there,
pick up the fucking phone.
Come on.
Pick it up, man,
this is an emergency.
'Dude? '
I'm at my place. I need you
to come and pick me up.
'I can't drive, Dude,
it's Erev Shabbos.'
- What?
- 'Erev Shabbos.'
- 'I can't drive.'
- Man!
'I'm not supposed
to pick up the phone
- 'unless it's an emergency.'
- This is a fucking emergency!
'That's why
I picked up the phone.'
Walter, you fuck,
we gotta go to Pasadena.
Pick me up
or I'm off the bowling team.
Get out of that
fucking car, man.
Get out of that fucking car!
Get the fuck out
of the car, man.
Get out of the fucking...
Who the fuck are you, man?
Easy, man. Relax, man.
No physical harm intended.
Who the fuck are you?
Why are you following me around?
Come on, fuckhead.
Relax, man.
I'm a brother Seamus.
Brother Seamus?
Like an Irish monk?
What the fuck are you
talking about?
My name is Da Fino. I'm a
private snoop, like you, man.
- What?
- A dick, man.
Let me tell you something.
I dig your work.
Playing one side
against the other.
In bed with everybody.
Fabulous stuff.
I'm not! Fuck it.
Just stay away
from my lady friend.
I'm not messing
with your special lady.
She's not my special lady.
I'm just helping her conceive.
- I'm not...
- Who are you working for?
Lebowski? Jackie Treehorn?
The Knutsens.
The... who the fuck
are the Knutsens?
The Knutsens.
It's a wandering... daughter job.
Bunny Lebowski, man.
Her real name is Fawn Knutsen.
Her parents want her back.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Crazy, huh? Ran away
about a year ago.
The Knutsens told me to
show her this when I found her.
It's the family farm
outside of Moorhead, Minnesota.
They think it'll
make her homesick.
How are you gonna keep 'em down
once they've seen Karl Hungus?
- She's been kidnapped, Da Fino.
- Oh, man.
Maybe not, but she's not around.
Hey, maybe you and me
could pool our resources.
Trade information.
Professional courtesy.
Compeers, you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Fuck off, Da Fino.
And stay away from my special...
from my fucking
lady friend, man.
Ze lingonberry pancakes.
Lingonberry pancakes.
Sree pigs in blanket.
She has lingonberry pancakes.
We totally fucked it up, man.
We fucked up his payoff,
we pissed off the kidnappers,
and Lebowski, he yelled at me
but he didn't do anything, huh?
Well, sometimes
it's a cathartic...
If he knows I'm a fuck... up,
why does he ask me
to get his wife back?
Because he doesn't
want her back.
He's had enough.
He no longer digs her.
But then,
why doesn't he give a shit
about his million bucks?
I mean, he knows we never
handed off his briefcase,
but he never asked for it back.
The million bucks was
never in the briefcase.
The briefcase was
fucking empty, man.
The asshole was hoping
that they would kill her.
You threw out a ringer
for a ringer.
How does
this add up to an emergency?
Huh?
I see what you're
getting at, Dude,
he kept the money.
My point is...
here we are, it's Shabbos,
which I'm allowed to break
only if it's a matter
of life or death.
Come off it.
You're not even fucking Jewish.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
You're fucking Polish... Catholic.
I converted when I married
Cynthia. Come on.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know this.
Five years ago,
you were divorced.
So when you get divorced,
you return your library card?
You get a new licence?
You stop being Jewish?
- This is the driveway.
- I'm Jewish as fucking Tevyé.
Man, it's all a part
of your sick Cynthia thing.
Taking care of her fucking dog.
Going to her fucking synagogue.
You're living in the past.
3,000 years
of beautiful tradition
from Moses to Sandy Koufax,
damn right I'm living
in the fucking past! I... Jesus.
What the hell happened?
Where was she, man?
Visiting friends
in Palm Springs.
She just left.
Never bothered to tell us.
I guess the nihilist
knew where she was.
She never
even kidnapped herself.
- Who is this gentleman, Dude?
- Who am I? A fucking veteran.
You shouldn't go in, Dude.
He's very angry.
So, man...
So, she's back,
no thanks to you.
- Where's the fucking money?
- A million bucks
from fucking needy little
urban achievers! You are scum!
- Who the hell is he?
- Who am I?
I'm the guy that's gonna kick
your goldbricking ass!
The briefcase was empty.
You kept the money for yourself.
You have your story,
I have mine.
I entrusted the money
to you, and you stole it.
As if we would ever
take your bullshit money!
You thought Bunny had been
kidnapped, and you were glad.
You could make
some money disappear.
You needed was a sap
to pin it on.
You just met me.
You... human paraquat!
You figured,
"Oh, here's a loser."
Somebody the square community
won't give a shit about.
- Well, aren't you?
- Well, yeah, but...
Get out, both of you.
Look at that phony.
Pretending to be a millionaire.
Out of this house now, you bums!
Let me tell you something.
I've seen
a lot of spinals, Dude,
and this guy's a fake.
A fucking goldbricker.
- Stay away from me!
- This guy fucking walks.
- I've never been more certain.
- Stay away!
Walter, for Christ's sake,
man, he's a cripple.
Get away from me!
- Put him down, man!
- Yeah, I'll put him down!
Rauss! Achtung, baby!
Come on, help me
put him back in his chair.
Sure, you'll see
some tank battles.
Fighting in desert
is very different
from fighting in jungle.
'Nam was a foot soldier's war,
whereas this thing should,
you know, be a piece of cake.
I mean, I had an M16 Jacko,
not an Abrams fucking tank.
Me and Charlie,
eyeball to eyeball.
- Yeah.
- That's fuckin' combat.
The man in
the black pyjamas, Dude.
Worthy fuckin' adversary.
- Who's in pyjamas, Walter?
- Shut the fuck up, Donny.
Whereas, what we have here...
Fig... eaters wearing
towels on their heads,
trying to find reverse
on a Soviet tank.
- This... this is not a worthy...
- Hey!
What's this day... of... rest shit?
What's this bullshit?!
I don't fuckin' care!
It don't matter to Jesus.
But you not fooling me, man.
You might fool
the league office,
but you don't fool Jesus.
It's bush league
psyche... out stuff.
Laughable, man.
I would have fucked you
in the ass Saturday.
I'll fuck you in the ass
next Wednesday instead.
Whoo! You got a date
Wednesday, baby.
He's cracking.
The whole concept of Asia.
Many learned men
have disputed this,
but in the 14th Century,
the Rabahm, he...
Well, they finally did it.
They killed my fucking car.
We want ze money, Lebowski.
Ja, otherwise, we kill ze girl.
Ja, it seems you have
forgotten our little deal.
You don't have
the fucking girl, dipshit.
< We know you never did.
Are these the Nazis?
No, nihilists.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Ve don't care. Ve still
want the money, Lebowski,
or we'll fuck you up.
Fuck you.
Fuck the three of yous.
No, without a hostage,
there is no ransom.
That's what ransom is.
Those are the fucking rules.
His girlfriend gave up her toe.
She zought
we'd be getting $1 million.
It's not fair.
Fair? Who's the fucking
nihilist around here,
you bunch of fucking crybabies.
Cool it, Walter. Hey, look, pal,
there never was any money.
The big Lebowski
gave me an empty briefcase,
so take it up with him, man.
I would like my undies back.
- Are these guys gonna hurt us?
- No, these men are cowards.
OK, so we take
ze money you have on you
and we calls it even.
Fuck you.
No, Walter, come on.
We're ending this cheap, man.
- No, what's mine is mine.
- Come on, Walter.
- No funny stuff.
- All right, I got...
- uh, 4 bucks, almost 5.
- I got $18.
What's mine is mine.
We fuck you up, man.
We takes the money.
Come and get it.
We fuck you up.
Show me what you got, nihilist.
I fuck you.
Come on, he's got a sword.
Dipshit with a nine... toed woman.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
I fuck you, I!
Take it easy, man.
Here's the $4.
I got a fucking ball, man.
Anti... Semite!
I fuck you in ze ass.
I fuck you! I fuck you!
We got a man down, Dude.
God, they shot him, man.
- No, Dude.
- They shot Donny?
There weren't any shots fired.
It's a heart attack.
Call the medics, Dude.
I'd go myself, but I'm
pumping blood. Might pass out.
Rest easy, good buddy,
you're doing fine.
We got help choppering in.
Hello, gentlemen.
You are the bereaved?
Yeah, man.
Francis Donnelly.
Pleased to meet you.
Jeff Lebowski.
Walter Sobchak.
The Dude, actually, is, uh...
- Excuse me?
- Oh, nothing.
Yes, I understand
you're taking away the remains.
Yeah.
We have the urn.
I assume this is credit card.
Yeah.
What's this?
That's for the urn.
Don't need it.
We're scattering the ashes.
Yes, so we were informed.
However, we must, of course,
transmit the remains
to you in a receptacle.
This is $180.
It is our most...
modestly priced receptacle.
- Can we just, uh...
- $180?
- They range up to 3,000.
- Uh, we're, uh, ahem...
Can't we just
rent it from you?
Sir, this is a mortuary,
not a rental house.
We're scattering the ashes!
Just because we're bereaved,
doesn't make us saps!
Sir, please, lower your voices.
Man, don't you have, you know,
something else we could
put him in, you know?
That is our most...
modestly priced receptacle.
Goddamn it!
Is there a Ralph's around here?
Donny was a good bowler
and a good man.
He was one of us.
He was a man who loved
the outdoors... and bowling.
As a surfer,
he explored the beaches
of Southern California,
from La Jolla to Leo Carrillo
and up to Pismo.
He died... he died as so
many men of his generation,
before his time.
In your wisdom, Lord,
you took him.
As you took so many bright,
flowering young men
at Khe Sanh, at Lan Doc,
and Hill 364.
These young men
gave their lives.
So did Donny.
Donny who loved bowling.
And so...
Theodore Donald Karabotsos,
in accordance
with what we think
your dying wishes
might well have been,
we commit your final,
mortal remains
to the bosom
of the Pacific Ocean,
which you loved so well.
Goodnight, sweet prince.
Shit.
Oh, shit, Dude, I'm sorry.
- Goddamn wind.
- Goddamn it, Walter.
- You fucking asshole!
- Dude, I'm sorry.
Everything's
a fucking travesty with you.
Sorry. It was an accident.
What was that shit
about Vietnam?
What does anything
have to do with Vietnam?
What the fuck
were you talking about?
Dude, I'm sorry.
Fuckin'...
Fuck, Walter.
Come on, Dude.
Hey, fuck it, man.
Let's go bowling.
Two oat sodas, Gary.
- Good luck tomorrow.
- Yeah, thanks, man.
I'm sorry to hear about Donny.
Oh, well, yeah, you know,
sometimes you eat the bar
and sometimes, you know...
Hey, man!
Howdy doo, Dude.
I wondered if I'd see you again.
I wouldn't miss the semis.
How have things been going?
Strikes and gutters,
ups and downs.
- Sure. I gotcha.
- Yeah.
Thanks, Gary.
Well, take care, man.
Gotta get back.
- Sure. Take it easy, Dude.
- Oh, yeah.
I know that you will.
Yeah, well, the Dude abides.
The Dude abides.
I don't know about you,
but I take comfort in that.
It's good knowing
he's out there, the Dude.
Takin' her easy
for all us sinners.
Shoosh.
I sure hope he makes the finals.
Well, that about does her.
Wraps her all up.
Things seem to have worked out
good for the Dude and Walter.
It was a pretty good story,
don't you think?
Made me laugh to beat the band.
Parts, anyway.
I didn't like seeing Donny go.
But then I happen to know
that there's
a little Lebowski on the way.
I guess that's how
the whole darn human comedy
keeps perpetuating itself
down through the generations.
Westward the wagons,
across the sands
of time until we...
Oh, look at me.
I'm ramblin' again.
Well, I hope you folks
enjoyed yourselves.
Catch ya later on
down the trail.
Say, friend, you got any more
of that good Sarsaparilla?
DVD subtitles by
European Captioning Institute