1
00:00:09,000 --> 00:00:14,000


2
00:00:22,000 --> 00:00:27,500


3
00:00:37,640 --> 00:00:39,039
Start talking.

4
00:00:39,040 --> 00:00:40,799
I'm not sure if we're on the air.

5
00:00:40,800 --> 00:00:42,919
This is a series of explosions...

6
00:00:42,920 --> 00:00:45,919
We're being told this is a major incident.

7
00:00:45,920 --> 00:00:47,999
The emergency is a major incident.

8
00:00:48,000 --> 00:00:49,719
bright lights and an orange glow.

9
00:00:49,720 --> 00:00:51,759
That was the moment the meteor hit.

10
00:00:51,760 --> 00:00:54,839
It does now appear to be a major attack.

11
00:00:54,840 --> 00:00:56,959
Since they landed outside Hamburg five years ago,

12
00:00:56,960 --> 00:01:01,359
they have steadily advanced across Europe. We've suffered millions of casualties.

13
00:01:01,360 --> 00:01:05,279
The evacuation of key government officials continuing.

14
00:01:05,280 --> 00:01:07,119
Nothing has stopped their advance.

15
00:01:07,120 --> 00:01:09,439
In human costs, the Europeans have paid the highest price.

16
00:01:09,440 --> 00:01:12,959
They have the ability to mimic and even anticipate our actions.

17
00:01:12,960 --> 00:01:14,999
If we do not defeat them in France...

18
00:01:15,000 --> 00:01:18,299
we'll be fighting them in the streets of London, then New York, then Tokyo.

19
00:01:19,440 --> 00:01:21,159
All of humanity's at stake.

20
00:01:21,160 --> 00:01:23,679
After five years we finally have a victory.

21
00:01:23,680 --> 00:01:26,239
These pictures are just in from Verdun.

22
00:01:26,240 --> 00:01:28,519
One of the striking things was how low casualties were

23
00:01:28,520 --> 00:01:30,359
and how little damage...

24
00:01:30,360 --> 00:01:33,103
We have seen a stunning victory here today.

25
00:01:33,320 --> 00:01:37,679
How do you convince people that this is a fight that can be won?

26
00:01:37,680 --> 00:01:39,759
This is an alien invasion in a global war.

27
00:01:39,760 --> 00:01:42,399
With the new jacket technology and limited training,

28
00:01:42,400 --> 00:01:45,189
we've been able to create super-soldiers.

29
00:01:45,200 --> 00:01:47,599
Look at Rita Vrataski, the Angel of Verdun.

30
00:01:47,600 --> 00:01:50,319
They're calling her the Angel of Verdun.

31
00:01:50,320 --> 00:01:52,839
She is seen as the new hope for this war.

32
00:01:52,840 --> 00:01:54,279
It's extraordinary.

33
00:01:54,280 --> 00:01:56,759
With the new jacket technology and limited training,

34
00:01:56,760 --> 00:01:58,999
Rita Vrataski was able to kill

35
00:01:59,000 --> 00:02:01,039
hundreds of mimics on only her first day.

36
00:02:01,040 --> 00:02:03,279
Is the tide of this war changing?

37
00:02:03,280 --> 00:02:06,719
The Army attribute this success to a revolutionary new technology:

38
00:02:06,720 --> 00:02:08,619
The Exosuit jacket.

39
00:02:08,100 --> 00:02:10,300


40
00:02:10,760 --> 00:02:14,319
She was able to kill hundreds of mimics on only her first day in combat.

41
00:02:14,320 --> 00:02:16,919
Imagine an army of Rita Vrataskis.

42
00:02:16,920 --> 00:02:20,879
We're managing to hold them back at the English Channel, but for how long?

43
00:02:20,880 --> 00:02:24,479
Of course this is dangerous talk, and it's easy to understand why people are suspicious about this invasion.

44
00:02:24,480 --> 00:02:26,079
Over 17 nations have joined the United Defense Force

45
00:02:26,080 --> 00:02:29,439
- which hopes to push them back, once and for all.  - We've got them contained.

46
00:02:29,440 --> 00:02:32,479
And with this new technology, we're gonna defeat them.

47
00:02:32,480 --> 00:02:36,479
Operation Downfall is going to be the largest mechanized invasion in history.

48
00:02:36,480 --> 00:02:40,907
We will be victorious. We fight. That's what we do.

49
00:02:41,000 --> 00:02:45,300


50
00:03:36,040 --> 00:03:39,799
Major William Cage, United States Military Media.

51
00:03:39,800 --> 00:03:41,300
Welcome to London, major.

52
00:03:41,310 --> 00:03:43,300


53
00:03:48,680 --> 00:03:51,389
The general will see you now.

54
00:03:51,640 --> 00:03:53,621
Thank you.

55
00:03:54,440 --> 00:03:56,519
Operation Downfall.

56
00:03:56,520 --> 00:04:00,759
The entire might of the UDF, invading from France, the Mediterranean, Scandinavia...

57
00:04:00,760 --> 00:04:02,839
relieving pressure on the eastern front...

58
00:04:02,840 --> 00:04:05,399
allowing the Russians and Chinese to push the enemy back.

59
00:04:05,400 --> 00:04:10,959
We all meet in the middle exterminating this mimic scourge along the way.

60
00:04:10,960 --> 00:04:13,479
A lot of good soldiers are gonna die tomorrow, major.

61
00:04:13,480 --> 00:04:15,079
When all the smoke clears...

62
00:04:15,080 --> 00:04:17,719
and the body bags start coming home, people tend to look for someone to blame...

63
00:04:17,720 --> 00:04:19,599
someone like me.

64
00:04:19,600 --> 00:04:22,799
Ideally, I'd prefer a different scenario.

65
00:04:22,800 --> 00:04:24,303
Please.

66
00:04:24,840 --> 00:04:28,266
A best-selling memoir, perhaps.

67
00:04:29,000 --> 00:04:31,345
Maybe a career in politics?

68
00:04:32,880 --> 00:04:37,359
Off the top of my head, I would go with the sense of Manifest Destiny.

69
00:04:37,360 --> 00:04:39,639
Rags to riches. Rapid rise through the ranks.

70
00:04:39,640 --> 00:04:43,759
Born to deliver us. And the people, they love that sort of thing.

71
00:04:43,760 --> 00:04:48,039
You misunderstand. I didn't ask you here to sell me, I want you to sell the invasion.

72
00:04:48,040 --> 00:04:49,199
Okay.

73
00:04:49,200 --> 00:04:52,679
You ship for the coast in one hour. Your camera crew is standing by.

74
00:04:52,680 --> 00:04:55,503
You'll be on the beach with the first wave.

75
00:04:57,080 --> 00:05:01,199
I'm sorry, the first wave? The beach? You mean the front?

76
00:05:01,200 --> 00:05:02,799
France.

77
00:05:02,800 --> 00:05:05,639
Satellites show minimal enemy movement on the coast.

78
00:05:05,640 --> 00:05:07,239
Little resistance.

79
00:05:07,240 --> 00:05:09,239
A little excitement, something to tell your grandchildren.

80
00:05:09,240 --> 00:05:12,639
I appreciate the confidence, general...

81
00:05:12,640 --> 00:05:15,099
I do this to avoid doing that.

82
00:05:19,000 --> 00:05:21,039
I was in ROTC in college.

83
00:05:21,040 --> 00:05:25,119
The war broke out, I lost my advertising firm...

84
00:05:25,120 --> 00:05:26,359
and here I am.

85
00:05:26,360 --> 00:05:30,070
You know, I do what I do, and you do what you do.

86
00:05:30,520 --> 00:05:31,839
But...

87
00:05:31,840 --> 00:05:35,983
I'm not a soldier, really.

88
00:05:36,280 --> 00:05:37,639
No, of course you're not.

89
00:05:37,640 --> 00:05:41,146
That's why I'm embedding you with several hundred thousand men and women who are.

90
00:05:41,280 --> 00:05:44,639
While it is an honor General, I'm afraid I'm gonna have to decline.

91
00:05:44,640 --> 00:05:47,819
Can't stand the sight of blood. Not so much as a paper cut.

92
00:05:53,320 --> 00:05:55,839
Uh, but, uh...

93
00:05:55,840 --> 00:05:58,559
sitting here thinking about this...

94
00:05:58,560 --> 00:06:00,759
a couple of names come to mind...

95
00:06:00,760 --> 00:06:03,959
that I feel like I could recommend to you.

96
00:06:03,960 --> 00:06:06,908
It's not an offer, major. It's an order.

97
00:06:08,040 --> 00:06:11,959
General, I am an officer in the United States military.

98
00:06:11,960 --> 00:06:15,279
- You don't even have the authority...  - I have spoken to your CO.

99
00:06:15,280 --> 00:06:17,591
You are now under my command.

100
00:06:17,680 --> 00:06:20,879
You will retain your present rank of course.

101
00:06:20,880 --> 00:06:23,111
My secretary has all the details.

102
00:06:25,080 --> 00:06:27,550
Do a good job, major.

103
00:06:27,880 --> 00:06:31,147
Good luck. You are dismissed.

104
00:06:44,040 --> 00:06:46,146
General?

105
00:06:47,960 --> 00:06:52,865
I just inspired millions of people to join your army.

106
00:06:54,360 --> 00:06:57,839
And when the body bags come home and they're looking for someone to blame...

107
00:06:57,840 --> 00:07:01,599
how hard do you think it would be...

108
00:07:01,600 --> 00:07:05,583
for me to convince people to blame you?

109
00:07:06,080 --> 00:07:10,585
I'd imagine the general would prefer to avoid that.

110
00:07:13,440 --> 00:07:15,865
Are you blackmailing me, major?

111
00:07:16,320 --> 00:07:18,359
I would prefer...

112
00:07:18,360 --> 00:07:23,265
not to be filming acts of heroism and valor on that beach tomorrow.

113
00:07:36,080 --> 00:07:38,311
You won't be.

114
00:07:40,000 --> 00:07:42,279
I'm glad we could, uh, work this out.

115
00:07:42,280 --> 00:07:44,909
Now if you'll excuse me, general. I...

116
00:07:49,160 --> 00:07:50,419
Thank you.

117
00:07:52,040 --> 00:07:54,066
Arrest this man.

118
00:07:54,480 --> 00:07:56,188
What?

119
00:07:58,200 --> 00:07:59,199
Hey! Hey!

120
00:07:59,200 --> 00:08:01,559
Stop right there!

121
00:08:01,560 --> 00:08:02,519
Hey! Stop!

122
00:08:02,520 --> 00:08:04,119
Get out of the way!

123
00:08:04,120 --> 00:08:05,079
Out of the way!

124
00:08:05,080 --> 00:08:06,469
Hold it!

125
00:08:16,920 --> 00:08:18,719
Left flank, march!

126
00:08:18,720 --> 00:08:21,145
Forward, march!

127
00:08:21,520 --> 00:08:23,539
About-turn!

128
00:08:30,320 --> 00:08:33,348
Supplies closing in 10 minutes.

129
00:08:45,000 --> 00:08:46,400


130
00:08:46,200 --> 00:08:49,400


131
00:08:48,760 --> 00:08:51,229
On your feet maggot!

132
00:08:53,560 --> 00:08:56,559
That is no way to address an officer, sergeant.

133
00:08:56,560 --> 00:08:59,839
It's how I address a slack-jawed recruit before I bust his hole

134
00:08:59,840 --> 00:09:01,559
with my boot heel, maggot!

135
00:09:01,560 --> 00:09:03,985
Hold up there, sergeant.

136
00:09:04,800 --> 00:09:07,065
Can I help you, sir?

137
00:09:07,800 --> 00:09:09,439
Where the hell am I, sergeant?

138
00:09:09,440 --> 00:09:11,239
Forward Operating Base Heathrow.

139
00:09:11,240 --> 00:09:13,769
You just came in with the fresh recruits.

140
00:09:13,770 --> 00:09:16,051
Do I strike you as a fresh recruit?

141
00:09:16,640 --> 00:09:18,039
No, sir, you do not.

142
00:09:18,040 --> 00:09:19,559
My name is Major William Cage.

143
00:09:19,560 --> 00:09:21,439
- I'm an American officer.  - Officer?

144
00:09:21,440 --> 00:09:23,519
This is processing.

145
00:09:23,520 --> 00:09:26,548
There's no officers down here. I got this, sergeant.

146
00:09:26,680 --> 00:09:30,439
How the hell did you end up in processing?

147
00:09:30,440 --> 00:09:33,799
What was it? Poker night? Bachelor party?

148
00:09:33,800 --> 00:09:35,919
If it's all the same to you, sergeant...

149
00:09:35,920 --> 00:09:38,959
I'd like to explain that to my commanding officer in Washington.

150
00:09:38,960 --> 00:09:41,639
- If you'll take me to a phone...  - Haven't you heard?

151
00:09:41,640 --> 00:09:44,719
We're T-minus-Haul-Ass-H-Hour.

152
00:09:44,720 --> 00:09:46,839
We're fixing to invade France.

153
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:51,426
This whole FOB's on lockdown. No calls, in or out.

154
00:09:53,600 --> 00:09:55,661
- Name is Farell.  - That's right.

155
00:09:55,680 --> 00:09:57,039
Master Sergeant Farell.

156
00:09:57,040 --> 00:09:58,399
Master Seargeant Farell you're an American.

157
00:09:58,400 --> 00:10:01,189
No, sir. I'm from Kentucky.

158
00:10:01,760 --> 00:10:05,199
Okay. Well, look at me.

159
00:10:05,200 --> 00:10:07,750
And look at where I am.

160
00:10:08,640 --> 00:10:10,905
I've been railroaded.

161
00:10:11,000 --> 00:10:14,346
It's obvious I don't belong here.

162
00:10:14,480 --> 00:10:19,305
So please, sergeant, there has to be a way I can make a phone call.

163
00:10:24,080 --> 00:10:25,839
I'll get you sorted out, sir.

164
00:10:25,840 --> 00:10:28,822
- Thank you.  - Right this way.

165
00:10:34,320 --> 00:10:35,639
Where you from in Kentucky, sergeant?

166
00:10:35,640 --> 00:10:37,879
Little town called Science Hill. Heard of it?

167
00:10:37,880 --> 00:10:38,959
I have now.

168
00:10:38,960 --> 00:10:41,199
- How about you, where you from?  - Cranbury, New Jersey.

169
00:10:41,200 --> 00:10:42,999
They grow a lot of cranberries there do they?

170
00:10:43,000 --> 00:10:44,719
Tomatoes. Best you ever had.

171
00:10:44,720 --> 00:10:46,679
Why they call it Cranberry, then?

172
00:10:46,680 --> 00:10:48,319
Why they call it Science Hill?

173
00:10:48,320 --> 00:10:50,984
Never asked. Don't care.

174
00:10:54,320 --> 00:10:56,221
After you.

175
00:11:00,120 --> 00:11:02,159
You're not taking me to a phone, are you sergeant?

176
00:11:02,160 --> 00:11:04,359
No, I am not.

177
00:11:04,360 --> 00:11:08,901
Seems about the only honest thing you said to me so far is your name.

178
00:11:10,160 --> 00:11:12,391
Says here you're a deserter.

179
00:11:12,480 --> 00:11:16,039
It says here you were caught impersonating an officer. It says here...

180
00:11:16,040 --> 00:11:20,079
you'd likely try to make an outside call, even compromise security of this operation.

181
00:11:20,080 --> 00:11:22,839
Anything to get out of combat duty tomorrow.

182
00:11:22,840 --> 00:11:25,079
But that's not gonna happen.

183
00:11:25,080 --> 00:11:26,439
Ever.

184
00:11:26,440 --> 00:11:28,830
Private Cage.

185
00:11:40,240 --> 00:11:41,839
Rumor is a terrible thing.

186
00:11:41,840 --> 00:11:45,159
Come nightfall, these men will all reach the same conclusion:

187
00:11:45,160 --> 00:11:48,399
that you're a coward and a liar, putting your life above theirs.

188
00:11:48,400 --> 00:11:50,999
Good news is there's hope for you, private.

189
00:11:51,000 --> 00:11:54,039
Hope in the form of glorious combat.

190
00:11:54,040 --> 00:11:55,839
Battle is the great redeemer.

191
00:11:55,840 --> 00:11:59,319
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.

192
00:11:59,320 --> 00:12:02,199
The one place where all men truly share the same rank...

193
00:12:02,200 --> 00:12:06,099
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.

194
00:12:07,360 --> 00:12:10,879
Squad! This here is Private Cage.

195
00:12:10,880 --> 00:12:13,359
Private Cage, J Squad.

196
00:12:13,360 --> 00:12:15,421
Isn't that an officer's uniform?

197
00:12:15,920 --> 00:12:19,141
Those sure ain't officer cufflinks.

198
00:12:20,040 --> 00:12:23,439
I see everyone is having a productive morning.

199
00:12:23,440 --> 00:12:27,719
You know, it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your...

200
00:12:27,720 --> 00:12:30,599
caliber will be leading the charge tomorrow.

201
00:12:30,600 --> 00:12:32,479
Tip of the spear.

202
00:12:32,480 --> 00:12:34,519
Edge of the knife.

203
00:12:34,520 --> 00:12:35,639
Crack of my...

204
00:12:35,640 --> 00:12:37,039
ass.

205
00:12:37,040 --> 00:12:38,599
Oh, shit.

206
00:12:38,600 --> 00:12:41,159
Private Kimmel, what is my view of gambling in the barracks?

207
00:12:41,160 --> 00:12:43,239
You dislike it, Sergeant Farell.

208
00:12:43,240 --> 00:12:44,719
Nance, why do I dislike it?

209
00:12:44,720 --> 00:12:48,039
It entertains the notion our fate is in hands other than our own.

210
00:12:48,040 --> 00:12:51,999
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate, chorus?

211
00:12:52,000 --> 00:12:56,382
Through readiness and discipline, we are masters of our fate.

212
00:12:57,400 --> 00:13:00,439
You might call that notion ironic.

213
00:13:00,440 --> 00:13:04,150
But trust me, you'll come around.

214
00:13:05,600 --> 00:13:08,184
Private Cage is a deserter.

215
00:13:09,000 --> 00:13:12,839
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.

216
00:13:12,840 --> 00:13:15,319
He will be combat ready at 0600 tomorrow.

217
00:13:15,320 --> 00:13:16,319
Combat ready?

218
00:13:16,320 --> 00:13:18,239
Private Cage is under the delusion he does not belong here.

219
00:13:18,240 --> 00:13:21,079
We must dissuade him of this delusion.

220
00:13:21,080 --> 00:13:24,959
If he tries to run, feel free to dissuade him until he can't piss standing up.

221
00:13:24,960 --> 00:13:26,319
Sergeant, you have to listen to me.

222
00:13:26,320 --> 00:13:29,519
- I will never be combat ready.  - I envy you, Cage.

223
00:13:29,520 --> 00:13:33,981
Tomorrow morning, you will be baptized. Born again.

224
00:13:34,720 --> 00:13:37,622
PT! Ten minutes!

225
00:13:37,640 --> 00:13:38,719
# So everybody #

226
00:13:38,720 --> 00:13:40,839
# Come along with me #

227
00:13:40,840 --> 00:13:43,239
# Go down the river and wash your feet #

228
00:13:43,240 --> 00:13:45,479
# To where the people live a life that's sweet #

229
00:13:45,480 --> 00:13:47,039
# And a place that's ripe... #

230
00:13:47,040 --> 00:13:51,586
You're not in uniform... private.

231
00:13:57,760 --> 00:14:00,039
Could all combat-ready squadrons proceed...

232
00:14:00,040 --> 00:14:01,799
It's a new day, people.

233
00:14:01,800 --> 00:14:03,439
Destiny calls.

234
00:14:03,440 --> 00:14:07,139
The world expects only one thing from us: That we will win.

235
00:14:39,200 --> 00:14:42,000


236
00:14:45,500 --> 00:14:47,200


237
00:14:48,040 --> 00:14:50,430
Come on, Kimmel, let's have it!

238
00:14:54,960 --> 00:14:56,799
Oh, for chrissake, Kimmel.

239
00:14:56,800 --> 00:14:59,668
I got to be free, man.

240
00:15:01,360 --> 00:15:04,661
Alright man let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.

241
00:15:05,080 --> 00:15:06,879
What's that noise? That...

242
00:15:06,880 --> 00:15:08,079
Let's go.

243
00:15:08,080 --> 00:15:10,359
Listen man, I've never been in one of these.

244
00:15:10,360 --> 00:15:12,559
I've never been with two girls at the same time before.

245
00:15:12,560 --> 00:15:15,827
You can bet when that day comes, I'll make it work.

246
00:15:16,120 --> 00:15:17,319
Kimmel.

247
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,599
It's Griff.

248
00:15:18,600 --> 00:15:19,959
Griff. Griff. You bet.

249
00:15:19,960 --> 00:15:24,159
Just think about this, man. I could hurt somebody with it.

250
00:15:24,160 --> 00:15:26,425
Not with the safety on, you won't.

251
00:15:27,040 --> 00:15:28,719
But...

252
00:15:28,720 --> 00:15:32,226
- Where is the safety?  - Exactly.

253
00:15:41,840 --> 00:15:43,980
It's time.

254
00:16:09,480 --> 00:16:12,826
Bloody hell, it's the Full Metal...

255
00:16:13,040 --> 00:16:15,146
Move.

256
00:16:15,840 --> 00:16:17,279
- Griff.  - Sarge?

257
00:16:17,280 --> 00:16:20,239
- Take care of Private Cage.  - What, all day?

258
00:16:20,240 --> 00:16:23,347
Something tells me it won't be nearly that long.

259
00:17:04,080 --> 00:17:06,239
Cage!

260
00:17:06,240 --> 00:17:08,187
- Cage!  - Cage!

261
00:17:31,040 --> 00:17:32,679
We lost Germany.

262
00:17:32,680 --> 00:17:34,359
We lost France.

263
00:17:34,360 --> 00:17:37,879
If we lose today we won't get to fight another.

264
00:17:37,880 --> 00:17:41,199
I know the pressure on you is enormous.

265
00:17:41,200 --> 00:17:43,159
Two minutes to drop.

266
00:17:43,160 --> 00:17:44,999
It's all right to be scared.

267
00:17:45,000 --> 00:17:48,506
Remember, there's no courage without fear.

268
00:17:50,120 --> 00:17:51,719
Oi!

269
00:17:51,720 --> 00:17:55,479
Oi, mate! I think there's something wrong with your suit.

270
00:17:55,480 --> 00:17:58,259
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.

271
00:18:00,120 --> 00:18:03,439
Hey, watch your back out there, sir.

272
00:18:03,440 --> 00:18:05,580
No one else will.

273
00:18:06,240 --> 00:18:07,319
One minute!

274
00:18:07,320 --> 00:18:09,949
One minute to drop!

275
00:18:15,040 --> 00:18:16,759
Hey.

276
00:18:16,760 --> 00:18:19,503
- Hey!  - What?

277
00:18:19,760 --> 00:18:22,239
How do I turn the safety off of my weapon?

278
00:18:22,240 --> 00:18:23,339
What?

279
00:18:24,520 --> 00:18:26,639
How do I turn the safety off...?

280
00:18:26,640 --> 00:18:28,541
Oh, my God!

281
00:18:33,320 --> 00:18:37,319
Get ready! Thirty seconds to drop!

282
00:18:37,320 --> 00:18:39,399
On my mark!

283
00:18:39,400 --> 00:18:41,079
Stand by to deploy!

284
00:18:41,080 --> 00:18:43,869
Activate drop lines. Remember...

285
00:18:46,680 --> 00:18:49,070
Aah! Aah!

286
00:18:49,240 --> 00:18:50,439
Drop now!

287
00:18:50,440 --> 00:18:51,679
Let's drop! Drop!

288
00:18:51,680 --> 00:18:53,502
Drop!

289
00:18:54,720 --> 00:18:55,519
Drop!

290
00:18:55,520 --> 00:18:56,679
Go!

291
00:18:56,680 --> 00:18:58,479
Go, let's go!

292
00:18:58,480 --> 00:18:59,949
Come on!

293
00:19:00,680 --> 00:19:01,479
Drop!

294
00:19:01,480 --> 00:19:02,983
Drop!

295
00:19:06,280 --> 00:19:08,545
Cage! Drop or die!

296
00:19:51,400 --> 00:19:53,439
Yeah! Whoo!

297
00:19:53,440 --> 00:19:55,399
We made it!

298
00:19:55,400 --> 00:19:57,381
Thank God, we made it!

299
00:20:19,280 --> 00:20:21,227
Select language.

300
00:21:07,840 --> 00:21:09,919
We need help!

301
00:21:09,920 --> 00:21:11,419
We need it now!

302
00:22:05,440 --> 00:22:07,671
What the...?

303
00:22:19,280 --> 00:22:20,999
Private Cage!

304
00:22:21,000 --> 00:22:22,599
You're going the wrong way.

305
00:22:22,600 --> 00:22:25,039
You're gonna miss your moment.

306
00:22:25,040 --> 00:22:26,959
What the hell?

307
00:22:26,960 --> 00:22:29,239
They're not supposed to know we're coming.

308
00:22:29,240 --> 00:22:31,239
We walked into a slaughterhouse, man.

309
00:22:31,240 --> 00:22:32,948
It's a slaughterhouse!

310
00:22:33,320 --> 00:22:34,719
Pull yourself together!

311
00:22:34,720 --> 00:22:37,270
On your feet, people!

312
00:22:37,360 --> 00:22:38,719
Get in line!

313
00:22:38,720 --> 00:22:40,439
Nance, get me a sitrep.

314
00:22:40,440 --> 00:22:43,479
- Safety! My safety!  - Griff, Ford, cover the flank!

315
00:22:43,480 --> 00:22:47,748
My safety. My safety. How do I get my safety...?

316
00:22:48,720 --> 00:22:50,559
- I'm waiting, Nance!  - I got traces!

317
00:22:50,560 --> 00:22:52,919
Five hundred meters and they're coming in fast!

318
00:22:52,920 --> 00:22:54,439
Son of a bitch.

319
00:22:54,440 --> 00:22:56,279
Out of the way!

320
00:22:56,280 --> 00:22:59,039
Look alive if you wanna stay that way!

321
00:22:59,040 --> 00:23:00,799
Firing positions!

322
00:23:00,800 --> 00:23:02,099
Move!

323
00:23:03,400 --> 00:23:04,519
Here they come.

324
00:23:04,520 --> 00:23:06,919
Mean as hell and thick as grass.

325
00:23:06,920 --> 00:23:08,679
Wait till they're right on us!

326
00:23:08,680 --> 00:23:10,308
Few more seconds!

327
00:23:12,560 --> 00:23:13,559
Hey!

328
00:23:13,560 --> 00:23:15,222
Hey!

329
00:23:20,480 --> 00:23:22,427
Fall back!

330
00:24:05,120 --> 00:24:06,599
Ha!

331
00:24:06,600 --> 00:24:08,659
Ha-ha!

332
00:24:26,240 --> 00:24:28,187
Reload.

333
00:24:31,020 --> 00:25:32,868


334
00:24:59,320 --> 00:25:01,868
On your feet maggot!

335
00:25:06,320 --> 00:25:09,079
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel, maggot!

336
00:25:09,080 --> 00:25:11,584
Hold up there, sergeant.

337
00:25:14,200 --> 00:25:16,670
Can I help you, sir?

338
00:25:16,960 --> 00:25:19,350
Sergeant Farell. Is it...?

339
00:25:20,000 --> 00:25:22,470
That is my name.

340
00:25:23,400 --> 00:25:25,519
I think I get it.

341
00:25:25,520 --> 00:25:29,999
What was it? Poker night? Bachelor party?

342
00:25:30,000 --> 00:25:32,061
You know, I'm not sure.

343
00:25:32,880 --> 00:25:34,702
It happens.

344
00:25:36,040 --> 00:25:37,987
I'll get you sorted out, sir.

345
00:25:38,160 --> 00:25:41,062
Let me take those for you.

346
00:25:41,240 --> 00:25:43,790
What day is it?

347
00:25:43,800 --> 00:25:45,906
For you?

348
00:25:47,440 --> 00:25:49,919
Judgment Day.

349
00:25:49,920 --> 00:25:52,479
The good news is there's hope for you, private.

350
00:25:52,480 --> 00:25:54,959
Hope in the form of glorious combat.

351
00:25:54,960 --> 00:25:57,079
Battle is the great redeemer.

352
00:25:57,080 --> 00:25:58,759
The fiery crucible in which...

353
00:25:58,760 --> 00:26:02,861
- the only true heroes are...  - The only true heroes are forged.

354
00:26:02,920 --> 00:26:05,948
Did you just interrupt me, private?

355
00:26:09,880 --> 00:26:11,861
Sarge, you're...

356
00:26:12,560 --> 00:26:15,479
you're not gonna believe what I'm about to tell you.

357
00:26:15,480 --> 00:26:17,347
No, I'm not.

358
00:26:17,720 --> 00:26:20,304
Now, where was I?

359
00:26:21,080 --> 00:26:23,027
The fiery crucible.

360
00:26:23,280 --> 00:26:27,559
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.

361
00:26:27,560 --> 00:26:29,519
The one place where all men truly share...

362
00:26:29,520 --> 00:26:33,779
the same rank, regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.

363
00:26:35,760 --> 00:26:37,079
- Welcome to hell.  - Squad!

364
00:26:37,080 --> 00:26:40,586
This here is Private Cage.

365
00:26:41,440 --> 00:26:42,919
Private Cage...

366
00:26:42,920 --> 00:26:44,759
J Squad.

367
00:26:44,760 --> 00:26:46,279
Isn't that an officer's uniform?

368
00:26:46,280 --> 00:26:48,359
They sure ain't officer cufflinks.

369
00:26:48,360 --> 00:26:52,959
You know, it gives me a swell of pride knowing soldiers of your caliber...

370
00:26:52,960 --> 00:26:55,039
will be leading the charge tomorrow.

371
00:26:55,040 --> 00:26:58,039
Tip of the spear, edge of the knife.

372
00:26:58,040 --> 00:27:00,479
Crack of my ass.

373
00:27:00,480 --> 00:27:04,039
Private Kimmel, what is my view of gambling in the barracks?

374
00:27:04,040 --> 00:27:06,799
- Dislike it, sergeant.  - Nance, why do I dislike it?

375
00:27:06,800 --> 00:27:10,119
It entertains the notion our fate is in hands other than our own.

376
00:27:10,120 --> 00:27:14,759
And what is my definitive position on the concept of fate, chorus?

377
00:27:14,760 --> 00:27:18,664
Through readiness and discipline, we are masters of our fate.

378
00:27:20,480 --> 00:27:22,719
You might call that notion ironic.

379
00:27:22,720 --> 00:27:25,559
Trust me, you'll come around.

380
00:27:25,560 --> 00:27:27,719
Oh, for Chrissake, Kimmel.

381
00:27:27,720 --> 00:27:30,359
- I gotta be free, man.  - All right, man.

382
00:27:30,360 --> 00:27:32,830
Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.

383
00:27:36,200 --> 00:27:38,067
Disengaged.

384
00:27:38,640 --> 00:27:40,559
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you?

385
00:27:40,560 --> 00:27:43,224
Haven't you ever been in one of these before?

386
00:27:44,040 --> 00:27:46,271
Maybe.

387
00:27:46,320 --> 00:27:48,460
Know where the safety is?

388
00:27:49,800 --> 00:27:53,180
- I'm not sure.  - Good.

389
00:27:53,920 --> 00:27:56,999
I know the pressure on you is enormous.

390
00:27:57,000 --> 00:27:59,119
Two minutes to drop.

391
00:27:59,120 --> 00:28:00,879
It's all right to be scared.

392
00:28:00,880 --> 00:28:03,999
There's no courage without fear.

393
00:28:04,000 --> 00:28:05,359
Oi!

394
00:28:05,360 --> 00:28:06,759
Oi, mate!

395
00:28:06,760 --> 00:28:09,359
I think there's something wrong with your suit.

396
00:28:09,360 --> 00:28:12,339
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.

397
00:28:15,400 --> 00:28:17,679
Watch your back out there, sir.

398
00:28:17,680 --> 00:28:19,799
- No one else will.  - No one else will.

399
00:28:19,800 --> 00:28:22,099
Ha-ha! Jinx, bitch!

400
00:28:28,320 --> 00:28:31,279
On my mark! Stand by to deploy!

401
00:28:31,280 --> 00:28:33,879
Activate drop lines, 30 seconds.

402
00:28:33,880 --> 00:28:35,861
- Remember, hit...  - Hey!

403
00:28:48,880 --> 00:28:50,667
Go! Go!

404
00:29:08,040 --> 00:29:09,279
Whoo-hoo!

405
00:29:09,280 --> 00:29:10,559
We made it!

406
00:29:10,560 --> 00:29:12,586
Behind you!

407
00:29:12,600 --> 00:29:14,501
Look out!

408
00:29:53,560 --> 00:29:55,302
Incoming!

409
00:29:57,440 --> 00:29:58,559
I'm hit.

410
00:29:58,560 --> 00:29:59,949
I'm hit.

411
00:30:00,960 --> 00:30:02,827
How bad is it?

412
00:30:03,520 --> 00:30:07,026
Is there a lot of blood?

413
00:30:07,440 --> 00:30:10,422
You have a hole in your chest.

414
00:30:10,560 --> 00:30:11,519
Really?

415
00:30:11,520 --> 00:30:13,421
Yeah.

416
00:30:17,800 --> 00:30:20,279
Did you just take my...?

417
00:30:20,280 --> 00:30:22,261
My battery?

418
00:30:25,040 --> 00:30:27,319
No, no, no. Holy fu...

419
00:30:27,320 --> 00:30:29,426
Aah!

420
00:30:33,560 --> 00:30:35,399
On your feet maggot!

421
00:30:35,400 --> 00:30:36,999
Sergeant Farell!

422
00:30:37,000 --> 00:30:38,839
Sergeant Farell.

423
00:30:38,840 --> 00:30:40,079
Can I help you, sir?

424
00:30:40,080 --> 00:30:43,079
My name is Major Bill Cage. I'm U.S. Army Media Relations.

425
00:30:43,080 --> 00:30:44,799
I was not at a bachelor party or a poker game.

426
00:30:44,800 --> 00:30:48,479
You have an order that says I'm a deserter caught impersonating an officer.

427
00:30:48,480 --> 00:30:50,159
But what it doesn't say is...

428
00:30:50,160 --> 00:30:52,879
your name is Master Sergeant Farell from Science Hill, Kentucky.

429
00:30:52,880 --> 00:30:55,780
If you give me 30 seconds to explain how I know that,

430
00:30:55,781 --> 00:30:59,991
you may save the lives of every soldier on this base.

431
00:31:01,160 --> 00:31:04,719
You have to listen to me! They know we're coming! They're waiting for us!

432
00:31:04,720 --> 00:31:07,399
I have been there! I've seen it!

433
00:31:07,400 --> 00:31:09,879
You're all doomed! You're doomed!

434
00:31:09,880 --> 00:31:13,919
Okay. Okay. Okay, I'm fine. I'm fine.

435
00:31:13,920 --> 00:31:15,439
This is J Squad. Yes?

436
00:31:15,440 --> 00:31:16,959
This is J Squad, yes.

437
00:31:16,960 --> 00:31:19,199
Not that I should know that, but okay.

438
00:31:19,200 --> 00:31:21,519
Have any of you met me before?

439
00:31:21,520 --> 00:31:22,839
Bitch, I don't know you.

440
00:31:22,840 --> 00:31:24,719
Exactly! Yes!

441
00:31:24,720 --> 00:31:25,759
Thank you.

442
00:31:25,760 --> 00:31:27,119
Your name is Nance. You're Bibble.

443
00:31:27,120 --> 00:31:31,119
Kibble... Kimmel! You fight balls out. Literally.

444
00:31:31,120 --> 00:31:33,679
Ford. Skinner. Griff.

445
00:31:33,680 --> 00:31:35,627
You're...

446
00:31:36,360 --> 00:31:37,919
He doesn't talk much.

447
00:31:37,920 --> 00:31:40,499
- But there's a card game under the bed.  - Thanks a lot, asshole.

448
00:31:40,500 --> 00:31:45,028
Kimmel's working on a flush. Spades... no, clubs.

449
00:31:46,360 --> 00:31:48,319
You're gonna make them eat those cards.

450
00:31:48,320 --> 00:31:50,710
Am I right?

451
00:31:52,200 --> 00:31:54,261
Now...

452
00:31:56,240 --> 00:31:59,302
what I'm about to tell you sounds crazy.

453
00:31:59,320 --> 00:32:01,301
It's true.

454
00:32:01,760 --> 00:32:04,742
And you have to listen to me.

455
00:32:06,000 --> 00:32:10,461
Your very lives depend on it.

456
00:32:12,560 --> 00:32:14,461
One minute!

457
00:32:22,200 --> 00:32:26,619
What? What is he saying? Nance! What is he saying?

458
00:32:37,200 --> 00:32:40,626
On my mark! Stand by to deploy!

459
00:32:40,720 --> 00:32:43,509
The ship is about to explode!

460
00:32:53,800 --> 00:32:55,639
Yeah! Whoo!

461
00:32:55,640 --> 00:32:57,439
We made it!

462
00:32:57,440 --> 00:32:59,148
Thank God, we made it!

463
00:33:00,280 --> 00:33:01,119
Aah!

464
00:33:01,120 --> 00:33:03,640
Before I bust your hole with my boot heel!

465
00:33:04,000 --> 00:33:05,519
Yeah! Whoo!

466
00:33:05,520 --> 00:33:07,439
We made it!

467
00:33:07,440 --> 00:33:09,148
Thank God, we made it!

468
00:33:26,040 --> 00:33:27,748
Aah!

469
00:33:38,160 --> 00:33:39,519
I'm sorry. I'm trying to save you.

470
00:33:39,520 --> 00:33:43,224
We're getting slaughtered. You need to get us off this beach.

471
00:33:48,240 --> 00:33:51,639
We have to go. This drop ship is about to explode.

472
00:33:51,640 --> 00:33:53,599
We have to go now.

473
00:33:53,600 --> 00:33:55,467
Wait.

474
00:34:00,400 --> 00:34:02,142
Come on!

475
00:34:12,920 --> 00:34:14,787
Come on!

476
00:34:17,720 --> 00:34:18,959
Come on!

477
00:34:18,960 --> 00:34:21,271
This ship is going to explode!

478
00:34:21,960 --> 00:34:23,759
What are you doing?

479
00:34:23,760 --> 00:34:26,025
Find me when you wake up.

480
00:34:26,160 --> 00:34:26,999
What?

481
00:34:27,000 --> 00:34:29,026
Come find me when you wake up.

482
00:34:30,080 --> 00:34:31,959
Aah!

483
00:34:31,960 --> 00:34:34,781
On your feet maggot!

484
00:34:38,360 --> 00:34:40,839
Get in line before I bust your hole with my boot heel!

485
00:34:40,840 --> 00:34:43,119
Good news is there's hope for you, private.

486
00:34:43,120 --> 00:34:44,599
Battle is the great redeemer.

487
00:34:44,600 --> 00:34:47,679
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.

488
00:34:47,680 --> 00:34:50,779
The one place where all men truly sh...

489
00:34:56,720 --> 00:34:57,959
Squad, this here is...

490
00:34:57,960 --> 00:35:00,639
Private Cage. And you must be J Squad.

491
00:35:00,640 --> 00:35:01,879
It's good to meet you.

492
00:35:01,880 --> 00:35:03,639
Isn't that an officer's uniform?

493
00:35:03,640 --> 00:35:07,631
- Those sure...  - These sure ain't officer's cufflinks.

494
00:35:09,120 --> 00:35:13,908
Keys in the... left pocket, probably.

495
00:35:17,600 --> 00:35:19,839
Private Cage is a deserter.

496
00:35:19,840 --> 00:35:23,599
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.

497
00:35:23,600 --> 00:35:27,439
He will be combat ready by 0600 tomorrow.

498
00:35:27,440 --> 00:35:30,279
Private Cage is under the delusion he does not belong here.

499
00:35:30,280 --> 00:35:32,159
We must dissuade him of this delusion.

500
00:35:32,160 --> 00:35:36,587
- If he tries to run, feel free to dissuade him...  - Oh, no. I'm not gonna run.

501
00:35:36,720 --> 00:35:38,879
- Not a chance.  - Till he can't piss standing up.

502
00:35:38,880 --> 00:35:41,350
Thank you, Sergeant Farell.

503
00:35:52,680 --> 00:35:55,679
What next? A little, uh, PT?

504
00:35:55,680 --> 00:35:58,119
PT! Ten minutes!

505
00:35:58,120 --> 00:36:02,199
Left! Left! Left!

506
00:36:02,200 --> 00:36:05,079
- What are you? Sound off!  - I'm a warrior!

507
00:36:05,080 --> 00:36:06,999
- What do warriors do?  - Kill!

508
00:36:07,000 --> 00:36:09,399
- What are you gonna do?  - Kill!

509
00:36:09,400 --> 00:36:10,999
- What are you gonna do?  - Kill!

510
00:36:11,000 --> 00:36:13,199
It's gonna be my 20th battle tomorrow.

511
00:36:13,200 --> 00:36:15,799
- You haven't been in 20 battles, mate.  - I have too.

512
00:36:15,800 --> 00:36:18,759
You're gonna dump your load the second we hit the beach.

513
00:36:18,760 --> 00:36:21,439
Why don't you get yourselves a cup of shut-the-hell-up?

514
00:36:21,440 --> 00:36:22,999
Ha-ha. You funny, girl.

515
00:36:23,000 --> 00:36:24,719
I bet I set a record tomorrow.

516
00:36:24,720 --> 00:36:29,119
Fastest time running backwards, Ford, slipping in your own shit.

517
00:36:29,120 --> 00:36:31,799
Knock off the grab-ass!

518
00:36:31,800 --> 00:36:32,959
Grab this, sarge!

519
00:36:32,960 --> 00:36:34,861
Hold up!

520
00:36:36,680 --> 00:36:39,861
Private, drop and give me...

521
00:36:40,840 --> 00:36:42,741
Fifty, sarge?

522
00:36:43,280 --> 00:36:44,919
That's right.

523
00:36:44,920 --> 00:36:46,599
Fifty.

524
00:36:46,600 --> 00:36:48,308
Platoon!

525
00:36:48,480 --> 00:36:50,222
Drop and give me 50!

526
00:36:50,280 --> 00:36:52,319
Compliments of Private Cage.

527
00:36:52,320 --> 00:36:54,559
Thank you, sarge.

528
00:36:54,560 --> 00:36:56,439
- And one!  - One!

529
00:36:56,440 --> 00:36:57,679
- And two!  - Two!

530
00:36:57,680 --> 00:36:59,581
- And three!  - Three!

531
00:37:04,840 --> 00:37:07,469
- Aah!  - Oh!

532
00:37:09,160 --> 00:37:11,599
What the hell were you thinking?

533
00:37:11,600 --> 00:37:15,239
There's hope for you, private. Hope in the form of glorious combat.

534
00:37:15,240 --> 00:37:17,999
Battle is the great redeemer.

535
00:37:18,000 --> 00:37:19,759
- Three!  - Three!

536
00:37:19,760 --> 00:37:21,399
- Four!  - Four!

537
00:37:21,400 --> 00:37:23,825
- Five!  - Five!

538
00:38:01,100 --> 00:38:03,825


539
00:38:05,880 --> 00:38:09,386
Excuse me. Sergeant Vrataski.

540
00:38:11,600 --> 00:38:13,308
Excuse me.

541
00:38:14,280 --> 00:38:16,625
Sergeant Vrataski?

542
00:38:35,480 --> 00:38:36,559
Excuse me.

543
00:38:36,560 --> 00:38:38,871
Yes? Who said you could talk to me?

544
00:38:40,040 --> 00:38:41,919
Have I got something on my face?

545
00:38:41,920 --> 00:38:43,799
You did. You did.

546
00:38:43,800 --> 00:38:45,839
Tomorrow. At the beach.

547
00:38:45,840 --> 00:38:48,504
Tomorrow. At the beach.

548
00:38:49,120 --> 00:38:50,862
We meet.

549
00:38:50,920 --> 00:38:54,471
You said to find you when I wake up.

550
00:38:56,720 --> 00:38:59,159
You do know what's happening to me.

551
00:38:59,160 --> 00:39:01,199
Come with me.

552
00:39:01,200 --> 00:39:02,679
Now.

553
00:39:02,680 --> 00:39:05,639
You don't talk to anyone about this but me.

554
00:39:05,640 --> 00:39:08,759
The best-case scenario is you're gonna end up in a psych ward.

555
00:39:08,760 --> 00:39:12,239
Worst case, you'll get dissected for study. Are we clear?

556
00:39:12,240 --> 00:39:13,679
- Yes?  - Yes.

557
00:39:13,680 --> 00:39:15,599
First time you died, what happened?

558
00:39:15,600 --> 00:39:17,159
- You killed a mimic?  - Yes.

559
00:39:17,160 --> 00:39:19,879
- Describe it.  - It was different.

560
00:39:19,880 --> 00:39:22,879
It was bigger. Bluish.

561
00:39:22,880 --> 00:39:25,639
And you got covered in its blood.

562
00:39:25,640 --> 00:39:27,839
As a matter of fact, I did.

563
00:39:27,840 --> 00:39:30,599
They know we're coming on the beach tomorrow.

564
00:39:30,600 --> 00:39:33,279
It's a slaughter, isn't it?

565
00:39:33,280 --> 00:39:36,039
How do you know this?

566
00:39:36,040 --> 00:39:37,639
Could you just...? Wait!

567
00:39:37,640 --> 00:39:40,119
Wait. Wait.

568
00:39:40,120 --> 00:39:43,239
Would you explain to me what the hell is happening.

569
00:39:43,240 --> 00:39:45,679
What happened to you happened to me.

570
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:48,079
I had it. I lost it. Okay?

571
00:39:48,080 --> 00:39:50,839
That's great. There's a cure. How do I get rid of this?

572
00:39:50,840 --> 00:39:52,479
First, I need your help.

573
00:39:52,480 --> 00:39:55,701
Help with what exactly?

574
00:39:55,720 --> 00:39:57,919
Winning the war.

575
00:39:57,920 --> 00:40:00,060
Let's go! Come on!

576
00:40:37,160 --> 00:40:38,399
Rita, what is this?

577
00:40:38,400 --> 00:40:41,199
What are you doing here? You gotta give me some warning.

578
00:40:41,200 --> 00:40:44,479
- Who's this?  - He's me. Before Verdun.

579
00:40:44,480 --> 00:40:46,825
He's gonna help us.

580
00:40:50,040 --> 00:40:52,119
What? You mean he's...?

581
00:40:52,120 --> 00:40:54,021
Yes.

582
00:40:55,680 --> 00:40:56,959
When did he die? Where?

583
00:40:56,960 --> 00:40:58,827
On the beach. Tomorrow.

584
00:41:00,600 --> 00:41:02,959
How many fingers am I holding up behind my back?

585
00:41:02,960 --> 00:41:05,191
How should I know that?

586
00:41:05,800 --> 00:41:06,719
Okay.

587
00:41:06,720 --> 00:41:10,719
So this is the first time we've had this conversation.

588
00:41:10,720 --> 00:41:13,159
- You should try this on him.  - What the hell is that?

589
00:41:13,160 --> 00:41:15,391
It doesn't work.

590
00:41:15,840 --> 00:41:17,119
Has he had any visions yet?

591
00:41:17,120 --> 00:41:18,319
Visions of what?

592
00:41:18,320 --> 00:41:19,519
There's still time.

593
00:41:19,520 --> 00:41:21,479
- Yes.  - Time? Look, I'm sorry.

594
00:41:21,480 --> 00:41:24,064
Who is this? Who are you?

595
00:41:24,240 --> 00:41:28,119
I'm Dr. Carter. Particle physics. Advanced microbiology.

596
00:41:28,120 --> 00:41:31,639
He's also the only other person who'll believe what's happening to you.

597
00:41:31,640 --> 00:41:33,919
No one understands mimic biology better than him.

598
00:41:33,920 --> 00:41:35,719
He's a top analyst at Whitehall.

599
00:41:35,720 --> 00:41:39,079
Well, I mean, I was until I met Rita and now I'm just...

600
00:41:39,080 --> 00:41:41,439
a "mechanic with psychiatric delusions."

601
00:41:41,440 --> 00:41:42,639
Carter.

602
00:41:42,640 --> 00:41:44,519
Show him.

603
00:41:44,520 --> 00:41:46,706
Yeah, right.

604
00:41:52,840 --> 00:41:54,719
Right. Well, first of all...

605
00:41:54,720 --> 00:41:55,999
you're not fighting an army.

606
00:41:56,000 --> 00:41:59,999
You have to think of this as a single organism.

607
00:42:00,000 --> 00:42:03,039
Now, these common drones, they act like its claws.

608
00:42:03,040 --> 00:42:07,079
And Alphas, like the one that you killed, are much more rare.

609
00:42:07,080 --> 00:42:08,479
Yeah. They're like one in...

610
00:42:08,480 --> 00:42:10,159
- 6.18 million, by my guess.  - Yes.

611
00:42:10,160 --> 00:42:11,879
They act as the enemy's...

612
00:42:11,880 --> 00:42:13,639
They're like its central nervous system.

613
00:42:13,640 --> 00:42:15,439
But this...

614
00:42:15,440 --> 00:42:17,479
is the brain.

615
00:42:17,480 --> 00:42:21,679
It controls them all. And this is the Omega.

616
00:42:21,680 --> 00:42:26,099
And the Omega has the ability to control time.

617
00:42:26,100 --> 00:42:28,799
Whenever an Alpha is killed...

618
00:42:28,800 --> 00:42:31,519
an automatic response is triggered.

619
00:42:31,520 --> 00:42:34,319
The Omega starts the day over again.

620
00:42:34,320 --> 00:42:39,519
But you see, this time, it can remember what's going to happen just like you do.

621
00:42:39,520 --> 00:42:42,759
It knows exactly what we're gonna do before we're gonna do it.

622
00:42:42,760 --> 00:42:46,311
- And an enemy that knows the future can't lose.  - It can't lose.

623
00:42:48,280 --> 00:42:50,399
But if that's true, how did you win at Verdun?

624
00:42:50,400 --> 00:42:52,559
We were allowed to win.

625
00:42:52,560 --> 00:42:55,599
This thing wants us to believe we can win.

626
00:42:55,600 --> 00:42:58,919
It wants us to throw everything we have into the invasion.

627
00:42:58,920 --> 00:43:03,919
Operation Downfall isn't our endgame it's the enemy's.

628
00:43:03,920 --> 00:43:08,399
The thing you've got to understand is this is a perfectly evolved...

629
00:43:08,400 --> 00:43:11,587
world-conquering organism.

630
00:43:11,680 --> 00:43:14,679
For all we know, there are millions of those asteroids...

631
00:43:14,680 --> 00:43:17,639
floating around in the cosmos like a virus.

632
00:43:17,640 --> 00:43:21,599
They're just waiting to crash-land into a world with just the right conditions.

633
00:43:21,600 --> 00:43:25,839
All they need is for the dominant life form to attack and

634
00:43:25,840 --> 00:43:27,719
There'll be nothing to stop the mimics...

635
00:43:27,720 --> 00:43:30,159
from conquering the rest of the world.

636
00:43:30,160 --> 00:43:33,062
Unless you change the outcome.

637
00:43:33,640 --> 00:43:35,039
Me?

638
00:43:35,040 --> 00:43:37,959
When you killed that Alpha, you inadvertently entered the enemy's nervous system.

639
00:43:37,960 --> 00:43:43,586
Cage, you've seized control of the Omega's ability to reset the day.

640
00:43:44,280 --> 00:43:46,759
- How's that even possible? - Perhaps this organism's...

641
00:43:46,760 --> 00:43:49,879
only vulnerability, its only vulnerability...

642
00:43:49,880 --> 00:43:51,119
is humanity.

643
00:43:51,120 --> 00:43:54,959
Regardless of that, you control the power now.

644
00:43:54,960 --> 00:43:57,679
Just as I did in Verdun.

645
00:43:57,680 --> 00:43:59,820
So I'm resetting the day?

646
00:44:01,680 --> 00:44:03,786
Okay.

647
00:44:03,800 --> 00:44:05,701
How do I control it?

648
00:44:08,080 --> 00:44:10,519
You have to die.

649
00:44:10,520 --> 00:44:12,039
Every day.

650
00:44:12,040 --> 00:44:14,942
Until the Omega's destroyed.

651
00:44:26,800 --> 00:44:28,479
First of all...

652
00:44:28,480 --> 00:44:30,679
this is a terrific presentation.

653
00:44:30,680 --> 00:44:33,105
Terrific.

654
00:44:33,200 --> 00:44:34,959
I know the general.

655
00:44:34,960 --> 00:44:37,519
We should take this to him.

656
00:44:37,520 --> 00:44:41,639
- You just tell him everything you told me.  - I went to see the general, Cage.

657
00:44:41,640 --> 00:44:44,383
Any number of times.

658
00:44:44,440 --> 00:44:48,184
Psych ward. Dissection. Remember?

659
00:44:50,400 --> 00:44:53,746
What are you expecting from me?

660
00:44:55,720 --> 00:44:58,304
Have you seen anything strange?

661
00:44:58,960 --> 00:45:00,199
Is he shitting me?

662
00:45:00,200 --> 00:45:01,279
Visions.

663
00:45:01,280 --> 00:45:04,387
Visions. Have you seen any visions like that?

664
00:45:05,120 --> 00:45:07,932
The Omega senses when it's losing control of its power.

665
00:45:07,933 --> 00:45:10,319
Even now it's mentally searching to find you.

666
00:45:10,320 --> 00:45:13,970
When it's close to finding you you will start having visions.

667
00:45:13,971 --> 00:45:18,587
- You'll start to see that.  - You'll even see where it is.

668
00:45:19,520 --> 00:45:21,279
And you had these visions?

669
00:45:21,280 --> 00:45:23,306
Yes.

670
00:45:25,280 --> 00:45:28,679
But eventually you saw it. I mean, you actually saw it.

671
00:45:28,680 --> 00:45:30,706
Right?

672
00:45:32,400 --> 00:45:34,347
Never in the flesh.

673
00:45:38,360 --> 00:45:41,342
So this is all just some...

674
00:45:41,440 --> 00:45:43,359
theory.

675
00:45:43,360 --> 00:45:46,159
You don't know if this thing even exists.

676
00:45:46,160 --> 00:45:50,621
The visions showed me it was at Verdun. I could see it. I...

677
00:45:50,640 --> 00:45:52,159
I just...

678
00:45:52,160 --> 00:45:55,461
lost the power before I could get to it.

679
00:45:55,920 --> 00:45:59,061
And by the time we took Verdun...

680
00:45:59,360 --> 00:46:02,262
the Omega was gone.

681
00:46:03,960 --> 00:46:08,439
Okay. So all I have to do is... wait to have these visions...

682
00:46:08,440 --> 00:46:12,239
and then tell you where this Omega thing is.

683
00:46:12,240 --> 00:46:14,399
No. Cage.

684
00:46:14,400 --> 00:46:19,026
You're gonna get me there. And I'm gonna kill it.

685
00:46:19,400 --> 00:46:21,586
Get you there?

686
00:46:22,840 --> 00:46:25,742
I'm not even trained for combat.

687
00:46:40,960 --> 00:46:42,383
Reload.

688
00:46:42,480 --> 00:46:44,745
Reload.

689
00:47:02,920 --> 00:47:05,159
Are you all right, Cage?

690
00:47:05,160 --> 00:47:06,879
I think I broke something.

691
00:47:06,880 --> 00:47:08,959
What?

692
00:47:08,960 --> 00:47:11,021
My back.

693
00:47:11,320 --> 00:47:14,479
The only thing I can feel are my lips.

694
00:47:14,480 --> 00:47:17,667
Now listen carefully. This is a very important rule.

695
00:47:18,120 --> 00:47:20,199
This is the only rule.

696
00:47:20,200 --> 00:47:24,024
You get injured on the field, you better make sure you die.

697
00:47:24,040 --> 00:47:25,119
Why?

698
00:47:25,120 --> 00:47:27,239
Last time I was in combat...

699
00:47:27,240 --> 00:47:28,919
I was hit.

700
00:47:28,920 --> 00:47:32,519
I was bleeding out. Just not fast enough.

701
00:47:32,520 --> 00:47:33,999
I woke up in a field hospital...

702
00:47:34,000 --> 00:47:38,382
with three pints of someone else's blood and I was out.

703
00:47:38,480 --> 00:47:42,239
I lost the power. Do you understand?

704
00:47:42,240 --> 00:47:43,719
Think we better start over.

705
00:47:43,720 --> 00:47:45,587
- Don't you?  - What?

706
00:47:46,000 --> 00:47:48,061
Aah!

707
00:47:49,360 --> 00:47:51,919
No one knows what happened to Private Cage!

708
00:47:51,920 --> 00:47:53,839
You dumb-ass. He was right next to you.

709
00:47:53,840 --> 00:47:56,559
You don't know where that slippery son of a bitch went?

710
00:47:56,560 --> 00:47:58,119
No, sarge!

711
00:47:58,120 --> 00:47:59,839
All right.

712
00:47:59,840 --> 00:48:02,119
Let's do another 50, shall we?

713
00:48:02,120 --> 00:48:03,559
And one!

714
00:48:03,560 --> 00:48:05,679
No, wait! Wait. My name is Bill Cage.

715
00:48:05,680 --> 00:48:09,159
I... We met on the beach. We meet on the beach. Tomorrow.

716
00:48:09,160 --> 00:48:11,186
I have what you had.

717
00:48:15,320 --> 00:48:18,382
Ugh. All right, let's go again.

718
00:48:22,200 --> 00:48:24,719
You don't have time to think. Remember.

719
00:48:24,720 --> 00:48:26,879
It's not enough knowing where they're going to be.

720
00:48:26,880 --> 00:48:30,021
You have to know how to kill them.

721
00:48:33,960 --> 00:48:38,262
Hold on. Hold on. Listen. List...

722
00:48:38,360 --> 00:48:40,261
Okay. Do it.

723
00:48:40,840 --> 00:48:42,479
Unh!

724
00:48:42,480 --> 00:48:44,063
On your feet, maggot!

725
00:48:47,960 --> 00:48:50,119
Stop! Wait! Wait, wait, wait!

726
00:48:50,120 --> 00:48:52,039
Stop! Wait! Wait a second!

727
00:48:52,040 --> 00:48:55,466
Wait a sec. Wait a second.

728
00:48:55,600 --> 00:48:57,439
You know, I've been thinking.

729
00:48:57,440 --> 00:49:00,999
I mean, this thing's in my blood.

730
00:49:01,000 --> 00:49:05,079
So maybe there's some way... I can transfer it to you.

731
00:49:05,080 --> 00:49:07,319
I've tried everything. It doesn't work.

732
00:49:07,320 --> 00:49:09,679
I mean, have you...

733
00:49:09,680 --> 00:49:11,581
you know...

734
00:49:12,280 --> 00:49:15,119
tried all the other options?

735
00:49:15,120 --> 00:49:18,022
Oh, you mean sex. Yep. Tried it.

736
00:49:18,360 --> 00:49:19,439
How many times?

737
00:49:19,440 --> 00:49:21,148
All right.

738
00:49:22,760 --> 00:49:23,599
Left.

739
00:49:23,600 --> 00:49:25,103
Left! Left, left!

740
00:49:28,640 --> 00:49:30,541
Keep your eyes open.

741
00:49:33,040 --> 00:49:34,463
Again.

742
00:49:34,600 --> 00:49:35,989
Again.

743
00:49:36,000 --> 00:49:37,423
Again.

744
00:49:39,680 --> 00:49:41,422
Again.

745
00:49:47,320 --> 00:49:48,879
Just wait! Wait.

746
00:49:48,880 --> 00:49:50,119
I think I'm okay.

747
00:49:50,120 --> 00:49:52,146
Unh!

748
00:49:52,240 --> 00:49:53,319
On your feet!

749
00:49:53,320 --> 00:49:54,839
Maggot! Maggot!

750
00:49:54,840 --> 00:49:57,822
I'm trying to be nice to you, maggot! Move!

751
00:49:59,760 --> 00:50:00,999
You okay, Cage?

752
00:50:01,000 --> 00:50:02,839
Oh yeah, yeah! I'm good! I'm good!

753
00:50:02,840 --> 00:50:04,079
Your leg's broken.

754
00:50:04,080 --> 00:50:07,221
No. I can still feel my toes.

755
00:50:07,680 --> 00:50:09,820
Oh, come on.

756
00:50:23,920 --> 00:50:26,265
Aah!

757
00:50:29,480 --> 00:50:32,519
Rita. Rita. What is this? What are you doing here?

758
00:50:32,520 --> 00:50:34,559
- Who's this guy?  - He's me...

759
00:50:34,560 --> 00:50:36,159
- before Verdun.  - Before Verdun.

760
00:50:36,160 --> 00:50:37,559
What do you mean? He's...?

761
00:50:37,560 --> 00:50:38,999
- Yes. Yes.  - When did he die?

762
00:50:39,000 --> 00:50:40,879
- Where?  - On the beach. Tomorrow.

763
00:50:40,880 --> 00:50:42,239
I'm Bill Cage. You're Dr. Carter.

764
00:50:42,240 --> 00:50:44,919
We've had this conversation before. Two fingers behind your back.

765
00:50:44,920 --> 00:50:46,759
I've had the visions.

766
00:50:46,760 --> 00:50:48,786
I've seen the Omega.

767
00:50:51,480 --> 00:50:53,108
Um...

768
00:50:53,920 --> 00:50:56,759
It's pretty much game over tomorrow.

769
00:50:56,760 --> 00:50:58,866
So can we move this along?

770
00:50:59,400 --> 00:51:02,029
Okay. Where?

771
00:51:02,320 --> 00:51:04,279
There's a dam.

772
00:51:04,280 --> 00:51:06,239
It's in the mountains. I saw German writing.

773
00:51:06,240 --> 00:51:08,279
Do you think you can work out where that is?

774
00:51:08,280 --> 00:51:12,002
I mean, there can't be... too many places that fit that description.

775
00:51:12,003 --> 00:51:13,405
I'll see what I can do.

776
00:51:13,440 --> 00:51:16,679
Training's over. I'll see you tomorrow.

777
00:51:16,680 --> 00:51:18,239
We don't even know where we're going.

778
00:51:18,240 --> 00:51:19,839
We will soon enough.

779
00:51:19,840 --> 00:51:24,062
In the meantime, you need to figure out a way to get us off that beach.

780
00:51:45,400 --> 00:51:47,559
What next? Where are we going?

781
00:51:47,560 --> 00:51:49,159
Which way? Focus. Which way?

782
00:51:49,160 --> 00:51:50,799
- I'm thinking.  - Okay.

783
00:51:50,800 --> 00:51:52,679
Oh, man!

784
00:51:52,680 --> 00:51:54,820
How far did we make it?

785
00:51:54,880 --> 00:51:58,989
You know, it's hard to say, really.

786
00:51:59,600 --> 00:52:02,119
Hold! Hold!

787
00:52:02,120 --> 00:52:04,226
Okay, go!

788
00:52:05,360 --> 00:52:06,439
Son of a bitch!

789
00:52:06,440 --> 00:52:09,239
I thought stepping left, ducking... Just for the record.

790
00:52:09,240 --> 00:52:11,839
- It was pretty specific.  - Stepping left, ducking right.

791
00:52:11,840 --> 00:52:15,789
Stepping left, ducking right. Move on.

792
00:52:18,880 --> 00:52:20,559
Hold on!

793
00:52:20,560 --> 00:52:23,479
Across the trench, 12:00!

794
00:52:23,480 --> 00:52:25,541
Then look to your right!

795
00:52:31,360 --> 00:52:32,919
You're not being specific.

796
00:52:32,920 --> 00:52:35,982
You need to be specific. Otherwise, I'm dead.

797
00:52:36,040 --> 00:52:38,305
Rita.

798
00:52:39,200 --> 00:52:41,101
Cage!

799
00:52:42,320 --> 00:52:45,199
Paces up to the top of the trench. I'm gonna step left.

800
00:52:45,200 --> 00:52:47,625
A mimic there, which I'll kill.

801
00:52:56,520 --> 00:52:59,199
Ship explosion. I'm gonna run 30 paces northwest.

802
00:52:59,200 --> 00:53:03,502
I'm gonna duck at the top of that trench and then I'm gonna turn left.

803
00:53:11,680 --> 00:53:14,150
Have I got something on my face?

804
00:53:15,360 --> 00:53:17,261
No.

805
00:53:24,720 --> 00:53:26,039
Cage!

806
00:53:26,040 --> 00:53:28,679
We've been looking everywhere for you.

807
00:53:28,680 --> 00:53:30,279
Cage!

808
00:53:30,280 --> 00:53:33,079
- Cage, we've been looking...  - Guys.

809
00:53:33,080 --> 00:53:34,719
Guys. Can we...

810
00:53:34,720 --> 00:53:36,079
just...

811
00:53:36,080 --> 00:53:37,759
not do this today?

812
00:53:37,760 --> 00:53:39,559
What are you talking about?

813
00:53:39,560 --> 00:53:43,508
Farell almost strung us up by our bollocks for losing track of you.

814
00:53:45,200 --> 00:53:47,590
Okay, Skinner. Watch this.

815
00:53:48,440 --> 00:53:50,439
Now I'm gonna close my eyes.

816
00:53:50,440 --> 00:53:52,179
- Ready?  - Yeah.

817
00:53:56,680 --> 00:53:59,479
Sneaky bastard.

818
00:53:59,480 --> 00:54:02,269
I didn't mind the extra push-ups.

819
00:54:11,080 --> 00:54:14,079
It's a new day people.

820
00:54:14,080 --> 00:54:15,719
Destiny calls.

821
00:54:15,720 --> 00:54:20,022
The world expects only one thing from us that we will win.

822
00:54:34,920 --> 00:54:37,119
current situation on the front line.

823
00:54:37,120 --> 00:54:39,559
Our troops have suffered heavy casualties.

824
00:54:39,560 --> 00:54:42,279
It's about time we showed those things what we're made of.

825
00:54:42,280 --> 00:54:44,839
My father flew in the Battle of Britain.

826
00:54:44,840 --> 00:54:48,039
Three years before the Yanks came into the war.

827
00:54:48,040 --> 00:54:49,879
Couldn't be broken.

828
00:54:49,880 --> 00:54:51,119
Backbone.

829
00:54:51,120 --> 00:54:53,439
My Uncle George landed on the beach at Normandy.

830
00:54:53,440 --> 00:54:54,719
Yeah?

831
00:54:54,720 --> 00:54:57,639
In their day, this war would have been over by now.

832
00:54:57,640 --> 00:54:59,599
What do they want with us, anyway?

833
00:54:59,600 --> 00:55:01,639
It's obvious, isn't it? Minerals.

834
00:55:01,640 --> 00:55:03,479
- Minerals?  - Yeah, minerals. Metals.

835
00:55:03,480 --> 00:55:04,919
- Oxygen, they want. - Oxygen?

836
00:55:04,920 --> 00:55:07,239
- Think about it.  - What difference does it make?

837
00:55:07,240 --> 00:55:09,599
They're here. They're winning.

838
00:55:09,600 --> 00:55:12,319
And whatever it is, they're gonna get it.

839
00:55:12,320 --> 00:55:15,319
Shouldn't you be over there?

840
00:55:15,320 --> 00:55:17,267
I've been over there.

841
00:55:17,280 --> 00:55:19,719
More times than anybody.

842
00:55:19,720 --> 00:55:24,625
As a matter of fact, I'm usually long dead by now.

843
00:55:26,400 --> 00:55:28,381
Coward.

844
00:55:30,800 --> 00:55:32,199
What's going on?

845
00:55:32,200 --> 00:55:34,340
The power's gone.

846
00:56:41,720 --> 00:56:43,159
I found the Omega.

847
00:56:43,160 --> 00:56:46,199
I found it. It has to be here. Curnera Dam, Germany.

848
00:56:46,200 --> 00:56:49,399
- This has got to be it. It fits the description.  - You found it.

849
00:56:49,400 --> 00:56:51,159
Again.

850
00:56:51,160 --> 00:56:53,279
What difference does it make?

851
00:56:53,280 --> 00:56:55,830
Because we're never gonna get there.

852
00:56:56,160 --> 00:56:58,221
No matter what we do...

853
00:56:58,400 --> 00:57:01,719
no matter how carefully we plan...

854
00:57:01,720 --> 00:57:04,622
we can't get off that beach.

855
00:57:14,120 --> 00:57:16,799
You can do this. You can.

856
00:57:16,800 --> 00:57:21,068
You keep coming here every day and I'll train you.

857
00:57:23,000 --> 00:57:25,345
You already have.

858
00:57:44,080 --> 00:57:48,039
- I'm waiting, Nance!  - Five hundred meters and closing fast!

859
00:57:48,040 --> 00:57:50,271
What the...?

860
00:57:57,880 --> 00:57:59,827
Reload.

861
00:58:11,080 --> 00:58:13,311
What's next?

862
00:58:14,080 --> 00:58:17,039
Straight shot up the hill.

863
00:58:17,040 --> 00:58:19,146
Okay.

864
00:58:19,400 --> 00:58:21,959
Hey, sarge, the new guy...

865
00:58:21,960 --> 00:58:24,305
what's his name again?

866
00:58:27,200 --> 00:58:30,559
We'll need a vehicle to get further inland.

867
00:58:30,560 --> 00:58:31,999
What's the problem?

868
00:58:32,000 --> 00:58:35,559
The ambush waiting for us. They kill us before we find a working car.

869
00:58:35,560 --> 00:58:37,919
Okay. So, what's the current plan?

870
00:58:37,920 --> 00:58:39,359
Two cars we haven't tried yet.

871
00:58:39,360 --> 00:58:42,519
- The minivan and the green SUV.  - Yeah. Okay.

872
00:58:42,520 --> 00:58:45,679
I'll head for the SUV, draw the mimics to me. You go for the minivan.

873
00:58:45,680 --> 00:58:48,759
You get it started, just go, take off. Do not wait for me.

874
00:58:48,760 --> 00:58:50,119
Okay.

875
00:58:50,120 --> 00:58:54,198
Just don't forget to disconnect the caravan before you take off.

876
00:58:54,199 --> 00:58:58,831
You are going to be in a hurry, you don't want any dead weight.

877
00:59:22,880 --> 00:59:24,659
Come on.

878
00:59:38,880 --> 00:59:40,781
Come on, Cage!

879
00:59:43,000 --> 00:59:46,559
casualties. The enemy has breached security at Dover.

880
00:59:46,560 --> 00:59:48,507
Can't see.

881
00:59:49,880 --> 00:59:51,941
Can you?

882
00:59:59,600 --> 01:00:02,279
Stay where you are and remain calm.

883
01:00:02,280 --> 01:00:07,500
If you are in a vehicle please lock doors and stay inside.

884
01:00:13,440 --> 01:00:16,279
I'm sorry. The enemy has reached London.

885
01:00:16,280 --> 01:00:17,879
Repeat.

886
01:00:17,880 --> 01:00:20,145
London is under attack.

887
01:00:24,680 --> 01:00:25,999
Good driving.

888
01:00:26,000 --> 01:00:28,186
I forgot to unhook the trailer.

889
01:01:13,720 --> 01:01:16,429
You don't talk much.

890
01:01:16,520 --> 01:01:18,119
I'm not a fan.

891
01:01:18,120 --> 01:01:19,679
Of talking?

892
01:01:19,680 --> 01:01:22,548
Not a fan of talking. No.

893
01:01:23,120 --> 01:01:26,307
You know you eventually do talk to me.

894
01:01:27,160 --> 01:01:28,399
It's usually around Lyons.

895
01:01:28,400 --> 01:01:31,399
You tell me about the time you went there with your family.

896
01:01:31,400 --> 01:01:33,984
Your brother got lost.

897
01:01:35,000 --> 01:01:37,439
I've never been to Lyons.

898
01:01:37,440 --> 01:01:40,024
You tell me your middle name.

899
01:01:40,720 --> 01:01:42,860
Peyton.

900
01:01:44,200 --> 01:01:47,023
That's not my middle name.

901
01:01:50,960 --> 01:01:54,386
You find your brother in the arcade, by the way.

902
01:01:55,440 --> 01:01:58,039
Well, maybe I made it all up just to keep you quiet.

903
01:01:58,040 --> 01:01:59,279
But you do talk to me.

904
01:01:59,280 --> 01:02:01,559
Cage, I do not need to get to know you.

905
01:02:01,560 --> 01:02:04,959
If you knew what was good for you, you wouldn't want to get to know me.

906
01:02:04,960 --> 01:02:07,999
It's the only way you make it through this thing.

907
01:02:08,000 --> 01:02:10,879
What about Hendricks? You get to know him?

908
01:02:10,880 --> 01:02:13,839
- How do you know that name?  - You mentioned him.

909
01:02:13,840 --> 01:02:15,119
That's not possible.

910
01:02:15,120 --> 01:02:16,639
Then how do I know his name?

911
01:02:16,640 --> 01:02:20,020
When did I mention him? Under what circumstance?

912
01:02:20,520 --> 01:02:23,343
Is he why you won't talk to me?

913
01:02:26,240 --> 01:02:29,461
Don't ever mention his name again.

914
01:02:29,840 --> 01:02:33,665
- Why? Are you... in love with him?  - He's dead.

915
01:02:36,080 --> 01:02:41,039
And I watched him die 300 times and I remember every detail.

916
01:02:41,040 --> 01:02:45,023
I remember everything. So I don't need to talk about it.

917
01:02:49,400 --> 01:02:50,879
I'm sorry.

918
01:02:50,880 --> 01:02:53,430
It's just war.

919
01:03:55,600 --> 01:03:58,502
There's nothing here. Let's keep going.

920
01:04:21,240 --> 01:04:23,301
We have to find the keys.

921
01:04:23,880 --> 01:04:25,439
Let's just siphon the gas.

922
01:04:25,440 --> 01:04:29,230
- Why drive when we can fly?  - In that thing?

923
01:04:29,360 --> 01:04:32,839
- Let me guess. You're afraid of heights.  - I'm afraid of crashing.

924
01:04:32,840 --> 01:04:34,759
And not at all ashamed to admit it.

925
01:04:34,760 --> 01:04:38,061
You'll be fine, Cage. You'll learn. Oh.

926
01:04:38,800 --> 01:04:40,039
What is it?

927
01:04:40,040 --> 01:04:42,079
It's nothing. I'm fine.

928
01:04:42,080 --> 01:04:43,679
- What is it?  - It's nothing.

929
01:04:43,680 --> 01:04:45,581
Rita.

930
01:04:48,800 --> 01:04:50,986
Let me see.

931
01:05:10,160 --> 01:05:12,399
We have to find the keys to the helicopter.

932
01:05:12,400 --> 01:05:14,919
I'm sure they're around here somewhere.

933
01:05:14,920 --> 01:05:19,159
You know, the heli's full of fuel, though. I found a hose.

934
01:05:19,160 --> 01:05:21,903
We're flying, Cage.

935
01:05:24,840 --> 01:05:28,359
Let's just say we find the keys. You know?

936
01:05:28,360 --> 01:05:30,599
Get that helicopter started.

937
01:05:30,600 --> 01:05:32,911
We don't have our jackets or ammunition.

938
01:05:32,920 --> 01:05:35,584
It's gonna be dark in a few hours.

939
01:05:37,440 --> 01:05:40,719
Might be better off just going back to the farmhouse.

940
01:05:40,720 --> 01:05:42,479
Seeing what we could salvage.

941
01:05:42,480 --> 01:05:45,799
Spend the night there. Come back here in the morning.

942
01:05:45,800 --> 01:05:49,226
And curl up by the fire and open a bottle of wine.

943
01:05:52,080 --> 01:05:54,345
I think we should just reset.

944
01:05:54,640 --> 01:05:55,519
Whoa!

945
01:05:55,520 --> 01:05:59,159
It's a dead end. If it's all the same to you I'm tired. I'm in pain.

946
01:05:59,160 --> 01:06:00,999
- I'd rather just start fresh.  - Tell you what.

947
01:06:01,000 --> 01:06:03,679
Take a few minutes. Coffee's ready.

948
01:06:03,680 --> 01:06:05,559
I'll look for the keys. That's productive.

949
01:06:05,560 --> 01:06:07,399
- Ten minutes.  - Okay.

950
01:06:07,400 --> 01:06:09,381
Then I'm killing you.

951
01:06:09,600 --> 01:06:11,501
Fine.

952
01:06:14,000 --> 01:06:16,026
I can't believe you found coffee.

953
01:06:18,200 --> 01:06:20,101
Thank you.

954
01:06:20,480 --> 01:06:22,461
Oh.

955
01:06:22,480 --> 01:06:24,279
Sugar, right?

956
01:06:24,280 --> 01:06:26,181
Yeah.

957
01:06:31,000 --> 01:06:34,551
- Thank you.  - No, hold on. Three. You like three.

958
01:06:47,800 --> 01:06:51,146
There's a shirt over there. It should be your size.

959
01:06:58,600 --> 01:07:01,787
How many times have we been here?

960
01:07:07,000 --> 01:07:08,947
How many times?

961
01:07:09,360 --> 01:07:11,591
Where are the keys?

962
01:07:11,760 --> 01:07:13,991
- Where are the goddamn keys?  - Okay.

963
01:07:17,000 --> 01:07:18,439
You can fly it, can't you?

964
01:07:18,440 --> 01:07:19,999
No. Well, yes.

965
01:07:20,000 --> 01:07:22,759
I mean, I can take off. I'm still working on my landing.

966
01:07:22,760 --> 01:07:24,799
What are we still doing here?

967
01:07:24,800 --> 01:07:28,067
- You're wasting time!  - Rita, if you start that engine, you die.

968
01:07:31,320 --> 01:07:33,399
This is as far as you go.

969
01:07:33,400 --> 01:07:35,665
No matter what I do...

970
01:07:35,920 --> 01:07:38,982
this is as far as you ever make it.

971
01:07:45,880 --> 01:07:49,439
There's a mimic buried 20 yards away.

972
01:07:49,440 --> 01:07:52,069
It attacks when you start the engine.

973
01:07:52,680 --> 01:07:55,359
Get your weapon and get in the helicopter, Cage.

974
01:07:55,360 --> 01:07:58,388
There's more in the field back there.

975
01:07:59,640 --> 01:08:01,239
Only one of us ever makes it.

976
01:08:01,240 --> 01:08:02,559
Get in.

977
01:08:02,560 --> 01:08:05,279
Only thing we haven't tried is you walk away. Go to the farmhouse.

978
01:08:05,280 --> 01:08:06,679
There's a cellar and there's food.

979
01:08:06,680 --> 01:08:09,639
Wait there... till I get back. You'll be safe.

980
01:08:09,640 --> 01:08:13,079
I'm a soldier. I volunteered. I'm not walking away.

981
01:08:13,080 --> 01:08:16,381
You die here. Right here.

982
01:08:18,320 --> 01:08:19,479
I can't save you.

983
01:08:19,480 --> 01:08:23,079
And if I go on and kill the Omega, you're dead.

984
01:08:23,080 --> 01:08:24,359
Forever.

985
01:08:24,360 --> 01:08:27,706
Why does it matter what happens to me?

986
01:08:30,440 --> 01:08:32,341
I wish...

987
01:08:32,360 --> 01:08:34,591
I didn't know you.

988
01:08:35,960 --> 01:08:38,191
But I do.

989
01:10:08,400 --> 01:10:11,029
My middle name...

990
01:10:11,240 --> 01:10:13,790
is Rose.

991
01:10:32,760 --> 01:10:35,230
On your feet, maggot!

992
01:10:45,720 --> 01:10:47,919
The good news is there's hope for you, private.

993
01:10:47,920 --> 01:10:51,079
Hope in the form of glorious combat.

994
01:10:51,080 --> 01:10:52,799
Battle is the great redeemer.

995
01:10:52,800 --> 01:10:57,147
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.

996
01:11:07,760 --> 01:11:09,661
Yes?

997
01:11:10,040 --> 01:11:12,783
Who said you could talk to me?

998
01:11:15,480 --> 01:11:18,587
Have I got something on my face, soldier?

999
01:11:21,280 --> 01:11:23,909
I'm sorry to disturb you, sergeant.

1000
01:11:45,320 --> 01:11:48,382
Let's get this show on the road. I gotta suit up.

1001
01:11:50,320 --> 01:11:52,221
Where's your helmet?

1002
01:11:53,520 --> 01:11:57,469
Never wear one. It's a distraction.

1003
01:11:59,080 --> 01:12:00,359
Have you been drinking?

1004
01:12:00,360 --> 01:12:02,599
I need three more clips of 5.56...

1005
01:12:02,600 --> 01:12:06,390
eight grenades and an extra battery.

1006
01:12:09,160 --> 01:12:11,061
Get it.

1007
01:12:17,200 --> 01:12:18,559
Oi!

1008
01:12:18,560 --> 01:12:20,279
Oi, mate!

1009
01:12:20,280 --> 01:12:22,750
There's something wrong with your suit.

1010
01:12:23,600 --> 01:12:26,159
There's a dead guy in it.

1011
01:12:26,160 --> 01:12:27,199
Whoo-hoo!

1012
01:12:27,200 --> 01:12:28,679
We made it!

1013
01:12:28,680 --> 01:12:31,025
Thank God, we made it!

1014
01:14:32,880 --> 01:14:35,066
Finish it!

1015
01:15:29,280 --> 01:15:31,359
- It isn't there.  - What do you mean?

1016
01:15:31,360 --> 01:15:33,279
My guess is it never was.

1017
01:15:33,280 --> 01:15:35,959
They knew we were coming. They ambushed us.

1018
01:15:35,960 --> 01:15:38,350
The visions were a trap.

1019
01:15:38,960 --> 01:15:42,147
Just like Rita's visions were a trap at Verdun.

1020
01:15:42,680 --> 01:15:45,479
It could have killed me, but it didn't. It was after my blood.

1021
01:15:45,480 --> 01:15:48,587
So they know who you are. They...

1022
01:15:49,080 --> 01:15:50,719
They want their power back.

1023
01:15:50,720 --> 01:15:54,439
They're gonna get it one way or another. Unless we find the Omega.

1024
01:15:54,440 --> 01:15:56,359
- There isn't any other way. We're finished.  - No.

1025
01:15:56,360 --> 01:15:58,519
We're not finished.

1026
01:15:58,520 --> 01:15:59,839
I can't get it to work.

1027
01:15:59,840 --> 01:16:01,519
You built a prototype at Whitehall.

1028
01:16:01,520 --> 01:16:04,119
Yes, and I got fired for it, thank you very much.

1029
01:16:04,120 --> 01:16:06,159
- What is this thing?  - It's a transponder.

1030
01:16:06,160 --> 01:16:09,399
Stick it into the Alpha and it taps into the wavelength connecting it to the Omega.

1031
01:16:09,400 --> 01:16:11,439
That's the idea, anyway.

1032
01:16:11,440 --> 01:16:14,820
I can't get it to work. Not with the equipment I have.

1033
01:16:16,800 --> 01:16:18,359
How do we get what you need?

1034
01:16:18,360 --> 01:16:21,159
That's the thing. When I was at Whitehall, I built one.

1035
01:16:21,160 --> 01:16:22,879
I was even ready to test it.

1036
01:16:22,880 --> 01:16:25,439
When I told my superiors about it, I lost my job.

1037
01:16:25,440 --> 01:16:27,399
They thought he was crazy.

1038
01:16:27,400 --> 01:16:29,599
So we need to go to Whitehall.

1039
01:16:29,600 --> 01:16:31,992
She'd be arrested 10 feet from the front door.

1040
01:16:31,993 --> 01:16:35,239
Psych ward, dissection, remember? Hey, hey, hey.

1041
01:16:35,240 --> 01:16:36,879
Aren't you forgetting something?

1042
01:16:36,880 --> 01:16:39,319
The transponder requires a live Alpha to make it work.

1043
01:16:39,320 --> 01:16:44,261
We don't need one. We got the next best thing.

1044
01:16:45,880 --> 01:16:50,350
When the Chinese delegation comes out we pick up the pace.

1045
01:16:50,960 --> 01:16:53,919
This guy with the yellow armband always recognizes you...

1046
01:16:53,920 --> 01:16:58,188
so just keep your head down and stay to my right.

1047
01:17:03,840 --> 01:17:06,071
Nicely done.

1048
01:17:08,000 --> 01:17:10,439
Three, two, one. Go.

1049
01:17:10,440 --> 01:17:12,387
One...

1050
01:17:14,200 --> 01:17:15,839
Six, seven...

1051
01:17:15,840 --> 01:17:17,741
eight...

1052
01:17:19,040 --> 01:17:20,941
Twelve...

1053
01:17:22,480 --> 01:17:23,879
Fifteen. Now.

1054
01:17:23,880 --> 01:17:26,589
And, turn.

1055
01:17:26,640 --> 01:17:29,668
Okay. Keep walking. Just stare straight ahead.

1056
01:17:30,560 --> 01:17:32,519
Robinson.

1057
01:17:32,520 --> 01:17:35,439
I've asked not to be disturbed. This had better be critical.

1058
01:17:35,440 --> 01:17:36,759
The fate of mankind.

1059
01:17:36,760 --> 01:17:38,479
Critical enough?

1060
01:17:38,480 --> 01:17:40,239
I don't believe what I'm seeing.

1061
01:17:40,240 --> 01:17:42,719
I've had more than my share of that.

1062
01:17:42,720 --> 01:17:45,279
Sit down, general. Stay away from the desk.

1063
01:17:45,280 --> 01:17:48,864
I'd take her very seriously if I were you.

1064
01:17:49,640 --> 01:17:51,919
Have to hand it to you, major.

1065
01:17:51,920 --> 01:17:54,839
When you left this office today, I never imagined you'd be back...

1066
01:17:54,840 --> 01:17:57,479
let alone with my most decorated soldier.

1067
01:17:57,480 --> 01:18:00,039
I'm gonna tell you a story. It's gonna sound ridiculous.

1068
01:18:00,040 --> 01:18:02,421
The longer I talk, the more rational it's going to appear.

1069
01:18:02,840 --> 01:18:04,079
Tell him you'll call back.

1070
01:18:04,080 --> 01:18:05,879
Tell who?

1071
01:18:05,880 --> 01:18:10,068
Major General Beaumont, calling from Halifax. His plane's just been delayed. Bad weather.

1072
01:18:10,280 --> 01:18:12,261
Yes.

1073
01:18:14,440 --> 01:18:17,468
Thank you, Beaumont. I'll call you back.

1074
01:18:18,440 --> 01:18:20,423
Tomorrow's invasion is a slaughter.

1075
01:18:20,424 --> 01:18:24,719
I'm dead within minutes of landing along with every other soldier you are sending.

1076
01:18:24,720 --> 01:18:27,439
And that's because the enemy knows we're coming.

1077
01:18:27,440 --> 01:18:29,719
How do I know this? Before I died...

1078
01:18:29,720 --> 01:18:31,999
I killed a mimic, only this one was different.

1079
01:18:32,000 --> 01:18:33,999
It passed something on to me. In my blood.

1080
01:18:34,000 --> 01:18:37,879
Now I live the same day over and over again. Just like they do.

1081
01:18:37,880 --> 01:18:40,679
Just like Sergeant Vrataski at Verdun.

1082
01:18:40,680 --> 01:18:43,199
Tell your secretary everything's fine.

1083
01:18:43,200 --> 01:18:45,226
Beg your pardon?

1084
01:18:48,520 --> 01:18:50,399
Sorry, general. I thought you were alone.

1085
01:18:50,400 --> 01:18:51,239
It's fine.

1086
01:18:51,240 --> 01:18:53,519
She typed up those orders for you to authorize.

1087
01:18:53,520 --> 01:18:57,580
But she left out the ones referring to the fuel dump at Greenwich.

1088
01:18:58,640 --> 01:18:59,919
Your name is Iris.

1089
01:18:59,920 --> 01:19:02,399
Your birthday is September 17th.

1090
01:19:02,400 --> 01:19:04,079
The general pulled some strings...

1091
01:19:04,080 --> 01:19:07,359
stationed your son in Australia, as far from the war as possible.

1092
01:19:07,360 --> 01:19:11,309
Tell the general his dinner's been canceled. The call came in just now.

1093
01:19:12,720 --> 01:19:14,679
Your dinner was canceled.

1094
01:19:14,680 --> 01:19:17,119
You forgot the fuel dump.

1095
01:19:17,120 --> 01:19:18,199
Thank you, Iris.

1096
01:19:18,200 --> 01:19:20,101
That'll be all.

1097
01:19:27,280 --> 01:19:29,679
- Cage, let's go. Come on.  - Rita.

1098
01:19:29,680 --> 01:19:32,879
- Let me... Don't shoot him again.  - What are we doing?

1099
01:19:32,880 --> 01:19:35,509
Okay? Just...

1100
01:19:38,720 --> 01:19:42,039
General, this isn't the first time we've had this conversation.

1101
01:19:42,040 --> 01:19:46,069
That's because you're stubborn.

1102
01:19:46,440 --> 01:19:50,199
You won't believe me when I tell you that Dr. Carter was right.

1103
01:19:50,200 --> 01:19:52,119
That the enemy can manipulate time.

1104
01:19:52,120 --> 01:19:56,159
The invasion will fail. No matter how many bodies you throw at it.

1105
01:19:56,160 --> 01:19:58,159
The only way to win this war is...

1106
01:19:58,160 --> 01:20:02,439
by finding this power source of the mimic horde and killing it.

1107
01:20:02,440 --> 01:20:06,389
And the only means of finding it is in that safe right there.

1108
01:20:08,320 --> 01:20:10,239
No matter how many times we have this conversation...

1109
01:20:10,240 --> 01:20:13,719
you refuse to accept that the enemy breaks through to London tomorrow...

1110
01:20:13,720 --> 01:20:17,590
and we lose. We lose everything.

1111
01:20:24,120 --> 01:20:26,260
Let's say for one moment...

1112
01:20:26,960 --> 01:20:29,225
that I can't rationally explain...

1113
01:20:29,920 --> 01:20:32,390
your impressive parlor tricks.

1114
01:20:34,520 --> 01:20:37,159
Dr. Carter told me...

1115
01:20:37,160 --> 01:20:41,199
this device requires a live mimic to work. What use is it to you?

1116
01:20:41,200 --> 01:20:43,750
- That's my concern.  - On the contrary.

1117
01:20:44,040 --> 01:20:46,759
According to you, this concerns the whole world.

1118
01:20:46,760 --> 01:20:50,869
Well, what would you do if you believed everything I just told you?

1119
01:20:51,440 --> 01:20:53,719
- I would locate this...  - Omega.

1120
01:20:53,720 --> 01:20:55,039
Bomb it out of existence.

1121
01:20:55,040 --> 01:20:59,706
You're not mentally equipped to fight this thing. And you never will be.

1122
01:21:15,440 --> 01:21:17,830
What do we do now?

1123
01:21:17,960 --> 01:21:21,431
I don't know. We've never gotten this far.

1124
01:21:26,440 --> 01:21:27,519
That was easy.

1125
01:21:27,520 --> 01:21:28,599
Down!

1126
01:21:28,600 --> 01:21:30,759
Stop right there! Don't move!

1127
01:21:30,760 --> 01:21:33,185
Nobody move!

1128
01:21:33,520 --> 01:21:35,182
Weapon!

1129
01:21:36,160 --> 01:21:38,061
Stop!

1130
01:21:41,520 --> 01:21:43,279
- They're off and away!  - They're...

1131
01:21:43,280 --> 01:21:47,667
- What am I supposed to do with this? - Stick it in your leg. Do it!

1132
01:22:05,280 --> 01:22:07,705
Cage, what's happening?

1133
01:22:07,760 --> 01:22:09,519
Talk to me.

1134
01:22:09,520 --> 01:22:12,679
I feel it. It's taking me there.

1135
01:22:12,680 --> 01:22:14,741
What do you see?

1136
01:22:15,680 --> 01:22:17,279
It's the Louvre.

1137
01:22:17,280 --> 01:22:19,119
Where? Where are you?

1138
01:22:19,120 --> 01:22:21,988
I'm inside now. It's flooded.

1139
01:22:22,440 --> 01:22:26,159
Now I'm going down. I'm in a garage. A garage underneath the museum.

1140
01:22:26,160 --> 01:22:28,550
The Omega. Can you see it?

1141
01:22:34,080 --> 01:22:35,902
It's in Paris.

1142
01:22:53,120 --> 01:22:54,623
Rita!

1143
01:23:03,440 --> 01:23:05,679
Stay in the car!

1144
01:23:05,680 --> 01:23:09,629
- Stay back.  - Move away. Move away.

1145
01:23:35,760 --> 01:23:37,639
What have you done?

1146
01:23:37,640 --> 01:23:40,461
What have you done?

1147
01:23:41,600 --> 01:23:44,319
You'll be fine. You just needed blood.

1148
01:23:44,320 --> 01:23:47,319
You don't know what you've just done.

1149
01:23:47,320 --> 01:23:50,386
- I can't talk to you.  - I was with someone.

1150
01:23:51,520 --> 01:23:54,079
Rita Vrataski. Is she alive?

1151
01:23:54,080 --> 01:23:55,999
Rita Vrataski.

1152
01:23:56,000 --> 01:23:57,901
Please.

1153
01:23:57,920 --> 01:24:00,106
Just tell me that.

1154
01:24:01,480 --> 01:24:03,759
Please tell me.

1155
01:24:03,760 --> 01:24:05,661
I'm sorry.

1156
01:24:41,960 --> 01:24:46,223
I was out of those things in three minutes flat. What's wrong with you?

1157
01:24:47,240 --> 01:24:49,279
I thought you were dead.

1158
01:24:49,280 --> 01:24:51,386
Not yet.

1159
01:24:55,640 --> 01:24:57,799
- Sorry, Cage.  - No! Whoa. Wait! Wait!

1160
01:24:57,800 --> 01:25:01,665
I'm out. I'm out. They gave me blood.

1161
01:25:05,040 --> 01:25:07,351
I lost the power.

1162
01:25:08,400 --> 01:25:10,519
I feel it.

1163
01:25:10,520 --> 01:25:13,422
I can't reset the day anymore.

1164
01:25:27,680 --> 01:25:32,063
We have to kill the Omega before the invasion starts.

1165
01:25:32,160 --> 01:25:34,919
That gives us less than three hours.

1166
01:25:34,920 --> 01:25:38,359
We need a drop ship to get to Paris in time.

1167
01:25:38,360 --> 01:25:40,479
Need more soldiers too.

1168
01:25:40,480 --> 01:25:43,621
Now, who's crazy enough to follow us to Paris?

1169
01:25:49,600 --> 01:25:50,799
Cage!

1170
01:25:50,800 --> 01:25:52,039
Cage!

1171
01:25:52,040 --> 01:25:54,519
- Guys!  - We've been looking everywhere for you.

1172
01:25:54,520 --> 01:25:56,719
- Just listen.  - Farell almost strung us up...

1173
01:25:56,720 --> 01:25:59,279
- for losing track of you.  - I know. Just listen.

1174
01:25:59,280 --> 01:26:00,879
You're gonna wanna hear this story.

1175
01:26:00,880 --> 01:26:02,759
It's gonna sound ridiculous at first.

1176
01:26:02,760 --> 01:26:05,679
The longer I talk, the more rational it's going to appear.

1177
01:26:05,680 --> 01:26:06,839
Yeah?

1178
01:26:06,840 --> 01:26:09,039
He named the school I went to.

1179
01:26:09,040 --> 01:26:13,519
And then he tells me my second grade teacher was called Miss Polio.

1180
01:26:13,520 --> 01:26:16,279
She wouldn't let him go to the bathroom made him wet his pants.

1181
01:26:16,280 --> 01:26:17,919
Shut up.

1182
01:26:17,920 --> 01:26:20,359
Look, I am telling you, man.

1183
01:26:20,360 --> 01:26:22,039
He knows everything.

1184
01:26:22,040 --> 01:26:23,159
About all of us.

1185
01:26:23,160 --> 01:26:25,359
- Bullshit.  - Yeah?

1186
01:26:25,360 --> 01:26:28,547
He says your name ain't really Ford.

1187
01:26:28,760 --> 01:26:30,479
Says Ford was your friend.

1188
01:26:30,480 --> 01:26:33,239
Died in combat on his first day.

1189
01:26:33,240 --> 01:26:35,599
You took his place. Send your checks to his family.

1190
01:26:35,600 --> 01:26:37,999
You slippery bitch.

1191
01:26:38,000 --> 01:26:41,559
Cage says the enemy knows us too. They're waiting for us on the beach.

1192
01:26:41,560 --> 01:26:42,719
And we all die.

1193
01:26:42,720 --> 01:26:45,279
The whole invasion is a slaughter.

1194
01:26:45,280 --> 01:26:47,359
Well, this is great.

1195
01:26:47,360 --> 01:26:49,879
Really good confidence boost for tomorrow. Thanks.

1196
01:26:49,880 --> 01:26:51,719
But we can change it, right?

1197
01:26:51,720 --> 01:26:53,679
There has to be something that we can do.

1198
01:26:53,680 --> 01:26:56,628
There has to be a way that we can win.

1199
01:26:57,200 --> 01:27:00,944
There is a chance. It's a slim one.

1200
01:27:02,080 --> 01:27:04,519
But it means coming with me right now.

1201
01:27:04,520 --> 01:27:05,639
Listen, pal.

1202
01:27:05,640 --> 01:27:08,879
I don't really care what you think you know about us.

1203
01:27:08,880 --> 01:27:11,225
We just met you.

1204
01:27:12,200 --> 01:27:14,181
Why follow him into combat?

1205
01:27:19,000 --> 01:27:21,439
I don't expect you to follow me.

1206
01:27:21,440 --> 01:27:24,183
I expect you to follow her.

1207
01:27:27,480 --> 01:27:29,984
- That's the Full Metal Bitch.  - J Squad.

1208
01:27:30,760 --> 01:27:32,879
This is Rita Vrataski.

1209
01:27:32,880 --> 01:27:35,719
- Otherwise known as...  - Yeah, yeah.

1210
01:27:35,720 --> 01:27:38,588
The Angel of Verdun.

1211
01:27:48,120 --> 01:27:50,181
Okay.

1212
01:27:58,560 --> 01:28:00,519
It's a new day, people.

1213
01:28:00,520 --> 01:28:02,199
Destiny calls.

1214
01:28:02,200 --> 01:28:05,719
The world expects only one thing from us: that we will win.

1215
01:28:05,720 --> 01:28:09,559
Rest assured the enemy will thank you for not giving 100 percent today.

1216
01:28:09,560 --> 01:28:11,188
Squad?

1217
01:28:13,960 --> 01:28:16,066
Where's J Squad?

1218
01:28:33,600 --> 01:28:37,159
Right, okay. So this Omega, it controls time.

1219
01:28:37,160 --> 01:28:39,799
Just blow the New Age bollocks back where it came from.

1220
01:28:39,800 --> 01:28:41,319
And then we go home.

1221
01:28:41,320 --> 01:28:44,159
- Right, it's guarded by an Alpha.  - Just kill it.

1222
01:28:44,160 --> 01:28:45,239
Okay?

1223
01:28:45,240 --> 01:28:46,239
No!

1224
01:28:46,240 --> 01:28:47,879
You heard what Cage said.

1225
01:28:47,880 --> 01:28:49,479
Do not kill an Alpha.

1226
01:28:49,480 --> 01:28:52,508
If we do, the Omega will reset this whole day.

1227
01:28:52,720 --> 01:28:54,519
We'll never remember we had this conversation.

1228
01:28:54,520 --> 01:28:56,599
They're gonna know we're coming.

1229
01:28:56,600 --> 01:28:59,319
What am I supposed to do if an Alpha is about to kill me?

1230
01:28:59,320 --> 01:29:01,904
You take a hit for the team.

1231
01:29:04,320 --> 01:29:06,199
When we're on the ground...

1232
01:29:06,200 --> 01:29:09,865
there's not gonna be a lot of time before they know we're there.

1233
01:29:09,920 --> 01:29:12,231
We're gonna need eyes up here.

1234
01:29:13,560 --> 01:29:15,905
I'm going in, Cage.

1235
01:29:26,960 --> 01:29:29,430
Thirty seconds till contact.

1236
01:29:43,280 --> 01:29:44,783
Cage!

1237
01:29:45,040 --> 01:29:47,465
Kimmel! No!

1238
01:29:55,480 --> 01:29:56,479
Ford!

1239
01:29:56,480 --> 01:29:57,319
Let's go!

1240
01:29:57,320 --> 01:29:58,709
Cage!

1241
01:29:58,760 --> 01:30:00,159
We gotta go.

1242
01:30:00,160 --> 01:30:01,079
Drop.

1243
01:30:01,080 --> 01:30:02,999
Cage, they know we're coming, man!

1244
01:30:03,000 --> 01:30:05,039
Drop! Drop!

1245
01:30:05,040 --> 01:30:06,907
Drop!

1246
01:30:07,880 --> 01:30:08,719
Drop.

1247
01:30:08,720 --> 01:30:10,701
You're not hooked in.

1248
01:32:28,360 --> 01:32:30,785
What took you so long?

1249
01:32:32,640 --> 01:32:34,871
Any others?

1250
01:32:38,960 --> 01:32:40,359
We're low on ammo.

1251
01:32:40,360 --> 01:32:43,359
I've got one Claymore. Ford, you're out.

1252
01:32:43,360 --> 01:32:46,279
Griff has only got half a magazine and he can hardly move.

1253
01:32:46,280 --> 01:32:48,319
I thought you could see the future.

1254
01:32:48,320 --> 01:32:50,585
I haven't lived this day.

1255
01:32:50,680 --> 01:32:52,799
I don't know what's gonna happen.

1256
01:32:52,800 --> 01:32:54,359
It doesn't matter.

1257
01:32:54,360 --> 01:32:56,639
What matters is we finish this.

1258
01:32:56,640 --> 01:32:58,746
With what?

1259
01:32:59,040 --> 01:33:01,999
I mean, Griff can't even walk. We're three men down.

1260
01:33:02,000 --> 01:33:03,639
- Come on.  - We're running out of time.

1261
01:33:03,640 --> 01:33:05,599
Collect your ammo.

1262
01:33:05,600 --> 01:33:08,199
Must be a thousand mimics between us and the pyramid.

1263
01:33:08,200 --> 01:33:10,479
What we gonna do? Walk up to the front door?

1264
01:33:10,480 --> 01:33:13,239
- If we stay here, we die.  - Yeah?

1265
01:33:13,240 --> 01:33:15,159
We'll never get through.

1266
01:33:15,160 --> 01:33:17,141
We could.

1267
01:33:18,080 --> 01:33:19,981
In that.

1268
01:33:21,400 --> 01:33:23,759
That ship will never fly.

1269
01:33:23,760 --> 01:33:25,919
Doesn't need to fly.

1270
01:33:25,920 --> 01:33:29,439
It just needs to get us across there with speed.

1271
01:33:29,440 --> 01:33:34,390
If the engines are still running, we could steer it with the power levers.

1272
01:33:34,800 --> 01:33:38,501
Skinner. Clear a path.

1273
01:33:43,240 --> 01:33:45,479
- Try it again, now.  - No, it's not reading.

1274
01:33:45,480 --> 01:33:47,188
Condition lever, low.

1275
01:33:53,280 --> 01:33:55,591
Master power, on.

1276
01:33:57,960 --> 01:33:59,861
Griff!

1277
01:34:00,080 --> 01:34:02,948
We've gotta go! Come on!

1278
01:34:04,760 --> 01:34:07,742
I'm not gonna be any good in there, mate.

1279
01:34:08,040 --> 01:34:10,430
Let me buy you some time.

1280
01:34:14,560 --> 01:34:16,222
Power's on.

1281
01:34:16,560 --> 01:34:18,399
This is gonna work.

1282
01:34:18,400 --> 01:34:20,119
Hey!

1283
01:34:20,120 --> 01:34:22,439
Hey, come on, man! We gotta go!

1284
01:34:22,440 --> 01:34:24,199
Don't wait for us!

1285
01:34:24,200 --> 01:34:25,199
Skinner!

1286
01:34:25,200 --> 01:34:27,519
Griff, come on!

1287
01:34:27,520 --> 01:34:30,679
- We're good to go. Where are they?  - Where's Skinner and Griff?

1288
01:34:30,680 --> 01:34:32,786
They're not coming.

1289
01:34:45,360 --> 01:34:48,467
Go, brother. You gotta go, man.

1290
01:34:48,720 --> 01:34:51,145
I'll see you in the next life.

1291
01:34:54,880 --> 01:34:56,986
Bollocks.

1292
01:34:58,800 --> 01:35:01,031
Move over! Move over!

1293
01:35:02,560 --> 01:35:04,199
We gotta go!

1294
01:35:04,200 --> 01:35:06,226
Yo, we gotta go now!

1295
01:35:08,960 --> 01:35:11,624
They're coming, Cage.

1296
01:35:18,120 --> 01:35:21,519
Come on, you bastards! Come on!

1297
01:35:21,520 --> 01:35:22,879
Reload.

1298
01:35:22,880 --> 01:35:25,464
Reload. Reload.

1299
01:35:37,280 --> 01:35:39,750
We got incoming!

1300
01:35:47,920 --> 01:35:49,707
Come on!

1301
01:35:57,120 --> 01:35:59,351
Cage!

1302
01:36:09,680 --> 01:36:12,070
You have to take over!

1303
01:37:03,880 --> 01:37:05,383
Rita!

1304
01:37:07,240 --> 01:37:09,059
Punch it! Punch it!

1305
01:37:46,960 --> 01:37:49,100
We've been through worse.

1306
01:38:27,440 --> 01:38:29,182
Okay.

1307
01:38:30,560 --> 01:38:32,461
It's there.

1308
01:38:32,840 --> 01:38:34,741
In the water. There.

1309
01:39:01,880 --> 01:39:03,319
That's an Alpha.

1310
01:39:03,320 --> 01:39:07,064
I'm gonna draw that thing away.

1311
01:39:07,200 --> 01:39:08,639
You kill the Omega.

1312
01:39:08,640 --> 01:39:13,359
No. You won't make it 10 feet before that thing kills you, Cage.

1313
01:39:13,360 --> 01:39:14,999
- I can do it.  - Take the grenades.

1314
01:39:15,000 --> 01:39:16,159
I can do it.

1315
01:39:16,160 --> 01:39:19,719
Listen to me. Listen to me.

1316
01:39:19,720 --> 01:39:23,226
Neither one of us is getting out of here.

1317
01:39:45,360 --> 01:39:47,591
Thank you...

1318
01:39:47,760 --> 01:39:50,503
for getting me this far.

1319
01:39:54,800 --> 01:39:57,464
You're a good man, Cage.

1320
01:39:58,480 --> 01:40:01,348
I wish I had the chance to know you better.

1321
01:43:30,880 --> 01:43:32,719
Welcome to London, major.

1322
01:43:32,720 --> 01:43:37,319
I'm Corporal Montgomery your liaison to General Brigham's press office.

1323
01:43:37,320 --> 01:43:39,585
Very good to have you.

1324
01:43:40,200 --> 01:43:43,546
Have you heard the news? Isn't it brilliant?

1325
01:43:50,920 --> 01:43:53,399
Just before sunrise this morning...

1326
01:43:53,400 --> 01:43:57,239
a large surge of energy was detected in Paris.

1327
01:43:57,240 --> 01:44:00,279
We do not know exactly what this signifies.

1328
01:44:00,280 --> 01:44:05,830
But the result appears to be a total collapse of the enemy's capacity to fight.

1329
01:44:06,200 --> 01:44:11,105
Russian and Chinese troops are now moving across Europe without resistance.

1330
01:44:12,240 --> 01:44:15,199
Tomorrow, we advance on the western front.

1331
01:44:15,200 --> 01:44:19,679
We believe we are marching to claim victory for ourselves...

1332
01:44:19,680 --> 01:44:24,599
for our loved ones, for our countrymen for the entire human race.

1333
01:44:24,600 --> 01:44:27,199
- What are you? Sound off!  - I'm a warrior!

1334
01:44:27,200 --> 01:44:28,919
- What do warriors do?  - Kill!

1335
01:44:28,920 --> 01:44:30,799
- What are you gonna do?  - Kill!

1336
01:44:30,800 --> 01:44:33,439
- You have not been in 20 battles.  - I have too.

1337
01:44:33,440 --> 01:44:35,959
You're gonna dump your load the second you hit the beach.

1338
01:44:35,960 --> 01:44:39,639
How about you two go get yourselves a nice hot cup of shut-the-hell-up!

1339
01:44:39,640 --> 01:44:40,799
Ha-ha. You funny, girl.

1340
01:44:40,800 --> 01:44:43,159
I bet you I set some kind of record tomorrow.

1341
01:44:43,160 --> 01:44:47,079
Fastest time running backwards, Ford, slipping in your own shit.

1342
01:44:47,080 --> 01:44:49,709
Knock off the grab-ass!

1343
01:44:50,160 --> 01:44:52,839
- What are you? Sound off! - I'm a warrior!

1344
01:44:52,840 --> 01:44:55,822
- What do warriors do? - Kill!

1345
01:44:57,200 --> 01:44:59,340
Attention!

1346
01:45:38,800 --> 01:45:40,439
Yes?

1347
01:45:40,440 --> 01:45:42,387
What do you want?
