[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 标题,汉仪双线体简,40,&H001C1DB6,&H0021218D,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.1,3,10,10,10,1
Style: 职员,微软雅黑,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.1,3,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.49,0:07:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\pos(270.8,179.2) }艾薩克的三星S5
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.00,0:07:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\c&H78704B&\3c&HCDC49A&\pos(157.2,239.467)}華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞:科爾比是否牽連其中?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.17,0:07:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\4c&HE0E0EE&\c&H090913&\fs20\pos(127.2,83.2)\frz4.313}在地下水和飲用水中發現污染物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.46,0:07:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(131.6,140.4)}{\4c&HE0E0EE&\c&H090913&\fs20\frz4.313}對健康造成一定的不利影響
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.52,0:07:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs12\frz18.85\org(186.8,94.533)\pos(197.2,102.533)}第7條 環境保護\N第26章 固體廢料\N第1分章 總則
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.48,0:07:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\pos(155.6,155.334)\frz13.42\org(164.4,127.601)}有證據表明 我們的員工的健康受到了不利影響
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.86,0:07:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(246.8,157.867)\frz15.46\fn鐘齊翰墨毛筆}貝克特律師
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.01,0:11:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(206.4,65.734)}點擊此處 免費獲取價值100美元\NeTunes禮品卡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.51,0:11:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(176.8,167.6)}{\fs10}問題1 你目前更喜歡哪一類音樂   搖滾  饒舌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.51,0:11:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(204.4,188.267)}{\fs10\3c&HCFCFEE&\c&H131314&}搖滾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.51,0:11:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(204.8,202.133)}{\fs10\3c&HCFCFEE&\c&H131314&}饒舌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.80,0:11:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\pos(165.6,166.4)}問題2 你更喜歡哪一流派的饒舌音樂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.80,0:11:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\pos(218.4,203.52)}硬核
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.80,0:11:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\pos(217.92,188.16)}嘻哈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.89,0:11:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs10\pos(182.4,167.68)}問題3 最喜歡Wu-Tang Clan組合中的哪一位成員
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.23,0:11:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(184.8,124.16)}惡意軟件 被攔截
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.23,0:11:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs12\pos(197.76,163.84)}avast!文件系統防護 已攔截一個威脅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.23,0:11:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs12\pos(166.08,191.36)}無需進一步操作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:01:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\an8\fad(500,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HE28609&\3a&HDC&\pos(189,3.6)}本字幕由{\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯制作，僅供學習，禁止用于任何商業盈利行為。若因私自散布傳播造成法律問題，本字幕組概不負責。更多影視請搜索并關注新浪微博{\c&H00FFFF&}@大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.00,0:22:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.00,0:22:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.90,0:43:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.90,0:43:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.90,0:43:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.90,0:43:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.90,0:43:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H2F21B9&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.90,0:44:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}{\fn微軟雅黑\fs16\b1\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&}本字幕由{\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯\N{\fs14}{\fs14}僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為\N{\fs14}{\fs14}彼以國士待我 我以國士待之\N用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人\N{\fs14}{\fs14}有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們\N{\fs14}{\fs14}{\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}請聯系QQ群：428872140
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\c&H240FA0&\b1\pos(193.08,101.2)}機器人先生 前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H25119F&\b1\pos(193.2,54.206)}大家字幕組 傾情譯制
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.67,0:01:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs80\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(197.04,48.88)}機器人先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.67,0:01:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(202.32,203.6)}第一季  第六集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.00,0:00:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(300,31.7,300,25.7,0,300)}翻譯    顧顧  子虛烏有  墳老絲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.00,0:00:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(300,25.7,300,19.7,1700,2000)}翻譯    顧顧  子虛烏有  墳老絲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.00,0:00:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(305,31.7,305,25.7,0,300)}翻譯    兔八哥  零零七  薇薇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(305,25.7,305,19.7,1700,2000)}翻譯    兔八哥  零零七  薇薇
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(297,31.7,297,25.7,0,300)}校對    Libear  寶馬蹄前大命狒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.00,0:00:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(297,25.7,297,19.7,1700,2000)}校對    Libear  寶馬蹄前大命狒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.00,0:00:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(323,31.7,323,25.7,0,300)}時間軸    嵬森  拉面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(323,25.7,323,19.7,1700,2000)}時間軸    嵬森  拉面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(347,31.7,347,25.7,0,300)}壓制    JEV
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.00,0:00:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(347,25.7,347,19.7,1700,2000)}壓制    JEV
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.00,0:00:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(280,31.7,280,25.7,0,300)}監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.00,0:00:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(280,25.7,280,19.7,1700,2000)}監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.79,0:21:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}他什么都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.34,0:21:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}我跟你說了他很危險
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.09,0:21:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}我差點就搞定她了!她腿都張開了!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.97,0:21:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}很明顯不夠開
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.48,0:21:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}這下我-我們-冒了太大的風險
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.82,0:21:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}這事躲不掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.36,0:21:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}我越界了 我需要退一步緩一緩
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.03,0:21:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}保持耐心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.66,0:21:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}你都快失去控制了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.29,0:22:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}要耐心 是的 但是不能膽怯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.92,0:22:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}實際上 她的行為可能對我們有所幫助
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.47,0:22:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}幫了我們什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.05,0:22:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}現在我們知道了她的需求
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.56,0:22:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}什么需求
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.81,0:22:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H20F0EF&}被需求的需求
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.22,0:00:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟維拉被逮捕這件事可有關聯?\N{\fs14}Did you have something to do with Vera getting busted?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.14,0:00:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰讓你把你的生意\N{\fs14}Who told you to put your business
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.40,0:00:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放到社交網絡上去的?\N{\fs14}anywhere near social media?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.21,0:00:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那上進的弟弟\N{\fs14}My aspirational little brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.11,0:00:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來有人要因此受些皮肉之苦了\N{\fs14}Someone's gonna get hurt for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.03,0:00:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉怎么了?\N{\fs14}What happened to Angela?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.00,0:00:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這個層面上 她對我們毫無用武之地\N{\fs14}She's not going to work out for us, not on this level.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.82,0:00:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當時并不用站出來幫我的\N{\fs14}You didn't have to stick up for me in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.56,0:00:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再這么做了\N{\fs14}Don't do it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.60,0:00:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪惡公司想挖你去當首席技術官 對嗎?\N{\fs14}Evil corp tapped you for CTO, yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.76,0:00:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是在毀了自己的生活\N{\fs14}You're ruining your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.55,0:00:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一起毀了你的\N{\fs14}I also ruined yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.39,0:00:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰利 科爾比參與包庇\N{\fs14}Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.20,0:00:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞\N{\fs14}The Washington Township toxic waste scandal.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.37,0:00:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏倫?\N{\fs14}Sharon?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.01,0:00:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫁給這種人 你竟然沒有開槍自殺?\N{\fs14}How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.05,0:00:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在這里\N{\fs14}I'm in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.86,0:00:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意今晚睡這里嗎?\N{\fs14}Would you mind sleeping here tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.87,0:00:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊那個女孩是我的\N{\fs14}That girl in there is mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.65,0:00:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你要是在附近的話\N{\fs14}If you're around tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.68,0:00:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就過來親自告訴我吧\N{\fs14}come over and tell me about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.16,0:00:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉?\N{\fs14}Shayla?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:00:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候 宇宙的排列組合真是奇妙無比\N{\fs14}Sometimes the universe aligns perfectly.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.87,0:00:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在 我被關起來了\N{\fs14}Here I am, locked away.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.68,0:00:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 手機能讓我找到你\N{\fs14}Still, it brings you right to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.38,0:01:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一種感覺\N{\fs14}I feel the sensation.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.02,0:01:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰斗還是逃跑\N{\fs14}Fight or flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.49,0:01:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,持續不斷地出現\N{\fs14}It's constant.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.89,0:01:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該從中選擇其一\N{\fs14}I should just pick one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.31,0:01:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 伊利艾特 奧爾德森 選擇戰斗\N{\fs14}I, Elliot Alderson, am flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.20,0:01:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是恐懼\N{\fs14}I am fear.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.52,0:01:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是焦慮 可怕 恐慌\N{\fs14}I am anxiety, terror, panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.48,0:01:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得這好不真實\N{\fs14}Doesn't feel real.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.19,0:01:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該吃點東西\N{\fs14}You should eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.29,0:01:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不餓\N{\fs14}Not hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.43,0:01:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道我點了些什么\N{\fs14}I don't know what I ordered.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.64,0:01:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.07,0:02:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喜歡墨西哥燉肉嗎?\N{\fs14}You don't like the guisado?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.13,0:02:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 它 它很好吃\N{\fs14}No, it's--it's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.37,0:02:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝\N{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.11,0:02:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么?\N{\fs14}What are you thinking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.50,0:02:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的初遇\N{\fs14}First time we met.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.44,0:02:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒也不覺得是很久之前\N{\fs14}Doesn't feel that long ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.04,0:02:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我們現在\N{\fs14}Now look at us.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.60,0:02:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰又能想到呢?\N{\fs14}Who would have thought?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.63,0:02:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我能回去并還原一切——\N{\fs14}If I could go back and undo this--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.84,0:02:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能\N{\fs14}You can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.98,0:02:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答應我了\N{\fs14}You promised me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.28,0:02:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你擺脫困境的 知道嗎?\N{\fs14}I'm gonna get you out of this, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.30,0:02:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間到了\N{\fs14}Time's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.37,0:03:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走\N{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.26,0:03:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特!\N{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.51,0:03:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下 給我坐下\N{\fs14}Sit down. Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.48,0:03:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我走\N{\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.37,0:03:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.98,0:03:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你好? -  你名字的來源\N{\fs14}- Hello? - The origin of your name.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.98,0:03:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特意為你去查了資料 老兄\N{\fs14}I looked it up for you, bruh.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.55,0:03:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把她帶去哪里了?\N{\fs14}Where are you taking her?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.64,0:03:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.04,0:03:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"勇敢與真實"\N{\fs14}"Brave and true."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.17,0:04:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道"勇敢"是由"野蠻"進化來的嗎?\N{\fs14}Did you know the origin of "Brave" Evolved from "Savage"?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.82,0:04:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你是怎樣看待這一切的\N{\fs14}I don't know what you think this is about,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.37,0:04:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你必須放她走\N{\fs14}but you need to let her go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.04,0:04:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說件有意思的事給你聽\N{\fs14}You know, funny thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.57,0:04:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字也有著跟你差不多的意思\N{\fs14}My name means something similar.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.57,0:04:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢的旅人\N{\fs14}Brave traveler.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.65,0:04:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒險家\N{\fs14}Adventurer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.97,0:04:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野蠻的旅人成為了勇敢的旅行者\N{\fs14}Savage traveler becomes brave traveler.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.70,0:04:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們究竟是野蠻呢 還是勇敢呢?\N{\fs14}Are we savages, or are we brave?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.28,0:04:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道 兄弟\N{\fs14}Don't know, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.59,0:04:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽我說 哥們\N{\fs14}Listen to me, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.38,0:04:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我發現是你做了這一切時 我沒有生氣\N{\fs14}When I found out you did this, I didn't get angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.15,0:04:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是給我留下了深刻印象\N{\fs14}I got impressed.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.92,0:04:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的力量\N{\fs14}Your power.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.64,0:04:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要它 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}I want it, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.20,0:04:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太想要它了 想得我吊都硬了\N{\fs14}And I want it so bad it makes my dick hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.58,0:04:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天就要擁有它\N{\fs14}And I want it today.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你認為我能做什么\N{\fs14}I don't know what you think I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.40,0:04:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不能用我的黑客技能直接帶你出獄\N{\fs14}I can't just hack you out of prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.14,0:04:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是所有的監獄都有聯網 即便你的監獄有網絡\N{\fs14}Not all prisons are networked, and even if yours is,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.16,0:04:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到安全漏洞也要花上好幾周\N{\fs14}it would take weeks to find security holes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.89,0:04:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須是今夜\N{\fs14}Has to be tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.59,0:04:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經被狙擊槍的十字射線瞄準了心臟\N{\fs14}I got crosshairs on my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.63,0:04:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出不去\N{\fs14}I don't make it out,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.91,0:04:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就會死 但我的大限還沒到呢\N{\fs14}I'm dead, and that ain't meant to be just yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.44,0:05:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做你的 兄弟\N{\fs14}You do your thing, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.24,0:05:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是在強求我去做不可能完成的事\N{\fs14}You're asking the impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們今晚相見的時候 伊利艾特 我會擁抱你的\N{\fs14}When we cross paths tonight, Elliot, I'ma hug you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.39,0:05:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽我說 哥們\N{\fs14}Please listen, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.43,0:05:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉——一切都是我的錯\N{\fs14}Shayla--this is on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.24,0:05:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎?\N{\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.23,0:05:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須放她走\N{\fs14}You got to let her go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.12,0:05:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 就這事?\N{\fs14}Oh, that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.40,0:05:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很好 兄弟\N{\fs14}She cool, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.01,0:05:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 她好得很\N{\fs14}Trust me, she cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.91,0:05:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚她也會去的\N{\fs14}She'll be there tonight too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.02,0:05:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這會是個大團圓結局的\N{\fs14}It'll be one big happy happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.43,0:05:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Hey, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.55,0:05:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛你 兄弟\N{\fs14}I love you, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.79,0:05:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉在哪里?\N{\fs14}Where's Shayla?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.97,0:05:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 最后警告你一次\N{\fs14}Man, I'm not gonna tell you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.20,0:05:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再問這么多問題了\N{\fs14}Stop asking so many questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.93,0:05:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟上\N{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.99,0:06:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,維拉也許是瘋了沒錯\N{\fs14}Vera may be out of his mind,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.15,0:06:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 黑進監獄網絡還是有可能的\N{\fs14}but yes, it is possible to hack into a prison's network.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.81,0:06:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多數監獄使用常規的工業控制系統\N{\fs14}Most of them use regular industrial control systems.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.23,0:06:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道維拉看中這小子哪點了\N{\fs14}I'm a blind man to what Vera sees in this dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.71,0:06:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是 啥天才黑客 有我的多明尼加吊吊么\N{\fs14}Amen. Techie computer hacker genius, my thick Dominican dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.99,0:06:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是能掌控住工業控制系統\N{\fs14}When you have control of that,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.00,0:06:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上就掌控了監獄的各扇門\N{\fs14}you basically have control of the cell doors.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.15,0:06:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這些白癡不知道的是\N{\fs14}But what these morons don't know is,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.93,0:06:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不事先做研究 根本不可能掌控住\N{\fs14}it's almost impossible without any research.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.52,0:06:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕緊麻利地干活\N{\fs14}Time to shine your cojones and get to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.84,0:06:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺們就一條規矩:\N{\fs14}Our only rule:
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照我們說的去做\N{\fs14}do what we say.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.43,0:06:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是違反了這條規矩 俺們就讓你的妞去見閻王爺\N{\fs14}You violate that dictate, we kill your sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 艾薩克\N{\fs14}Yo, Isaac.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.45,0:06:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的龜-距怎么樣?\N{\fs14}How my dic-tate?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.53,0:06:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴 傻吊\N{\fs14}Shut up, bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.16,0:06:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,規矩\N{\fs14}Dictate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.36,0:07:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,維拉的兄弟 艾薩克\N{\fs14}Vera's bro, Isaac.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.53,0:07:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關于他 總有點什么讓我心煩\N{\fs14}Something about him bugs me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.77,0:07:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我喜歡怎樣應對這種情況嗎?\N{\fs14}and you know what I like to do when that happens?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.48,0:07:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 請幫我接貝克特先生\N{\fs14}Hi, I'm trying to reach Mr. Beckett.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.62,0:07:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉蒂默先生什么時候有空呢?\N{\fs14}When would Mr. Lattimer be available?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.78,0:07:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天可以過來的\N{\fs14}I can come in today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.16,0:07:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經告訴過你 是關于什么事情的了\N{\fs14}I already told you what it's in reference to.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.59,0:08:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是找納亞爾夫人\N{\fs14}I'm trying again for Mrs. Nayar.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.67,0:08:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關于華盛頓鎮丑聞的事情\N{\fs14}Regarding the Washington Township Scandal.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.29,0:08:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能發現了一些信息\N{\fs14}I may have found some information.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.16,0:08:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別又讓我等候接聽了\N{\fs14}Please don't put me on hold again.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.26,0:08:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周一愉快 安吉拉\N{\fs14}Happy Monday, Angela.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.71,0:08:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是愉快\N{\fs14}How fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.06,0:08:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝了\N{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.52,0:09:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是艾蜜莉 莫斯的女兒\N{\fs14}I'm Emily Moss's daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.32,0:09:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫安吉拉 莫斯 我打了\N{\fs14}Angela Moss. I called--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.32,0:09:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六次\N{\fs14}Six times.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.19,0:09:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是來討論華盛頓鎮一案的\N{\fs14}I'm here to discuss the Washington Township case.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.88,0:09:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽著呢\N{\fs14}I'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.27,0:09:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您當時代表受害人家屬\N{\fs14}You represented the victim's families.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.29,0:09:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,26個家庭 包括我們一家\N{\fs14}26 families, mine included.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.78,0:09:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想 隨著近期數據轉儲引發的新聞\N{\fs14}I thought with the latest news in the data dumps--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.09,0:09:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰利 科爾比的丑聞曝光\N{\fs14}the Terry Colby scandal,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.74,0:09:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在掩蓋化學廢料泄露一事\N{\fs14}his covering up the chemical waste spill.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.68,0:09:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尚未證實\N{\fs14}Alleged.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.46,0:09:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 但還有文件資料\N{\fs14}Well, and documents.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.50,0:09:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微不足道\N{\fs14}Superficial.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.21,0:09:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若是我們拿這個更加有力 強硬的案例\N{\fs14}But if we bring this stronger, more concrete case--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.76,0:09:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就會知道我從這些數據里找到了證據\N{\fs14}You'll see that I have the evidence from the data dumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的是深入研究\N{\fs14}Along with further research.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.32,0:09:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還貼紙了\N{\fs14}Stickies.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.66,0:10:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 你還做了劃了重點啊\N{\fs14}Oh, and you've highlighted and underlined.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.72,0:10:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很認真嘛\N{\fs14}This is serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.22,0:10:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你想把網絡流言呈上聯邦法院\N{\fs14}So, you want to take internet gossip to federal court
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.38,0:10:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和人類文明史上最強大的綜合企業\N{\fs14}and throw it at the strongest conglomerate
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.70,0:10:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對簿公堂?\N{\fs14}in the history of civilization?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.39,0:10:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西裝革履的男人\N{\fs14}Guy in the suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.07,0:10:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩次因性侵犯被判有罪\N{\fs14}Twice convicted of sexual assault,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.40,0:10:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周末又被控告\N{\fs14}charged again this past weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.35,0:10:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強奸了他有孕在身的女朋友\N{\fs14}Raped his pregnant girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.90,0:10:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用xBox把她的頭砸了個洞\N{\fs14}Bashed her head in with an xbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.06,0:10:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理由是她在打"光暈"(射擊游戲)的時候作弊了\N{\fs14}Claims she cheated during Halo.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.72,0:10:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而我為他辯護 勝訴的幾率還要比你的高一些\N{\fs14}Yet I have a better chance of defending him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.46,0:10:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你回我電話了\N{\fs14}You called back.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.23,0:11:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給本案相關的所有律師都打了電話\N{\fs14}I called every lawyer from this case,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.34,0:11:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你給我回了電話\N{\fs14}and you're the only one that called me back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.73,0:12:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 糟了 糟了\N{\fs14}Shit. Shit, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.39,0:12:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遠程主機斷開連接\N{\fs14}Connection closed by remote host.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.68,0:12:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但魚兒已經上鉤了 我已經進入過系統\N{\fs14}But we had a fish. I was in.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.40,0:12:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,程序跑了一半就停下了 是因為代碼寫錯了嗎?\N{\fs14}The exploit started to run, and then--was it the code?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.04,0:12:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子 它要干嘛?\N{\fs14}Brah, what's the deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.09,0:12:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得帶她出去溜達一下\N{\fs14}I got to take her for a walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.75,0:12:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么?\N{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.50,0:12:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不溜她 她就會尿在地板上\N{\fs14}'Cause she'll piss on the floor if I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.93,0:12:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的地板他媽的與我何干?\N{\fs14}You think I give a shit about your goddamn floor?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.82,0:12:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逗你玩呢 小子\N{\fs14}I'm just playing, brah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.53,0:12:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去溜她吧\N{\fs14}Yeah, you can take her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.13,0:12:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽見我說了什么嗎?\N{\fs14}You hear what I said?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.55,0:12:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你可以帶她出去\N{\fs14}I said you can take her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.05,0:13:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧\N{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.64,0:13:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煙滅了\N{\fs14}It's out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.38,0:13:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了\N{\fs14}Okay, got you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.01,0:13:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她喜歡我送的小玩具嗎?\N{\fs14}Did she like my little toy?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.11,0:13:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個釣魚程序是你一個人寫的?\N{\fs14}Did you write that exploit yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.56,0:13:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一個小時的時間\N{\fs14}I had an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.94,0:13:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你的代碼都是東拼西湊出來的?\N{\fs14}So what, you just pulled code from rapid nine or some shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么也開始亂來了?\N{\fs14}Since when did you become a script kiddie?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.23,0:13:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再說一遍 我只有一個小時\N{\fs14}I repeat, I had an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.13,0:13:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是被反惡意程序軟件滅了\N{\fs14}Malware detection must have caught it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.15,0:13:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我害慘了\N{\fs14}You fucked me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.42,0:14:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 這事不賴我 成嗎?\N{\fs14}Hey, don't put this on me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.86,0:14:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這本來就是個爛活兒\N{\fs14}This is a shit show
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.24,0:14:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你都沒給夠我時間來好好完成\N{\fs14}and you gave me no time to do it right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.40,0:14:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是給我正確的白皮書和足夠的時間\N{\fs14}I can run circles around an ics given the proper whitepapers and time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.22,0:14:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫想去哪兒呢?\N{\fs14}Where the hell are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.99,0:14:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全可以跟那兩個混球說\N{\fs14}I have no problem telling these two douchetools
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.17,0:14:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我們找到更好的解決方案前\N{\fs14}they're gonna have to sit on their pricks
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.23,0:14:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們還是乖乖坐等吧\N{\fs14}till we can find a better solution.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.00,0:14:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不明白 這些人是\N{\fs14}You don't understand. These guys are--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.81,0:14:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋? 沒錯 我要告訴他們實情\N{\fs14}Assholes? Yeah, I'm gonna tell them what's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.92,0:14:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實情就是這個 小妞\N{\fs14}That's what's up, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.97,0:14:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我們走吧\N{\fs14}Now, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以那些人都沒給你回電話 拉蒂默也沒有?\N{\fs14}So none of those guys called you back, not even lattimer?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.01,0:14:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,膽小鬼\N{\fs14}Pussies.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.10,0:14:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜他們都不高興去看那些數據轉儲\N{\fs14}I bet they didn't even bother to read the data dumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.59,0:14:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你看了\N{\fs14}But you read them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.16,0:14:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎 在我們的案子被駁回后\N{\fs14}You know it took me eight years
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.13,0:14:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我花了八年時間來重建我的事業?\N{\fs14}to rebuild my career after our case was dismissed?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.72,0:15:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我認為這公司就是邪惡的化身\N{\fs14}So, as much as I think this company is evil incarnate--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.57,0:15:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 他們肯定是\N{\fs14}and trust me, they are--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.64,0:15:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這么做不值得\N{\fs14}you know, it's not worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.50,0:15:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們到底要怎樣\N{\fs14}What would it take,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.35,0:15:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假設的話...\N{\fs14}hypothetically...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.05,0:15:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要些什么證據?\N{\fs14}what do we need to prove our case?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.34,0:15:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假設的話 我們需要一個可靠的證人\N{\fs14}Hypothetically, a reliable eye witness.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.04,0:15:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 如果你能奇跡般地找到一個人\N{\fs14}You know, if you miraculously find someone
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.92,0:15:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個愿意作證的內部人員\N{\fs14}on the inside to flip.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.76,0:15:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個當時在決定制造關于\N{\fs14}Someone who was there
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.56,0:15:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化學廢棄物的假消息的時候 在現場的人\N{\fs14}when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.80,0:15:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說\N{\fs14}So,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.03,0:15:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你和他們其中的哪個人渣是社交網絡上的小伙伴\N{\fs14}unless you're facebook friends with one of those assholes,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.47,0:15:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個假設也就只能假設假設\N{\fs14}this hypothetical is just that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.32,0:15:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還是往前看吧\N{\fs14}Let's move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.32,0:15:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最近在哪上班?\N{\fs14}Where are you working these days?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.00,0:15:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有男朋友嗎?\N{\fs14}You have a boyfriend?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.64,0:15:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸還好嗎?\N{\fs14}How's your dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.53,0:15:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我工作的公司不尊重我\N{\fs14}I work for a company that doesn't respect me,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.05,0:15:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我男朋友最近出軌了\N{\fs14}my boyfriend recently cheated on me,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.76,0:16:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸欠了一屁股債\N{\fs14}and my father is drowning in debt.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.13,0:16:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我們下次見 - 好的\N{\fs14}- I'll see you next time. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.32,0:16:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熒光燈真讓人難受 是吧?\N{\fs14}Fluorescent lights are hell, no?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.69,0:16:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日程表臨時改了嗎?\N{\fs14}Was there a change in schedule?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.44,0:16:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為我下一個要見的是斯潘塞\N{\fs14}I thought I had Spencer next.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.47,0:16:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些面試 簡直就是浪費時間\N{\fs14}These interviews, they're just a waste of your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.11,0:16:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說 你對監管和IP問題的情況了若指掌\N{\fs14}I mean, you know our regulatory and IP issues inside out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.30,0:16:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我們今天就翹了吧\N{\fs14}I was thinking we play hooky the rest of the day,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.24,0:16:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去玩玩高爾夫\N{\fs14}hit the back nine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.00,0:16:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是支江詩丹頓表嗎?\N{\fs14}Is that a vacheron?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.54,0:16:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是百達翡麗\N{\fs14}Patek Philippe tourbillon.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.03,0:16:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一個王子送給我的 他是...\N{\fs14}A gift from the prince of, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.53,0:16:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰有所謂嗎?\N{\fs14}Oh, does it even matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.37,0:17:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會取消剩下的面試的\N{\fs14}But I'm not blowing off my remaining interviews.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.83,0:17:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著\N{\fs14}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.77,0:17:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你以為你當定CTO了\N{\fs14}I know you think you were a shoo-in for CTO,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.86,0:17:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你現在不爽了\N{\fs14}And you're pissed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.71,0:17:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說不定甚至希望我摔下地鐵軌道\N{\fs14}Probably wishing I'd fall into the subway tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.89,0:17:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以廢話少說\N{\fs14}So how about you cut the bullshit?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.50,0:17:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你是太多疑了吧 不過\N{\fs14}I'm afraid your paranoia has gotten the best of you, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.81,0:17:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡管如此 失陪了\N{\fs14}nevertheless, please excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.67,0:17:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不打擾你回顧你的筆記了\N{\fs14}I'll leave you to review your notes
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.20,0:17:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待會兒斯潘塞就來了\N{\fs14}before Spencer arrives.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.84,0:17:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 謝謝你邀請我參加晚宴\N{\fs14}Oh, and thank you for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.69,0:17:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我度過了一個美好的夜晚\N{\fs14}The entire evening was enchanting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.98,0:17:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美食 美酒 美麗的夏倫\N{\fs14}The food, the wine, the lovely Sharon.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.10,0:17:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻煩你代問她好\N{\fs14}Please tell her I say hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.67,0:17:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看得爽嗎?\N{\fs14}Did you enjoy the view?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.13,0:18:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 你以為她不會跟我說嗎\N{\fs14}What, do you think she wouldn't tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.96,0:18:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不確定你到底想表達什么...\N{\fs14}I'm not sure what you're trying...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.77,0:18:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是也想看我尿?\N{\fs14}You want to watch me piss too?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.65,0:18:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可喝了好幾杯水了\N{\fs14}I've had several glasses of water.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.40,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯考特 這中間有誤會--\N{\fs14}Scott, a misunderstand--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.48,0:18:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了你我很樂意把我的老二掏出來\N{\fs14}Happy to pull my dick out for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.64,0:18:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你喜歡\N{\fs14}if that's your thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.99,0:18:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看諾斯一家小便\N{\fs14}watching the Knowles family urinate.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.65,0:18:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至可以讓我兄弟從邁阿密飛過來\N{\fs14}Hell, I could fly my brother in from Miami.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.17,0:18:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他膀胱就像小屁孩兒一樣 尿個不停\N{\fs14}He has the bladder of a small child.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.61,0:18:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看他尿一泡是不是直接就射了?\N{\fs14}You'd probably bust a nut watching him take a leak.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.99,0:18:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道她跟你說了啥 我是你的話\N{\fs14}I'm not sure what she told you, but if I were you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.16,0:18:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓她好好地\N{\fs14}I would tell her to find more appropriate ways
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.29,0:18:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制一下她的想象力\N{\fs14}of managing her imagination.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.57,0:18:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提瑞爾\N{\fs14}Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.39,0:18:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你能接受殘酷的現實\N{\fs14}I want you to accept a hard truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.01,0:18:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在這里 就現在 在我面前\N{\fs14}right here, right now, in front of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.69,0:18:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當不成CTO\N{\fs14}You are not going to be CTO.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.41,0:18:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想在你臉上看到這樣的表情\N{\fs14}I want to see that look wash over your face.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.56,0:18:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有這樣我才確定你會停止這些\N{\fs14}It's the only way I know you'll stop playing these
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.56,0:18:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無比可笑的游戲\N{\fs14}silly, silly games.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.72,0:19:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我非常明白你是CTO 斯考特\N{\fs14}Oh, I am fully aware you're CTO, Scott.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.89,0:19:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道還能為你做些什么了\N{\fs14}I'm not sure what more I can offer you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.04,0:19:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fs14}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.62,0:19:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來\N{\fs14}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.38,0:19:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很愧疚\N{\fs14}I feel bad,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.19,0:19:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟 你是要當爸爸的人了\N{\fs14}after all, you got a child on the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.56,0:19:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你急需幫助\N{\fs14}You need all the help you can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.88,0:19:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上\N{\fs14}In fact,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.32,0:19:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個可能會幫你把剩下的債都抵了吧\N{\fs14}this would probably pay off the rest of your mortgage.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.07,0:19:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是還住在切爾西區那個小巧玲瓏的兩室一廳嗎?\N{\fs14}Aren't you still in that neat little two-bedroom in Chelsea?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.31,0:19:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看\N{\fs14}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.60,0:19:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的就是這個表情\N{\fs14}That's the look I was looking for.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.78,0:19:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我頭都要想爆了 然而并沒有什么卵用\N{\fs14}I keep brute-force thinking, but it's not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.72,0:19:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要幫助\N{\fs14}I need help.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.70,0:20:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 你在嗎?\N{\fs14}Elliot, you in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.23,0:20:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操蛋\N{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.33,0:20:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她來干嘛?\N{\fs14}Why is she here?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.39,0:20:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特!\N{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.20,0:20:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我進來\N{\fs14}Let me in.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.20,0:20:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 你到底在不在?\N{\fs14}Elliot, you in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.22,0:20:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個金發小美女\N{\fs14}Little blonde bitty.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.78,0:20:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 幫我開門\N{\fs14}Elliot, hit the buzzer.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.66,0:20:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在\N{\fs14}I know you're in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.99,0:20:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去\N{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.27,0:20:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓她閉嘴 把她給我趕走\N{\fs14}Shut her up, and get her the hell out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.38,0:20:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 開門 現在\N{\fs14}Elliot. Buzzer. Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.78,0:20:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳怎么辦?\N{\fs14}What about Darlene?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.27,0:20:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她留在這里 我們會盯著你的\N{\fs14}She stays with us. And we'll be watching you,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.40,0:20:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以別他媽給老子耍花樣 你個臭傻逼\N{\fs14}so don't bother trying any dumb shit, you dumb shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.09,0:21:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知不知道你為什么生氣?\N{\fs14}Do you understand why you're angry?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.64,0:21:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你知道我是對的\N{\fs14}'Cause you know I'm right.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.77,0:22:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上從吉迪恩那走后我到處找你\N{\fs14}I tried looking for you after Gideon's the other night.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.29,0:22:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跑哪去了?\N{\fs14}Where were you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.10,0:22:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有些事情要想清楚\N{\fs14}I had to think about things, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.55,0:22:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一直以來都清楚邪惡公司做了些什么\N{\fs14}We always knew what Evil Corp did.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.03,0:22:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我們沒有證據\N{\fs14}We didn't have the proof,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.69,0:22:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們知道\N{\fs14}but we knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.96,0:22:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一直是對的\N{\fs14}We were right about it all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.62,0:22:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那則新聞的內容對我們來說沒什么新鮮的\N{\fs14}In fact, that news report wasn't a confirmation.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.10,0:23:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻讓我怒火中燒\N{\fs14}It was a reminder of how angry I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.76,0:23:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記得負責那個案子的律師嗎 納亞爾？\N{\fs14}You remember Nayar, the lawyer on the case?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.28,0:23:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找過她了 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}I went to her, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.47,0:23:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 安吉拉 現在不是\N{\fs14}Listen, Angela, now's not--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.58,0:23:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一個討回公道的辦法\N{\fs14}I have an idea that will change the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.83,0:23:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道可能貌似行不通\N{\fs14}I know it sounds really stupid,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.47,0:23:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道怎么去做\N{\fs14}but I know how to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.58,0:23:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我覺得會有用\N{\fs14}I think it could actually work.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.61,0:23:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具體我現在不能告訴你 因為\N{\fs14}I can't tell you what it is, because--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.14,0:23:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪惡公司 安吉拉 維拉\N{\fs14}Evil Corp, Angela, Vera,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.73,0:23:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的兄弟 戴琳 夏拉\N{\fs14}his brother, Darlene, Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.06,0:23:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的事都撞一起了\N{\fs14}This is too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.86,0:23:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就說她想聽的給她聽吧\N{\fs14}I should just tell her what she wants to hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.78,0:23:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉\N{\fs14}Angela,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.02,0:23:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信你自己\N{\fs14}trust yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.78,0:23:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的判斷是正確的\N{\fs14}You'll do what's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.13,0:23:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你這句話就夠了\N{\fs14}That's all I needed.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.30,0:24:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便問下 夏拉好嗎？\N{\fs14}How's Shayla, by the way?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.35,0:24:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她...\N{\fs14}She's...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.85,0:24:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的\N{\fs14}you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.34,0:24:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我向她問聲好\N{\fs14}Tell her I say hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.81,0:24:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在沒時間\N{\fs14}You have no time to pull off
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.92,0:24:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來管你正關的這檔子事\N{\fs14}whatever it is you think you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.58,0:24:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這里干嘛？ 你怎么知道這事的？\N{\fs14}What are you doing here? How did you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.14,0:24:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳聯系的我 這些家伙可不是鬧著玩的\N{\fs14}Darlene. These guys aren't playing around.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.34,0:24:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會殺了你 放聰明點 跟我走吧\N{\fs14}They will fucking kill you. Now wise up, and let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.86,0:24:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不能走 戴琳還在上面\N{\fs14}Darlene's in there. We can't leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.24,0:24:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好 我們叫條子來\N{\fs14}Okay, then we call the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.48,0:24:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有其他的選擇\N{\fs14}There's no other choice here.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.55,0:24:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能這么辦\N{\fs14}It's the only way out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.37,0:24:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能報警\N{\fs14}I can't call the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.54,0:24:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會殺了夏拉的\N{\fs14}Shayla will die.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.45,0:24:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶 拜托\N{\fs14}Oh, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.64,0:24:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很清楚自己的處境\N{\fs14}She knew exactly what she was getting herself into.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.46,0:24:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指望幫這種人干活還能長命百歲？\N{\fs14}You think his employees have a long life expectancy?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.84,0:24:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和這瘋子沾上關系的那一刻 就半只腳進棺材了\N{\fs14}She was dead the minute she started working with that maniac.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.68,0:24:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別勸我了 我已經決定了\N{\fs14}Forget it. It's not happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.23,0:24:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是一個零和游戲\N{\fs14}This is a zero-sum game.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.13,0:24:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想想所有可能的結果\N{\fs14}Calculate all the outcomes.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.10,0:25:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你搞砸了他荒唐的要求 他會殺了你和夏拉\N{\fs14}If you don't pull off this ridiculous miracle--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.03,0:25:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你很有可能會搞砸 然后你就掛了 夏拉也是\N{\fs14}and odds are, you won't-- you die, and so does Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.42,0:25:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我們都知道了\N{\fs14}That much we know.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.78,0:25:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假設另一種可能性\N{\fs14}But assume for a second
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.66,0:25:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成功把維拉救出監獄\N{\fs14}that you do pull this off, bust Vera out of prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.14,0:25:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰又能保證他不會照樣殺了你和夏拉呢？\N{\fs14}Who's to say he doesn't kill you, Shayla, Darlene?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.82,0:25:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留著你們倆的小命對他半點好處沒有\N{\fs14}It would be in his own best interest to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.25,0:25:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管哪種情況 你都得死\N{\fs14}Either way, you all end up dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.23,0:25:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了你 維拉才會放心\N{\fs14}It's the only way Vera wins.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.34,0:25:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零和游戲  伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Zero-sum, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.03,0:25:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你輸了是輸 贏了還是輸\N{\fs14}You're playing a game you already lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.54,0:25:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是對的\N{\fs14}You know I'm right.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.51,0:25:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定有辦法的\N{\fs14}There's got to be a way.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.12,0:25:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能想出來\N{\fs14}I can think of a way.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.01,0:25:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂的 小伙計\N{\fs14}I get it, kiddo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.74,0:25:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想幫助別人  守護他們\N{\fs14}You want to help people. Watch over 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.20,0:25:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你能為夏拉做的\N{\fs14}The best thing you can do for Shayla--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.18,0:25:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有放手\N{\fs14}allow her to become a memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.98,0:25:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.11,0:25:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不自欺欺人是真正的勇敢\N{\fs14}True courage is about being honest with yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.55,0:25:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是面對艱難抉擇的時候\N{\fs14}Especially when it's difficult.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.57,0:25:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和夏拉都能全身而退是不可能的\N{\fs14}There is no plan where both you and Shayla survive.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.35,0:25:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能想出辦法的\N{\fs14}I can think of a way.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.38,0:26:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們離創造一個新世界已經很近了 你死了就一切泡湯了\N{\fs14}This new world that we are so close to creating will never be.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.67,0:26:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個新世界將代表你的成功\N{\fs14}And that new world, that is success.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.24,0:26:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,F社會就是你的成功\N{\fs14}Fsociety is success.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.88,0:26:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象你在鐵山取得的成功\N{\fs14}Look at what you accomplished at Steel Mountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.74,0:26:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種爛尾算什么成功\N{\fs14}That got us nowhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.78,0:26:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你滲透成功\N{\fs14}You took them down.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.23,0:26:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏得漂亮\N{\fs14}You won that battle.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.39,0:26:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你現在這樣 只能算是失敗\N{\fs14}This--this is failure.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.85,0:26:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又變回以前的你了\N{\fs14}This is the old Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.99,0:26:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個靠嗎啡和毒品來緩解內心無力感的伊利艾特\N{\fs14}The one who turns to morphine, to drugs when he feels weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.53,0:26:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個懦夫 因為事實就在眼前\N{\fs14}A coward who can't face the truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.77,0:26:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你卻連看一眼的勇氣都沒有\N{\fs14}even though it's staring him right in the face.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.69,0:26:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種感覺又來了\N{\fs14}There's that sensation again.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.74,0:26:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃避或是抗爭\N{\fs14}Fight or flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.47,0:26:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我在內 三條命有危險\N{\fs14}Three lives at stake, including my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.65,0:26:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我   伊利艾特·奧爾德森是\N{\fs14}I, Elliot Alderson, am...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.48,0:26:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？\N{\fs14}what?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.58,0:26:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湯姆拍迪 粉紅弗洛伊德 范海倫？\N{\fs14}Tom Petty, Pink Floyd, Van Halen?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.13,0:26:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這人怎么回事\N{\fs14}What's up, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.46,0:26:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不聽德雷克 不聽皮普保羅? 那不就是什么都沒聽過嗎?\N{\fs14}You ain't got no Drake, no Pitbull, no nothing?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.96,0:26:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 怎么了？干什么\N{\fs14}Like, what's up? What the--?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.76,0:26:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雨人 出什么事了？\N{\fs14}What's up, rain man?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.30,0:27:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我準備去把維拉救出來\N{\fs14}I'm ready to bust Vera out.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.69,0:27:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有辦法黑進監獄的網絡\N{\fs14}I can get into the network.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.41,0:27:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要親自去一趟監獄\N{\fs14}We need to go to the jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.04,0:27:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就去\N{\fs14}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.70,0:27:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她留在這兒\N{\fs14}She stays here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.27,0:27:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我不會離開你的\N{\fs14}No, I'm not leaving you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.35,0:27:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別擔心\N{\fs14}Don't worry,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.64,0:27:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人會聽他的\N{\fs14}He's in no position to be giving out orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.72,0:27:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走 小妞\N{\fs14}Let's go, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.46,0:27:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有過那種急中生智的經歷嗎？\N{\fs14}Remember when the panic would set in and we had a solution?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.09,0:27:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說實話 我懷念那種感覺\N{\fs14}To be honest, I miss that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.25,0:27:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候麻木一點 生活反而簡單\N{\fs14}Life is so much easier when you're numb.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.27,0:27:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來怎么做 小屁精？\N{\fs14}What's the plan, bitch boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.60,0:27:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉被抓 戴琳又被抓\N{\fs14}First Shayla, now Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.66,0:27:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 什么鬼?\N{\fs14}Yo, what the fuck?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.72,0:27:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 你要干什么？\N{\fs14}Elliot, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.23,0:27:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像一個被過高的電壓弄爆的硬盤\N{\fs14}Like a hard drive blasted by excessive voltage,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.72,0:27:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我內心煩操不堪\N{\fs14}my mind is frayed.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.88,0:27:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾近崩潰\N{\fs14}Close to fried.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.81,0:27:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能感受到數據在我的大腦中運行\N{\fs14}I can feel the static running through my brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.70,0:27:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血清素受體超時工作\N{\fs14}Serotonin receptors working overtime.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.17,0:27:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要更多時間\N{\fs14}I need more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.96,0:28:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚 今晚 今晚\N{\fs14}Tonight, tonight, tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.54,0:28:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在需要更多時間\N{\fs14}More time right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.88,0:28:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們說話的當口我就在弄這事\N{\fs14}I'm working on our project as we speak,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.80,0:28:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你最好保持給我的對話\N{\fs14}so it's in your best interest to keep talking with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.29,0:28:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在安保的桌子那邊\N{\fs14}At the security desk,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.21,0:28:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手機在運行一個\N{\fs14}my cell phone is running
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.51,0:28:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們無法察覺的活動信號嗅探器\N{\fs14}an undetectable activated signal sniffer
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.40,0:28:17.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠定位這里所有無線信\N{\fs14}that will locate any kind of wireless signal in sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.06,0:28:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我離開這棟大樓的時候\N{\fs14}By the time I leave this building,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.32,0:28:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的網絡就是我的了\N{\fs14}I'll own its network.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.35,0:28:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊\N{\fs14}Good on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.42,0:28:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很勇敢 但夠蠢\N{\fs14}Brave, but stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.75,0:28:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你露了臉 然后今晚我逃走了\N{\fs14}You showed your face, and then I skip out tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.87,0:28:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他們會懷疑到誰頭上吧?\N{\fs14}Who do you think they're gonna finger?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.91,0:28:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會打開所有牢門\N{\fs14}I'm opening every cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.92,0:28:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣 他們就不會找上你和我了\N{\fs14}That way, they can't trace it back to you or me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.58,0:28:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 兄弟\N{\fs14}Yeah, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.37,0:28:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就說了\N{\fs14}That's what I'm talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.80,0:28:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你說過 對吧?\N{\fs14}I told you, didn't I?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.62,0:28:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇宙已經給我們哥倆計劃好了 要我們做點大事\N{\fs14}The universe got big plans for us, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.11,0:28:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我坐下來\N{\fs14}Sit back down.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.77,0:29:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看等你出去 你要換個地方做你的生意\N{\fs14}When you get out, I realize you're gonna have to split.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.29,0:29:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不能再在三州地區活動\N{\fs14}You won't be able to stay in the tri-state area.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.75,0:29:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那也很好啊\N{\fs14}Oh, I love this.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.20,0:29:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢\N{\fs14}Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.45,0:29:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論你去哪兒\N{\fs14}Wherever you go,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.84,0:29:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都要找到賺錢的營生\N{\fs14}you're gonna need funding to keep surviving.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.87,0:29:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這意味著你的所有運作\N{\fs14}Which means your whole operation
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.25,0:29:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是要能獲利\N{\fs14}still needs to be making you money.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.33,0:29:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直說吧 伊利亞特 你想說什么\N{\fs14}Come on, Elliot. Give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.47,0:29:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我黑了艾薩克的手機\N{\fs14}I hacked Isaac's phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.97,0:29:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里面什么都有\N{\fs14}He had everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.59,0:29:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的團隊 貨物 所有業務\N{\fs14}Your crew, shipments, the entire operation.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.35,0:29:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都拿到了 我現在擁有你的真個世界\N{\fs14}I took it all. I own your whole world.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.77,0:29:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你一句話\N{\fs14}I need your word.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.28,0:29:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等這事兒搞定 夏拉和我可以全身而退\N{\fs14}When this goes down, Shayla and I go free.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.49,0:29:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永遠都不會再找我們\N{\fs14}You leave us alone. Forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.64,0:29:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有任何人企圖傷害我們\N{\fs14}If anyone tries to hurt us,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.04,0:29:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我看到你們有人跟蹤我 我也會把所有信息透露出去\N{\fs14}if I even see one of your guys following me, I leak everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.84,0:29:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說這些話知道--\N{\fs14}You're saying this knowing--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.76,0:30:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能隨時會來殺我 我知道\N{\fs14}You can kill me anytime, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.37,0:30:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我把信息透露設成了每天自動發送\N{\fs14}That's why I coded the leak to auto-send every 24 hours
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.01,0:30:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非我本人不斷中止它\N{\fs14}unless I continuously disable it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.04,0:30:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我誰也沒有權限\N{\fs14}No one else has access.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.00,0:30:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我或者夏拉發生什么意外\N{\fs14}If anything happens to me or Shayla,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.34,0:30:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的錢就全沒了喲\N{\fs14}your money gets deleted.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.78,0:30:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間到 維拉 走了\N{\fs14}Time's up, Vera, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.87,0:30:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記住\N{\fs14}Remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.50,0:30:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會擁抱你的\N{\fs14}I'ma hug you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.05,0:30:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么事?\N{\fs14}So what's your deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.90,0:31:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是來見泰利 科爾比的\N{\fs14}I'm hear to see Terry Colby.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.48,0:31:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰啊 又是個該死的記者?\N{\fs14}Who is that, another damn reporter?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.58,0:31:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不發表任何評論 明白嗎?\N{\fs14}No comment. Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.15,0:31:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認識你嗎?\N{\fs14}Do I know you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.43,0:31:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他媽的給我滾出去\N{\fs14}Get the hell away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.77,0:31:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從我家滾出去\N{\fs14}Get away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.08,0:31:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無線網絡安全防護? 我日\N{\fs14}wpa2 wi-fi? Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.64,0:31:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊界無法侵入\N{\fs14}Borderline unhackable.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.57,0:31:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要連上可能需要好幾天\N{\fs14}Getting that handshake could take days.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.11,0:31:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可怎么辦呢\N{\fs14}The noose is tightening.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.11,0:32:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警車上的攝像頭也是聯網的\N{\fs14}The mobile feed on the cameras.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.42,0:32:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 如果有4g 就不用去黑無線網絡安全防護了\N{\fs14}I don't need to hack wpa2 when there's dedicated 4g.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.32,0:32:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問題解決了\N{\fs14}We're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.11,0:32:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能把這個打開\N{\fs14}I can pull this off.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.05,0:32:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 上車 - 我們走吧 姑娘\N{\fs14}- Get in. - Let's go, girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.14,0:32:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 就他一個人\N{\fs14}Nah, just him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.23,0:32:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 呦 艾薩克 你是要做什么-- - 沒什么 兄弟 沒事\N{\fs14}- Yo, Isaac, what you doing-- - Nah, bro, it's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.38,0:32:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想和他單獨聊聊\N{\fs14}I just want to have a private chat with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.04,0:32:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 很有勁的\N{\fs14}Come on, it's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.07,0:32:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒時間了 伙計\N{\fs14}We don't have any time, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.26,0:32:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我也有事要做 - 趕緊他媽的滾上車\N{\fs14}- I got to get to work. - Get the fuck in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.83,0:32:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你 要去那兒 要干什么?\N{\fs14}Yo man, where you going, what you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.11,0:32:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事 沒事 就是說說話\N{\fs14}All good, all good. Just gonna have a talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.75,0:32:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你--?\N{\fs14}Are you--?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.72,0:33:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么要這么干?\N{\fs14}Why are you doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.95,0:33:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以讓你大哥重獲自由\N{\fs14}I can free your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.81,0:33:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經搞出眉目了\N{\fs14}I figured it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.06,0:33:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你今天運氣不好 兄弟\N{\fs14}It just wasn't your day, bruh.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.06,0:33:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經黑了你所有的生意 如果你殺了我--\N{\fs14}I hacked your whole operation. If you kill me--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.62,0:33:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的所有生意也就抖沒了\N{\fs14}You don't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.38,0:33:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過了 今兒是你運氣不好\N{\fs14}Like I said, it just wasn't your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.98,0:33:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下\N{\fs14}Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.00,0:33:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜有一顆子彈正平靜地等著\N{\fs14}I suppose a bullet through
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.24,0:33:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿過我的大腦\N{\fs14}the brain is peaceful in its own right.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.82,0:33:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想讓我救維拉\N{\fs14}You don't want me to free Vera.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.81,0:33:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是為什么你并不關心事情進展\N{\fs14}That's why you don't care about the operation.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.03,0:33:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臨終遺言還是說點別的吧\N{\fs14}I'd pick better last words.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.33,0:33:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只想置他于死地\N{\fs14}You're trying to kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.84,0:34:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,維拉想要今晚行動也是因為這個\N{\fs14}That's why Vera wants to leave tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.78,0:34:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是你一直以來讓我覺得心煩意亂的地方\N{\fs14}That's what's been bugging me about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.29,0:34:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你壓根就不想讓我把他弄出來\N{\fs14}You never wanted me to break him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.54,0:34:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了自保你最好的選擇就是讓他死在監獄里\N{\fs14}Your best option for survival is to kill him in prison,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.71,0:34:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為如果他不死\N{\fs14}because if you don't,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.09,0:34:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就活不了了\N{\fs14}you're dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.78,0:34:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你讓維拉身陷囹圄\N{\fs14}You're the reason Vera's locked up right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.54,0:34:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他都知道\N{\fs14}and he knows it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.18,0:34:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣這些都不重要了\N{\fs14}Doesn't matter anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.05,0:34:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,維拉剛還洋洋得意的想著他的團隊如何如何\N{\fs14}Vera was just gloating about how he got in with the right crew,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.16,0:34:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想著他如何能騎在別人頭上為所欲為\N{\fs14}how he got the jump on some men.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.40,0:34:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一點兒都不擔心 伙計\N{\fs14}He's not worried, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.52,0:34:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他現在是受保護的\N{\fs14}He's protected now.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.24,0:34:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放屁\N{\fs14}Bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.44,0:34:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就導致你只有一個 一方收益另一方就損失 和為零的情況\N{\fs14}That leaves you with a zero-sum game.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.83,0:34:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不把他弄出監獄\N{\fs14}If you don't get him out of jail,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.02,0:34:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會殺了你 因為你失敗了\N{\fs14}he'll have you killed for failing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.08,0:34:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事只有在一種情況下發生才對你有利\N{\fs14}Only way this works in your favor
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.66,0:34:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你先把他殺了\N{\fs14}is for you to kill him first,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.47,0:34:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他在里面 你不能殺了他\N{\fs14}and you can't do that with him inside anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.63,0:34:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉你媽的嘴\N{\fs14}Shut up, motherfucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.93,0:34:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴\N{\fs14}Shut the fuck up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.33,0:34:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我放他出來\N{\fs14}Let me free him.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.57,0:34:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我今晚把維拉弄出去的時候\N{\fs14}When I break Vera out tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.29,0:34:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么處理他是你的事\N{\fs14}you do with your brother what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.12,0:34:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是唯一一種\N{\fs14}That's the only outcome
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.40,0:34:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還能繼續活著的結果\N{\fs14}where you got the possibility of living.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.81,0:35:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你最好的方法\N{\fs14}It's your best move.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.57,0:35:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道事后我不會殺了你?\N{\fs14}What makes you think I still won't kill you afterwards?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.77,0:35:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fs14}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.37,0:35:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這是我最佳的選擇\N{\fs14}I'm just playing my best move.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.83,0:35:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要大概30-40秒\N{\fs14}I need 30 to 40 seconds with the patrol car's
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.95,0:35:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來和巡邏車藍牙連接上 運行黑客軟件\N{\fs14}bluetooth connection to run the exploit on the plc.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.76,0:35:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢?\N{\fs14}And then?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.24,0:35:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9點49分計劃開始\N{\fs14}The plan executes at 9:49.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.08,0:35:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有牢房的門都會打開\N{\fs14}All the cell doors should open.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.80,0:36:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 我想跟你說件事\N{\fs14}Hey, I wanted to ask you about something.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.09,0:36:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 是嗎 你想說啥? - 你\N{\fs14}- Oh, yeah, what's that? - You.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.81,0:36:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得給我打電話哦\N{\fs14}Give me a call.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.60,0:36:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們可以一起喝點東西 聊聊天 隨便什么\N{\fs14}We'll grab a drink, talk, whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.18,0:36:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.96,0:36:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軟件現在在他的電腦上運行了\N{\fs14}The exploit's on his laptop.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.57,0:36:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我需要逼它進入監獄網絡\N{\fs14}Now I need to force-feed it into the jail's network.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.45,0:37:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些我喜歡\N{\fs14}I like what I hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.19,0:37:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我暫停了軟件的運行\N{\fs14}I paused the exploit.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.98,0:37:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開車吧\N{\fs14}Drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.68,0:37:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳不再是計劃的一部分了\N{\fs14}Darlene's no longer part of the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.28,0:37:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有一個警鈴被觸發了 東邊出口那里的\N{\fs14}We got an alarm going off, east-side exit.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.30,0:37:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臥槽這是啥\N{\fs14}What in the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.77,0:37:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你說\N{\fs14}Tell you what.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.10,0:37:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們出去玩 喝喝小酒 跳跳舞\N{\fs14}We go out, we drink, we dance,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.60,0:37:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上看看優衣庫試衣間的風景\N{\fs14}see where the night takes us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.96,0:37:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確定你現在要做出這個選擇嗎?\N{\fs14}You sure you want to make that choice right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.61,0:37:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只需要按一個按鈕來繼續運行黑客軟件\N{\fs14}I only need to press one key to run the exploit.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.80,0:37:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者 我可以按另一個按鈕 撤銷整個計劃\N{\fs14}Or, I can press another and disable the entire plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.51,0:37:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出了我的招\N{\fs14}I made my move.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.11,0:37:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做你的選擇\N{\fs14}You make yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.92,0:37:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肏\N{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.19,0:37:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 請你往邊站點\N{\fs14}Please move back, miss.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.71,0:37:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須馬上回去\N{\fs14}I got to get back asap.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.28,0:37:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨便你\N{\fs14}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.40,0:38:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 我得馬上回去了 我的電腦不運行了\N{\fs14}Look, I got to come back now. My computer's on the fritz.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.66,0:38:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們走吧 DJ\N{\fs14}Let's go to the meet, DJ.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.44,0:38:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我打錯一個指令 點錯一個鍵\N{\fs14}If I mis-typed one command, hit one wrong key,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.59,0:38:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,監獄門就不會打開\N{\fs14}the cell doors won't open.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.57,0:38:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們倆都知道那樣會發生什么\N{\fs14}And we both know what that means.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.08,0:38:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我犯了一個錯誤嗎?\N{\fs14}Did I make a mistake?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.76,0:38:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我從不犯錯\N{\fs14}No, I don't make mistakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.44,0:38:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,維拉還有一分鐘\N{\fs14}One minute till Vera.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.83,0:38:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論他有多少瘋狂 多少沒人性的想法\N{\fs14}For all his insane, inhumane ideas,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.48,0:38:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他確實理解這個世界\N{\fs14}he does understand the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.31,0:38:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界的殘酷\N{\fs14}The wild savagery of the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.07,0:38:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用那個干干嗎 兄弟?\N{\fs14}What you need your piece for, bro?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.26,0:38:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇妙男孩說他把所有監獄門都能打開\N{\fs14}Boy wonder says he's opening all the cells.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.62,0:38:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果什么煞筆 朝咱們沖過來\N{\fs14}If some fool tries to rush us,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.06,0:38:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做好準備\N{\fs14}I want to be ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.97,0:39:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咋回事\N{\fs14}Hey, what the shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.84,0:39:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的牢房門同時打開\N{\fs14}Power surge caused by all
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.02,0:39:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成了對電力的需求激增\N{\fs14}the cell doors opening at the same time.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.91,0:39:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保安和警報怎么辦?\N{\fs14}What about security? Sirens?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.83,0:39:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,監獄的網絡會顯示所有的老房門都是鎖好的 關住的\N{\fs14}The jail's network will show all cells locked and closed.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.89,0:39:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警報兩分鐘內是沒聲音的\N{\fs14}Alarms are silent for two minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.67,0:40:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈\N{\fs14}Yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.01,0:40:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個\N{\fs14}This shit right here,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.84,0:40:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這比我草過的任何一個人都感覺好\N{\fs14}this shit tastes better than any pussy I ever had.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.68,0:40:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DJ 殺死這個屌絲\N{\fs14}DJ, shoot the cocksucker.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.52,0:40:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的親兄弟\N{\fs14}My own brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.58,0:40:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是宇宙要求我做的\N{\fs14}That's what the universe asked of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.39,0:40:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做他監護人\N{\fs14}To be my brother's keeper.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.43,0:40:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像該隱殺死亞伯(創世紀中哥哥因嫉妒殺死弟弟的故事)\N{\fs14}Like Cain after Abel,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.31,0:40:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會成為地球上的 一個逃犯 一個漂泊者\N{\fs14}I'll be a fugitive and wanderer on the earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.36,0:41:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢的逃犯\N{\fs14}Brave fugitive.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.56,0:41:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇敢的漂泊者\N{\fs14}Brave wanderer.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.57,0:41:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你怎么幫了我\N{\fs14}Look how you helped me.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.49,0:41:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我欣賞的那種勇敢\N{\fs14}That's the kind of bravery I've been talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.42,0:41:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在\N{\fs14}But now...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.85,0:41:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我想讓你好好看俺艾薩克\N{\fs14}Now I want you to look at Isaac.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.88,0:41:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fs14}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.51,0:41:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死證\N{\fs14}Dead proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.92,0:41:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的行動結束了\N{\fs14}My operation is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.88,0:41:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以現在上去  碾碎它\N{\fs14}So go on, crash it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.57,0:41:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燒毀它\N{\fs14}Burn it to the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.15,0:41:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不重要\N{\fs14}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.72,0:41:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了\N{\fs14}I'm gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.91,0:41:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個靈魂\N{\fs14}A spirit.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.89,0:41:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個和所有天堂\N{\fs14}One with all the heavens.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.64,0:41:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的存在一起的\N{\fs14}All existence.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.29,0:41:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉\N{\fs14}Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.07,0:41:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪?\N{\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.95,0:41:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鑰匙給我\N{\fs14}Keys, yo.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.99,0:42:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早跟你說了她會回到你身邊的 兄弟\N{\fs14}Told you you'd get her back, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.15,0:42:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是沒有意識到\N{\fs14}You just didn't realize
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.19,0:42:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全程她都跟你在一起\N{\fs14}she was with you the whole time.
