11
00:00:00,430 --> 00:00:03,000
The redundant backups at their eastern data center in China,

12
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:04,640
the Dark Army is covering us on that.

13
00:00:04,680 --> 00:00:05,680
We can go now!

14
00:00:05,700 --> 00:00:07,100
If we move forward and they don't,

15
00:00:07,140 --> 00:00:09,200
China still holds all the redundant information.

16
00:00:09,260 --> 00:00:10,340
It will be pointless.

17
00:00:10,360 --> 00:00:12,120
If we can talk to whiterose directly--

18
00:00:12,140 --> 00:00:13,960
No way he's meeting you face to face.

19
00:00:13,960 --> 00:00:15,780
You fools actually got your wish.

20
00:00:15,840 --> 00:00:17,740
I don't know why, but the meeting's actually gonna be on.

21
00:00:17,760 --> 00:00:18,880
I'd tell you to be careful,

22
00:00:18,920 --> 00:00:20,820
but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.

23
00:00:20,920 --> 00:00:23,680
I had the sysadmin check that server again.

24
00:00:23,720 --> 00:00:25,320
Of course, there was nothing.

25
00:00:25,360 --> 00:00:27,560
I have no idea what there was to even be suspicious about.

26
00:00:27,600 --> 00:00:29,220
Why do you have my work ID?

27
00:00:29,280 --> 00:00:31,460
I placed a malicious CD in my work computer.

28
00:00:31,480 --> 00:00:33,320
I need you to do something for me.

29
00:00:33,340 --> 00:00:36,280
Our new Chief Technology Officer,

30
00:00:36,440 --> 00:00:37,820
Scott Knowles.

31
00:00:37,840 --> 00:00:40,380
Meet me tonight, on the roof.

32
00:00:40,420 --> 00:00:42,040
Cameras have been out since March.

33
00:00:42,120 --> 00:00:43,220
No one will know.

34
00:00:47,460 --> 00:00:49,020
Stop!

35
00:01:18,980 --> 00:01:21,440
What if this all went away?

36
00:01:21,840 --> 00:01:23,940
The city.

37
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:25,360
The money.

38
00:01:26,000 --> 00:01:27,480
All of it.

39
00:01:27,640 --> 00:01:30,580
What, like a zombie apocalypse or something?

40
00:01:30,670 --> 00:01:33,280
More like a revolution.

41
00:01:34,560 --> 00:01:35,960
Last time we hooked up,

42
00:01:36,020 --> 00:01:38,060
we agreed to check politics at the door.

43
00:01:38,100 --> 00:01:39,580
There's no middle anymore.

44
00:01:39,820 --> 00:01:42,020
Just rich and poor.

45
00:01:42,340 --> 00:01:45,200
Okay, this shit is way too heavy for me this early.

46
00:01:45,260 --> 00:01:45,980
I gotta go to work.

47
00:01:46,040 --> 00:01:46,760
Right.

48
00:01:46,860 --> 00:01:48,680
Solving the world's problems

49
00:01:48,720 --> 00:01:50,820
one spreadsheet at a time.

50
00:01:51,340 --> 00:01:53,900
Hey, it's either suits like me or the government.

51
00:01:53,980 --> 00:01:55,560
We all know how well they handle things.

52
00:01:55,660 --> 00:01:57,660
Why can't the world just take care of itself?

53
00:01:58,280 --> 00:02:00,700
Because the world is filled with stupid people.

54
00:02:00,800 --> 00:02:03,040
And I get paid a lot to be smart.

55
00:02:04,060 --> 00:02:05,200
Hey.

56
00:02:06,740 --> 00:02:08,960
There's not just the rich and the poor.

57
00:02:09,720 --> 00:02:12,020
There's you, in the middle somewhere.

58
00:02:12,180 --> 00:02:14,280
The consummate survivor.

59
00:03:45,280 --> 00:03:49,280
I--I'm in a ballet class right now.

60
00:03:51,280 --> 00:03:54,500
No, Ollie, I can't talk to you about this right now.

61
00:03:56,380 --> 00:03:59,200
I don't care, Ollie.

62
00:04:00,280 --> 00:04:03,080
I don't care who you ran into

63
00:04:03,140 --> 00:04:04,760
or what he said.

64
00:04:06,560 --> 00:04:08,060
I...

65
00:04:15,060 --> 00:04:16,300
Sorry.

66
00:04:16,540 --> 00:04:19,200
Tell me you're not getting back together with him.

67
00:04:19,300 --> 00:04:20,820
Jesus, no.

68
00:04:21,260 --> 00:04:23,960
No. Just leftover work stuff.

69
00:04:24,760 --> 00:04:26,640
Have you talked to Elliot?

70
00:04:26,700 --> 00:04:28,200
Yesterday.

71
00:04:28,720 --> 00:04:30,460
Seems like he's pulling himself together,

72
00:04:30,500 --> 00:04:33,060
but you know how he is.

73
00:04:33,080 --> 00:04:35,100
It feels like I'm always worried about him.

74
00:04:35,180 --> 00:04:36,760
- You know? - Yeah.

75
00:04:36,790 --> 00:04:38,330
He's had a shitty month.

76
00:04:38,360 --> 00:04:40,060
Or 20 years.

77
00:04:40,100 --> 00:04:41,660
Take your pick.

78
00:04:41,700 --> 00:04:42,970
Then why are we the ones

79
00:04:43,000 --> 00:04:45,670
that always end up so stressed?

80
00:04:45,700 --> 00:04:48,940
Try waking up in your childhood bedroom,

81
00:04:48,970 --> 00:04:51,570
then taking Jersey transit for two hours

82
00:04:51,610 --> 00:04:54,860
to make a 7:00 ballet class in the city.

83
00:04:55,450 --> 00:04:57,380
Well, silver lining,

84
00:04:57,480 --> 00:04:59,280
you get to see moi.

85
00:04:59,360 --> 00:05:01,400
All right, everyone, first position.

86
00:05:25,310 --> 00:05:27,220
I hurt Krista.

87
00:05:27,400 --> 00:05:29,420
I don't feel good about that.

88
00:05:29,540 --> 00:05:31,560
I hope you're not mad at me.

89
00:05:31,680 --> 00:05:33,480
But you have to admit,

90
00:05:33,520 --> 00:05:35,250
she's just like everyone else.

91
00:05:35,500 --> 00:05:37,980
Too afraid to peek over their walls

92
00:05:38,040 --> 00:05:40,490
for fear of what they might see.

93
00:05:50,100 --> 00:05:51,530
Not me.

94
00:05:52,060 --> 00:05:53,870
That's what I do.

95
00:05:54,340 --> 00:05:56,180
I look.

96
00:06:14,420 --> 00:06:17,430
Did you get everybody back?

97
00:07:07,640 --> 00:07:09,880
Tell him to follow the proper commands,

98
00:07:09,960 --> 00:07:11,800
or the sequence won't initiate.

99
00:07:23,590 --> 00:07:26,380
Using the backdoor we planted with our raspberry pie.

100
00:07:26,460 --> 00:07:28,960
Jesus Christ, man, how long have you been sitting on all this?

101
00:07:29,000 --> 00:07:30,860
I installed a patch four weeks ago,

102
00:07:30,880 --> 00:07:32,140
and I've been monitoring it daily.

103
00:07:32,200 --> 00:07:33,400
No rest for the wicked.

104
00:07:33,440 --> 00:07:35,660
I wanted to make sure it was all updated

105
00:07:35,720 --> 00:07:37,280
at the Steel Mountain locations

106
00:07:37,320 --> 00:07:39,240
before the meeting with whiterose.

107
00:07:39,280 --> 00:07:41,260
Yeah, those Airdream guys are so dumb.

108
00:07:41,280 --> 00:07:44,760
Who has all their thermostats phone home the same network?

109
00:07:44,820 --> 00:07:46,560
I'll sync up all five locations

110
00:07:46,600 --> 00:07:48,480
so they heat at exactly the same rate.

111
00:07:48,540 --> 00:07:50,040
No offense, but I'll handle that.

112
00:07:50,080 --> 00:07:51,390
You should take care of the alarms,

113
00:07:51,420 --> 00:07:53,560
so there's not a signal of the temp raising in the vaults.

114
00:07:53,600 --> 00:07:54,680
- No, reroute

115
00:07:54,720 --> 00:07:56,140
Airdream's traffic.

116
00:07:56,160 --> 00:07:59,030
Make sure to erase and and all signs of our activity.

117
00:08:02,730 --> 00:08:04,880
- Where were you? - I need a word.

118
00:08:04,900 --> 00:08:05,840
I gotta get to work.

119
00:08:05,900 --> 00:08:07,400
I'm not sure that's wise.

120
00:08:08,940 --> 00:08:10,340
What the hell is that?

121
00:08:10,370 --> 00:08:11,560
They're following me

122
00:08:11,580 --> 00:08:13,010
and they're probably following you too.

123
00:08:13,040 --> 00:08:14,940
They were on the subway, okay?

124
00:08:15,000 --> 00:08:16,400
Cisco's warned me about them.

125
00:08:16,440 --> 00:08:18,440
These guys are dangerous, Elliot.

126
00:08:18,480 --> 00:08:22,680
The whiterose meet might not go down the way we want it to.

127
00:08:22,720 --> 00:08:24,120
Yeah.

128
00:08:24,150 --> 00:08:28,020
Well, I don't even know how to use a gun.

129
00:08:28,380 --> 00:08:31,680
Besides, I'm not even sure I'm the one they wanna meet with.

130
00:08:31,680 --> 00:08:34,030
You're definitely the one they wanna meet with.

131
00:08:34,060 --> 00:08:37,470
And when you do, you need to be careful.

132
00:08:37,500 --> 00:08:39,500
I'm serious, Elliot.

133
00:08:40,770 --> 00:08:42,000
What are you doing?

134
00:08:42,040 --> 00:08:43,980
I'm calling myself from your phone.

135
00:08:43,980 --> 00:08:45,340
That way we have each other's number.

136
00:08:45,340 --> 00:08:46,980
Wait, Darlene, we don't do that.

137
00:08:47,000 --> 00:08:48,510
That's to protect a fsociety.

138
00:08:48,700 --> 00:08:51,670
Okay, but we need to protect each other right now.

139
00:09:22,910 --> 00:09:26,070
Lose Darlene's number. It's a rule for a reason.

140
00:09:26,110 --> 00:09:29,240
Don't worry, I'm not gonna use it.

141
00:09:29,280 --> 00:09:31,510
She's right about one thing.

142
00:09:31,550 --> 00:09:33,880
You're the one they want to talk to.

143
00:09:33,920 --> 00:09:36,990
We can't afford any distractions.

144
00:10:04,960 --> 00:10:07,700
My boss invited me again. He's so obvious.

145
00:10:07,760 --> 00:10:09,780
Why don't you just kill me now?

146
00:10:10,200 --> 00:10:11,380
Oh!

147
00:10:11,500 --> 00:10:13,960
Jesus, Blake! Were you f---ing tiptoeing?

148
00:10:14,000 --> 00:10:15,880
God damn it, look what you've done.

149
00:10:15,900 --> 00:10:17,010
Watch where you're going!

150
00:10:17,050 --> 00:10:19,020
- But you-- - Good morning.

151
00:10:19,060 --> 00:10:21,300
Not now, Elizabeth. Hold all calls.

152
00:10:21,320 --> 00:10:22,900
Cancel any meetings. I'm busy today.

153
00:10:22,940 --> 00:10:24,050
But, Mr. Wellick,

154
00:10:24,090 --> 00:10:25,920
Gideon Goddard is here to see you.

155
00:10:25,960 --> 00:10:27,800
I'm sorry. He was very persistent.

156
00:10:27,800 --> 00:10:29,720
He wouldn't leave.

157
00:10:29,760 --> 00:10:31,730
Okay.

158
00:10:32,020 --> 00:10:34,800
Okay, no, that's fine. Thank you.

159
00:10:34,840 --> 00:10:37,130
Um, do you want me to, uh...

160
00:10:41,700 --> 00:10:44,200
Oh, yes, I'd love some coffee.

161
00:11:01,720 --> 00:11:04,800
One of my employees confessed to

162
00:11:04,820 --> 00:11:06,590
breaking chain of custody with the Colby dat file.

163
00:11:06,900 --> 00:11:09,360
Unfortunately, this admission

164
00:11:09,380 --> 00:11:11,440
will render the evidence inadmissible

165
00:11:11,440 --> 00:11:12,920
and Colby free of charges.

166
00:11:12,960 --> 00:11:14,020
Now before you say anything,

167
00:11:14,060 --> 00:11:17,160
I want to assure you that Allsafe has doubled its efforts

168
00:11:17,200 --> 00:11:18,360
to find the hackers,

169
00:11:18,400 --> 00:11:20,600
whether it be reconfirming Colby's involvement

170
00:11:20,660 --> 00:11:22,210
or finding the real perpetrators.

171
00:11:22,240 --> 00:11:25,150
We've air-gapped your private network,

172
00:11:25,180 --> 00:11:26,510
implemented a honeypot,

173
00:11:26,550 --> 00:11:30,160
reconfigured all the firewalls and systematically--

174
00:11:30,180 --> 00:11:31,500
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.

175
00:11:31,560 --> 00:11:33,480
A honeypot, for what?

176
00:11:33,520 --> 00:11:37,630
A specific server involved in the last fsociety attack,

177
00:11:38,080 --> 00:11:39,490
CS30.

178
00:11:39,530 --> 00:11:42,720
I know we checked it out, but if there's even a chance

179
00:11:42,780 --> 00:11:43,980
the hackers are still in the network,

180
00:11:44,040 --> 00:11:47,040
the honeypot will ensure that they can't cause any damage.

181
00:11:47,070 --> 00:11:49,280
They'll log into the decoy server we've set up,

182
00:11:49,300 --> 00:11:50,920
thinking they're on the main network.

183
00:11:51,000 --> 00:11:53,560
And I'm personally keeping tabs on all traffic.

184
00:11:53,580 --> 00:11:55,200
So you have our full attention.

185
00:11:57,380 --> 00:12:01,960
Well, I appreciate your transparency.

186
00:12:02,000 --> 00:12:04,490
Well, so you understand then.

187
00:12:04,520 --> 00:12:06,220
Of course.

188
00:12:06,260 --> 00:12:09,090
In fact, I'd like to look over your findings,

189
00:12:09,120 --> 00:12:10,760
especially this server.

190
00:12:12,940 --> 00:12:15,020
So, please send me the research.

191
00:12:15,080 --> 00:12:16,180
Of course, of course.

192
00:12:16,280 --> 00:12:18,170
Well, thank you again for seeing me.

193
00:13:09,320 --> 00:13:11,390
Mr. Wellick.

194
00:13:12,760 --> 00:13:13,990
Mr. Wellick!

195
00:13:14,020 --> 00:13:17,020
I specifically asked not to be disturbed.

196
00:13:17,080 --> 00:13:18,500
I know, but, um--

197
00:13:18,540 --> 00:13:19,890
What is it?

198
00:13:19,930 --> 00:13:21,700
The police.

199
00:13:21,730 --> 00:13:24,030
It's awful.

200
00:13:24,070 --> 00:13:25,760
What about the police?

201
00:13:26,120 --> 00:13:28,360
They found a body on the roof.

202
00:13:28,660 --> 00:13:30,640
A body? Who?

203
00:13:30,740 --> 00:13:32,960
They're not saying,but detectives came by.

204
00:13:32,980 --> 00:13:34,320
They want to speak with you.

205
00:13:34,700 --> 00:13:35,580
With me?

206
00:13:35,660 --> 00:13:37,240
They're questioning everyone

207
00:13:37,280 --> 00:13:39,760
who was at the reception last night.

208
00:13:47,220 --> 00:13:50,900
Clearly, this is tragic, but unfortunately work goes on.

209
00:13:50,960 --> 00:13:52,260
But don't you think you should--

210
00:13:52,290 --> 00:13:55,460
Tell them they can set an appointment.

211
00:13:55,500 --> 00:13:58,170
I'd be happy to speak with them then.

212
00:14:01,770 --> 00:14:04,520
Oh, and, Elizabeth,I need you to connect me

213
00:14:04,540 --> 00:14:05,600
with the Dulles Server Farm.

214
00:14:05,680 --> 00:14:07,420
I'll take it on my mobile.

215
00:14:10,140 --> 00:14:11,440
And the file shares?

216
00:14:11,460 --> 00:14:12,960
'Cause client data is inaccessible

217
00:14:13,000 --> 00:14:13,800
until we're back online.

218
00:14:13,820 --> 00:14:15,250
Jumping on that now.

219
00:14:15,280 --> 00:14:17,120
Check the logs on the ASA firewall.

220
00:14:17,160 --> 00:14:18,250
I want a full report.

221
00:14:18,290 --> 00:14:20,360
Ollie, sales.

222
00:14:20,380 --> 00:14:21,720
All appointments at Allsafe

223
00:14:21,740 --> 00:14:23,160
are cancelled until further notice.

224
00:14:23,180 --> 00:14:24,590
Word of this cannot get out.

225
00:14:24,630 --> 00:14:27,430
All right,let's get to it.

226
00:14:39,880 --> 00:14:43,580
This hack is far from devastating. They already own us.

227
00:14:43,760 --> 00:14:46,280
They're not going after anything valuable.

228
00:14:46,380 --> 00:14:48,420
This is more of a distraction.

229
00:14:48,600 --> 00:14:51,220
But what are they trying to distract us from?

230
00:14:57,940 --> 00:14:59,870
Hey, bro.

231
00:15:03,900 --> 00:15:05,760
Always the chatterbox.

232
00:15:06,380 --> 00:15:07,960
You're sweating.

233
00:15:08,020 --> 00:15:10,600
Oh, yeah? Yeah, maybe a little.

234
00:15:10,700 --> 00:15:12,000
Been running around.

235
00:15:12,040 --> 00:15:15,520
Um, look, I sorta need you to handle something for me.

236
00:15:15,560 --> 00:15:16,600
What have they got you doing here?

237
00:15:16,620 --> 00:15:18,720
Trying to reverse engineer the malware.

238
00:15:18,740 --> 00:15:20,960
Okay, um, I'm gonna need you to stop doing that

239
00:15:21,020 --> 00:15:22,760
Try and take these engineer corrupted drives malware.

240
00:15:22,800 --> 00:15:24,470
over to Blank's Disk Recovery on 36th and 5th.

241
00:15:26,040 --> 00:15:28,380
Why me? Get one of the IT guys.

242
00:15:28,420 --> 00:15:32,340
Everyone is swamped, Elliot.

243
00:15:34,060 --> 00:15:39,300
Dude, this isn't, like,a debate.

244
00:15:39,820 --> 00:15:42,100
I've always wanted things to be cool between us,

245
00:15:42,140 --> 00:15:45,360
but I outrank you.

246
00:15:45,720 --> 00:15:47,160
So...

247
00:15:48,800 --> 00:15:50,720
Here are the drives.

248
00:15:50,960 --> 00:15:52,940
Your appointment is at 2:00.

249
00:15:52,980 --> 00:15:55,200
You cannot be late.

250
00:15:56,020 --> 00:15:59,720
In fact, um, how 'bout you leave right now?

251
00:16:00,360 --> 00:16:02,380
It's only 12:00.

252
00:16:02,400 --> 00:16:05,000
Elliot, bro, just--

253
00:16:05,060 --> 00:16:08,310
just do me this solid, okay?

254
00:16:21,480 --> 00:16:23,340
He wasn't just stressed.

255
00:16:23,380 --> 00:16:25,160
He was scared.

256
00:16:25,600 --> 00:16:27,940
Let's see what he's hiding.

257
00:16:35,640 --> 00:16:38,810
What does Angela have to do with this?

258
00:18:13,500 --> 00:18:15,660
Why didn't you tell me?

259
00:18:16,120 --> 00:18:17,720
And say what?

260
00:18:18,220 --> 00:18:20,500
"Hey, Elliot, there's a bunch of nude pics of me

261
00:18:20,540 --> 00:18:21,940
that some asshole wants to leak online"?

262
00:18:21,980 --> 00:18:23,140
I could have helped.

263
00:18:23,180 --> 00:18:24,850
You weren't around.

264
00:18:25,280 --> 00:18:26,480
Yeah.

265
00:18:26,900 --> 00:18:29,820
Kinda had a rough month.

266
00:18:31,100 --> 00:18:32,950
I'm sorry.

267
00:18:33,560 --> 00:18:36,590
Tell me what happened.

268
00:18:36,740 --> 00:18:38,840
We were being pressured.

269
00:18:39,400 --> 00:18:40,660
By who?

270
00:18:41,000 --> 00:18:42,460
Some guy.

271
00:18:42,980 --> 00:18:46,140
He gave Ollie a CD that infected his laptop,

272
00:18:46,160 --> 00:18:49,940
stole his pictures, his emails,and browser cache.

273
00:18:50,520 --> 00:18:53,060
He said to install the disk at Allsafe,

274
00:18:53,120 --> 00:18:55,360
or he would leak everything online.

275
00:18:55,940 --> 00:18:57,920
It was a while ago.

276
00:18:57,960 --> 00:18:59,460
I thought he forgot about us.

277
00:18:59,500 --> 00:19:00,640
I was right.

278
00:19:00,660 --> 00:19:02,320
The hack was a distraction.

279
00:19:02,380 --> 00:19:04,450
This is about me.This is the meeting.

280
00:19:06,480 --> 00:19:08,480
You should have come to me.

281
00:19:08,860 --> 00:19:10,240
I told you,

282
00:19:10,360 --> 00:19:12,000
you weren't there.

283
00:19:12,100 --> 00:19:13,630
You're never there anymore.

284
00:19:15,600 --> 00:19:18,040
Something is going on with you, Elliot.

285
00:19:18,120 --> 00:19:20,280
You have not been the same the past couple of months,

286
00:19:20,340 --> 00:19:22,140
and this happened before Shayla.

287
00:19:22,180 --> 00:19:23,200
You're wrong.

288
00:19:23,260 --> 00:19:24,010
You're lying!

289
00:19:24,540 --> 00:19:27,280
You don't talk to me anymore!

290
00:19:27,400 --> 00:19:29,260
Just tell me what to do here!

291
00:19:29,260 --> 00:19:31,360
Because the only solution I can think of

292
00:19:31,360 --> 00:19:33,650
is to give up.

293
00:19:40,760 --> 00:19:43,480
God, say something!

294
00:19:47,360 --> 00:19:49,280
You're right.

295
00:19:50,120 --> 00:19:52,200
We don't talk anymore.

296
00:20:01,760 --> 00:20:04,120
It's so strange.

297
00:20:05,160 --> 00:20:07,280
I really miss us.

298
00:20:08,960 --> 00:20:11,600
Why is that strange?

299
00:20:15,520 --> 00:20:17,960
Because I never thought I'd have to.

300
00:20:21,200 --> 00:20:23,100
Hackers.

301
00:20:23,130 --> 00:20:25,400
We inherently trust no one,

302
00:20:25,800 --> 00:20:27,730
including each other.

303
00:20:27,770 --> 00:20:29,700
I'll never be able to tell her.

304
00:20:29,740 --> 00:20:31,770
There will always be this divide,

305
00:20:31,810 --> 00:20:34,840
my wall that she can't look over.

306
00:20:36,640 --> 00:20:39,000
And she knows it.

307
00:20:45,800 --> 00:20:48,800
Trust issues, the dark army

308
00:20:48,800 --> 00:20:50,680
has taken extraordinary steps

309
00:20:50,680 --> 00:20:53,600
to make sure this meeting's exactly how they want it.

310
00:20:53,600 --> 00:20:56,800
Is that why the infamous whiterose is such a legend?

311
00:20:56,840 --> 00:21:01,040
Because he's more paranoid than the rest of us.

312
00:21:09,400 --> 00:21:13,160
I'm Elliot. Alderson.

313
00:21:35,480 --> 00:21:37,640
A Faraday cage.

314
00:21:38,000 --> 00:21:42,640
A room specifically designed to prevent electromagnetic interference

315
00:21:42,640 --> 00:21:48,000
No radio, no signal, no WiFi, nothing to hack.

316
00:21:51,880 --> 00:21:54,880
I think I'm here to see you.

317
00:21:59,840 --> 00:22:03,680
Am I supposed to follow you?

318
00:22:07,360 --> 00:22:09,360
Are you just going to stand there

319
00:22:09,360 --> 00:22:12,040
or do you want to hand me those drives?

320
00:22:12,890 --> 00:22:14,960
Mm-mm-mm.

321
00:22:15,040 --> 00:22:17,680
This meeting has started.

322
00:22:17,720 --> 00:22:20,600
I manage my time very carefully, Mr. Alderson.

323
00:22:20,600 --> 00:22:22,920
Each beep indicates one minute of my time

324
00:22:22,920 --> 00:22:24,200
that has passed.

325
00:22:24,200 --> 00:22:26,920
I have allotted you no more than three minutes.

326
00:22:30,760 --> 00:22:33,080
Are you really gonna do that?

327
00:22:33,080 --> 00:22:35,640
I suggest you pick better topics of conversation.

328
00:22:35,640 --> 00:22:38,480
I have 17 more items on my agenda today.

329
00:22:38,520 --> 00:22:40,280
The Evil Corp hack,

330
00:22:40,280 --> 00:22:41,600
we should go through with it this time.

331
00:22:41,600 --> 00:22:43,760
You are turning out to be a grave disappointment.

332
00:22:43,760 --> 00:22:46,040
We were ready. We had everything set to go.

333
00:22:46,040 --> 00:22:48,200
Dwelling is so inefficient.

334
00:22:48,200 --> 00:22:49,920
Hey, you pulled out last time.

335
00:22:49,920 --> 00:22:51,480
Wasting more time,

336
00:22:51,520 --> 00:22:53,720
telling me things I already know.

337
00:22:54,040 --> 00:22:55,760
But we were ready.

338
00:22:55,760 --> 00:22:58,040
That is the third time that you have expressed that.

339
00:22:58,040 --> 00:23:00,200
She's trolling me.

340
00:23:00,230 --> 00:23:03,400
You have not advanced this conversation.

341
00:23:03,400 --> 00:23:04,640
Do you intend to?

342
00:23:04,640 --> 00:23:06,000
Since last month,

343
00:23:06,040 --> 00:23:08,280
Evil Corp has moved its tapes to five--

344
00:23:08,320 --> 00:23:09,640
Backup facilities,

345
00:23:09,680 --> 00:23:11,800
and you have a plan to take them all down.

346
00:23:11,800 --> 00:23:12,920
Yes.

347
00:23:12,920 --> 00:23:15,400
Finally, you have communicated something.

348
00:23:15,400 --> 00:23:17,360
So are you ready to do this or not?

349
00:23:17,360 --> 00:23:19,800
You are the one who is not ready.

350
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:22,480
It was you who failed all along.

351
00:23:22,520 --> 00:23:24,240
What you've lacked was focus.

352
00:23:24,240 --> 00:23:27,120
You strayed from the hack to target Terry Colby.

353
00:23:27,120 --> 00:23:28,880
This opened a vulnerability.

354
00:23:28,880 --> 00:23:30,080
Suspicion.

355
00:23:30,080 --> 00:23:34,000
Specifically by Gideon Goddard.

356
00:23:34,480 --> 00:23:37,360
That's why you hacked Allsafe.

357
00:23:37,400 --> 00:23:39,360
To monitor his activities.

358
00:23:39,360 --> 00:23:41,160
And that's when we discovered

359
00:23:41,200 --> 00:23:44,880
that he turned your infected server into a honeypot.

360
00:23:46,400 --> 00:23:49,520
Oh, 60 seconds and this meeting will be over.

361
00:23:49,520 --> 00:23:50,520
Wait.

362
00:23:50,520 --> 00:23:53,040
The concept of waiting bewilders me.

363
00:23:53,040 --> 00:23:54,400
There are always deadlines.

364
00:23:54,400 --> 00:23:56,920
There are always ticking clocks.

365
00:23:56,920 --> 00:23:58,840
That's why you must manage your time.

366
00:23:58,840 --> 00:24:00,520
I'll find a way to remove the honeypot.

367
00:24:00,520 --> 00:24:02,200
Until 16 seconds ago,

368
00:24:02,200 --> 00:24:04,120
you were not aware there was a honeypot.

369
00:24:04,120 --> 00:24:06,560
This does not inspire confidence.

370
00:24:06,650 --> 00:24:08,080
- Wait.- There's that word again.

371
00:24:08,080 --> 00:24:09,320
We'll take care of it.

372
00:24:09,320 --> 00:24:12,320
You know you could have told us about the honeypot weeks ago.

373
00:24:12,320 --> 00:24:14,280
Every hacker has her fixation.

374
00:24:14,280 --> 00:24:16,760
You hack people, I hack time.

375
00:24:16,800 --> 00:24:20,040
So you should know that when I set a time line,

376
00:24:20,080 --> 00:24:21,800
there's a reason.

377
00:24:21,800 --> 00:24:24,840
You have 50 hours and 23 minutes.

378
00:24:24,840 --> 00:24:27,280
At that point, when all parties are ready,

379
00:24:27,280 --> 00:24:29,600
we will initiate the hack.

380
00:24:29,600 --> 00:24:31,800
We'll do it.

381
00:24:32,720 --> 00:24:34,640
Maybe next time--

382
00:24:34,680 --> 00:24:36,760
Understand something, Mr. Alderson.

383
00:24:36,760 --> 00:24:38,360
After I leave,

384
00:24:38,560 --> 00:24:40,260
you will never see me again.

385
00:24:40,420 --> 00:24:42,780
There are very few people in my life

386
00:24:42,780 --> 00:24:44,740
that I have enough time to see more than once,

387
00:24:44,780 --> 00:24:46,200
and you are not one of them.

388
00:24:50,880 --> 00:24:52,280
Trust me,

389
00:24:53,360 --> 00:24:56,050
that's not going to matter.

390
00:24:58,500 --> 00:25:00,160
Why are you doing all of this?

391
00:25:00,180 --> 00:25:01,740
The hack?

392
00:25:02,720 --> 00:25:05,660
Why are you working with us?

393
00:25:15,560 --> 00:25:18,740
50 hours and 20 minutes left.

394
00:25:18,840 --> 00:25:20,180
I need to figure this out.

395
00:25:20,220 --> 00:25:22,220
Gideon's been spying on me the whole time.

396
00:25:22,240 --> 00:25:24,120
Honeypot service order, shit.

397
00:25:24,240 --> 00:25:25,720
I gotta do that now.

398
00:25:25,800 --> 00:25:28,380
Security token. Gideon's phone.

399
00:25:28,400 --> 00:25:29,620
I need his phone.

400
00:25:29,680 --> 00:25:32,180
50 hours and 19 minutes left.

401
00:25:32,240 --> 00:25:34,780
Damn, she infected me with her time paranoia.

402
00:25:34,820 --> 00:25:37,280
We're all living in each other's paranoia.

403
00:25:37,340 --> 00:25:39,420
You definitely can't argue that.

404
00:25:39,460 --> 00:25:42,300
Is that why everyone tries to avoid each other?

405
00:25:42,340 --> 00:25:43,740
I need to calm down.

406
00:25:43,780 --> 00:25:45,780
I wish I could be an observer like you.

407
00:25:45,820 --> 00:25:47,760
Then I could think more calmly.

408
00:25:57,260 --> 00:25:59,740
This is comfortable.

409
00:25:59,800 --> 00:26:01,700
Less stressful.

410
00:26:01,800 --> 00:26:04,680
In fact, I feel like I can see everything,

411
00:26:04,760 --> 00:26:07,150
know everything this way.

412
00:26:07,190 --> 00:26:08,590
Hmm.

413
00:26:09,060 --> 00:26:11,060
Do you know more than me?

414
00:26:11,180 --> 00:26:13,080
That wouldn't be fair,

415
00:26:13,120 --> 00:26:16,060
my imaginary friend knowing more than me.

416
00:26:16,180 --> 00:26:18,100
So what would you do now?

417
00:26:18,220 --> 00:26:21,500
We need a distraction to get Gideon's phone.

418
00:26:28,620 --> 00:26:32,220
Darlene, I need you to do something for me.

419
00:26:32,300 --> 00:26:33,280
She can help.

420
00:26:33,320 --> 00:26:34,920
My boss at Allstate, Gideon--

421
00:26:34,960 --> 00:26:36,020
Sometimes it's hard

422
00:26:36,060 --> 00:26:37,900
to listen to an explanation,

423
00:26:37,960 --> 00:26:39,920
even when it's from myself.

424
00:26:39,960 --> 00:26:42,280
Especially when it's from myself.

425
00:26:42,560 --> 00:26:44,560
It would be so much easier

426
00:26:44,580 --> 00:26:46,560
to only pay attention when I needed to.

427
00:26:47,080 --> 00:26:48,800
To just--

428
00:26:51,840 --> 00:26:53,840
Arrive at the conclusion.

429
00:26:56,760 --> 00:26:58,580
Is that what you do?

430
00:27:28,280 --> 00:27:31,400
100 large MMS files to Gideon's phone.

431
00:27:31,400 --> 00:27:32,400
Drained it.

432
00:27:50,540 --> 00:27:53,560
Corporate greed is a trickle down desire

433
00:27:53,600 --> 00:27:55,600
that reaches even the bottom of the food chain.

434
00:27:55,660 --> 00:27:58,580
- And for what? - Wealth? - What the shit? - Power?

435
00:27:58,960 --> 00:28:00,640
It's a pathetic fable,

436
00:28:00,700 --> 00:28:03,180
and you, Allsafe, are a defender of this pitiful avarice.

437
00:28:03,200 --> 00:28:04,680
Holy shit, fsociety knows us.

438
00:28:04,720 --> 00:28:06,420
But your sweet dream is over,

439
00:28:06,460 --> 00:28:08,460
and your nightmare is about to begin.

440
00:28:09,740 --> 00:28:12,780
We have won.Let those who are complicit...

441
00:28:12,820 --> 00:28:14,280
What the hell's happening now?

442
00:28:14,320 --> 00:28:15,500
Those who aid the tyrants,

443
00:28:15,540 --> 00:28:17,460
those who accept the tyranny

444
00:28:17,520 --> 00:28:19,840
have no place in the new order.

445
00:28:19,880 --> 00:28:21,620
The distraction is momentary.

446
00:28:22,180 --> 00:28:23,840
Hopefully all I need.

447
00:28:23,880 --> 00:28:25,900
They will know our justice,

448
00:28:25,940 --> 00:28:27,900
and we will show no mercy.

449
00:28:27,960 --> 00:28:31,980
Gideon Goddard, you are a lackey

450
00:28:32,020 --> 00:28:33,620
to your corporate overlords.

451
00:28:33,660 --> 00:28:34,940
Someone shut this off.

452
00:28:34,980 --> 00:28:36,000
Defending those

453
00:28:36,040 --> 00:28:38,080
that bleed the innocent.

454
00:28:38,120 --> 00:28:41,000
Serving them, slave to master.

455
00:28:41,020 --> 00:28:42,360
It's ignoring the remote.

456
00:28:42,480 --> 00:28:43,760
They hacked our smart TV.

457
00:28:43,780 --> 00:28:45,500
Congratulations, Mr. Goddard.

458
00:28:45,540 --> 00:28:46,660
It's posted to our website.

459
00:28:46,700 --> 00:28:47,620
And YouTube.

460
00:28:47,640 --> 00:28:49,140
You will soon be finished.

461
00:28:49,900 --> 00:28:52,720
In 90 seconds this code will change.

462
00:28:52,740 --> 00:28:56,060
If I don't log in with it on my computer before then,

463
00:28:56,160 --> 00:28:57,800
I'll lose everything to time.

464
00:28:57,820 --> 00:28:59,720
We are exposing your role to the world.

465
00:28:59,760 --> 00:29:01,300
No, let it finish.

466
00:29:01,380 --> 00:29:04,340
And the world is very angry.

467
00:29:12,180 --> 00:29:14,180
60 seconds. Whiterose was right.

468
00:29:14,220 --> 00:29:16,030
We run from one deadline to the next.

469
00:29:18,600 --> 00:29:19,660
Where's Elliot?

470
00:29:32,060 --> 00:29:34,060
What are you doing?

471
00:29:34,140 --> 00:29:36,780
I was working on the local backups.

472
00:29:36,840 --> 00:29:38,280
Why weren't you in there with us?

473
00:29:39,740 --> 00:29:41,200
I was worried about the--

474
00:29:41,240 --> 00:29:42,420
It just doesn't add up.

475
00:29:42,500 --> 00:29:43,720
All these events keep happening

476
00:29:43,740 --> 00:29:45,500
around your appearance, your disappearance.

477
00:29:45,520 --> 00:29:46,920
- Gideon-- - Forget it.

478
00:29:47,000 --> 00:29:48,380
I don't wanna hear it.

479
00:29:48,480 --> 00:29:50,900
Every member in this company stood in there,

480
00:29:50,940 --> 00:29:53,220
watching the single worst thing that's happened to Allsafe,

481
00:29:53,240 --> 00:29:54,800
and where are you, at your cubicle?

482
00:29:55,480 --> 00:29:57,540
Doing what?

483
00:30:00,820 --> 00:30:02,400
Uh, Gideon, I hate to interrupt...

484
00:30:02,400 --> 00:30:02,940
No, not now, Ollie.

485
00:30:02,940 --> 00:30:03,940
But Evil Corp's on the phone.

486
00:30:06,520 --> 00:30:07,880
I'll be back.

487
00:30:07,900 --> 00:30:09,180
We're not finished here.

488
00:30:15,440 --> 00:30:16,520
I know.

489
00:30:16,550 --> 00:30:18,540
You thought I didn't put the code in time,

490
00:30:18,540 --> 00:30:21,800
but I had to hide it quickly before Gideon saw it.

491
00:30:21,860 --> 00:30:22,960
Sorry.

492
00:30:32,400 --> 00:30:35,880
Have I told you what I saw when I hacked Gideon?

493
00:30:35,900 --> 00:30:38,420
When I peeked into his secrets?

494
00:30:39,000 --> 00:30:41,910
I saw a good, honest man.

495
00:30:42,460 --> 00:30:44,580
Gideon was wrong.

496
00:30:44,680 --> 00:30:46,020
I am finished here.

497
00:30:46,460 --> 00:30:48,800
I'm no good for him or this place.

498
00:30:48,860 --> 00:30:51,440
He was only protecting his people.

499
00:30:51,820 --> 00:30:53,290
But me?

500
00:30:53,320 --> 00:30:56,960
I'm doing this to protect everyone.

501
00:30:59,930 --> 00:31:02,800
Seems you've been very busy lately.

502
00:31:05,920 --> 00:31:08,620
I have to know what you're planning.

503
00:31:08,640 --> 00:31:10,980
We were meant to be allies.

504
00:31:12,840 --> 00:31:14,800
We might just want the same thing,

505
00:31:14,820 --> 00:31:16,450
and I need to be involved.

506
00:31:16,480 --> 00:31:19,540
I'm pretty positive you're dead wrong about that, my friend.

507
00:31:19,580 --> 00:31:22,890
I don't think there's anything we could possibly agree on.

508
00:31:24,520 --> 00:31:26,580
I don't know what game you're playing,

509
00:31:26,600 --> 00:31:28,440
but I suggest you cut the bullshit.

510
00:31:28,480 --> 00:31:30,900
If there's nothing else, I think we're done here.

511
00:31:31,160 --> 00:31:35,280
Aren't you forgetting that I know your dirty little secret?

512
00:31:35,380 --> 00:31:38,420
There are people close to you that wouldn't be happy

513
00:31:38,440 --> 00:31:39,900
if they knew what I know.

514
00:31:45,840 --> 00:31:48,280
We're both too smart to allow pettiness

515
00:31:48,340 --> 00:31:49,380
to dictate our actions.

516
00:31:49,440 --> 00:31:50,810
We're better than that.

517
00:31:51,100 --> 00:31:52,700
Weigh the pros and cons.

518
00:31:53,160 --> 00:31:54,920
Do what you need to do.

519
00:31:55,000 --> 00:31:56,920
As soon as the tabulations are over with,

520
00:31:56,940 --> 00:31:58,740
you'll know that telling anyone about that

521
00:31:58,760 --> 00:32:00,420
does neither one of us any good.

522
00:32:01,060 --> 00:32:02,500
In fact, you'll realize

523
00:32:02,500 --> 00:32:04,140
that the only thing to do in your position

524
00:32:04,180 --> 00:32:07,480
when it comes to me is nothing.

525
00:34:10,680 --> 00:34:13,140
Good evening, Mr. Wellick. I'm Detective Quattlander.

526
00:34:13,220 --> 00:34:14,840
This is Detective Jones.

527
00:34:15,220 --> 00:34:16,760
As I know you're aware,

528
00:34:16,800 --> 00:34:19,380
we were hoping to speak with you at your office today,

529
00:34:19,400 --> 00:34:21,820
but your assistant said you're out.

530
00:34:21,820 --> 00:34:22,860
What's this about?

531
00:34:23,060 --> 00:34:24,640
We're investigating a murder

532
00:34:24,660 --> 00:34:27,440
that occurred at your husband's place of employment, ma'am.

533
00:34:27,880 --> 00:34:29,360
May we please come in?

534
00:34:29,380 --> 00:34:30,340
A murder?

535
00:34:31,860 --> 00:34:34,480
Ma'am, do you mind speaking in English, please?

536
00:34:34,540 --> 00:34:35,940
I think this is inappropriate,

537
00:34:35,960 --> 00:34:38,160
you coming to my house like this, upsetting my wife.

538
00:34:38,180 --> 00:34:39,720
I will be in my office tomorrow--

539
00:34:39,740 --> 00:34:42,520
Mr. Wellick, as you can imagine this is very time sensitive.

540
00:34:42,540 --> 00:34:44,640
We just need to ask you a few questions.

541
00:34:44,660 --> 00:34:47,360
Actually, both of you, since you were both

542
00:34:47,400 --> 00:34:49,760
in attendance at the reception last night.

543
00:34:49,860 --> 00:34:53,140
Yeah, I can assure you, we have no information whatsoever.

544
00:34:53,160 --> 00:34:54,480
It will only take a moment.

545
00:34:55,300 --> 00:34:58,600
And you both did know the deceased, Sharon Knowles.

546
00:34:59,440 --> 00:35:01,060
You did know her, yes?

547
00:35:01,320 --> 00:35:02,560
Sharon Knowles?

548
00:35:05,480 --> 00:35:07,660
That's terrible.

549
00:35:07,700 --> 00:35:08,440
Um...

550
00:35:08,600 --> 00:35:11,180
Yes, yes, we did know her.

551
00:35:11,320 --> 00:35:13,040
Please, come in.

552
00:35:23,240 --> 00:35:25,060
Have a seat. Can I get you anything?

553
00:35:25,100 --> 00:35:26,420
Coffee? Tea?

554
00:35:26,460 --> 00:35:27,540
Coffee would be great.

555
00:35:27,840 --> 00:35:30,960
Tea. Herbal if possible, please.

556
00:35:35,100 --> 00:35:39,060
Mr. Wellick, what time did you last see

557
00:35:39,080 --> 00:35:41,900
Sharon Knowles last night?

558
00:35:44,040 --> 00:35:45,580
Mr. Wellick?

559
00:35:46,540 --> 00:35:48,550
Are you okay?

560
00:35:51,300 --> 00:35:53,160
Joanna?

561
00:35:57,960 --> 00:35:59,300
I think the baby's coming.

562
00:35:59,320 --> 00:36:01,360
We gotta get her to the hospital.

563
00:36:22,090 --> 00:36:24,620
How'd it go with the climate control hack?

564
00:36:26,540 --> 00:36:28,440
Handled.

565
00:36:28,600 --> 00:36:30,980
I happen to be really smart and good at things.

566
00:36:31,120 --> 00:36:33,290
Not like you give a shit.

567
00:36:44,100 --> 00:36:46,970
We should celebrate then.

568
00:36:54,950 --> 00:36:59,500
In 43 hours, exactly,

569
00:36:59,760 --> 00:37:02,740
our server will no longer be a honeypot.

570
00:37:04,020 --> 00:37:05,860
And that rootkit you wrote

571
00:37:06,780 --> 00:37:09,180
will take down Evil Corp.

572
00:37:10,340 --> 00:37:12,460
We did it, Darlene.

573
00:37:12,860 --> 00:37:14,800
It's gonna happen.

574
00:37:17,540 --> 00:37:20,220
We're really doing this?

575
00:37:30,050 --> 00:37:31,950
Oh, my God!

576
00:37:34,750 --> 00:37:36,790
Be happy!

577
00:37:36,820 --> 00:37:38,700
You did this.

578
00:37:39,000 --> 00:37:40,930
You did it.

579
00:37:40,960 --> 00:37:42,260
Just like that, Elliot,

580
00:37:42,290 --> 00:37:44,080
you're gonna change the world.

581
00:37:46,330 --> 00:37:47,930
We did this.

582
00:37:47,970 --> 00:37:51,760
I would love to take credit on this one.

583
00:37:51,820 --> 00:37:54,020
But I can't.

584
00:37:54,710 --> 00:37:57,040
No, really, this was you.

585
00:37:59,620 --> 00:38:03,810
You are seriously the best person I know,

586
00:38:03,850 --> 00:38:05,500
you know that?

587
00:38:10,190 --> 00:38:12,620
I love you so much.

588
00:38:17,640 --> 00:38:20,560
Oh, my God, Elliot! What the f---?

589
00:38:21,970 --> 00:38:23,070
I'm--I'm sorry.

590
00:38:23,100 --> 00:38:26,140
What the hell is wrong with you?

591
00:38:26,170 --> 00:38:27,610
I'm sorry.

592
00:38:27,640 --> 00:38:29,240
I'm sorry, I thought--

593
00:38:29,270 --> 00:38:30,980
I just--

594
00:38:31,010 --> 00:38:32,340
I'm sorry.

595
00:38:33,880 --> 00:38:36,180
Oh, my God, Elliot.

596
00:38:36,210 --> 00:38:39,720
Did you forget again?

597
00:38:39,750 --> 00:38:42,720
Did you forget who I am?

598
00:38:45,090 --> 00:38:47,020
What do you mean?

599
00:38:47,630 --> 00:38:48,990
Forget what?

600
00:38:51,100 --> 00:38:54,700
Elliot, I need you to tell me who you think I am.

601
00:38:56,230 --> 00:38:58,100
What are you talking about?

602
00:38:58,140 --> 00:39:00,570
Tell me right now.

603
00:39:05,140 --> 00:39:07,110
What are you saying?

604
00:39:07,150 --> 00:39:09,980
Elliot.

605
00:39:12,250 --> 00:39:17,120
Of course I didn't-- didn't forget.

606
00:39:17,160 --> 00:39:19,700
You're Darlene.

607
00:39:24,700 --> 00:39:27,720
You're Darlene.

608
00:39:28,100 --> 00:39:30,000
Elliot.

609
00:39:31,380 --> 00:39:33,880
You're Darlene.

610
00:39:39,710 --> 00:39:40,950
I know.

611
00:39:40,980 --> 00:39:42,680
I know what she's going to say.

612
00:39:42,710 --> 00:39:43,680
I'm your...

613
00:39:43,720 --> 00:39:46,150
Sister.

614
00:39:49,750 --> 00:39:52,620
You're my sister.

615
00:40:14,510 --> 00:40:16,940
Darlene and I'd hide in movie theaters all day.

616
00:40:16,980 --> 00:40:18,140
Darlene would sing

617
00:40:18,220 --> 00:40:19,880
She rode her scooter in front of our house.

618
00:40:19,920 --> 00:40:21,450
I'm crazy.I'm crazy--crazy.

619
00:40:21,490 --> 00:40:22,990
She tried to run away in the third grade.

620
00:40:23,020 --> 00:40:24,660
How come I didn't remember this?

621
00:40:24,690 --> 00:40:26,760
Slept in the same bed when our mom was mean to us.

622
00:40:26,790 --> 00:40:28,490
Why did I forget? I remember her voice.

623
00:40:28,530 --> 00:40:30,130
How could I forget? I'm crazy.

624
00:40:30,160 --> 00:40:33,700
I'm crazy--crazy-- I'm crazy--crazy--I'm crazy.

625
00:40:33,730 --> 00:40:35,130
Are you freaking out?

626
00:40:35,170 --> 00:40:36,870
Tell me the truth.

627
00:40:36,900 --> 00:40:38,840
Were you in on this the whole time?

628
00:40:38,870 --> 00:40:41,070
Were you?

629
00:40:43,240 --> 00:40:44,680
Think, God damn it. Think.

630
00:40:44,710 --> 00:40:46,180
How can I just forget her like that?

631
00:40:46,210 --> 00:40:48,150
A whole person. A relationship.

632
00:40:48,180 --> 00:40:49,550
Is this amnesia?

633
00:40:49,580 --> 00:40:50,610
What else am I not remembering?

634
00:40:50,650 --> 00:40:51,600
I'm crazy.

635
00:40:51,640 --> 00:40:53,150
I should have stayed on the meds.

636
00:40:53,180 --> 00:40:54,690
I'm crazy.I'm out of my mind.

637
00:40:54,720 --> 00:40:56,720
I knew it, I should have never created you.

638
00:40:56,760 --> 00:40:58,960
I should have listened to Krista.

639
00:41:02,830 --> 00:41:05,130
I avoid myself.

640
00:41:05,160 --> 00:41:06,530
Why?

641
00:41:06,560 --> 00:41:08,170
I'm afraid.

642
00:41:08,200 --> 00:41:09,230
Okay.

643
00:41:09,270 --> 00:41:10,730
Afraid of what?

644
00:41:10,770 --> 00:41:12,540
Finding too much.

645
00:41:12,570 --> 00:41:14,610
Too little. Nothing at all.

646
00:41:14,640 --> 00:41:16,670
Do I even exist?

647
00:41:16,710 --> 00:41:20,210
See me, Elliot Alderson.

648
00:41:20,250 --> 00:41:21,810
I am here.

649
00:41:25,050 --> 00:41:27,990
Now I'm gone.

650
00:41:41,830 --> 00:41:43,970
We have to hack...

651
00:41:44,000 --> 00:41:46,000
me.

652
00:42:08,890 --> 00:42:11,200
Nothing.

653
00:42:11,230 --> 00:42:13,000
No identity.

654
00:42:13,030 --> 00:42:16,170
I'm a ghost.

655
00:42:28,560 --> 00:42:31,180
Did I erase myself?

656
00:44:25,160 --> 00:44:27,660
I think we should talk.

