3
00:00:00,310 --> 00:00:03,450
So, what do we got?

4
00:00:03,610 --> 00:00:06,100
Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of

5
00:00:06,120 --> 00:00:08,830
Washington Township toxic waste scandal.

6
00:00:08,850 --> 00:00:11,210
What do we need to prove our case?

7
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:12,770
Someone who was there

8
00:00:12,790 --> 00:00:16,520
when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.

9
00:00:16,540 --> 00:00:17,900
Get the hell away from my home.

10
00:00:17,920 --> 00:00:19,090
Get away from my home.

11
00:00:19,110 --> 00:00:21,210
Elliot, what is going on with you.

12
00:00:21,230 --> 00:00:23,860
I cannot help you if you keep me in the dark.

13
00:00:23,880 --> 00:00:25,280
We got problems.

14
00:00:25,310 --> 00:00:27,160
The Dark Army is bailing.

15
00:00:27,180 --> 00:00:28,210
It's not over.

16
00:00:28,280 --> 00:00:30,360
We'll find a way, just not tonight.

17
00:00:30,380 --> 00:00:33,150
How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?

18
00:00:33,170 --> 00:00:34,800
You want to watch me piss too?

19
00:00:34,820 --> 00:00:35,920
Scott, a misunderstand--

20
00:00:35,940 --> 00:00:38,450
Happy to pull my dick out for you,

21
00:00:38,820 --> 00:00:39,620
Elliot!

22
00:00:40,040 --> 00:00:40,850
Where is she?

23
00:00:40,870 --> 00:00:42,820
Told you you'd get her back, bro.

24
00:01:50,990 --> 00:01:51,990
Shit!

25
00:02:04,110 --> 00:02:05,150
Shit!

26
00:02:09,560 --> 00:02:10,890
Open up!

27
00:02:11,350 --> 00:02:13,360
I'm bleeding all over the hallway!

28
00:02:15,090 --> 00:02:17,870
It's a life-or-death situation out here!

29
00:02:18,420 --> 00:02:20,420
Look, I know you're in there. I just saw you go in.

30
00:02:20,450 --> 00:02:22,080
Open up!

31
00:02:24,040 --> 00:02:24,850
I'm lo--

32
00:02:27,600 --> 00:02:29,260
Well, are you just gonna stand there?

33
00:02:29,840 --> 00:02:31,460
Get me a glass of water, dummy.

34
00:02:32,490 --> 00:02:34,790
Can I use this? Thanks.

35
00:02:37,310 --> 00:02:38,730
My niece gave him to me.

36
00:02:39,140 --> 00:02:41,230
I haven't even named him yet. God.

37
00:02:41,250 --> 00:02:44,080
Do you know the pressure of an ecstatic six-year-old?

38
00:02:44,200 --> 00:02:48,220
I mean, I kill that thing, and her whole world collapses.

39
00:02:48,240 --> 00:02:49,910
I like what you did with the place.

40
00:02:53,150 --> 00:02:56,020
Yeah, nice setup. Still like mine better though.

41
00:03:08,940 --> 00:03:11,190
Yo, let me know if you want a top-shelf hookup.

42
00:03:12,490 --> 00:03:14,000
Actually, now that I have you...

43
00:03:14,840 --> 00:03:18,750
Will you help me move a dresser...Mr. Muscles?

44
00:03:19,670 --> 00:03:21,380
Okay, come on. Just come on.

45
00:03:33,000 --> 00:03:35,730
Man 'n' van is getting way too legit.

46
00:03:36,270 --> 00:03:37,550
They used to just be, like, drummers

47
00:03:37,570 --> 00:03:38,970
with their mom's Honda Odysseys.

48
00:03:38,990 --> 00:03:41,500
Now it's an actual company in Queens.

49
00:03:41,520 --> 00:03:44,790
I mean, the guys are literally men in vans.

50
00:03:44,810 --> 00:03:46,890
I'd buy morphine from you,

51
00:03:47,310 --> 00:03:49,570
if you could also get me suboxone.

52
00:03:51,640 --> 00:03:55,550
Well, um, it's pretty much impossible to get suboxone.

53
00:03:55,580 --> 00:03:57,090
My supplier doesn't have it.

54
00:04:02,460 --> 00:04:05,450
I saw this song live once. It was so rad.

55
00:04:05,470 --> 00:04:07,910
Don't you just love hearing your favorite songs in person,

56
00:04:07,930 --> 00:04:10,450
like, half deaf from the speakers,

57
00:04:10,470 --> 00:04:12,470
everyone going nuts around you?

58
00:04:12,490 --> 00:04:13,350
No.

59
00:04:15,270 --> 00:04:16,880
Direct. I respect that.

60
00:04:19,490 --> 00:04:21,290
I just hate concerts.

61
00:04:22,940 --> 00:04:24,140
Lots of people.

62
00:04:29,350 --> 00:04:30,920
You don't like people, huh?

63
00:04:31,910 --> 00:04:33,640
Not most of them, no.

64
00:04:35,940 --> 00:04:36,820
Okay.

65
00:04:37,370 --> 00:04:39,060
Well, so by that rationale,

66
00:04:39,380 --> 00:04:42,120
if you were to really like one person, it'd be, like,

67
00:04:42,540 --> 00:04:46,480
considered an aberration or an abnormality

68
00:04:46,500 --> 00:04:48,670
or special, even.

69
00:04:50,550 --> 00:04:51,470
I guess.

70
00:04:52,680 --> 00:04:54,670
Well, I aim for special,

71
00:04:54,700 --> 00:04:56,790
so challenge accepted.

72
00:05:04,170 --> 00:05:07,900
I wish we already knew each other.

73
00:05:09,590 --> 00:05:11,850
Would make this feel less awkward.

74
00:05:13,780 --> 00:05:15,960
You really feel awkward right now?

75
00:05:18,640 --> 00:05:19,350
Yeah.

76
00:05:22,270 --> 00:05:24,320
Well, then I wish we knew each other too then.

77
00:05:30,150 --> 00:05:31,460
Oh, yikes.

78
00:05:31,480 --> 00:05:34,850
I, um, I'm late. Meeting the girls for drinks.

79
00:05:36,310 --> 00:05:38,230
Oh, um, I'm Shayla.

80
00:05:43,260 --> 00:05:44,110
Elliot.

81
00:05:48,620 --> 00:05:51,880
You know, I do know of a guy who sells Suboxone.

82
00:05:52,070 --> 00:05:53,230
He's supposed to be a fucking psychopath,

83
00:05:53,250 --> 00:05:54,880
but if you want, I can call him.

84
00:05:55,280 --> 00:05:56,780
You might be worth a psychopath.

85
00:05:56,800 --> 00:05:58,200
I don't know. Maybe.

86
00:05:59,400 --> 00:06:02,470
Oh, and keep the fish, you filthy animal.

87
00:06:24,440 --> 00:06:26,620
Sorry I haven't talked to you in a while.

88
00:06:27,270 --> 00:06:29,770
I mean, it's only been a month, which I guess

89
00:06:29,790 --> 00:06:32,450
in the grand scheme of things isn't that long.

90
00:06:33,850 --> 00:06:35,250
Isn't our life like a blip

91
00:06:35,270 --> 00:06:37,540
in the cosmic calender or something?

92
00:06:40,450 --> 00:06:41,760
So that's Shayla.

93
00:06:42,210 --> 00:06:43,000
A blip.

94
00:06:43,920 --> 00:06:44,870
Not even.

95
00:06:45,650 --> 00:06:47,770
Here one blip, gone the next.

96
00:06:48,100 --> 00:06:50,470
Makes me hate myself that I've already gotten used to

97
00:06:50,490 --> 00:06:52,600
the idea of her not being here.

98
00:06:53,430 --> 00:06:55,360
In a year, I'll maybe think about her

99
00:06:55,380 --> 00:06:56,860
every once in a while.

100
00:06:57,150 --> 00:07:00,460
Then she'll become an anecdote, a thing to say.

101
00:07:00,850 --> 00:07:02,600
"I knew a girl that died,"

102
00:07:03,150 --> 00:07:06,240
with the added bonus of, "She died because of me."

103
00:07:08,070 --> 00:07:10,150
Maybe I should hate myself.

104
00:07:10,250 --> 00:07:12,600
Here are the last two forms.

105
00:07:12,700 --> 00:07:14,060
She's getting rid of me,

106
00:07:14,240 --> 00:07:16,370
in case you're still trying to figure that out.

107
00:07:16,460 --> 00:07:18,100
- Once I... - Sign on the bottom.

108
00:07:23,130 --> 00:07:24,110
Then I'll deliver it to the court,

109
00:07:24,130 --> 00:07:25,630
and in two weeks' time, you'll receive

110
00:07:25,650 --> 00:07:28,390
an official release from the mandate.

111
00:07:29,270 --> 00:07:32,080
That second form means that we've been sitting in this room for a year.

112
00:07:32,100 --> 00:07:35,900
Over 52 hours of Krista's voice bouncing around this room.

113
00:07:36,190 --> 00:07:39,740
She thinks she's a wasted echo. Maybe she is.

114
00:07:40,030 --> 00:07:41,600
I wonder how much time I've spent

115
00:07:41,620 --> 00:07:43,500
not listening to her in here.

116
00:07:43,710 --> 00:07:44,740
I'm worried about you, Elliot.

117
00:07:44,760 --> 00:07:46,150
I really want you to keep coming here.

118
00:07:46,170 --> 00:07:47,670
We've got a lot more work to do.

119
00:07:47,690 --> 00:07:48,980
She wants more from me

120
00:07:49,000 --> 00:07:50,640
but she doesn't believe in me.

121
00:07:50,660 --> 00:07:53,700
I tried because I believe some part inside of you

122
00:07:53,920 --> 00:07:55,800
wants to do this right.

123
00:07:56,120 --> 00:07:56,890
You?

124
00:07:57,560 --> 00:07:59,040
Are you on her side?

125
00:08:22,310 --> 00:08:24,140
You should clean your sockets.

126
00:08:36,480 --> 00:08:39,480
Sounds too good to be true, but I'll bite.

127
00:08:40,060 --> 00:08:41,150
What's the ask?

128
00:08:41,640 --> 00:08:43,040
Given my client has information

129
00:08:43,060 --> 00:08:45,080
that could help your client's case,

130
00:08:45,160 --> 00:08:48,210
we want the meeting restricted to her, Colby, and myself,

131
00:08:48,440 --> 00:08:50,320
And we want it conducted off-record.

132
00:08:51,710 --> 00:08:52,890
Antara, come on.

133
00:08:53,480 --> 00:08:55,360
My client won't accept your presence.

134
00:08:56,170 --> 00:08:57,680
Our client pays for ours.

135
00:08:57,700 --> 00:08:59,400
Then you're duty-bound to present him

136
00:08:59,420 --> 00:09:02,500
with any legitimate offer of beneficial evidence.

137
00:09:03,370 --> 00:09:04,310
Of course.

138
00:09:04,880 --> 00:09:08,010
Give us something truly legitimate and beneficial.

139
00:09:09,330 --> 00:09:11,700
You won't even tell us what the hell your client has.

140
00:09:12,010 --> 00:09:14,960
Seth, we've been sitting on opposite sides

141
00:09:14,980 --> 00:09:17,520
of the negotiating table for two decades.

142
00:09:17,550 --> 00:09:19,020
I'm not some joker come out of the woodwork

143
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:20,920
trying to scam Colby for millions.

144
00:09:20,940 --> 00:09:23,330
I'm giving him the only glimmer of hope he's had.

145
00:09:26,100 --> 00:09:29,280
We'll pass along your offer. Thanks for your time.

146
00:09:46,960 --> 00:09:48,620
Lloyd said you wanted to see me.

147
00:09:54,330 --> 00:09:57,430
Look, I appreciate your commitment to this job.

148
00:09:57,680 --> 00:09:58,720
I really do.

149
00:10:01,300 --> 00:10:03,440
But I don't see how you've plowed through

150
00:10:03,870 --> 00:10:05,610
these last few weeks, so

151
00:10:05,670 --> 00:10:07,810
I want to offer you some time off.

152
00:10:08,560 --> 00:10:10,090
- Just some time to... - I don't need time off.

153
00:10:10,110 --> 00:10:10,960
I'm good.

154
00:10:16,480 --> 00:10:19,060
Uh...Uh, one more thing.

155
00:10:25,630 --> 00:10:28,340
I'm so sorry she was taken away, Elliot,

156
00:10:28,420 --> 00:10:33,180
but don't let her death close you off entirely.

157
00:10:33,890 --> 00:10:37,310
Find someone you can be your honest self with,

158
00:10:38,570 --> 00:10:39,440
okay?

159
00:10:40,500 --> 00:10:42,740
I remember when I was a kid, I got into web design

160
00:10:42,770 --> 00:10:45,090
by ripping off sites I liked.

161
00:10:45,160 --> 00:10:47,250
All you had to do was view source on your browser

162
00:10:47,270 --> 00:10:49,550
and there it was, the code.

163
00:10:49,930 --> 00:10:52,960
You could copy-paste it, modify it a little,

164
00:10:53,120 --> 00:10:57,730
Put your name on it, and like that, it was your site.

165
00:10:59,160 --> 00:11:00,360
View source.

166
00:11:00,810 --> 00:11:02,640
What if we had that for people?

167
00:11:04,130 --> 00:11:05,880
Would people really want to see?

168
00:11:17,990 --> 00:11:20,670
Find someone to be your honest self with?

169
00:11:21,760 --> 00:11:22,910
Bullshit.

170
00:11:26,920 --> 00:11:29,530
Really good advice. Thanks.

171
00:11:33,600 --> 00:11:37,350
I quote, "The U.S. contingent of the hacker group fsociety

172
00:11:37,370 --> 00:11:39,070
has remained quiet since the upheaval inflicted

173
00:11:39,090 --> 00:11:41,650
upon the world's largest multinational conglomerate.

174
00:11:41,670 --> 00:11:44,120
Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson

175
00:11:44,140 --> 00:11:46,130
released a statement today stating that,

176
00:11:46,150 --> 00:11:49,090
'these groups lack the resources and knowledge

177
00:11:49,110 --> 00:11:52,400
of the U.S. cell to successfully mount an attack.'"

178
00:11:52,420 --> 00:11:53,840
End quote.

179
00:11:55,390 --> 00:11:56,850
Yeah, so?

180
00:11:57,800 --> 00:11:59,700
We gotta get the Dark Army back.

181
00:12:00,420 --> 00:12:03,200
Dude, I've been trying.

182
00:12:03,790 --> 00:12:06,370
How many times do you want me to hack him?

183
00:12:06,390 --> 00:12:08,870
Do you know how hard hacking a hacker is?

184
00:12:08,890 --> 00:12:11,010
Cisco switches OSes, like, all the time.

185
00:12:11,030 --> 00:12:13,040
Darlene, we need one meeting.

186
00:12:13,060 --> 00:12:15,460
Yeah, well, I've been using Cisco's handle

187
00:12:15,480 --> 00:12:18,030
to send requests for the past month.

188
00:12:18,410 --> 00:12:19,770
I got nothing.

189
00:12:20,570 --> 00:12:23,000
He's slower than me, but not by much.

190
00:12:23,320 --> 00:12:25,000
If we can talk to WhiteRose directly...

191
00:12:25,020 --> 00:12:27,760
WhiteRose? WhiteRose?

192
00:12:27,780 --> 00:12:28,680
Really?

193
00:12:30,480 --> 00:12:34,200
Okay, if--if the guy even exists,

194
00:12:34,220 --> 00:12:36,920
and that's a big if,

195
00:12:36,940 --> 00:12:39,380
no way he's meeting you face-to-face.

196
00:12:39,940 --> 00:12:41,050
For all we know...

197
00:12:42,390 --> 00:12:44,420
This dude's WhiteRose.

198
00:12:45,260 --> 00:12:46,560
Excuse me!

199
00:12:47,350 --> 00:12:49,540
Are you WhiteRose?

200
00:12:52,280 --> 00:12:53,760
A likely story.

201
00:12:55,740 --> 00:12:58,650
'sides, the tape backups already shipped

202
00:12:58,670 --> 00:13:00,720
to all the new Steel Mountain facilities,

203
00:13:00,740 --> 00:13:03,380
and we still haven't found a way around that.

204
00:13:05,210 --> 00:13:06,860
I got a plan in motion.

205
00:13:08,640 --> 00:13:10,240
And god's laughing.

206
00:13:31,370 --> 00:13:33,490
This is all I have left of her.

207
00:13:39,900 --> 00:13:41,310
I will miss her.

208
00:13:51,210 --> 00:13:52,670
I need to wipe again.

209
00:14:16,490 --> 00:14:18,270
So if you scroll to the next page,

210
00:14:18,290 --> 00:14:20,150
you'll see the summary of capital budgets

211
00:14:20,170 --> 00:14:22,380
for purchasing and operations.

212
00:14:22,400 --> 00:14:23,870
We get it. The goddamn earning reports

213
00:14:23,900 --> 00:14:25,550
are gonna look good come monday.

214
00:14:25,750 --> 00:14:27,520
Our aim is to facilitate bill payment

215
00:14:27,540 --> 00:14:29,180
and heighten financial security,

216
00:14:29,200 --> 00:14:31,080
so that's an extra 2%.

217
00:14:31,100 --> 00:14:32,600
You know, if we hadn't turned our profits around,

218
00:14:32,630 --> 00:14:34,770
- I was gonna leave. - No way.

219
00:14:35,100 --> 00:14:37,030
Where? Don't tell me apple.

220
00:14:37,120 --> 00:14:39,160
- Google. - Don't buy it.

221
00:14:39,180 --> 00:14:41,120
I got a blow job from the hiring executive

222
00:14:41,140 --> 00:14:43,370
on the Googleplex volleyball court.

223
00:14:43,500 --> 00:14:47,730
Oh, she was hot. Had a Marissa Mayer thing going on, too.

224
00:14:49,880 --> 00:14:51,410
Hot execs started as hot assistants

225
00:14:51,430 --> 00:14:53,140
who fucked their way to the top

226
00:14:53,170 --> 00:14:55,130
twice as fast as the rest of us.

227
00:14:55,150 --> 00:14:56,850
You know something screwed up?

228
00:14:57,320 --> 00:14:59,640
I heard that, some assistants, they're going gay

229
00:14:59,660 --> 00:15:01,700
to move up the ladder.

230
00:15:01,640 --> 00:15:02,760
I'll do you one better.

231
00:15:02,770 --> 00:15:04,470
There's a special handful

232
00:15:04,490 --> 00:15:07,770
of pathetically desperate execs going cock jockey.

233
00:15:07,790 --> 00:15:10,010
No. Oh, my god!

234
00:15:10,510 --> 00:15:13,140
Hey, Dwight, I meant to ask. How are your children?

235
00:15:13,160 --> 00:15:15,530
Hell if I know. Sent 'em off to Lawrence.

236
00:15:15,550 --> 00:15:17,250
I think Julia likes art.

237
00:15:17,560 --> 00:15:19,430
Oh, well. Can't win 'em all.

238
00:15:19,760 --> 00:15:21,050
Lawrence?

239
00:15:21,430 --> 00:15:22,240
You'll never be able

240
00:15:22,260 --> 00:15:24,340
to afford that tuition on unemployment.

241
00:15:24,570 --> 00:15:26,590
- Sorry? - You're fired!

242
00:15:46,040 --> 00:15:47,280
You two as well.

243
00:15:48,150 --> 00:15:51,010
I'm making sure you all receive the minimum severance packages.

244
00:15:52,590 --> 00:15:55,230
Mr. Wellick, I-I don't understand.

245
00:15:56,490 --> 00:15:57,670
What did we do?

246
00:16:04,830 --> 00:16:05,820
Nothing.

247
00:16:09,400 --> 00:16:11,760
- After... - You said you would update me.

248
00:16:12,310 --> 00:16:13,950
I needed to discuss our situation

249
00:16:13,970 --> 00:16:15,380
with the state's attorney.

250
00:16:16,160 --> 00:16:17,510
Thanks for coming in, Roy.

251
00:16:24,110 --> 00:16:25,360
I think you should have a seat.

252
00:16:32,450 --> 00:16:34,510
Colby's lawyers called 30 minutes ago.

253
00:16:34,530 --> 00:16:37,220
They wanted a promise of total immunity before the meeting,

254
00:16:37,240 --> 00:16:39,550
which I obtained from the man you just met.

255
00:16:39,920 --> 00:16:42,820
So, yes, Colby agreed...

256
00:16:43,990 --> 00:16:45,170
with a caveat.

257
00:16:47,280 --> 00:16:50,430
I can't be in the room. You have to go in alone.

258
00:16:55,480 --> 00:16:59,530
Look, you made a ballsy move...

259
00:17:00,020 --> 00:17:01,770
But you doing what you're about to do...

260
00:17:02,450 --> 00:17:04,710
entering the home of a very powerful man

261
00:17:04,730 --> 00:17:07,400
with a lot at stake and asking him for something...

262
00:17:07,460 --> 00:17:09,780
That's always a dangerous proposition.

263
00:17:11,390 --> 00:17:13,830
So one last time...

264
00:17:14,860 --> 00:17:16,860
Are you sure you want to do this?

265
00:17:33,130 --> 00:17:34,540
Shit, man.

266
00:17:35,670 --> 00:17:37,160
Thought you was one of them high schoolers

267
00:17:37,180 --> 00:17:38,970
stole my mom's chaise lounge.

268
00:17:39,640 --> 00:17:41,450
As heartbreaking as it is to hear that,

269
00:17:41,470 --> 00:17:42,840
you're gonna have to put that off.

270
00:17:42,860 --> 00:17:44,010
Getting everybody back together.

271
00:17:44,030 --> 00:17:45,640
- Come on. - No, man, not this time.

272
00:17:45,660 --> 00:17:46,780
I'm out.

273
00:17:48,220 --> 00:17:50,100
You can't be out. We need you.

274
00:17:50,280 --> 00:17:53,070
Look, man, I got a new set of people depending on me, okay?

275
00:17:53,460 --> 00:17:54,610
Clients out the wazoo.

276
00:17:54,630 --> 00:17:56,640
So, you know, I mean, good luck,

277
00:17:56,670 --> 00:17:58,330
and tell the kids I said hi.

278
00:17:59,540 --> 00:18:01,070
What is this? What are you doing here?

279
00:18:01,400 --> 00:18:03,630
Well, I figured out how to insert

280
00:18:03,650 --> 00:18:06,980
THC's genetic information code into yeast cells.

281
00:18:07,300 --> 00:18:08,540
Tripled my earning speed.

282
00:18:08,970 --> 00:18:11,870
Plants need weeks to develop. Microbes need days.

283
00:18:12,450 --> 00:18:14,670
So, what, you got a bath and body works

284
00:18:14,690 --> 00:18:16,890
bottling facility in your backyard?

285
00:18:18,960 --> 00:18:20,110
Try it.

286
00:18:20,810 --> 00:18:23,230
The THC level is borderline in that blend,

287
00:18:23,250 --> 00:18:26,490
and the lavender doesn't mess with the high.

288
00:18:26,520 --> 00:18:28,150
You just smooth it on your skin.

289
00:18:28,330 --> 00:18:31,630
So you're rejecting a revolution in favor of aroma profiles?

290
00:18:31,750 --> 00:18:33,040
What a waste of potential.

291
00:18:33,510 --> 00:18:35,380
Look, man, I know I got a good brain.

292
00:18:35,880 --> 00:18:37,310
Besides...

293
00:18:38,830 --> 00:18:41,390
What was our little project in the end, anyway?

294
00:18:42,180 --> 00:18:44,120
Wasted shit, if you ask me.

295
00:18:45,610 --> 00:18:47,790
Well, now you're borderline pissing me off.

296
00:18:49,030 --> 00:18:50,080
Is that a fact?

297
00:18:52,810 --> 00:18:54,370
And what exactly are you gonna do

298
00:18:54,390 --> 00:18:56,460
if I decide to cross that border?

299
00:18:58,340 --> 00:18:59,860
Look at my face, Romero.

300
00:19:00,830 --> 00:19:02,470
You and I both know I'm crazy.

301
00:19:03,200 --> 00:19:04,790
Not the cute kind either.

302
00:19:04,870 --> 00:19:06,940
I'm talking crazy crazy!

303
00:19:12,330 --> 00:19:13,520
You lost touch.

304
00:19:14,000 --> 00:19:15,500
You forgot the feeling of spilling blood

305
00:19:15,520 --> 00:19:17,350
on the battlefield by winning the fight.

306
00:19:18,860 --> 00:19:20,450
I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.

307
00:19:21,240 --> 00:19:22,420
I love you, man.

308
00:19:23,270 --> 00:19:25,190
I just wanted you to come back to the arcade with me

309
00:19:25,300 --> 00:19:27,090
so we could change the world together.

310
00:19:28,950 --> 00:19:31,870
I am clearly too crazy for you to say no to.

311
00:19:39,420 --> 00:19:41,390
Look on your face is priceless!

312
00:19:43,400 --> 00:19:44,600
Goddamn lunatic.

313
00:19:46,100 --> 00:19:47,930
You gave me your word when we started this thing

314
00:19:47,950 --> 00:19:49,040
that you'd finish it.

315
00:19:49,060 --> 00:19:51,380
I gave you my word what I'd do if you didn't.

316
00:19:52,330 --> 00:19:53,980
See you back at the arcade.

317
00:20:10,880 --> 00:20:12,510
Good. I see the girl got you tea.

318
00:20:17,820 --> 00:20:19,350
Well, let's get started.

319
00:20:26,220 --> 00:20:27,370
How much do you want?

320
00:20:31,740 --> 00:20:32,830
Write your number.

321
00:20:35,070 --> 00:20:36,450
You can ask me anything you want,

322
00:20:37,660 --> 00:20:39,720
but I promise you, at the end of the day,

323
00:20:39,820 --> 00:20:42,890
money will always be better than what you're looking for.

324
00:20:46,510 --> 00:20:49,830
Mr. Colby, did you attend

325
00:20:49,860 --> 00:20:53,090
the executive board meetings during 1993?

326
00:20:57,220 --> 00:21:00,070
Were you in the room when the decision was made

327
00:21:00,090 --> 00:21:02,230
to ignore the treatment of hazardous waste

328
00:21:02,250 --> 00:21:03,700
in Washington Township?

329
00:21:10,980 --> 00:21:13,040
I have information which can help you...

330
00:21:13,710 --> 00:21:15,010
if you answer my question.

331
00:21:18,620 --> 00:21:19,850
I don't know what you're talking about.

332
00:21:22,810 --> 00:21:25,650
If you agree to testify against the executives

333
00:21:25,670 --> 00:21:28,720
who covered up the illegal dumping of expoxy resin waste,

334
00:21:30,120 --> 00:21:32,200
I will testify that I broke chain of custody

335
00:21:32,220 --> 00:21:34,710
with the dat file central to your case.

336
00:21:41,280 --> 00:21:42,310
You're that hot little thing

337
00:21:42,330 --> 00:21:44,050
that came by here a month ago.

338
00:21:44,430 --> 00:21:45,790
The girl from Allsafe.

339
00:21:50,550 --> 00:21:53,020
I remember, yeah.

340
00:21:57,740 --> 00:22:01,370
Okay...I'm gonna answer your question.

341
00:22:03,270 --> 00:22:05,000
But here's what I need from you first.

342
00:22:06,620 --> 00:22:08,210
So I'm gonna pull down my pants,

343
00:22:09,500 --> 00:22:12,480
and then I'm gonna need you to take that pouty mouth of yours

344
00:22:12,630 --> 00:22:14,380
and swallow up my balls.

345
00:22:14,880 --> 00:22:18,260
Now, they're big and hairy, especially the left one,

346
00:22:18,280 --> 00:22:20,500
so you're really gonna have to, I don't know,

347
00:22:20,520 --> 00:22:23,270
squish 'em up to get 'em inside there.

348
00:22:23,860 --> 00:22:26,320
You're probably gonna have to do one cheek at a time.

349
00:22:26,660 --> 00:22:31,290
But then, once they're all warm and snug in there,

350
00:22:31,590 --> 00:22:34,290
I want you to repeat your question to me

351
00:22:34,860 --> 00:22:36,470
as clearly as you can.

352
00:22:38,030 --> 00:22:40,710
Then, and only then, am I willing to answer.

353
00:22:46,340 --> 00:22:47,290
What do you say?

354
00:23:07,100 --> 00:23:08,800
If you don't take this deal...

355
00:23:11,140 --> 00:23:12,500
you'll become like me.

356
00:23:14,920 --> 00:23:17,750
Sure, maybe you'll live in this house...

357
00:23:19,560 --> 00:23:20,870
Maybe you'll have money,

358
00:23:22,380 --> 00:23:26,870
but even if your expensive lawyers find a way to get you off,

359
00:23:26,890 --> 00:23:28,440
people will still think that you're guilty.

360
00:23:35,400 --> 00:23:38,120
Losing everyone's respect...

361
00:23:43,310 --> 00:23:47,590
the respect of people you know and the people you don't...

362
00:23:52,330 --> 00:23:53,880
It's a shitty feeling.

363
00:23:57,060 --> 00:23:58,070
Trust me.

364
00:24:13,400 --> 00:24:15,590
I'll have "the girl" let me out.

365
00:24:24,000 --> 00:24:26,880
Flipper. Is she microchipped?

366
00:24:34,500 --> 00:24:36,900
Okay, very good.

367
00:24:38,350 --> 00:24:39,480
Housekeeping done.

368
00:24:39,720 --> 00:24:41,200
Now onto the real business.

369
00:24:42,980 --> 00:24:44,760
Has your dog ever eaten trash before?

370
00:24:45,110 --> 00:24:48,950
No. I mean, not that I remember.

371
00:24:49,130 --> 00:24:50,750
Well, lucky for your bank account,

372
00:24:50,770 --> 00:24:53,420
The piece is small enough to pass on its own.

373
00:24:53,520 --> 00:24:55,250
Unfortunately, though, it's large enough

374
00:24:55,270 --> 00:24:57,350
to send her puking all over your apartment.

375
00:24:57,560 --> 00:25:01,040
So I would crate her for a few days and monitor her.

376
00:25:01,440 --> 00:25:03,710
She won't know what you're doing is good for her.

377
00:25:19,400 --> 00:25:22,030
You were right. I was only trying to prove--

378
00:25:22,050 --> 00:25:24,440
Colby's lawyers just called. He wants to talk.

379
00:25:25,910 --> 00:25:26,990
Get back there.

380
00:25:39,180 --> 00:25:41,620
It's a little early in the morning to be nerding out,

381
00:25:41,880 --> 00:25:42,930
don't you think?

382
00:25:44,820 --> 00:25:45,840
How long?

383
00:25:53,040 --> 00:25:53,970
I knew if I asked you that--

384
00:25:53,990 --> 00:25:55,040
How long?

385
00:25:57,510 --> 00:25:58,650
Couple weeks.

386
00:26:01,670 --> 00:26:04,680
And you had the balls to ask for WhiteRose with my shit?

387
00:26:05,240 --> 00:26:07,090
It's like you want to get us both killed.

388
00:26:08,240 --> 00:26:09,680
What happened? He responded?

389
00:26:12,820 --> 00:26:13,910
You know,

390
00:26:15,260 --> 00:26:17,880
you didn't have to make me look like a shitty foot soldier.

391
00:26:18,190 --> 00:26:19,350
Nobody would ever even know--

392
00:26:19,370 --> 00:26:21,560
You got root on my box and found the IP,

393
00:26:21,580 --> 00:26:24,600
then you joined their channel with my handle.

394
00:26:30,670 --> 00:26:31,830
We're so done.

395
00:26:34,390 --> 00:26:35,640
I don't want to see you again.

396
00:26:42,730 --> 00:26:44,690
But you fools actually got your wish.

397
00:26:46,830 --> 00:26:47,320
I don't know why,

398
00:26:47,340 --> 00:26:48,990
but the meeting's actually gonna be on.

399
00:26:49,780 --> 00:26:50,880
I'd tell you to be careful,

400
00:26:50,900 --> 00:26:53,620
but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.

401
00:27:09,900 --> 00:27:11,720
My lawyers are looking over the paperwork.

402
00:27:14,900 --> 00:27:17,270
- Does that mean that-- - exactly what I said.

403
00:27:18,550 --> 00:27:21,670
I asked you back here to make sure that you can pull off your testimony,

404
00:27:21,690 --> 00:27:24,840
make sure that this chain of custody, story of yours is straight.

405
00:27:24,860 --> 00:27:26,230
I can't afford any trips.

406
00:27:28,110 --> 00:27:29,620
I'm not going to trip.

407
00:27:33,780 --> 00:27:34,880
So, what--

408
00:27:35,950 --> 00:27:37,410
What's in this for you, anyway?

409
00:27:37,860 --> 00:27:39,440
I know you hate me.

410
00:27:40,830 --> 00:27:43,240
So, what, you're gonna just let me off scot-free?

411
00:27:43,280 --> 00:27:44,310
What do you get out of this?

412
00:27:47,570 --> 00:27:49,570
Earlier, I asked you a question.

413
00:27:51,080 --> 00:27:52,320
You never answered it.

414
00:27:54,270 --> 00:27:58,140
If I'm agreeing to testify in your case, then,

415
00:27:59,120 --> 00:28:02,240
yes, you know, I attended several meetings.

416
00:28:02,270 --> 00:28:05,280
Tell me about the one when they decided to ignore the leak.

417
00:28:07,410 --> 00:28:09,250
I'm--I'm not sure what you're asking.

418
00:28:09,270 --> 00:28:13,140
What was the meeting like when you decided this?

419
00:28:15,820 --> 00:28:16,870
I get it.

420
00:28:18,290 --> 00:28:21,020
You want to know, like, what was it like?

421
00:28:21,290 --> 00:28:25,300
Like, um, did we all have cigars and laugh hysterically

422
00:28:25,320 --> 00:28:27,240
as we signed the evil documents?

423
00:28:27,620 --> 00:28:28,810
Is that what you pictured?

424
00:28:29,390 --> 00:28:30,470
Well, I'm sorry, hon.

425
00:28:30,490 --> 00:28:32,490
See, the world doesn't work like that.

426
00:28:33,310 --> 00:28:37,110
Tell me. Tell me how it works.

427
00:28:40,770 --> 00:28:44,360
Uh, Jesus, um...All right, all right.

428
00:28:44,380 --> 00:28:48,490
Let's see. January, '93.

429
00:28:49,400 --> 00:28:51,710
Well, my secretary then was Elaine.

430
00:28:52,090 --> 00:28:54,480
So Elaine brought us a platter of shrimp cocktail

431
00:28:54,500 --> 00:28:57,920
to tide us to dinner, which pissed us off

432
00:28:58,720 --> 00:29:00,980
because we just had a platter at the holiday party.

433
00:29:02,180 --> 00:29:03,430
Jim opened the bar.

434
00:29:03,460 --> 00:29:05,870
Now Jim was a real piece of work.

435
00:29:06,180 --> 00:29:08,540
I mean, half pansy, half Mafia.

436
00:29:08,660 --> 00:29:11,520
First sign of a tight decision, he'd be chain smoking

437
00:29:11,940 --> 00:29:13,380
down a river of Scotch.

438
00:29:18,200 --> 00:29:19,620
You know, it rained.

439
00:29:19,790 --> 00:29:21,410
It rained. I remember that, yeah.

440
00:29:26,890 --> 00:29:28,230
So...

441
00:29:29,270 --> 00:29:33,320
You were drunk, eating shrimp cockail,

442
00:29:34,900 --> 00:29:37,810
and it was raining when you decided my mother would die?

443
00:29:46,650 --> 00:29:47,870
That's why.

444
00:29:49,860 --> 00:29:52,820
So people like you won't keep sitting in rooms together.

445
00:30:01,270 --> 00:30:04,370
Did any of it ever give you or anyone pause

446
00:30:05,940 --> 00:30:07,640
when you made those decisions?

447
00:30:11,290 --> 00:30:11,930
Yeah.

448
00:30:14,480 --> 00:30:16,570
Yeah, sure.

449
00:30:19,680 --> 00:30:20,800
But, um...

450
00:30:23,790 --> 00:30:27,530
then you go home, and, uh, and you have dinner,

451
00:30:28,270 --> 00:30:31,640
you know, and--and you wake up the next morning.

452
00:30:40,610 --> 00:30:43,980
Here's to a man who has a bright future at our company,

453
00:30:44,180 --> 00:30:45,350
a man you all know,

454
00:30:46,530 --> 00:30:50,210
a man who is going to change this company for the good,

455
00:30:51,330 --> 00:30:55,400
a man smart enough to marry a woman every bit his equal...

456
00:30:56,870 --> 00:31:01,640
Our new Chief Technology Officer, Scott Knowles.

457
00:31:01,790 --> 00:31:03,000
Here, here!

458
00:31:03,600 --> 00:31:05,260
Thank you. Thank you.

459
00:31:05,280 --> 00:31:06,830
- Thank you, Phillip. - Welcome.

460
00:31:06,850 --> 00:31:08,000
- Thank you very much. - Here we go.

461
00:31:08,020 --> 00:31:09,800
It's great to be here. And we're off.

462
00:31:09,970 --> 00:31:11,530
- Thanks, Phillip. - You're very welcome.

463
00:31:11,550 --> 00:31:13,160
- Congratulations, darling. - Thank you, thank you.

464
00:31:16,720 --> 00:31:18,660
Hey, Joe, how are you?

465
00:31:39,350 --> 00:31:39,990
Thank you.

466
00:31:46,900 --> 00:31:49,130
Tyrell, nice to see you.

467
00:31:49,230 --> 00:31:50,020
Is it?

468
00:31:50,480 --> 00:31:52,640
I hear you shared our moment with your husband.

469
00:31:54,100 --> 00:31:56,060
Oh, come on. That was over a month ago.

470
00:31:56,200 --> 00:31:57,660
Don't tell me you're still sore.

471
00:31:59,180 --> 00:32:01,270
Hmm, I sense some defeat.

472
00:32:09,560 --> 00:32:13,280
Well, I considered myself, at the very least, reprimanded.

473
00:32:14,590 --> 00:32:15,760
How disappointing.

474
00:32:16,240 --> 00:32:18,040
One tiny curveball and you gave up.

475
00:32:18,790 --> 00:32:19,490
Miss.

476
00:32:19,940 --> 00:32:20,670
Thank you.

477
00:32:22,320 --> 00:32:25,580
Should have known that you were nothing more than a bold entrance.

478
00:32:26,580 --> 00:32:28,930
Are you saying you don't crave a bold entrance

479
00:32:28,950 --> 00:32:32,490
every time, over and over, sustained?

480
00:32:33,360 --> 00:32:34,370
Meet me tonight.

481
00:32:35,450 --> 00:32:36,540
I'm a little busy.

482
00:32:37,160 --> 00:32:38,520
Come to my office now.

483
00:32:38,540 --> 00:32:40,140
Are you really asking me that?

484
00:32:40,160 --> 00:32:42,410
I don't recall phrasing it as a question, no.

485
00:32:43,520 --> 00:32:45,630
Fine, then I just won't show up.

486
00:32:46,530 --> 00:32:47,640
Then the roof.

487
00:32:48,630 --> 00:32:50,040
Take the back stairwell.

488
00:32:51,040 --> 00:32:52,870
The cameras have been out since March.

489
00:32:53,230 --> 00:32:54,290
No one will know.

490
00:33:01,470 --> 00:33:02,960
Well, you just made a long day longer.

491
00:33:02,990 --> 00:33:04,710
I know that Allsafe will have to fire me,

492
00:33:04,740 --> 00:33:06,590
but testifying was the right thing to do.

493
00:33:06,610 --> 00:33:09,190
I have worked my ass off to take care of you

494
00:33:09,480 --> 00:33:11,070
and of every person in this company.

495
00:33:11,090 --> 00:33:13,230
Do you know what that means?

496
00:33:13,250 --> 00:33:15,290
You've been a great boss, Gideon--

497
00:33:15,610 --> 00:33:18,320
See, once this confession goes public,

498
00:33:18,340 --> 00:33:20,250
no one will want to do business with us.

499
00:33:20,270 --> 00:33:21,910
The company will go under.

500
00:33:21,930 --> 00:33:23,880
I couldn't let Colby take the fall

501
00:33:23,900 --> 00:33:24,810
- for something that I did. - Oh, come on!

502
00:33:24,830 --> 00:33:26,710
You and I both know you didn't break chain of custody.

503
00:33:26,730 --> 00:33:28,780
I did and I feel terrible--

504
00:33:28,800 --> 00:33:32,630
Angela! Please! Stop lying.

505
00:33:36,460 --> 00:33:40,970
You do this... All these people go down,

506
00:33:42,020 --> 00:33:43,170
all their families

507
00:33:44,200 --> 00:33:46,810
that rely on what this company provides for them.

508
00:34:10,160 --> 00:34:12,130
So this is where the rabbit hole leads?

509
00:34:14,740 --> 00:34:15,380
Got to be honest,

510
00:34:15,410 --> 00:34:17,410
I half-expected you not to show up.

511
00:34:18,770 --> 00:34:21,320
And I half-expected you to be a tattletale.

512
00:34:22,600 --> 00:34:24,190
So you are sore.

513
00:34:24,300 --> 00:34:26,990
Oh, come on. You intrigued me.

514
00:34:27,010 --> 00:34:28,820
I intrigued back.

515
00:34:29,520 --> 00:34:31,620
Can't we just be more straightforward?

516
00:34:31,650 --> 00:34:34,600
Oh, that's no fun, but if you insist,

517
00:34:35,870 --> 00:34:37,600
I just came up here to see if you were really

518
00:34:37,620 --> 00:34:39,240
as gullible as you seem.

519
00:34:40,610 --> 00:34:42,930
My husband's downstairs getting the job that you want,

520
00:34:42,950 --> 00:34:44,970
and you're up here trying to fuck me.

521
00:34:44,990 --> 00:34:48,700
Now whether that's you being straightforward or a game,

522
00:34:49,320 --> 00:34:51,820
either way, it's played pretty poorly, if you ask me.

523
00:34:52,610 --> 00:34:54,590
Again, I asked no question.

524
00:34:55,090 --> 00:34:57,410
All I can tell you is you need this

525
00:34:57,480 --> 00:34:59,080
'cause you're dissatisfied.

526
00:35:00,260 --> 00:35:02,350
Scott plans on firing you,

527
00:35:06,390 --> 00:35:07,700
You seem desperate.

528
00:35:59,390 --> 00:36:01,180
What do you-- get off of me!

529
00:36:01,780 --> 00:36:03,000
Stop!

530
00:38:02,330 --> 00:38:04,210
We connected with WhiteRose.

531
00:38:04,490 --> 00:38:05,760
The plan is back on.

532
00:38:08,740 --> 00:38:13,210
I could bullshit you, tell you you're the only person

533
00:38:13,230 --> 00:38:16,360
who can fill the exact void we have at fsociety.

534
00:38:17,800 --> 00:38:19,950
The truth is, I need this group back together.

535
00:38:25,410 --> 00:38:28,310
Have you ever considered which part of our scheme motivates you?

536
00:38:29,540 --> 00:38:30,860
When the Dark Army bailed,

537
00:38:30,940 --> 00:38:32,170
you didn't care if pushing a button

538
00:38:32,190 --> 00:38:34,100
would bring an economic revolution.

539
00:38:34,630 --> 00:38:36,460
You want momentary anarchy.

540
00:38:37,940 --> 00:38:38,810
The others?

541
00:38:39,370 --> 00:38:41,130
Mobley likes palling around.

542
00:38:41,490 --> 00:38:43,420
Romero wants a whiff of fame.

543
00:38:44,040 --> 00:38:45,740
Those reasons depress me.

544
00:38:50,620 --> 00:38:54,020
- What's the part you want? - You don't care.

545
00:39:02,040 --> 00:39:03,640
My parents were born in Iran.

546
00:39:04,630 --> 00:39:06,390
They came here like everybody else,

547
00:39:06,410 --> 00:39:07,300
for freedom,

548
00:39:07,330 --> 00:39:09,770
but my dad works 60-hour weeks

549
00:39:09,790 --> 00:39:13,200
to determine tax loopholes for a millionaire art dealer.

550
00:39:13,830 --> 00:39:16,650
My mom, she ran up loans into five digits

551
00:39:16,670 --> 00:39:18,190
to get an online degree.

552
00:39:19,110 --> 00:39:21,180
They won't shut up about how great America is.

553
00:39:23,310 --> 00:39:25,190
But they're gonna die in debt

554
00:39:25,420 --> 00:39:27,350
doing things they never wanted to do.

555
00:39:35,180 --> 00:39:38,010
There are how many billion people in this world?

556
00:39:39,230 --> 00:39:40,420
7.3.

557
00:39:40,960 --> 00:39:43,900
Somehow you and I landed together...

558
00:39:44,690 --> 00:39:47,360
Doing something impossible if we were alone,

559
00:39:47,840 --> 00:39:51,390
not to mention at the right point in history with the right resources.

560
00:39:52,100 --> 00:39:55,530
We have what we've worked for right there for the taking.

561
00:39:56,600 --> 00:39:58,890
We just need each other to see this through.

562
00:40:14,120 --> 00:40:15,870
You come any closer, I'm calling the cops.

563
00:40:21,910 --> 00:40:25,580
Hi, operator. I'd like to report an emergency.

564
00:40:25,950 --> 00:40:28,490
I placed a malicious cd in my work computer,

565
00:40:28,520 --> 00:40:31,040
and now this guy at the gym is saying hi to me.

566
00:40:32,350 --> 00:40:33,140
I'm going home.

567
00:40:33,160 --> 00:40:34,640
I need you to do something for me.

568
00:40:34,660 --> 00:40:37,220
Call the girl who wants to be involved, okay?

569
00:40:37,240 --> 00:40:38,580
Her name is Angela Moss.

570
00:40:38,600 --> 00:40:39,350
Let me give you her phone number.

571
00:40:39,370 --> 00:40:41,820
Listen, pussy. If you don't do what I say,

572
00:40:41,850 --> 00:40:44,510
then the giant shit storm that rains turds later

573
00:40:44,530 --> 00:40:48,100
will leave a trail of clouds in the sky spelling out your name.

574
00:40:56,990 --> 00:41:00,860
Elliot? I wasn't expecting you.

575
00:41:02,070 --> 00:41:03,670
I'm here for my appointment.

576
00:41:06,490 --> 00:41:08,860
Well, you can slip in before my first patient.

577
00:41:29,290 --> 00:41:31,160
You told me I should tell you the truth.

578
00:41:32,560 --> 00:41:33,270
Yes.

579
00:41:35,610 --> 00:41:40,300
Everything I say will still be protected and confidential?

580
00:41:46,520 --> 00:41:47,790
I've been lying to you.

581
00:41:50,990 --> 00:41:52,380
I don't take my pills.

582
00:41:53,600 --> 00:41:54,620
But you don't either.

583
00:41:56,900 --> 00:41:59,040
Your refill frequency for ativan doesn't match

584
00:41:59,060 --> 00:42:01,120
your prescription divided by the dosage.

585
00:42:06,450 --> 00:42:07,430
This morning...

586
00:42:10,060 --> 00:42:12,460
You bought a tall hazelnut latte.

587
00:42:12,920 --> 00:42:14,980
Paid for it on your evil corp card.

588
00:42:15,870 --> 00:42:18,490
By text, you justified the indulgence to your sister

589
00:42:18,510 --> 00:42:21,040
because evil corp gives you double rewards.

590
00:42:21,130 --> 00:42:24,230
But those points only accumulate on travel expenses.

591
00:42:24,700 --> 00:42:25,910
You're not good with money.

592
00:42:27,410 --> 00:42:31,710
On paper, your Thursday 2:00, Marilyn O'Brien,

593
00:42:31,820 --> 00:42:33,290
is your doppelganger.

594
00:42:34,410 --> 00:42:37,810
I think you're encouraging her

595
00:42:37,830 --> 00:42:39,140
to leave her husband...

596
00:42:41,940 --> 00:42:44,040
Because you're tired of being dumped.

597
00:42:47,920 --> 00:42:49,810
You like porn, especially anal.

598
00:42:49,830 --> 00:42:51,070
Whether you like it yourself, I don't know.

599
00:42:51,090 --> 00:42:53,000
That's not relevant to me.

600
00:42:53,880 --> 00:42:55,720
You've told your best friend Jennifer

601
00:42:55,750 --> 00:42:58,780
that you wish your mom would die.

602
00:43:01,830 --> 00:43:03,950
I sometimes watch you on your webcam.

603
00:43:05,290 --> 00:43:06,790
You cry sometimes...

604
00:43:09,500 --> 00:43:10,610
Just like me.

605
00:43:13,760 --> 00:43:15,500
Because you're lonely.

606
00:43:22,480 --> 00:43:24,250
I don't just hack you, Krista.

607
00:43:24,270 --> 00:43:25,560
I hack everyone--

608
00:43:27,240 --> 00:43:30,010
My friends, coworkers.

609
00:43:35,650 --> 00:43:37,420
But I've helped a lot of people.

610
00:43:44,470 --> 00:43:45,250
I want...

611
00:43:48,470 --> 00:43:50,700
A way out of loneliness...

612
00:43:53,420 --> 00:43:54,630
Just like you.

613
00:44:07,410 --> 00:44:09,330
Is that what you wanted to hear?

