[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 职员,MingLiU,16,&H00E8E8E8,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.5,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 标题,汉仪双线体简,40,&H001C1DB6,&H0021218D,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.1,7,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,-22,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效标记,微软雅黑,13,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,14,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 短信文本,微软雅黑,20,&H006D6D77,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,-11,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 短信文本-1,微软雅黑,20,&H00161617,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,9,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 短信文本-3,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,9,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 二维码,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:01:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\an8\fad(500,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HE28609&\3a&HDC&\pos(189.24,0.4)}本字幕由{\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯制作，僅供學習，禁止用于任何商業盈利行為。若因私自散布傳播造成法律問題，本字幕組概不負責。更多影視請搜索并關注新浪微博{\c&H00FFFF&}@大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(200,200)\fscx116\fscy150\c&H000000&\move(71.2,198.933,32.8,246.933,0,2000)}m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(200,200)\fscx116\fscy150\\c&HFFFFFF&\move(-3.2,290.8,32.4,247.466,0,2000)}m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(200,200)\fscx116\fscy150\c&H000000&\move(71.2,198.933,32.4,246.4,0,2000)}m 32 27 l 32 27 l 32 29 l 31 29 l 31 28 l 30 28 l 30 29 l 29 29 l 29 30 l 28 30 l 28 31 l 27 31 l 27 32 l 26 32 l 26 33 l 28 33 l 28 32 l 30 32 l 30 33 l 28 33 l 28 34 l 27 34 l 27 36 l 26 36 l 26 37 l 25 37 l 25 36 l 24 36 l 24 33 l 22 33 l 22 32 l 23 32 l 23 31 l 22 31 l 22 30 l 24 30 l 24 31 l 26 31 l 26 30 l 24 30 l 24 28 l 23 28 l 23 29 l 22 29 l 22 30 l 21 30 l 21 31 l 19 31 l 19 32 l 20 32 l 20 33 l 19 33 l 19 32 l 18 32 l 18 33 l 17 33 l 17 32 l 18 32 l 18 31 l 17 31 l 17 30 l 19 30 l 19 29 l 19 29 l 20 29 l 20 30 l 21 30 l 21 29 l 20 29 l 20 28 l 22 28 l 22 27 l 27 27 l 27 28 l 25 28 l 25 29 l 28 29 l 28 25 l 27 25 l 27 26 l 26 26 l 26 25 l 27 25 l 27 24 l 28 24 l 28 23 l 27 23 l 27 22 l 29 22 l 29 27 l 32 27 m 16 29 l 17 29 l 17 28 l 16 28 l 16 29 m 17 26 l 16 26 l 16 25 l 17 25 l 17 26 m 18 29 l 18 27 l 19 27 l 19 26 l 20 26 l 20 25 l 19 25 l 19 26 l 18 26 l 18 25 l 19 25 l 19 24 l 20 24 l 20 22 l 21 22 l 21 21 l 22 21 l 22 24 l 20 24 l 20 25 l 21 25 l 21 27 l 20 27 l 20 28 l 19 28 l 19 29 l 18 29 m 23 26 l 22 26 l 22 25 l 23 25 l 23 26 m 24 26 l 24 24 l 23 24 l 23 21 l 24 21 l 24 22 l 26 22 l 26 24 l 25 24 l 25 26 m 0 28 l 0 30 l 1 30 l 1 29 l 2 29 l 2 30 l 3 30 l 3 33 l 2 33 l 2 34 l 1 34 l 1 33 l 0 33 l 0 34 l 1 34 l 1 35 l 2 35 l 2 37 l 1 37 l 1 36 l 0 36 l 0 38 l 2 38 l 2 39 l 5 39 l 5 40 l 7 40 l 7 39 l 6 39 l 6 38 l 8 38 l 8 37 l 9 37 l 9 36 l 10 36 l 10 37 l 11 37 l 11 36 l 10 36 l 10 34 l 9 34 l 9 36 l 8 36 l 8 34 l 9 34 l 9 33 l 6 33 l 6 32 l 5 32 l 5 31 l 6 31 l 6 32 l 8 32 l 8 31 l 6 31 l 6 30 l 8 30 l 8 28 l 7 28 l 7 29 l 6 29 l 6 30 l 4 30 l 4 28 l 5 28 l 5 29 l 6 29 l 6 28 l 7 28 l 7 27 l 6 27 l 6 28 l 5 28 l 5 27 l 2 27 l 2 28 l 3 28 l 3 29 l 2 29 l 2 28 l 1 28 m 0 31 l 2 31 l 2 32 l 0 32 m 9 31 l 10 31 l 10 32 l 9 32 l 9 31 m 21 32 l 22 32 l 22 31 l 21 31 l 21 32 m 37 27 l 34 27 l 34 28 l 33 28 l 33 29 l 32 29 l 32 30 l 31 30 l 31 29 l 30 29 l 30 32 l 31 32 l 31 33 l 30 33 l 30 34 l 29 34 l 29 36 l 28 36 l 28 37 l 26 37 l 26 40 l 25 40 l 25 41 l 24 41 l 24 39 l 23 39 l 23 41 l 24 41 l 24 43 l 22 43 l 22 42 l 19 42 l 19 43 l 20 43 l 20 44 l 21 44 l 21 45 l 19 45 l 19 46 l 22 46 l 22 44 l 25 44 l 25 41 l 26 41 l 26 44 l 27 44 l 27 42 l 28 42 l 28 44 l 30 44 l 30 45 l 32 45 l 32 46 l 33 46 l 33 45 l 34 45 l 34 44 l 35 44 l 35 43 l 33 43 l 33 45 l 32 45 l 32 44 l 32 42 l 31 42 l 31 43 l 30 43 l 30 42 l 29 42 l 29 41 l 26 41 l 26 40 l 27 40 l 27 38 l 28 38 l 28 39 l 29 39 l 29 41 l 30 41 l 30 42 l 31 42 l 31 41 l 32 41 l 32 40 l 34 40 l 34 41 l 34 42 l 36 42 l 36 44 l 37 44 l 37 43 l 37 40 l 36 40 l 36 41 l 35 41 l 35 39 l 36 39 l 36 38 l 37 38 l 37 37 l 35 37 l 35 35 l 34 35 l 34 36 l 33 36 l 33 37 l 35 37 l 35 39 l 33 39 l 33 37 l 32 37 l 32 38 l 30 38 l 30 39 l 29 39 l 29 38 l 28 38 l 28 37 l 30 37 l 30 36 l 31 36 l 31 37 l 32 37 l 32 36 l 33 36 l 33 34 l 34 34 l 34 33 l 35 33 l 35 34 l 36 34 l 36 35 l 37 35 l 37 33 l 35 33 l 35 31 l 32 31 l 32 30 l 33 30 l 33 29 l 35 29 l 35 28 l 37 28 l 37 27 m 33 32 l 33 33 l 32 33 l 32 32 m 31 34 l 32 34 l 32 35 l 31 35 m 25 35 l 26 35 l 26 34 l 25 34 m 36 29 l 36 29 l 37 29 l 37 30 l 36 30 m 36 31 l 37 31 l 37 32 l 36 32 m 14 36 l 14 34 l 13 34 l 13 35 l 12 35 l 12 38 l 13 38 l 13 36 m 4 38 l 4 37 l 3 37 l 3 38 l 2 38 l 2 37 l 3 37 l 3 33 l 5 33 l 5 34 l 4 34 l 4 35 l 6 35 l 6 34 l 7 34 l 7 35 l 6 35 l 6 36 l 7 36 l 7 37 l 6 37 l 6 38 l 4 38 m 4 36 l 5 36 l 5 37 l 4 37 m 37 46 l 37 45 l 36 45 l 36 44 l 35 44 l 35 45 l 34 45 l 34 46 l 35 46 l 35 47 l 34 47 l 34 48 l 35 48 l 35 51 l 34 51 l 34 53 l 33 53 l 33 55 l 31 55 l 31 54 l 32 54 l 32 53 l 33 53 l 33 50 l 34 50 l 34 49 l 33 49 l 33 47 l 29 47 l 29 46 l 28 46 l 28 47 l 27 47 l 27 46 l 28 46 l 28 45 l 26 45 l 26 47 l 25 47 l 25 48 l 24 48 l 24 46 l 25 46 l 25 45 l 23 45 l 23 47 l 21 47 l 21 48 l 20 48 l 20 47 l 19 47 l 19 50 l 21 50 l 21 53 l 19 53 l 19 54 l 21 54 l 21 56 l 23 56 l 23 55 l 22 55 l 22 54 l 23 54 l 23 53 l 22 53 l 22 52 l 24 52 l 24 53 l 25 53 l 25 52 l 26 52 l 26 51 l 25 51 l 25 50 l 24 50 l 24 51 l 22 51 l 22 50 l 23 50 l 23 49 l 26 49 l 26 48 l 28 48 l 28 49 l 28 49 l 26 49 l 26 51 l 27 51 l 27 50 l 28 50 l 28 51 l 27 51 l 27 52 l 28 52 l 28 54 l 27 54 l 27 53 l 26 53 l 26 56 l 28 56 l 28 55 l 29 55 l 29 52 l 30 52 l 30 53 l 31 53 l 31 52 l 32 52 l 32 53 l 31 53 l 31 54 l 30 54 l 30 55 l 29 55 l 29 56 l 37 56 l 37 53 l 36 53 l 36 55 l 34 55 l 34 54 l 35 54 l 35 51 l 37 51 l 37 49 l 36 49 l 36 46 m 29 48 l 32 48 l 32 51 l 29 51 m 30 49 l 31 49 l 31 50 l 30 50 m 13 50 l 15 50 l 15 47 l 16 47 l 16 46 l 17 46 l 17 45 l 18 45 l 18 43 l 17 43 l 17 42 l 14 42 l 14 43 l 16 43 l 16 46 l 15 46 l 15 44 l 14 44 l 14 43 l 13 43 l 13 45 l 11 45 l 11 44 l 12 44 l 12 43 l 9 43 l 9 45 l 8 45 l 8 43 l 6 43 l 6 42 l 10 42 l 10 40 l 11 40 l 11 42 l 13 42 l 13 41 l 14 41 l 14 40 l 13 40 l 13 41 l 12 41 l 12 40 l 11 40 l 11 38 l 9 38 l 9 39 l 8 39 l 8 41 l 5 41 l 5 42 l 3 42 l 3 41 l 0 41 l 0 43 l 1 43 l 1 42 l 2 42 l 2 44 l 0 44 l 0 48 l 1 48 l 1 45 l 2 45 l 2 47 l 3 47 l 3 45 l 2 45 l 2 44 l 3 44 l 3 43 l 4 43 l 4 48 l 5 48 l 5 47 l 6 47 l 6 46 l 7 46 l 7 45 l 6 45 l 6 44 l 5 44 l 5 43 l 6 43 l 6 44 l 7 44 l 7 45 l 8 45 l 8 47 l 6 47 l 6 48 l 8 48 l 8 49 l 9 49 l 9 46 l 10 46 l 10 45 l 11 45 l 11 46 l 10 46 l 10 47 l 11 47 l 11 48 l 10 48 l 10 49 l 11 49 l 11 48 l 14 48 l 14 49 l 13 49 m 13 47 l 12 47 l 12 46 l 13 46 m 15 56 l 11 56 l 11 55 l 9 55 l 9 54 l 8 54 l 8 51 l 9 51 l 9 53 l 10 53 l 10 50 l 11 50 l 11 54 l 12 54 l 12 52 l 13 52 l 13 51 l 14 51 l 14 52 l 13 52 l 13 54 l 12 54 l 12 55 l 15 55 l 15 55 m 15 54 l 15 53 l 17 53 l 17 54 l 18 54 l 18 56 l 16 56 l 16 54 m 17 48 l 18 48 l 18 50 l 16 50 l 16 49 l 17 49 m 17 51 l 18 51 l 18 52 l 17 52 m 19 51 l 20 51 l 20 52 l 19 52 m 19 55 l 20 55 l 20 56 l 19 56 m 0 39 l 1 39 l 1 40 l 0 40 m 0 49 l 7 49 l 7 56 l 0 56 l 0 56 m 1 50 l 1 55 l 1 55 l 6 55 l 6 50 m 2 51 l 5 51 l 5 54 l 2 54 m 30 19 l 30 26 l 37 26 l 37 19 m 31 20 l 36 20 l 36 25 l 31 25 m 32 21 l 32 24 l 35 24 l 35 21 m 0 19 l 7 19 l 7 26 l 0 26 m 1 20 l 1 25 l 6 25 l 6 20 m 2 21 l 2 24 l 5 24 l 5 21 m 8 19 l 8 22 l 11 22 l 11 23 l 10 23 l 10 24 l 8 24 l 8 28 l 10 28 l 10 29 l 12 29 l 12 33 l 10 33 l 10 34 l 11 34 l 11 35 l 12 35 l 12 34 l 13 34 l 13 33 l 15 33 l 15 32 l 16 32 l 16 30 l 15 30 l 15 31 l 14 31 l 14 30 l 15 30 l 15 29 l 14 29 l 14 28 l 13 28 l 13 24 l 15 24 l 15 25 l 14 25 l 14 27 l 15 27 l 15 28 l 16 28 l 16 26 l 15 26 l 15 25 l 16 25 l 16 24 l 17 24 l 17 25 l 18 25 l 18 23 l 19 23 l 19 21 l 21 21 l 21 20 l 23 20 l 23 19 l 21 19 l 21 20 l 19 20 l 19 19 l 18 19 l 18 21 l 17 21 l 17 23 l 15 23 l 15 22 l 16 22 l 16 21 l 17 21 l 17 20 l 16 20 l 16 21 l 15 21 l 15 20 l 16 20 l 16 19 l 14 19 l 14 21 l 15 21 l 15 22 l 14 22 l 14 21 l 13 21 l 13 22 l 12 22 l 12 20 l 13 20 l 13 19 l 11 19 l 11 20 l 9 20 l 9 19 m 9 27 l 9 25 l 10 25 l 10 24 l 11 24 l 11 23 l 12 23 l 12 28 l 11 28 l 11 27 m 10 26 l 10 25 l 11 25 l 11 26 m 25 19 l 25 20 l 26 20 l 26 19 m 28 19 l 29 19 l 29 21 l 27 21 l 27 20 l 28 20
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\p1\c&H000000&\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&\fscx16\fscy26\move(71.2,198.933,32.443,248.194,0,2000)}m 56 35 l 43 41 l 52 41 l 52 39 l 56 39 m 73 28 l 77 41 l 82 41 m 69 21 l 61 21 l 64 23 l 64 39 l 63 41 l 70 41 l 65 28 l 67 23 l 71 23 m 25 28 l 17 41 l 33 41 m 31 21 l 52 21 l 42 25 l 42 29 l 53 24 l 55 26 l 42 32 l 42 35 l 56 29 l 56 31 l 42 37 l 41 39 m 29 9 l 55 9 l 55 11 l 41 11 l 41 17 l 51 17 l 51 14 l 65 14 l 68 18 l 29 18 m 20 11 l 16 18 l 20 18 m 14 21 l 19 21 l 8 39 l 7 39 l 7 41 l 1 41
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.97,0:00:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\fs13\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H14&\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\pos(33.149,216.075)}{\fsp1.5\3c&H000000&\3a&H00&\4c&H000000&\4a&H00&} {\4c&H000000&\3c&H000000&\3a&H64&\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&\4a&HFF&}掃掃加微信
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.00,0:22:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.00,0:22:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.00,0:22:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.00,0:44:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.00,0:44:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.00,0:44:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.00,0:44:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.00,0:44:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\c&H240FA0&\b1\pos(194.04,57.68)}機器人先生 前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H25119F&\b1\pos(203.28,234.686)}大家字幕組 傾情譯制
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.00,0:00:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    墳老絲  Serafina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.00,0:00:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    墳老絲  Serafina
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.00,0:00:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    Silent Bob  芫荽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    Silent Bob  芫荽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    哎喲我去  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.00,0:00:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    哎喲我去  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.00,0:00:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    條子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    條子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}校對    LilBear
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.00,0:00:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}校對    LilBear
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.00,0:00:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}時間軸 & 特效    柯迪夫  沒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.00,0:00:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}時間軸 & 特效    柯迪夫  沒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.00,0:00:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}壓制    宋胖子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.00,0:00:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}壓制    宋胖子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.00,0:00:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)\}監制    LilBear  嵬森  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.00,0:00:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}監制    LilBear  嵬森  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.74,0:05:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs80\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(197.04,48.88)}機器人先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.74,0:05:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(202.32,203.6)}第一季  第八集
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.00,0:44:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,300)}{\fs14}{\fs14}{\fn微軟雅黑\fs16\b1\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&}本字幕由{\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯\N{\fs14}{\fs14}僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為\N{\fs14}{\fs14}彼以國士待我 我以國士待之\N{\fs14}用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人\N{\fs14}有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們\N{\fs14}{\fs14\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}請聯系：dajiazimuzu@163.com
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.32,0:07:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(197.04,198.88)\b1}羅伊德{\b0}
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.32,0:07:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(197.04,218.88)\c&HFFFFFF&}萬安公司被侵入了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(197.04,108.88)\c&HFFFFFF&}給辦公室回電話!急
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.00,0:11:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(177.04,258.88)\i0\c&HFFFFFF&}整個網絡癱瘓了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.00,0:12:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs35\pos(177.04,258.88)\c&HADADB0&}沒 有 權 限
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.00,0:16:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(145.04,158.88)\fs21\c&HFFFFFF&}已發郵件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.00,0:16:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(145.04,168.88)\fs21}至: 安吉拉 莫斯      夠了! 這次黑客行動是你的錯!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.00,0:16:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(88.04,205.88)\fs21}至: 安吉拉 莫斯      我要復仇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.00,0:16:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(135.04,238.88)\fs21}至: 安吉拉 莫斯      你看- 這是你想要的嗎?!?!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.00,0:16:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}你怎么還在家? 慶典就在今晚 你沒多少時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.36,0:16:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}勒索這種事兒太捉摸不定了 無法保證能成功
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.64,0:16:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}她這么輕易的動搖了你的信心?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}你只是睡了她而已 沒必要那么害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.04,0:17:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}我想你應該已經拍下了需要拍的照片了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.08,0:17:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}我們得重新分析件事情的重點 想其他辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.44,0:17:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}我們有辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.96,0:17:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}斯科特知道公司經不起另一起丑聞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.88,0:17:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}尤其是在公司盈利報告期間
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.56,0:17:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}這是我們最好的時機
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.80,0:17:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}他必然會降職
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.34,0:17:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}普萊斯就別無選擇只能任命你為首席技術官了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.06,0:17:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}沒必要把事情復雜化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.44,0:17:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}我們付出多少努力才走到今天
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.76,0:17:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(189.6,277.2)\c&H00FFFF&}別在關鍵時刻泄氣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.33,0:20:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(177.04,58.88)\b1\fs30\c&H36FBCA&}布蘭科的硬盤
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.33,0:20:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(157.04,118.88)}{\c&H36FCC5&}數據恢復服務
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.00,0:21:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(157.04,118.88)\fs19\c&H000000&}無服務
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.00,0:03:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(230.04,108.88)\c&H000000&\fs(24)}工商管理碩士
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.00,0:03:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220.04,248.88)\c&H000000&\fs(25)}2007年7月7日
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.76,0:30:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200.04,268.88)}請去除在CS30服務器上的蜂蜜陷阱并恢復其正常連接
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.48,0:30:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(180,200)}收到請求 請允許48小時的時間去完成操作
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.73,0:32:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,275.6)}這是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.44,0:32:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192.6,277.2)}我是打算恭喜你來著 但你這樣一點兒都不鼓舞人心
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.30,0:32:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,275.6)}恭喜我?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.38,0:32:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,278)}你的助手打來電話 說慶祝會取消了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.24,0:32:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,277.2)}我以為或許你的行動
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.36,0:32:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(193.2,274.8)}昨晚真的有了起色 即使你不想告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.88,0:32:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(193.8,277.2)}他拒絕了那個職務?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.94,0:32:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,276.4)}現在無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.18,0:32:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192.6,274.8)}無所謂了?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.48,0:32:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,276.4)}真的沒關系
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.26,0:32:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,274.8)}真的無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.98,0:33:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,277.2)}我們被一個目光短淺的錯誤人選蒙蔽了雙眼
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.30,0:33:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(193.8,276.4)}幾個月前 我看見一個技術員 一個你永遠不會懷疑的人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.22,0:33:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(193.2,275.6)}利用別人的一個快捷方式
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.76,0:33:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(190.8,276.4)}什么快捷方式?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.52,0:33:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(189.6,275.6)}這就是問題所在
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.64,0:33:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(190.8,275.6)}我一開始以為只是個小小的報復
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.86,0:33:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,274.8)}但不是 這個快捷鍵指向一個更大的東西 更宏偉的東西 更漂亮的東西\N{\fs14}
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.74,0:33:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,277.2)}我們一直以來只關注眼前的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.36,0:33:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,278)}但我們一直忽視了眼睛上方的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.32,0:33:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,275.6)}我們上面的東西是?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.66,0:33:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(189.6,277.2)}上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.12,0:33:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,276.4)}告訴我接下來怎么了 蒂雷爾
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.54,0:33:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(191.4,278)}是你把我逼到這個地步的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.92,0:33:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(192,278)}起來
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.86,0:33:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(187.2,274.8)}去開門
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.28,0:34:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(186.6,273.2)}他在說什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.30,0:36:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H00FFFF&\pos(193.8,276.4)}我不會讓他們帶你走 你不能離開我們
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.43,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在中國的東方數據中心的數據備份\N{\fs14}The redundant backups at their eastern data center in China,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由黑暗軍團幫我們搞定\N{\fs14}the Dark Army is covering us on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.68,0:00:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在就可以行動!\N{\fs14}We can go now!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.70,0:00:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們開始了而他們按兵不動\N{\fs14}If we move forward and they don't,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.14,0:00:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中國方面的備份信息還在\N{\fs14}China still holds all the redundant information.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.26,0:00:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一切都將是無用功\N{\fs14}It will be pointless.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.36,0:00:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我們可以和白玫瑰面談的話--\N{\fs14}If we can talk to whiterose directly--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.14,0:00:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是不可能和你見面的\N{\fs14}No way he's meeting you face to face.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.96,0:00:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們這些笨蛋的愿望居然實現了\N{\fs14}You fools actually got your wish.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.84,0:00:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道意義何在 不過至少你們可以見一面了\N{\fs14}I don't know why, but the meeting's actually gonna be on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.76,0:00:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想告訴你讓你小心點\N{\fs14}I'd tell you to be careful,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.92,0:00:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道你一向莽撞\N{\fs14}but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.92,0:00:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讓系統管理員再檢查了一次服務器\N{\fs14}I had the sysadmin check that server again.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.72,0:00:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然也沒發現啥\N{\fs14}Of course, there was nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.36,0:00:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不知道有什么可疑的\N{\fs14}I have no idea what there was to even be suspicious about.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.60,0:00:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么我的工作證在你那?\N{\fs14}Why do you have my work ID?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.28,0:00:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放了一張惡意含惡意軟件的CD在我辦公室的電腦里\N{\fs14}I placed a malicious CD in my work computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.48,0:00:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你為我做件事\N{\fs14}I need you to do something for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.34,0:00:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎我們新上任的首席技術官\N{\fs14}Our new Chief Technology Officer,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.44,0:00:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯考特 諾斯\N{\fs14}Scott Knowles.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.84,0:00:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚在天臺和我單獨見一面\N{\fs14}Meet me tonight, on the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.42,0:00:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攝像頭三月就壞了\N{\fs14}Cameras have been out since March.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.12,0:00:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人會知道\N{\fs14}No one will know.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.46,0:00:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣!\N{\fs14}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.98,0:01:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果這一切都消失了會怎樣?\N{\fs14}What if this all went away?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.84,0:01:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整個城市\N{\fs14}The city.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.00,0:01:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的錢\N{\fs14}The money.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.00,0:01:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切的一切\N{\fs14}All of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.64,0:01:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如發生了喪尸末日之類的情況?\N{\fs14}What, like a zombie apocalypse or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.67,0:01:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是一場革命\N{\fs14}More like a revolution.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.56,0:01:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次我們一起勾搭的時候\N{\fs14}Last time we hooked up,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.02,0:01:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們說好了不談政治\N{\fs14}we agreed to check politics at the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.10,0:01:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在再也沒有中產階級了\N{\fs14}There's no middle anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.82,0:01:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有土豪和屌絲\N{\fs14}Just rich and poor.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.34,0:01:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大早上的談這話題太沉重了\N{\fs14}Okay, this shit is way too heavy for me this early.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.26,0:01:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去上班了\N{\fs14}I gotta go to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.04,0:01:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.86,0:01:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要一頁紙一頁紙地\N{\fs14}Solving the world's problems
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.72,0:01:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去解決整個世界的問題\N{\fs14}one spreadsheet at a time.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.34,0:01:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了啊 我們不做就是政府去做\N{\fs14}Hey, it's either suits like me or the government.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.98,0:01:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都知道他們做事有多厲害\N{\fs14}We all know how well they handle things.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.66,0:01:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么這個世界就不能好好地自己轉下去?\N{\fs14}Why can't the world just take care of itself?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.28,0:02:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為世界上愚蠢的人太多\N{\fs14}Because the world is filled with stupid people.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.80,0:02:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我的聰明是錢砸出來的\N{\fs14}And I get paid a lot to be smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.06,0:02:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿\N{\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.74,0:02:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上不僅僅只有富人和窮人\N{\fs14}There's not just the rich and the poor.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.72,0:02:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有你 在中間的某個地方\N{\fs14}There's you, in the middle somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.18,0:02:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個完美的生存者\N{\fs14}The consummate survivor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.28,0:03:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我--我現在在上芭蕾課\N{\fs14}I--I'm in a ballet class right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.28,0:03:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 奧利 我現在不能和你討論這個問題\N{\fs14}No, Ollie, I can't talk to you about this right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.38,0:03:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管 奧利\N{\fs14}I don't care, Ollie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.28,0:04:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管你碰到了誰\N{\fs14}I don't care who you ran into
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.14,0:04:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是他說了些什么\N{\fs14}or what he said.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.56,0:04:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.06,0:04:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fs14}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.54,0:04:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請告訴我你們不會復合\N{\fs14}Tell me you're not getting back together with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.30,0:04:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天 當然不會\N{\fs14}Jesus, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.26,0:04:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不 只是些工作上的事\N{\fs14}No. Just leftover work stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.76,0:04:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和伊利艾特談了嗎?\N{\fs14}Have you talked to Elliot?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.70,0:04:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天聊了\N{\fs14}Yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.72,0:04:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好像他在試著振作\N{\fs14}Seems like he's pulling himself together,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.50,0:04:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道他那個樣子\N{\fs14}but you know how he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.08,0:04:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺我時時刻刻都在擔心他\N{\fs14}It feels like I'm always worried about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.18,0:04:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你知道嗎? - 我懂\N{\fs14}- You know? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.79,0:04:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他這個月糟透了\N{\fs14}He's had a shitty month.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.36,0:04:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這20年都糟透了\N{\fs14}Or 20 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.10,0:04:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你選一個吧\N{\fs14}Take your pick.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.70,0:04:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為什么到頭來\N{\fs14}Then why are we the ones
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.00,0:04:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐立不安的反而是我們?\N{\fs14}that always end up so stressed?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.70,0:04:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,設想一下你在兒時的臥室里醒來\N{\fs14}Try waking up in your childhood bedroom,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.97,0:04:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后乘坐2個小時的公交\N{\fs14}then taking Jersey transit for two hours
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.61,0:04:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來上市區里7點的芭蕾課\N{\fs14}to make a 7:00 ballet class in the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.45,0:04:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少\N{\fs14}Well, silver lining,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.48,0:04:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以見到我\N{\fs14}you get to see {\i1}moi.{\i}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 各位 第一個動作\N{\fs14}All right, everyone, first position.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.31,0:05:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我傷害了克里斯塔\N{\fs14}I hurt Krista.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.40,0:05:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太好受\N{\fs14}I don't feel good about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.54,0:05:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你沒有生我的氣\N{\fs14}I hope you're not mad at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.68,0:05:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你必須承認\N{\fs14}But you have to admit,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.52,0:05:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和其他人一樣\N{\fs14}she's just like everyone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.50,0:05:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢看墻外面的東西\N{\fs14}Too afraid to peek over their walls
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.04,0:05:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為害怕可能會看到的東西\N{\fs14}for fear of what they might see.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.10,0:05:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我不一樣\N{\fs14}Not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.06,0:05:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我專門做這樣的事\N{\fs14}That's what I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.34,0:05:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會去窺視\N{\fs14}I look.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.42,0:06:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把大家都找回來了嗎?\N{\fs14}Did you get everybody back?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.64,0:07:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他使用正確的命令\N{\fs14}Tell him to follow the proper commands,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.96,0:07:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然步驟不會啟動\N{\fs14}or the sequence won't initiate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.59,0:07:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用我們植入的單片機的后門\N{\fs14}Using the backdoor we planted with our raspberry pie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.46,0:07:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的個神 你這些弄了多久了?\N{\fs14}Jesus Christ, man, how long have you been sitting on all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.00,0:07:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四個星期前我裝了個補丁\N{\fs14}I installed a patch four weeks ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.88,0:07:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后每天都在監測\N{\fs14}and I've been monitoring it daily.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.20,0:07:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪人無眠\N{\fs14}No rest for the wicked.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.44,0:07:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想確認在和白玫瑰見面前\N{\fs14}I wanted to make sure it was all updated
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.72,0:07:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐵山各個新的地點\N{\fs14}at the Steel Mountain locations
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.32,0:07:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都更新好了\N{\fs14}before the meeting with whiterose.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.28,0:07:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 那些空調公司的人太傻了\N{\fs14}Yeah, those Airdream guys are so dumb.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.28,0:07:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰會把所有恒溫器控制放在同一個網絡上?\N{\fs14}Who has all their thermostats phone home the same network?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.82,0:07:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會把五個地點進行同步\N{\fs14}I'll sync up all five locations
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.60,0:07:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓它們以同樣的速率升溫\N{\fs14}so they heat at exactly the same rate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.54,0:07:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你別介意 這個我來就可以了\N{\fs14}No offense, but I'll handle that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.08,0:07:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去解決警報\N{\fs14}You should take care of the alarms,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.42,0:07:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別讓庫房升溫發出信號\N{\fs14}so there's not a signal of the temp raising in the vaults.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.60,0:07:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不行 得換個方法\N{\fs14}- No, reroute
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.72,0:07:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空調公司行不通\N{\fs14}Airdream's traffic.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.16,0:07:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得抹去所有我們活動的痕跡\N{\fs14}Make sure to erase and and all signs of our activity.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.73,0:08:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你去哪了? - 我需要和你談談\N{\fs14}- Where were you? - I need a word.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.90,0:08:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去上班了\N{\fs14}I gotta get to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.90,0:08:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勸你別去\N{\fs14}I'm not sure that's wise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.94,0:08:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什么鬼?\N{\fs14}What the hell is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.37,0:08:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在跟蹤我\N{\fs14}They're following me
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.58,0:08:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們可能也在跟蹤你\N{\fs14}and they're probably following you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.04,0:08:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們當時就在地鐵上 知道嗎?\N{\fs14}They were on the subway, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.00,0:08:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思科跟我說了他們不好惹\N{\fs14}Cisco's warned me about them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.44,0:08:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些人很危險 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}These guys are dangerous, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.48,0:08:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和白玫瑰的見面可能和我們預計的不一樣\N{\fs14}The whiterose meet might not go down the way we want it to.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.72,0:08:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有可能啊\N{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.15,0:08:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可 我連槍都不會用\N{\fs14}Well, I don't even know how to use a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.38,0:08:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說了 我不確定他們想見的就是我\N{\fs14}Besides, I'm not even sure I'm the one they wanna meet with.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.68,0:08:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想見的肯定是你\N{\fs14}You're definitely the one they wanna meet with.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.06,0:08:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去的時候 一定要小心\N{\fs14}And when you do, you need to be careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.50,0:08:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很認真 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}I'm serious, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.77,0:08:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛?\N{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.04,0:08:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用你的手機給我自己打電話\N{\fs14}I'm calling myself from your phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.98,0:08:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我們就有了彼此的號碼\N{\fs14}That way we have each other's number.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.34,0:08:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 戴琳 我們不能這樣\N{\fs14}Wait, Darlene, we don't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.00,0:08:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是為了保護F社會\N{\fs14}That's to protect a fsociety.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.70,0:08:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 但是現在我們必須保護對方\N{\fs14}Okay, but we need to protect each other right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.91,0:09:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刪了戴琳的號碼 我讓你這么做必然有我的道理\N{\fs14}Lose Darlene's number. It's a rule for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.11,0:09:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別急 我沒打算使用它\N{\fs14}Don't worry, I'm not gonna use it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.28,0:09:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有一件事說對了\N{\fs14}She's right about one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.55,0:09:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想談判的人是你\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}You're the one they want to talk to.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.92,0:09:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不能分心\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}We can't afford any distractions.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.96,0:10:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老板又邀請了我一次 他的行為太明顯了\N{\fs14}My boss invited me again. He's so obvious.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.76,0:10:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不現在殺了我?\N{\fs14}Why don't you just kill me now?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.20,0:10:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢!\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Oh!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.50,0:10:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天哪 布萊克! 你他X是在用腳尖走路嗎?\N{\fs14}Jesus, Blake! Were you f---ing tiptoeing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的 看看你干了什么好事\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}God damn it, look what you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.90,0:10:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走路看著點兒!\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Watch where you're going!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.05,0:10:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 但是你… - 早上好\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}- But you-- - Good morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.06,0:10:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在不是時候 伊麗莎白 所有電話都不要接進來\N{\fs14}Not now, Elizabeth. Hold all calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.32,0:10:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消所有的會議 我今天很忙\N{\fs14}Cancel any meetings. I'm busy today.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.94,0:10:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 威力克先生\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}But, Mr. Wellick,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.09,0:10:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉迪恩 戈達德來找你\N{\fs14}Gideon Goddard is here to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.96,0:10:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉 他堅持要見你\N{\fs14}I'm sorry. He was very persistent.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.80,0:10:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不肯走\N{\fs14}He wouldn't leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.76,0:10:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.02,0:10:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 就這樣 謝謝你\N{\fs14}Okay, no, that's fine. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.84,0:10:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔 你需要我 呃...\N{\fs14}Um, do you want me to, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.70,0:10:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 當然 我想要杯咖啡\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Oh, yes, I'd love some coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.72,0:11:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的一個員工承認\N{\fs14}One of my employees confessed to
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.82,0:11:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,違反了科爾比公司dat文件的監管鏈\N{\fs14}breaking chain of custody with the Colby dat file.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.90,0:11:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不幸 他的承認\N{\fs14}Unfortunately, this admission
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.38,0:11:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會使證據失效\N{\fs14}will render the evidence inadmissible
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.44,0:11:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且使科爾比公司免遭罰款\N{\fs14}and Colby free of charges.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.96,0:11:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你說任何話之前\N{\fs14}Now before you say anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.06,0:11:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你確保萬安公司已經做出雙倍努力\N{\fs14}I want to assure you that Allsafe has doubled its efforts
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.20,0:11:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尋找黑客\N{\fs14}to find the hackers,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.40,0:11:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論是再次確認科爾比的參與\N{\fs14}whether it be reconfirming Colby's involvement
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.66,0:11:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是找到真正的罪犯\N{\fs14}or finding the real perpetrators.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.24,0:11:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們已經隔離了您的個人網絡\N{\fs14}We've air-gapped your private network,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.18,0:11:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開啟了蜜罐系統\N{\fs14}implemented a honeypot,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.55,0:11:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新部署了所有的防火墻以及系統地...\N{\fs14}reconfigured all the firewalls and systematically--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.18,0:11:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等等 等等\N{\fs14}Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.56,0:11:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜罐系統 有什么用?\N{\fs14}A honeypot, for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.52,0:11:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上一次F社會的攻擊中使用的一個特殊的服務器\N{\fs14}A specific server involved in the last fsociety attack,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.08,0:11:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CS30\N{\fs14}CS30.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.53,0:11:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我們已經檢查過了 不過如果有那么一點可能\N{\fs14}I know we checked it out, but if there's even a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.78,0:11:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑客們仍然在網絡中的話\N{\fs14}the hackers are still in the network,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.04,0:11:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜罐系統可以確保他們不會造成任何傷害\N{\fs14}the honeypot will ensure that they can't cause any damage.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.07,0:11:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會登錄到我們設置好的誘餌服務器中\N{\fs14}They'll log into the decoy server we've set up,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.30,0:11:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以為他們是在主網絡上\N{\fs14}thinking they're on the main network.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.00,0:11:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且我會親自監視所有網絡流量\N{\fs14}And I'm personally keeping tabs on all traffic.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.58,0:11:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你擁有我們的全程監護\N{\fs14}So you have our full attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.38,0:12:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很感激你清楚的解釋\N{\fs14}Well, I appreciate your transparency.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.00,0:12:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你聽明白了\N{\fs14}Well, so you understand then.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.52,0:12:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.26,0:12:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上 我想查看你們的發現\N{\fs14}In fact, I'd like to look over your findings,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.12,0:12:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特別是這臺服務器\N{\fs14}especially this server.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.94,0:12:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 請給我發一份你們的研究報告\N{\fs14}So, please send me the research.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.08,0:12:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然 當然\N{\fs14}Of course, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.28,0:12:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再次感謝你能見我\N{\fs14}Well, thank you again for seeing me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.32,0:13:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.76,0:13:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生!\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.02,0:13:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特意強調不想被打擾\N{\fs14}I specifically asked not to be disturbed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.08,0:13:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 但是 呃...\N{\fs14}I know, but, um--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.54,0:13:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.93,0:13:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是警察\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}The police.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.73,0:13:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很糟糕的事情\N{\fs14}It's awful.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.07,0:13:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察有什么事?\N{\fs14}\N{\fs14}What about the police?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.12,0:13:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在屋頂發現一具尸體\N{\fs14}They found a body on the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.66,0:13:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸體? 誰的?\N{\fs14}A body? Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.74,0:13:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們沒說 但警探來了\N{\fs14}They're not saying,but detectives came by.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.98,0:13:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想和你談談\N{\fs14}They want to speak with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.70,0:13:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我?\N{\fs14}With me?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.66,0:13:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會詢問\N{\fs14}They're questioning everyone
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.28,0:13:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚參加接待會的每一個人\N{\fs14}who was at the reception last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.22,0:13:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顯然 這是不幸的 但工作還得繼續\N{\fs14}Clearly, this is tragic, but unfortunately work goes on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.96,0:13:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你不覺得你應該--\N{\fs14}But don't you think you should--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.29,0:13:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴警探他們可以提前預約\N{\fs14}Tell them they can set an appointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.50,0:13:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時 我會很高興和他們交談\N{\fs14}I'd be happy to speak with them then.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.77,0:14:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 還有 伊麗莎白 我需要你幫我聯系\N{\fs14}Oh, and, Elizabeth,I need you to connect me
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.54,0:14:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杜勒斯服務器農場\N{\fs14}with the Dulles Server Farm.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.68,0:14:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉接到我手機\N{\fs14}I'll take it on my mobile.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.14,0:14:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共享文件了嗎?\N{\fs14}And the file shares?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.46,0:14:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在我們重新上線之前\N{\fs14}'Cause client data is inaccessible
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.00,0:14:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,客戶數據無法訪問\N{\fs14}until we're back online.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.82,0:14:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就辦\N{\fs14}Jumping on that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.28,0:14:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,檢查ASA防火墻日志\N{\fs14}Check the logs on the ASA firewall.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.16,0:14:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要一份完整報告\N{\fs14}I want a full report.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.29,0:14:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧利 銷售員\N{\fs14}Ollie, sales.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.38,0:14:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我另行通知之前\N{\fs14}All appointments at Allsafe
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.74,0:14:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消所有萬安的預約\N{\fs14}are cancelled until further notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.18,0:14:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要向外走漏風聲\N{\fs14}Word of this cannot get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.63,0:14:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我們開始吧\N{\fs14}All right,let's get to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.88,0:14:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次攻擊沒什么破壞性 他們已經進入了我們的系統\N{\fs14}This hack is far from devastating. They already own us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.76,0:14:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們并非來尋求有價值的東西\N{\fs14}They're not going after anything valuable.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.38,0:14:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是轉移我們注意\N{\fs14}This is more of a distraction.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.60,0:14:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們試圖讓我們在什么上面分心呢?\N{\fs14}But what are they trying to distract us from?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.94,0:14:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 哥們\N{\fs14}Hey, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.90,0:15:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是讓我做話匣子\N{\fs14}Always the chatterbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.38,0:15:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在流汗\N{\fs14}You're sweating.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.02,0:15:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 是嗎? 有一點\N{\fs14}Oh, yeah? Yeah, maybe a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.70,0:15:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,東奔西跑的\N{\fs14}Been running around.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.04,0:15:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 聽著 我需要你幫我處理一些事情\N{\fs14}Um, look, I sorta need you to handle something for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.56,0:15:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們讓你現在干什么\N{\fs14}What have they got you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.62,0:15:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試著逆向還原惡意軟件\N{\fs14}Trying to reverse engineer the malware.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.74,0:15:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 呃 你得停下手頭工作\N{\fs14}Okay, um, I'm gonna need you to stop doing that
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.02,0:15:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把這些被毀壞的惡意驅動軟件\N{\fs14}Try and take these engineer corrupted drives malware.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉存到36號和5號空白磁盤恢復區間\N{\fs14}over to Blank's Disk Recovery on 36th and 5th.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.04,0:15:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么找我?這是IT部門的事\N{\fs14}Why me? Get one of the IT guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.42,0:15:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每個人都很忙 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Everyone is swamped, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.06,0:15:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 我不是來跟你爭論的\N{\fs14}Dude, this isn't, like,a debate.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.82,0:15:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直希望我們之間能相處好一點\N{\fs14}I've always wanted things to be cool between us,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.14,0:15:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是你上司\N{\fs14}but I outrank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.72,0:15:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...\N{\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你硬盤\N{\fs14}Here are the drives.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.96,0:15:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你安排在2點開始\N{\fs14}Your appointment is at 2:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.98,0:15:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要遲到\N{\fs14}You cannot be late.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.02,0:15:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上 呃 不如你現在就去?\N{\fs14}In fact, um, how 'bout you leave right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.36,0:16:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才12點\N{\fs14}It's only 12:00.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.40,0:16:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 哥們兒 你就--\N{\fs14}Elliot, bro, just--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.06,0:16:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就幫我這一次 好嗎?\N{\fs14}just do me this solid, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.48,0:16:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不僅僅只是緊張\N{\fs14}He wasn't just stressed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.38,0:16:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他感到恐懼\N{\fs14}He was scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.60,0:16:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我瞧瞧他在隱瞞什么\N{\fs14}Let's see what he's hiding.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.64,0:16:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉和這一切有什么關系?\N{\fs14}What does Angela have to do with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.50,0:18:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不告訴我?\N{\fs14}Why didn't you tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.12,0:18:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么告訴你?\N{\fs14}And say what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.22,0:18:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿 艾略特 有群混蛋\N{\fs14}"Hey, Elliot, there's a bunch of nude pics of me
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.54,0:18:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把我的裸照發布在網上"?\N{\fs14}that some asshole wants to leak online"?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.98,0:18:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能幫助你的\N{\fs14}I could have helped.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.18,0:18:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在身邊\N{\fs14}You weren't around.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.28,0:18:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.90,0:18:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個月過的很糟心\N{\fs14}Kinda had a rough month.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.10,0:18:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.56,0:18:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我發生什么了\N{\fs14}Tell me what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.74,0:18:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們被盯上了\N{\fs14}We were being pressured.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.40,0:18:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被誰?\N{\fs14}By who?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.00,0:18:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某些家伙\N{\fs14}Some guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.98,0:18:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他給了奧利一張CD 讓他的電腦中毒了\N{\fs14}He gave Ollie a CD that infected his laptop,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.16,0:18:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盜取了他的照片 電郵 還有瀏覽器緩存\N{\fs14}stole his pictures, his emails,and browser cache.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.52,0:18:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫他在萬安系統安裝一個磁盤\N{\fs14}He said to install the disk at Allsafe,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.12,0:18:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否則他就在網上曝光我們\N{\fs14}or he would leak everything online.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.94,0:18:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是前一段時間的事了\N{\fs14}It was a while ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.96,0:18:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為他把我們忘了\N{\fs14}I thought he forgot about us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.50,0:19:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜對了\N{\fs14}I was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.66,0:19:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次入侵是調虎離山\N{\fs14}The hack was a distraction.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.38,0:19:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是針對我的 這就是會面\N{\fs14}This is about me.This is the meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.48,0:19:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該來找我的\N{\fs14}You should have come to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.86,0:19:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說了\N{\fs14}I told you,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到你\N{\fs14}you weren't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.10,0:19:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你從來就是心不在焉\N{\fs14}You're never there anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.60,0:19:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怎么了 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Something is going on with you, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.12,0:19:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你過去幾個月一直魂不守舍\N{\fs14}You have not been the same the past couple of months,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.34,0:19:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉死之前你就是這樣了\N{\fs14}and this happened before Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.18,0:19:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你錯了\N{\fs14}You're wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.26,0:19:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在欺騙我!\N{\fs14}You're lying!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.54,0:19:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至不和我說話了!\N{\fs14}You don't talk to me anymore!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.40,0:19:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我現在改怎么做!\N{\fs14}Just tell me what to do here!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.26,0:19:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我能想到的唯一辦法\N{\fs14}Because the only solution I can think of
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.36,0:19:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是放棄\N{\fs14}is to give up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.76,0:19:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 說話呀!\N{\fs14}God, say something!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.36,0:19:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的對\N{\fs14}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.12,0:19:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不再交流了\N{\fs14}We don't talk anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.76,0:20:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這太奇怪了\N{\fs14}It's so strange.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.16,0:20:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的懷念過去的我們\N{\fs14}I really miss us.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.96,0:20:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這有什么奇怪的?\N{\fs14}Why is that strange?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.52,0:20:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我從未想過我必須這樣\N{\fs14}Because I never thought I'd have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.20,0:20:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑客\N{\fs14}Hackers.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.13,0:20:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們天生不相信任何人\N{\fs14}We inherently trust no one,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.80,0:20:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括對其他黑客\N{\fs14}including each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.77,0:20:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我將永遠都不能告訴她\N{\fs14}I'll never be able to tell her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.74,0:20:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們之間會永遠存在一道分水嶺\N{\fs14}There will always be this divide,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.81,0:20:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是她翻越不了的墻\N{\fs14}my wall that she can't look over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.64,0:20:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也清楚\N{\fs14}And she knows it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.80,0:20:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信譽問題 黑暗軍團\N{\fs14}Trust issues, the dark army
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.80,0:20:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,采取了絕妙的辦法\N{\fs14}has taken extraordinary steps
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.68,0:20:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確保會議完美地按照他們的想法進行\N{\fs14}to make sure this meeting's exactly how they want it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.60,0:20:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道這就是臭名昭著的白玫瑰成為傳奇的原因?\N{\fs14}Is that why the infamous whiterose is such a legend?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.84,0:21:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他比我們其余人都更偏執\N{\fs14}Because he's more paranoid than the rest of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.40,0:21:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是伊利艾特 奧爾德森\N{\fs14}I'm Elliot. Alderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.48,0:21:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個法拉第籠\N{\fs14}A Faraday cage.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.00,0:21:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個為避免電磁干擾而特殊設計的房間\N{\fs14}A room specifically designed to prevent electromagnetic interference
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.64,0:21:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有無線電 沒有信號 沒有Wifi 什么都黑不了\N{\fs14}No radio, no signal, no WiFi, nothing to hack.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.88,0:21:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我是來找你的\N{\fs14}I think I'm here to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.84,0:22:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該跟你走嗎?\N{\fs14}Am I supposed to follow you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.36,0:22:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算一直傻站在那\N{\fs14}Are you just going to stand there
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.36,0:22:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是把那些驅動遞給我?\N{\fs14}or do you want to hand me those drives?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.89,0:22:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快快快\N{\fs14}Mm-mm-mm.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.04,0:22:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會議已經開始了\N{\fs14}This meeting has started.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.72,0:22:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個時間觀念很強的人 奧爾德森先生\N{\fs14}I manage my time very carefully, Mr. Alderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.60,0:22:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表每響一下就代表著\N{\fs14}Each beep indicates one minute of my time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又少了一分鐘\N{\fs14}that has passed.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.20,0:22:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分給你的時間只有不到三分鐘\N{\fs14}I have allotted you no more than three minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.76,0:22:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確定要這么做嗎?\N{\fs14}Are you really gonna do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.08,0:22:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好挑一個好一點的話題\N{\fs14}I suggest you pick better topics of conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.64,0:22:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天還有十七項日程\N{\fs14}I have 17 more items on my agenda today.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.52,0:22:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應該這次\N{\fs14}The Evil Corp hack,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.28,0:22:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把邪惡公司的黑客解決掉\N{\fs14}we should go through with it this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.60,0:22:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會大失所望的\N{\fs14}You are turning out to be a grave disappointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.76,0:22:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們萬事俱備 該有的都有了\N{\fs14}We were ready. We had everything set to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.04,0:22:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住處太沒有效率了\N{\fs14}Dwelling is so inefficient.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.20,0:22:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你上次成功了啊\N{\fs14}Hey, you pulled out last time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.92,0:22:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別浪費時間在\N{\fs14}Wasting more time,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.52,0:22:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經知道了的事情上了\N{\fs14}telling me things I already know.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.04,0:22:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我們準備好了\N{\fs14}But we were ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.76,0:22:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你第三次這么說了\N{\fs14}That is the third time that you have expressed that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:23:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在拖延時間\N{\fs14}She's trolling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.23,0:23:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這次對話里不占一點上風\N{\fs14}You have not advanced this conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.40,0:23:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一希望占上風么?\N{\fs14}Do you intend to?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.64,0:23:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從上個月起\N{\fs14}Since last month,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.04,0:23:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪惡公司把他們的磁帶\N{\fs14}Evil Corp has moved its tapes to five--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.32,0:23:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉移到了五個備用設備里\N{\fs14}Backup facilities,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.68,0:23:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且你計劃把它們都毀掉\N{\fs14}and you have a plan to take them all down.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.80,0:23:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.92,0:23:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你終于說了點有用的了\N{\fs14}Finally, you have communicated something.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.40,0:23:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你到底準備好了沒?\N{\fs14}So are you ready to do this or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.36,0:23:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是沒準備好的那個\N{\fs14}You are the one who is not ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.80,0:23:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以來你才總是失敗\N{\fs14}It was you who failed all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.52,0:23:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你缺少的是注意力\N{\fs14}What you've lacked was focus.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.24,0:23:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你背離了黑客的道路反而針對泰利 科爾比\N{\fs14}You strayed from the hack to target Terry Colby.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.12,0:23:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這成為了一個安全隱患\N{\fs14}This opened a vulnerability.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.88,0:23:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶來了猜疑\N{\fs14}Suspicion.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.08,0:23:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是從吉迪恩 戈達德那里\N{\fs14}Specifically by Gideon Goddard.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.48,0:23:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是你為什么黑了萬安公司\N{\fs14}That's why you hacked Allsafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.40,0:23:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了監視他的活動\N{\fs14}To monitor his activities.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.36,0:23:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是那時我們發現\N{\fs14}And that's when we discovered
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.20,0:23:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把你攻擊的服務器變成了陷阱\N{\fs14}that he turned your infected server into a honeypot.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.40,0:23:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 六十秒后會議就結束了\N{\fs14}Oh, 60 seconds and this meeting will be over.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.52,0:23:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下\N{\fs14}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.52,0:23:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂為什么要等一下\N{\fs14}The concept of waiting bewilders me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.04,0:23:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡事都有期限\N{\fs14}There are always deadlines.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.40,0:23:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間總在流逝\N{\fs14}There are always ticking clocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.92,0:23:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是為什么你必須管理時間\N{\fs14}That's why you must manage your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.84,0:24:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會想辦法消除陷阱的\N{\fs14}I'll find a way to remove the honeypot.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.52,0:24:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到十六秒前\N{\fs14}Until 16 seconds ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.20,0:24:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還沒察覺有陷阱\N{\fs14}you were not aware there was a honeypot.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.12,0:24:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這對你的信心沒什么好處\N{\fs14}This does not inspire confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.65,0:24:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 等一下 - 又是這個詞\N{\fs14}- Wait.- There's that word again.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.08,0:24:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會處理好的\N{\fs14}We'll take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.32,0:24:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你本可以幾周前就把陷阱的事告訴我們的\N{\fs14}You know you could have told us about the honeypot weeks ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.32,0:24:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,術業有專攻\N{\fs14}Every hacker has her fixation.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.28,0:24:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你專攻人類 我專攻時間\N{\fs14}You hack people, I hack time.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.80,0:24:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你應該了解 我設下時間線\N{\fs14}So you should know that when I set a time line,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.08,0:24:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是有原因的\N{\fs14}there's a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.80,0:24:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還有五十個小時二十三分鐘\N{\fs14}You have 50 hours and 23 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.84,0:24:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時 當所有組織都準備好了\N{\fs14}At that point, when all parties are ready,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.28,0:24:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們將會發起黑客攻擊\N{\fs14}we will initiate the hack.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.60,0:24:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會做的\N{\fs14}We'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.72,0:24:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能下次吧\N{\fs14}Maybe next time--
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.68,0:24:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要知道 奧爾德森先生\N{\fs14}Understand something, Mr. Alderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.76,0:24:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走之后\N{\fs14}After I leave,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.56,0:24:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會再見到我\N{\fs14}you will never see me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.42,0:24:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的生命中很少有人\N{\fs14}There are very few people in my life
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.78,0:24:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠讓我有足夠的時間見到第二次\N{\fs14}that I have enough time to see more than once,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.78,0:24:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是其中之一\N{\fs14}and you are not one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.88,0:24:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fs14}Trust me,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.36,0:24:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不會有任何影響\N{\fs14}that's not going to matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.50,0:25:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么要這么做?\N{\fs14}Why are you doing all of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.18,0:25:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑電腦?\N{\fs14}The hack?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.72,0:25:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么你和我們一起行動?\N{\fs14}Why are you working with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.56,0:25:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還剩50小時20分鐘\N{\fs14}50 hours and 20 minutes left.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.84,0:25:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要搞明白這件事\N{\fs14}I need to figure this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.22,0:25:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉迪恩一直都在暗中窺視我\N{\fs14}Gideon's been spying on me the whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.24,0:25:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜罐技術 我靠\N{\fs14}Honeypot service order, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.24,0:25:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在得行動了\N{\fs14}I gotta do that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.80,0:25:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全令牌 吉迪恩的手機\N{\fs14}Security token. Gideon's phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.40,0:25:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要他的手機\N{\fs14}I need his phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.68,0:25:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還剩50小時19分鐘\N{\fs14}50 hours and 19 minutes left.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.24,0:25:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死 她的時間偏執癥傳染到我了\N{\fs14}Damn, she infected me with her time paranoia.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.82,0:25:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都生活在互相的偏執癥里\N{\fs14}We're all living in each other's paranoia.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.34,0:25:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定無法否定這個\N{\fs14}You definitely can't argue that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.46,0:25:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這難道就是為什么人們相互回避嗎?\N{\fs14}Is that why everyone tries to avoid each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.34,0:25:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要冷靜下來\N{\fs14}I need to calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.78,0:25:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望我能成為像你那樣的觀察家\N{\fs14}I wish I could be an observer like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.82,0:25:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就能更冷靜的思考\N{\fs14}Then I could think more calmly.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.26,0:25:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這很舒服\N{\fs14}This is comfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.80,0:26:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那么多壓力\N{\fs14}Less stressful.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.80,0:26:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事實上 我覺得我能夠看見所有事\N{\fs14}In fact, I feel like I can see everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.76,0:26:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解所有事 以這種舒服的方式\N{\fs14}know everything this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.19,0:26:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fs14}Hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.06,0:26:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我知道更多嗎?\N{\fs14}Do you know more than me?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.18,0:26:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不公平\N{\fs14}That wouldn't be fair,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.12,0:26:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的想象力比我知道更多\N{\fs14}my imaginary friend knowing more than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.18,0:26:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你現在可以干什么?\N{\fs14}So what would you do now?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.22,0:26:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要一個干擾來拿到吉迪恩手機\N{\fs14}We need a distraction to get Gideon's phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.62,0:26:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳 我需要你做點事\N{\fs14}Darlene, I need you to do something for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.30,0:26:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她能幫上忙\N{\fs14}She can help.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.32,0:26:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在Allstate的我老板 吉迪恩\N{\fs14}My boss at Allstate, Gideon--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.96,0:26:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候\N{\fs14}Sometimes it's hard
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.06,0:26:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽一個解釋很難\N{\fs14}to listen to an explanation,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.96,0:26:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是來自自己的解釋\N{\fs14}even when it's from myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.96,0:26:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是自己做出的解釋\N{\fs14}Especially when it's from myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.56,0:26:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果只是注意我需要做什么\N{\fs14}It would be so much easier
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.58,0:26:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會簡單很多\N{\fs14}to only pay attention when I needed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.08,0:26:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了\N{\fs14}To just--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.84,0:26:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得出一個結論\N{\fs14}Arrive at the conclusion.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.76,0:26:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你所做的事嗎?\N{\fs14}Is that what you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.28,0:27:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,100份MMS文件傳送到吉迪恩的手機上\N{\fs14}100 large MMS files to Gideon's phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.40,0:27:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耗盡它\N{\fs14}Drained it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.54,0:27:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,企業貪婪是一個向下流的欲望\N{\fs14}Corporate greed is a trickle down desire
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.60,0:27:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它甚至會留向食物鏈的最低端\N{\fs14}that reaches even the bottom of the food chain.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.66,0:27:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 為了什么 - 財富? - 什么鬼? - 權利?\N{\fs14}- And for what? - Wealth? - What the shit? - Power?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.96,0:28:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是個令人悲傷的寓言故事\N{\fs14}It's a pathetic fable,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.70,0:28:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們 萬安公司 是這個可憐貪婪的辯護人\N{\fs14}and you, Allsafe, are a defender of this pitiful avarice.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.20,0:28:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 F社會知道我們\N{\fs14}Holy shit, fsociety knows us.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.72,0:28:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你們的美夢結束了\N{\fs14}But your sweet dream is over,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.46,0:28:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們的噩夢現在才剛剛開始\N{\fs14}and your nightmare is about to begin.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.74,0:28:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們已經贏了 讓那些串通一氣的...\N{\fs14}We have won.Let those who are complicit...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.82,0:28:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在發生了什么?\N{\fs14}What the hell's happening now?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.32,0:28:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些援助專橫暴君的人\N{\fs14}Those who aid the tyrants,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.54,0:28:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些接受暴虐的人\N{\fs14}those who accept the tyranny
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.52,0:28:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在新的統治下沒有地位\N{\fs14}have no place in the new order.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.88,0:28:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個干擾是短暫的\N{\fs14}The distraction is momentary.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.18,0:28:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望我需要的\N{\fs14}Hopefully all I need.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.88,0:28:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會知道我們的正義\N{\fs14}They will know our justice,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.94,0:28:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不會表現一點仁慈\N{\fs14}and we will show no mercy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.96,0:28:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉迪恩 戈達德 你對你的企業\N{\fs14}Gideon Goddard, you are a lackey
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.02,0:28:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是男仆\N{\fs14}to your corporate overlords.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.66,0:28:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來人把它關掉\N{\fs14}Someone shut this off.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.98,0:28:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為壓榨無辜者的人\N{\fs14}Defending those
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.04,0:28:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辯護\N{\fs14}that bleed the innocent.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.12,0:28:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為他們服務\N{\fs14}Serving them, slave to master.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.02,0:28:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遙控沒有反應\N{\fs14}It's ignoring the remote.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.48,0:28:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們黑進了我們的智能電視\N{\fs14}They hacked our smart TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.78,0:28:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝賀你 戈達德先生\N{\fs14}Congratulations, Mr. Goddard.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.54,0:28:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個被放上了我們的網站\N{\fs14}It's posted to our website.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.70,0:28:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有YouTube\N{\fs14}And YouTube.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.64,0:28:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很快會被完結\N{\fs14}You will soon be finished.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.90,0:28:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,90秒之內這個密碼會改變\N{\fs14}In 90 seconds this code will change.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.74,0:28:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我沒有在那之前用我的電腦登陸\N{\fs14}If I don't log in with it on my computer before then,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.16,0:28:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會丟失所有東西\N{\fs14}I'll lose everything to time.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.82,0:28:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們把你的角色公告天下\N{\fs14}We are exposing your role to the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.76,0:29:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 讓它結束\N{\fs14}No, let it finish.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.38,0:29:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整個世界會很生氣\N{\fs14}And the world is very angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.18,0:29:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,60秒 白玫瑰是對的\N{\fs14}60 seconds. Whiterose was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.22,0:29:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們從一個截止時間到另一個截止時間來回奔波\N{\fs14}We run from one deadline to the next.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.60,0:29:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特在哪里?\N{\fs14}Where's Elliot?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.06,0:29:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么?\N{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.14,0:29:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做本地備份\N{\fs14}I was working on the local backups.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.84,0:29:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不和我們一起在那看?\N{\fs14}Why weren't you in there with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.74,0:29:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很擔心--\N{\fs14}I was worried about the--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.24,0:29:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這說不通啊\N{\fs14}It just doesn't add up.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.50,0:29:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些事一直在發生\N{\fs14}All these events keep happening
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.74,0:29:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論你在不在\N{\fs14}around your appearance, your disappearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.52,0:29:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 吉迪恩 - 別說了\N{\fs14}- Gideon-- - Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.00,0:29:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想聽到\N{\fs14}I don't wanna hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.48,0:29:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個公司的每個員工站在那里\N{\fs14}Every member in this company stood in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.94,0:29:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著最糟糕的事情發生在萬安公司身上\N{\fs14}watching the single worst thing that's happened to Allsafe,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.24,0:29:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你在哪里? 在你的小隔間?\N{\fs14}and where are you, at your cubicle?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.48,0:29:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做著什么?\N{\fs14}Doing what?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.82,0:30:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 吉迪恩 我不是有意打擾...\N{\fs14}Uh, Gideon, I hate to interrupt...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.40,0:30:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 現在不行 奧利\N{\fs14}No, not now, Ollie.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.94,0:30:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是邪惡公司的電話\N{\fs14}But Evil Corp's on the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.52,0:30:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會回來\N{\fs14}I'll be back.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.90,0:30:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還沒說完\N{\fs14}We're not finished here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.44,0:30:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.55,0:30:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為我沒有及時的輸入密碼\N{\fs14}You thought I didn't put the code in time,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.54,0:30:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我得快點把它藏起來在吉迪恩看見之前\N{\fs14}but I had to hide it quickly before Gideon saw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.86,0:30:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起\N{\fs14}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.40,0:30:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告訴過你我在黑入吉迪恩時看見了什么嗎?\N{\fs14}Have I told you what I saw when I hacked Gideon?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.90,0:30:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我瞥見他的秘密時?\N{\fs14}When I peeked into his secrets?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.00,0:30:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到一善良誠實的人\N{\fs14}I saw a good, honest man.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.46,0:30:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉迪恩錯了\N{\fs14}Gideon was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.68,0:30:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完成了這兒的使命\N{\fs14}I am finished here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.46,0:30:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不適合他也不屬于這個地方\N{\fs14}I'm no good for him or this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.86,0:30:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只保護自己的人\N{\fs14}He was only protecting his people.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.82,0:30:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我呢?\N{\fs14}But me?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.32,0:30:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所做的一切是為了保護每個人\N{\fs14}I'm doing this to protect everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.93,0:31:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來你最近很忙碌啊\N{\fs14}Seems you've been very busy lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.92,0:31:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得知道你計劃是什么\N{\fs14}I have to know what you're planning.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.64,0:31:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們注定是盟友啊\N{\fs14}We were meant to be allies.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.84,0:31:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或許我們想要的東西是一樣的\N{\fs14}We might just want the same thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.82,0:31:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想加入其中\N{\fs14}and I need to be involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.48,0:31:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢說你大錯特錯了 我的朋友\N{\fs14}I'm pretty positive you're dead wrong about that, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.58,0:31:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們要達成一致是很困難的\N{\fs14}I don't think there's anything we could possibly agree on.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.52,0:31:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你在玩兒什么把戲\N{\fs14}I don't know what game you're playing,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.60,0:31:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我勸你廢話少說\N{\fs14}but I suggest you cut the bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.48,0:31:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒有別的啥事兒 我想我們就聊到這兒吧\N{\fs14}If there's nothing else, I think we're done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.16,0:31:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道你忘記了我可是知道你那骯臟小秘密的人?\N{\fs14}Aren't you forgetting that I know your dirty little secret?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.38,0:31:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你周圍的人要是知道了你的把柄\N{\fs14}There are people close to you that wouldn't be happy
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.44,0:31:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕不會太開心吧\N{\fs14}if they knew what I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.84,0:31:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都是聰明人 不可能受擺布于\N{\fs14}We're both too smart to allow pettiness
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.34,0:31:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些小事的\N{\fs14}to dictate our actions.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.44,0:31:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們肯定比那有能耐吧\N{\fs14}We're better than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.10,0:31:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,權衡一下利弊吧\N{\fs14}Weigh the pros and cons.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.16,0:31:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做你該做的\N{\fs14}Do what you need to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.00,0:31:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦表格的事兒結束\N{\fs14}As soon as the tabulations are over with,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.94,0:31:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就會知道告訴別人這件事兒\N{\fs14}you'll know that telling anyone about that
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.76,0:32:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我們大家都沒有好處\N{\fs14}does neither one of us any good.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.06,0:32:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上 你應該有自覺\N{\fs14}In fact, you'll realize
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.50,0:32:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在你的位置上做任何事兒\N{\fs14}that the only thing to do in your position
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.18,0:32:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說都不是事兒\N{\fs14}when it comes to me is nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.68,0:34:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好 威力克先生 我是庫特蘭德警探\N{\fs14}Good evening, Mr. Wellick. I'm Detective Quattlander.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.22,0:34:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是瓊斯警探\N{\fs14}This is Detective Jones.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.22,0:34:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很清楚\N{\fs14}As I know you're aware,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.80,0:34:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們今天想和你在你的辦公室談談\N{\fs14}we were hoping to speak with you at your office today,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.40,0:34:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你的助手說你出去了\N{\fs14}but your assistant said you're out.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.82,0:34:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事?\N{\fs14}What's this about?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.06,0:34:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在調查一個殺手\N{\fs14}We're investigating a murder
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.66,0:34:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他出現在你丈夫工作的地方 女士\N{\fs14}that occurred at your husband's place of employment, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.88,0:34:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能進去談嗎?\N{\fs14}May we please come in?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.38,0:34:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺手?\N{\fs14}A murder?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.86,0:34:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 麻煩你說英語 好嗎?\N{\fs14}Ma'am, do you mind speaking in English, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.54,0:34:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你們這樣不合適吧\N{\fs14}I think this is inappropriate,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.96,0:34:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣唐突地來我家 讓我的妻子擔心\N{\fs14}you coming to my house like this, upsetting my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.18,0:34:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天回去我的辦公室--\N{\fs14}I will be in my office tomorrow--
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.74,0:34:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生 要知道現在可是非常時期\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick, as you can imagine this is very time sensitive.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.54,0:34:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只需要問你一些問題\N{\fs14}We just need to ask you a few questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.66,0:34:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上 你們兩都要問 因為你兩\N{\fs14}Actually, both of you, since you were both
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.40,0:34:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都出席了昨晚的招待會\N{\fs14}in attendance at the reception last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.86,0:34:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我向你保證 我們真的一點點相關信息都沒有\N{\fs14}Yeah, I can assure you, we have no information whatsoever.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.16,0:34:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一點兒時間\N{\fs14}It will only take a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.30,0:34:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你們都認識死者 夏倫 諾斯\N{\fs14}And you both did know the deceased, Sharon Knowles.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.44,0:35:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確實認識她吧?\N{\fs14}You did know her, yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.32,0:35:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎朗 諾爾斯?\N{\fs14}Sharon Knowles?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.48,0:35:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這真可怕\N{\fs14}That's terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.70,0:35:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃...\N{\fs14}Um...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.60,0:35:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是 我們認識她\N{\fs14}Yes, yes, we did know her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.32,0:35:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進\N{\fs14}Please, come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.24,0:35:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請坐 需要點兒啥嗎?\N{\fs14}Have a seat. Can I get you anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.10,0:35:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡? 茶?\N{\fs14}Coffee? Tea?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.46,0:35:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡就好\N{\fs14}Coffee would be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.84,0:35:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶 如果有草本的更好 謝謝\N{\fs14}Tea. Herbal if possible, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.10,0:35:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生 昨晚你最后一次\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick, what time did you last see
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.08,0:35:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看見夏倫 諾斯是什么時候?\N{\fs14}Sharon Knowles last night?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.04,0:35:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生?\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.54,0:35:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好嗎?\N{\fs14}Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.30,0:35:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬安娜?\N{\fs14}Joanna?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.96,0:35:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寶寶好像要出生了\N{\fs14}I think the baby's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.32,0:36:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得送她去醫院\N{\fs14}We gotta get her to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.09,0:36:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,氣候控制系統黑得怎么樣了?\N{\fs14}How'd it go with the climate control hack?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.54,0:36:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞定了\N{\fs14}Handled.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.60,0:36:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我確實聰明又能干\N{\fs14}I happen to be really smart and good at things.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.12,0:36:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你也不在乎這些\N{\fs14}Not like you give a shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.10,0:36:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們應該為此慶祝慶祝嘍\N{\fs14}We should celebrate then.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.95,0:36:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再過整整43小時\N{\fs14}In 43 hours, exactly,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.76,0:37:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的服務器將不再只是蜜罐系統陷阱\N{\fs14}our server will no longer be a honeypot.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.02,0:37:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你編的隱匿程序\N{\fs14}And that rootkit you wrote
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.78,0:37:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將會打垮邪惡公司\N{\fs14}will take down Evil Corp.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.34,0:37:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳 我們總算成功了\N{\fs14}We did it, Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.86,0:37:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定會的\N{\fs14}It's gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.54,0:37:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們真的在這樣做嗎?\N{\fs14}We're really doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.05,0:37:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天哪\N{\fs14}Oh, my God!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.75,0:37:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太高興了!\N{\fs14}Be happy!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.82,0:37:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那多虧了你\N{\fs14}You did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.00,0:37:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧了你啊\N{\fs14}You did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.96,0:37:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 你就要\N{\fs14}Just like that, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.29,0:37:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改變世界啦\N{\fs14}you're gonna change the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.33,0:37:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我們一起做到的\N{\fs14}We did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.97,0:37:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想獨占這個功勞的\N{\fs14}I would love to take credit on this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.82,0:37:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能\N{\fs14}But I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.71,0:37:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說真的 這確實是你的功勞啊\N{\fs14}No, really, this was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.62,0:38:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫無置疑 你確實是我見過的最厲害的人\N{\fs14}You are seriously the best person I know,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.85,0:38:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎?\N{\fs14}you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.19,0:38:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是太愛你了\N{\fs14}I love you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.64,0:38:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天哪 伊利艾特! 你搞什么啊?\N{\fs14}Oh, my God, Elliot! What the f---?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.97,0:38:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我很抱歉\N{\fs14}I'm--I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.10,0:38:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是怎么了?\N{\fs14}What the hell is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.17,0:38:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.64,0:38:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉 我以為\N{\fs14}I'm sorry, I thought--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.27,0:38:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\fs14}I just--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.01,0:38:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很對不起\N{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.88,0:38:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天哪 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Oh, my God, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.21,0:38:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又忘了么?\N{\fs14}Did you forget again?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.75,0:38:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘記我是誰了嗎?\N{\fs14}Did you forget who I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.09,0:38:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什么?\N{\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.63,0:38:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘記什么?\N{\fs14}Forget what?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.10,0:38:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 我想讓你告訴我你把我看做誰\N{\fs14}Elliot, I need you to tell me who you think I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.23,0:38:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什么啊?\N{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.14,0:39:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點告訴我\N{\fs14}Tell me right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.14,0:39:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白你在說什么\N{\fs14}What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.15,0:39:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.25,0:39:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當然 當然沒忘記\N{\fs14}Of course I didn't-- didn't forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.16,0:39:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是戴琳\N{\fs14}You're Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.70,0:39:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是戴琳啊\N{\fs14}You're Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.10,0:39:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.38,0:39:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是戴琳\N{\fs14}You're Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.71,0:39:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的\N{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.98,0:39:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂她要說什么了\N{\fs14}I know what she's going to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.71,0:39:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你的\N{\fs14}I'm your...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.72,0:39:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹\N{\fs14}Sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.75,0:39:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的妹妹\N{\fs14}You're my sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.51,0:40:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳曾和我整天躲在電影院里\N{\fs14}Darlene and I'd hide in movie theaters all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.98,0:40:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她總是會唱歌\N{\fs14}Darlene would sing
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.22,0:40:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她曾經在我們的家里玩滑板車\N{\fs14}She rode her scooter in front of our house.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.92,0:40:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要崩潰了 我要瘋了 瘋了\N{\fs14}I'm crazy.I'm crazy--crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.49,0:40:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她三年級時曾試圖逃跑\N{\fs14}She tried to run away in the third grade.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.02,0:40:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么會不記得這些了呢?\N{\fs14}How come I didn't remember this?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.69,0:40:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽對我們不好的時候我們會睡在同一張床上\N{\fs14}Slept in the same bed when our mom was mean to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.79,0:40:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么會忘記呢? 我記得她的聲音的\N{\fs14}Why did I forget? I remember her voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.53,0:40:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么能夠忘記呢? 我要瘋掉了\N{\fs14}How could I forget? I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.16,0:40:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要發瘋了 瘋了 我快瘋了 瘋了 我絕對是瘋了\N{\fs14}I'm crazy--crazy-- I'm crazy--crazy--I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.73,0:40:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你難道瘋了嗎?\N{\fs14}Are you freaking out?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.17,0:40:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快告訴我事實\N{\fs14}Tell me the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.90,0:40:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以來你都是這樣想的嗎?\N{\fs14}Were you in on this the whole time?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.87,0:40:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?\N{\fs14}Were you?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.24,0:40:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快想想 該死的 快回想下\N{\fs14}Think, God damn it. Think.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.71,0:40:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能就這樣輕易忘記她呢?\N{\fs14}How can I just forget her like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.21,0:40:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是一個人啊 有著難以改變的關系啊\N{\fs14}A whole person. A relationship.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.18,0:40:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算是健忘癥嗎?\N{\fs14}Is this amnesia?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.58,0:40:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還有什么不記得了呢?\N{\fs14}What else am I not remembering?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.65,0:40:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要崩潰了\N{\fs14}I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.64,0:40:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本該繼續吃藥的\N{\fs14}I should have stayed on the meds.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.18,0:40:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要瘋了 我要得失心瘋了\N{\fs14}I'm crazy.I'm out of my mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.72,0:40:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂 我真是不該把你創造出來\N{\fs14}I knew it, I should have never created you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.76,0:40:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該聽聽克里斯塔的話的\N{\fs14}I should have listened to Krista.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.83,0:41:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在逃避自己\N{\fs14}I avoid myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.16,0:41:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么?\N{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.56,0:41:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好害怕\N{\fs14}I'm afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.20,0:41:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.27,0:41:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕什么?\N{\fs14}Afraid of what?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.77,0:41:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕發現太多\N{\fs14}Finding too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.57,0:41:14.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太少 發現不了\N{\fs14}Too little. Nothing at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.64,0:41:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的存在嗎?\N{\fs14}Do I even exist?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.71,0:41:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著我 伊利艾特 奧爾德森\N{\fs14}See me, Elliot Alderson.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.25,0:41:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在你眼前\N{\fs14}I am here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.05,0:41:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我要走了\N{\fs14}Now I'm gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.83,0:41:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須深挖一下\N{\fs14}We have to hack...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.00,0:41:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的信息\N{\fs14}me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.89,0:42:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都沒了\N{\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.23,0:42:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沒身份\N{\fs14}No identity.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.03,0:42:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全就是個鬼魂啊\N{\fs14}I'm a ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.56,0:42:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛剛是不是把自己刪掉了?\N{\fs14}Did I erase myself?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:25.16,0:44:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們有必要談談\N{\fs14}I think we should talk.
