22
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,000
機器人先生 前情提要

23
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:01,000
大家字幕組 傾情譯制

24
00:00:27,000 --> 00:00:29,000
翻譯    墳老絲  Serafina

25
00:00:29,000 --> 00:00:31,000
翻譯    墳老絲  Serafina

26
00:00:31,000 --> 00:00:33,000
翻譯    Silent Bob  芫荽

27
00:00:33,000 --> 00:00:35,000
翻譯    Silent Bob  芫荽

28
00:00:35,000 --> 00:00:37,000
翻譯    哎喲我去  坑坑

29
00:00:37,000 --> 00:00:39,000
翻譯    哎喲我去  坑坑

30
00:00:39,000 --> 00:00:41,000
翻譯    條子

31
00:00:41,000 --> 00:00:43,000
翻譯    條子

32
00:00:43,000 --> 00:00:45,000
校對    LilBear

33
00:00:45,000 --> 00:00:47,000
校對    LilBear

34
00:00:47,000 --> 00:00:49,000
時間軸 & 特效    柯迪夫  沒啦

35
00:00:49,000 --> 00:00:51,000
時間軸 & 特效    柯迪夫  沒啦

36
00:00:51,000 --> 00:00:53,000
壓制    宋胖子

37
00:00:53,000 --> 00:00:55,000
壓制    宋胖子

38
00:00:55,000 --> 00:00:57,000
監制    LilBear  嵬森  坑坑

39
00:00:57,000 --> 00:00:59,000
監制    LilBear  嵬森  坑坑

40
00:05:17,740 --> 00:05:23,190
機器人先生

41
00:05:17,740 --> 00:05:23,190
第一季  第八集

42
00:44:20,000 --> 00:44:29,000
本字幕由大家字幕組原創翻譯
僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
彼以國士待我 我以國士待之
用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人
有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們
請聯系：dajiazimuzu@163.com

43
00:07:57,320 --> 00:07:59,000
羅伊德

44
00:07:57,320 --> 00:07:59,000
萬安公司被侵入了

45
00:11:57,000 --> 00:11:59,000
給辦公室回電話!急

46
00:11:57,000 --> 00:11:59,000
整個網絡癱瘓了

47
00:12:53,000 --> 00:12:54,000
沒 有 權 限

48
00:16:31,000 --> 00:16:32,000
已發郵件

49
00:16:32,000 --> 00:16:35,000
至: 安吉拉 莫斯      夠了! 這次黑客行動是你的錯!!!

50
00:16:32,000 --> 00:16:35,000
至: 安吉拉 莫斯      我要復仇

51
00:16:32,000 --> 00:16:35,000
至: 安吉拉 莫斯      你看- 這是你想要的嗎?!?!

52
00:16:45,000 --> 00:16:48,040
你怎么還在家? 慶典就在今晚 你沒多少時間了

53
00:16:48,360 --> 00:16:53,240
勒索這種事兒太捉摸不定了 無法保證能成功

54
00:16:53,640 --> 00:16:56,680
她這么輕易的動搖了你的信心?

55
00:16:56,800 --> 00:16:59,840
你只是睡了她而已 沒必要那么害怕

56
00:17:00,040 --> 00:17:02,080
我想你應該已經拍下了需要拍的照片了

57
00:17:02,080 --> 00:17:06,440
我們得重新分析件事情的重點 想其他辦法

58
00:17:06,440 --> 00:17:08,240
我們有辦法

59
00:17:08,960 --> 00:17:11,880
斯科特知道公司經不起另一起丑聞

60
00:17:11,880 --> 00:17:13,560
尤其是在公司盈利報告期間

61
00:17:13,560 --> 00:17:15,400
這是我們最好的時機

62
00:17:15,800 --> 00:17:17,320
他必然會降職

63
00:17:17,340 --> 00:17:20,040
普萊斯就別無選擇只能任命你為首席技術官了

64
00:17:20,060 --> 00:17:21,560
沒必要把事情復雜化

65
00:17:36,440 --> 00:17:40,440
我們付出多少努力才走到今天

66
00:17:41,760 --> 00:17:44,400
別在關鍵時刻泄氣

67
00:20:42,330 --> 00:20:46,000
布蘭科的硬盤

68
00:20:42,330 --> 00:20:46,000
數據恢復服務

69
00:21:43,000 --> 00:21:44,000
無服務

70
00:03:15,000 --> 00:03:17,000
工商管理碩士

71
00:03:15,000 --> 00:03:17,000
2007年7月7日

72
00:30:23,760 --> 00:30:27,760
請去除在CS30服務器上的蜂蜜陷阱并恢復其正常連接

73
00:30:54,480 --> 00:30:57,320
收到請求 請允許48小時的時間去完成操作

74
00:32:20,730 --> 00:32:21,800
這是什么?

75
00:32:26,440 --> 00:32:29,760
我是打算恭喜你來著 但你這樣一點兒都不鼓舞人心

76
00:32:30,300 --> 00:32:31,600
恭喜我?

77
00:32:32,380 --> 00:32:34,820
你的助手打來電話 說慶祝會取消了

78
00:32:35,240 --> 00:32:37,240
我以為或許你的行動

79
00:32:38,360 --> 00:32:43,560
昨晚真的有了起色 即使你不想告訴我

80
00:32:43,880 --> 00:32:45,840
他拒絕了那個職務?

81
00:32:45,940 --> 00:32:49,640
現在無所謂了

82
00:32:50,180 --> 00:32:51,380
無所謂了?

83
00:32:51,480 --> 00:32:52,720
真的沒關系

84
00:32:54,260 --> 00:32:55,680
真的無所謂

85
00:33:00,980 --> 00:33:05,240
我們被一個目光短淺的錯誤人選蒙蔽了雙眼

86
00:33:06,300 --> 00:33:10,820
幾個月前 我看見一個技術員 一個你永遠不會懷疑的人

87
00:33:11,220 --> 00:33:14,660
利用別人的一個快捷方式

88
00:33:14,760 --> 00:33:16,400
什么快捷方式?

89
00:33:16,520 --> 00:33:18,360
這就是問題所在

90
00:33:18,640 --> 00:33:20,840
我一開始以為只是個小小的報復

91
00:33:21,860 --> 00:33:26,440
但不是 這個快捷鍵指向一個更大的東西 更宏偉的東西 更漂亮的東西

92
00:33:26,740 --> 00:33:29,040
我們一直以來只關注眼前的事物

93
00:33:29,360 --> 00:33:33,440
但我們一直忽視了眼睛上方的東西

94
00:33:35,320 --> 00:33:36,800
我們上面的東西是?

95
00:33:37,660 --> 00:33:38,540
上帝

96
00:33:43,120 --> 00:33:45,160
告訴我接下來怎么了 蒂雷爾

97
00:33:46,540 --> 00:33:49,040
是你把我逼到這個地步的

98
00:33:50,920 --> 00:33:52,120
起來

99
00:33:52,860 --> 00:33:54,280
去開門

100
00:34:30,280 --> 00:34:32,320
他在說什么?

101
00:36:09,300 --> 00:36:13,780
我不會讓他們帶你走 你不能離開我們

102
00:00:00,430 --> 00:00:03,000
他們在中國的東方數據中心的數據備份
The redundant backups at their eastern data center in China,

103
00:00:03,000 --> 00:00:04,640
由黑暗軍團幫我們搞定
the Dark Army is covering us on that.

104
00:00:04,680 --> 00:00:05,680
我們現在就可以行動!
We can go now!

105
00:00:05,700 --> 00:00:07,100
如果我們開始了而他們按兵不動
If we move forward and they don't,

106
00:00:07,140 --> 00:00:09,200
中國方面的備份信息還在
China still holds all the redundant information.

107
00:00:09,260 --> 00:00:10,340
這一切都將是無用功
It will be pointless.

108
00:00:10,360 --> 00:00:12,120
要是我們可以和白玫瑰面談的話--
If we can talk to whiterose directly--

109
00:00:12,140 --> 00:00:13,960
他是不可能和你見面的
No way he's meeting you face to face.

110
00:00:13,960 --> 00:00:15,780
你們這些笨蛋的愿望居然實現了
You fools actually got your wish.

111
00:00:15,840 --> 00:00:17,740
我不知道意義何在 不過至少你們可以見一面了
I don't know why, but the meeting's actually gonna be on.

112
00:00:17,760 --> 00:00:18,880
我很想告訴你讓你小心點
I'd tell you to be careful,

113
00:00:18,920 --> 00:00:20,820
但我知道你一向莽撞
but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.

114
00:00:20,920 --> 00:00:23,680
我讓系統管理員再檢查了一次服務器
I had the sysadmin check that server again.

115
00:00:23,720 --> 00:00:25,320
當然也沒發現啥
Of course, there was nothing.

116
00:00:25,360 --> 00:00:27,560
我完全不知道有什么可疑的
I have no idea what there was to even be suspicious about.

117
00:00:27,600 --> 00:00:29,220
怎么我的工作證在你那?
Why do you have my work ID?

118
00:00:29,280 --> 00:00:31,460
我放了一張惡意含惡意軟件的CD在我辦公室的電腦里
I placed a malicious CD in my work computer.

119
00:00:31,480 --> 00:00:33,320
我要你為我做件事
I need you to do something for me.

120
00:00:33,340 --> 00:00:36,280
歡迎我們新上任的首席技術官
Our new Chief Technology Officer,

121
00:00:36,440 --> 00:00:37,820
斯考特 諾斯
Scott Knowles.

122
00:00:37,840 --> 00:00:40,380
今晚在天臺和我單獨見一面
Meet me tonight, on the roof.

123
00:00:40,420 --> 00:00:42,040
攝像頭三月就壞了
Cameras have been out since March.

124
00:00:42,120 --> 00:00:43,220
沒有人會知道
No one will know.

125
00:00:47,460 --> 00:00:49,020
別這樣!
Stop!

126
00:01:18,980 --> 00:01:21,440
如果這一切都消失了會怎樣?
What if this all went away?

127
00:01:21,840 --> 00:01:23,940
整個城市
The city.

128
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:25,360
所有的錢
The money.

129
00:01:26,000 --> 00:01:27,480
一切的一切
All of it.

130
00:01:27,640 --> 00:01:30,580
比如發生了喪尸末日之類的情況?
What, like a zombie apocalypse or something?

131
00:01:30,670 --> 00:01:33,280
我的意思是一場革命
More like a revolution.

132
00:01:34,560 --> 00:01:35,960
上次我們一起勾搭的時候
Last time we hooked up,

133
00:01:36,020 --> 00:01:38,060
我們說好了不談政治
we agreed to check politics at the door.

134
00:01:38,100 --> 00:01:39,580
現在再也沒有中產階級了
There's no middle anymore.

135
00:01:39,820 --> 00:01:42,020
只有土豪和屌絲
Just rich and poor.

136
00:01:42,340 --> 00:01:45,200
大早上的談這話題太沉重了
Okay, this shit is way too heavy for me this early.

137
00:01:45,260 --> 00:01:45,980
我要去上班了
I gotta go to work.

138
00:01:46,040 --> 00:01:46,760
好吧
Right.

139
00:01:46,860 --> 00:01:48,680
你要一頁紙一頁紙地
Solving the world's problems

140
00:01:48,720 --> 00:01:50,820
去解決整個世界的問題
one spreadsheet at a time.

141
00:01:51,340 --> 00:01:53,900
夠了啊 我們不做就是政府去做
Hey, it's either suits like me or the government.

142
00:01:53,980 --> 00:01:55,560
我們都知道他們做事有多厲害
We all know how well they handle things.

143
00:01:55,660 --> 00:01:57,660
為什么這個世界就不能好好地自己轉下去?
Why can't the world just take care of itself?

144
00:01:58,280 --> 00:02:00,700
因為世界上愚蠢的人太多
Because the world is filled with stupid people.

145
00:02:00,800 --> 00:02:03,040
而我的聰明是錢砸出來的
And I get paid a lot to be smart.

146
00:02:04,060 --> 00:02:05,200
嘿
Hey.

147
00:02:06,740 --> 00:02:08,960
世上不僅僅只有富人和窮人
There's not just the rich and the poor.

148
00:02:09,720 --> 00:02:12,020
還有你 在中間的某個地方
There's you, in the middle somewhere.

149
00:02:12,180 --> 00:02:14,280
一個完美的生存者
The consummate survivor.

150
00:03:45,280 --> 00:03:49,280
我--我現在在上芭蕾課
I--I'm in a ballet class right now.

151
00:03:51,280 --> 00:03:54,500
不行 奧利 我現在不能和你討論這個問題
No, Ollie, I can't talk to you about this right now.

152
00:03:56,380 --> 00:03:59,200
我不管 奧利
I don't care, Ollie.

153
00:04:00,280 --> 00:04:03,080
我不管你碰到了誰
I don't care who you ran into

154
00:04:03,140 --> 00:04:04,760
或是他說了些什么
or what he said.

155
00:04:06,560 --> 00:04:08,060
我...
I...

156
00:04:15,060 --> 00:04:16,300
抱歉
Sorry.

157
00:04:16,540 --> 00:04:19,200
請告訴我你們不會復合
Tell me you're not getting back together with him.

158
00:04:19,300 --> 00:04:20,820
天 當然不會
Jesus, no.

159
00:04:21,260 --> 00:04:23,960
肯定不 只是些工作上的事
No. Just leftover work stuff.

160
00:04:24,760 --> 00:04:26,640
你和伊利艾特談了嗎?
Have you talked to Elliot?

161
00:04:26,700 --> 00:04:28,200
昨天聊了
Yesterday.

162
00:04:28,720 --> 00:04:30,460
感覺好像他在試著振作
Seems like he's pulling himself together,

163
00:04:30,500 --> 00:04:33,060
你也知道他那個樣子
but you know how he is.

164
00:04:33,080 --> 00:04:35,100
感覺我時時刻刻都在擔心他
It feels like I'm always worried about him.

165
00:04:35,180 --> 00:04:36,760
- 你知道嗎? - 我懂
- You know? - Yeah.

166
00:04:36,790 --> 00:04:38,330
他這個月糟透了
He's had a shitty month.

167
00:04:38,360 --> 00:04:40,060
是這20年都糟透了
Or 20 years.

168
00:04:40,100 --> 00:04:41,660
你選一個吧
Take your pick.

169
00:04:41,700 --> 00:04:42,970
那為什么到頭來
Then why are we the ones

170
00:04:43,000 --> 00:04:45,670
坐立不安的反而是我們?
that always end up so stressed?

171
00:04:45,700 --> 00:04:48,940
設想一下你在兒時的臥室里醒來
Try waking up in your childhood bedroom,

172
00:04:48,970 --> 00:04:51,570
然后乘坐2個小時的公交
then taking Jersey transit for two hours

173
00:04:51,610 --> 00:04:54,860
來上市區里7點的芭蕾課
to make a 7:00 ballet class in the city.

174
00:04:55,450 --> 00:04:57,380
至少
Well, silver lining,

175
00:04:57,480 --> 00:04:59,280
你可以見到我
you get to see moi.

176
00:04:59,360 --> 00:05:01,400
好了 各位 第一個動作
All right, everyone, first position.

177
00:05:25,310 --> 00:05:27,220
我傷害了克里斯塔
I hurt Krista.

178
00:05:27,400 --> 00:05:29,420
我不太好受
I don't feel good about that.

179
00:05:29,540 --> 00:05:31,560
我希望你沒有生我的氣
I hope you're not mad at me.

180
00:05:31,680 --> 00:05:33,480
但你必須承認
But you have to admit,

181
00:05:33,520 --> 00:05:35,250
她和其他人一樣
she's just like everyone else.

182
00:05:35,500 --> 00:05:37,980
不敢看墻外面的東西
Too afraid to peek over their walls

183
00:05:38,040 --> 00:05:40,490
因為害怕可能會看到的東西
for fear of what they might see.

184
00:05:50,100 --> 00:05:51,530
而我不一樣
Not me.

185
00:05:52,060 --> 00:05:53,870
我專門做這樣的事
That's what I do.

186
00:05:54,340 --> 00:05:56,180
我會去窺視
I look.

187
00:06:14,420 --> 00:06:17,430
你把大家都找回來了嗎?
Did you get everybody back?

188
00:07:07,640 --> 00:07:09,880
讓他使用正確的命令
Tell him to follow the proper commands,

189
00:07:09,960 --> 00:07:11,800
不然步驟不會啟動
or the sequence won't initiate.

190
00:07:23,590 --> 00:07:26,380
利用我們植入的單片機的后門
Using the backdoor we planted with our raspberry pie.

191
00:07:26,460 --> 00:07:28,960
我的個神 你這些弄了多久了?
Jesus Christ, man, how long have you been sitting on all this?

192
00:07:29,000 --> 00:07:30,860
四個星期前我裝了個補丁
I installed a patch four weeks ago,

193
00:07:30,880 --> 00:07:32,140
然后每天都在監測
and I've been monitoring it daily.

194
00:07:32,200 --> 00:07:33,400
罪人無眠
No rest for the wicked.

195
00:07:33,440 --> 00:07:35,660
我想確認在和白玫瑰見面前
I wanted to make sure it was all updated

196
00:07:35,720 --> 00:07:37,280
鐵山各個新的地點
at the Steel Mountain locations

197
00:07:37,320 --> 00:07:39,240
都更新好了
before the meeting with whiterose.

198
00:07:39,280 --> 00:07:41,260
對啊 那些空調公司的人太傻了
Yeah, those Airdream guys are so dumb.

199
00:07:41,280 --> 00:07:44,760
有誰會把所有恒溫器控制放在同一個網絡上?
Who has all their thermostats phone home the same network?

200
00:07:44,820 --> 00:07:46,560
我會把五個地點進行同步
I'll sync up all five locations

201
00:07:46,600 --> 00:07:48,480
讓它們以同樣的速率升溫
so they heat at exactly the same rate.

202
00:07:48,540 --> 00:07:50,040
你別介意 這個我來就可以了
No offense, but I'll handle that.

203
00:07:50,080 --> 00:07:51,390
你去解決警報
You should take care of the alarms,

204
00:07:51,420 --> 00:07:53,560
別讓庫房升溫發出信號
so there's not a signal of the temp raising in the vaults.

205
00:07:53,600 --> 00:07:54,680
- 不行 得換個方法
- No, reroute

206
00:07:54,720 --> 00:07:56,140
空調公司行不通
Airdream's traffic.

207
00:07:56,160 --> 00:07:59,030
記得抹去所有我們活動的痕跡
Make sure to erase and and all signs of our activity.

208
00:08:02,730 --> 00:08:04,880
-你去哪了? - 我需要和你談談
- Where were you? - I need a word.

209
00:08:04,900 --> 00:08:05,840
我要去上班了
I gotta get to work.

210
00:08:05,900 --> 00:08:07,400
勸你別去
I'm not sure that's wise.

211
00:08:08,940 --> 00:08:10,340
這是什么鬼?
What the hell is that?

212
00:08:10,370 --> 00:08:11,560
他們在跟蹤我
They're following me

213
00:08:11,580 --> 00:08:13,010
他們可能也在跟蹤你
and they're probably following you too.

214
00:08:13,040 --> 00:08:14,940
他們當時就在地鐵上 知道嗎?
They were on the subway, okay?

215
00:08:15,000 --> 00:08:16,400
思科跟我說了他們不好惹
Cisco's warned me about them.

216
00:08:16,440 --> 00:08:18,440
這些人很危險 伊利艾特
These guys are dangerous, Elliot.

217
00:08:18,480 --> 00:08:22,680
和白玫瑰的見面可能和我們預計的不一樣
The whiterose meet might not go down the way we want it to.

218
00:08:22,720 --> 00:08:24,120
是有可能啊
Yeah.

219
00:08:24,150 --> 00:08:28,020
可 我連槍都不會用
Well, I don't even know how to use a gun.

220
00:08:28,380 --> 00:08:31,680
再說了 我不確定他們想見的就是我
Besides, I'm not even sure I'm the one they wanna meet with.

221
00:08:31,680 --> 00:08:34,030
他們想見的肯定是你
You're definitely the one they wanna meet with.

222
00:08:34,060 --> 00:08:37,470
你去的時候 一定要小心
And when you do, you need to be careful.

223
00:08:37,500 --> 00:08:39,500
我很認真 伊利艾特
I'm serious, Elliot.

224
00:08:40,770 --> 00:08:42,000
你干嘛?
What are you doing?

225
00:08:42,040 --> 00:08:43,980
我用你的手機給我自己打電話
I'm calling myself from your phone.

226
00:08:43,980 --> 00:08:45,340
這樣我們就有了彼此的號碼
That way we have each other's number.

227
00:08:45,340 --> 00:08:46,980
等等 戴琳 我們不能這樣
Wait, Darlene, we don't do that.

228
00:08:47,000 --> 00:08:48,510
這是為了保護F社會
That's to protect a fsociety.

229
00:08:48,700 --> 00:08:51,670
好吧 但是現在我們必須保護對方
Okay, but we need to protect each other right now.

230
00:09:22,910 --> 00:09:26,070
刪了戴琳的號碼 我讓你這么做必然有我的道理
Lose Darlene's number. It's a rule for a reason.

231
00:09:26,110 --> 00:09:29,240
別急 我沒打算使用它
Don't worry, I'm not gonna use it.

232
00:09:29,280 --> 00:09:31,510
她有一件事說對了
She's right about one thing.

233
00:09:31,550 --> 00:09:33,880
他們想談判的人是你
You're the one they want to talk to.

234
00:09:33,920 --> 00:09:36,990
我們不能分心
We can't afford any distractions.

235
00:10:04,960 --> 00:10:07,700
我的老板又邀請了我一次 他的行為太明顯了
My boss invited me again. He's so obvious.

236
00:10:07,760 --> 00:10:09,780
你為什么不現在殺了我?
Why don't you just kill me now?

237
00:10:10,200 --> 00:10:11,380
噢!
Oh!

238
00:10:11,500 --> 00:10:13,960
我的天哪 布萊克! 你他X是在用腳尖走路嗎?
Jesus, Blake! Were you f---ing tiptoeing?

239
00:10:14,000 --> 00:10:15,880
去你的 看看你干了什么好事
God damn it, look what you've done.

240
00:10:15,900 --> 00:10:17,010
走路看著點兒!
Watch where you're going!

241
00:10:17,050 --> 00:10:19,020
- 但是你… - 早上好
- But you-- - Good morning.

242
00:10:19,060 --> 00:10:21,300
現在不是時候 伊麗莎白 所有電話都不要接進來
Not now, Elizabeth. Hold all calls.

243
00:10:21,320 --> 00:10:22,900
取消所有的會議 我今天很忙
Cancel any meetings. I'm busy today.

244
00:10:22,940 --> 00:10:24,050
但是 威力克先生
But, Mr. Wellick,

245
00:10:24,090 --> 00:10:25,920
吉迪恩 戈達德來找你
Gideon Goddard is here to see you.

246
00:10:25,960 --> 00:10:27,800
我很抱歉 他堅持要見你
I'm sorry. He was very persistent.

247
00:10:27,800 --> 00:10:29,720
他不肯走
He wouldn't leave.

248
00:10:29,760 --> 00:10:31,730
好吧
Okay.

249
00:10:32,020 --> 00:10:34,800
好吧 就這樣 謝謝你
Okay, no, that's fine. Thank you.

250
00:10:34,840 --> 00:10:37,130
唔 你需要我 呃...
Um, do you want me to, uh...

251
00:10:41,700 --> 00:10:44,200
噢 當然 我想要杯咖啡
Oh, yes, I'd love some coffee.

252
00:11:01,720 --> 00:11:04,800
我的一個員工承認
One of my employees confessed to

253
00:11:04,820 --> 00:11:06,590
違反了科爾比公司dat文件的監管鏈
breaking chain of custody with the Colby dat file.

254
00:11:06,900 --> 00:11:09,360
很不幸 他的承認
Unfortunately, this admission

255
00:11:09,380 --> 00:11:11,440
會使證據失效
will render the evidence inadmissible

256
00:11:11,440 --> 00:11:12,920
并且使科爾比公司免遭罰款
and Colby free of charges.

257
00:11:12,960 --> 00:11:14,020
在你說任何話之前
Now before you say anything,

258
00:11:14,060 --> 00:11:17,160
我向你確保萬安公司已經做出雙倍努力
I want to assure you that Allsafe has doubled its efforts

259
00:11:17,200 --> 00:11:18,360
尋找黑客
to find the hackers,

260
00:11:18,400 --> 00:11:20,600
無論是再次確認科爾比的參與
whether it be reconfirming Colby's involvement

261
00:11:20,660 --> 00:11:22,210
或是找到真正的罪犯
or finding the real perpetrators.

262
00:11:22,240 --> 00:11:25,150
我們已經隔離了您的個人網絡
We've air-gapped your private network,

263
00:11:25,180 --> 00:11:26,510
開啟了蜜罐系統
implemented a honeypot,

264
00:11:26,550 --> 00:11:30,160
重新部署了所有的防火墻以及系統地...
reconfigured all the firewalls and systematically--

265
00:11:30,180 --> 00:11:31,500
等等 等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.

266
00:11:31,560 --> 00:11:33,480
蜜罐系統 有什么用?
A honeypot, for what?

267
00:11:33,520 --> 00:11:37,630
在上一次F社會的攻擊中使用的一個特殊的服務器
A specific server involved in the last fsociety attack,

268
00:11:38,080 --> 00:11:39,490
CS30
CS30.

269
00:11:39,530 --> 00:11:42,720
我知道我們已經檢查過了 不過如果有那么一點可能
I know we checked it out, but if there's even a chance

270
00:11:42,780 --> 00:11:43,980
黑客們仍然在網絡中的話
the hackers are still in the network,

271
00:11:44,040 --> 00:11:47,040
蜜罐系統可以確保他們不會造成任何傷害
the honeypot will ensure that they can't cause any damage.

272
00:11:47,070 --> 00:11:49,280
他們會登錄到我們設置好的誘餌服務器中
They'll log into the decoy server we've set up,

273
00:11:49,300 --> 00:11:50,920
以為他們是在主網絡上
thinking they're on the main network.

274
00:11:51,000 --> 00:11:53,560
并且我會親自監視所有網絡流量
And I'm personally keeping tabs on all traffic.

275
00:11:53,580 --> 00:11:55,200
所以你擁有我們的全程監護
So you have our full attention.

276
00:11:57,380 --> 00:12:01,960
我很感激你清楚的解釋
Well, I appreciate your transparency.

277
00:12:02,000 --> 00:12:04,490
那么 你聽明白了
Well, so you understand then.

278
00:12:04,520 --> 00:12:06,220
當然
Of course.

279
00:12:06,260 --> 00:12:09,090
事實上 我想查看你們的發現
In fact, I'd like to look over your findings,

280
00:12:09,120 --> 00:12:10,760
特別是這臺服務器
especially this server.

281
00:12:12,940 --> 00:12:15,020
所以 請給我發一份你們的研究報告
So, please send me the research.

282
00:12:15,080 --> 00:12:16,180
當然 當然
Of course, of course.

283
00:12:16,280 --> 00:12:18,170
再次感謝你能見我
Well, thank you again for seeing me.

284
00:13:09,320 --> 00:13:11,390
威力克先生
Mr. Wellick.

285
00:13:12,760 --> 00:13:13,990
威力克先生!
Mr. Wellick!

286
00:13:14,020 --> 00:13:17,020
我特意強調不想被打擾
I specifically asked not to be disturbed.

287
00:13:17,080 --> 00:13:18,500
我知道 但是 呃...
I know, but, um--

288
00:13:18,540 --> 00:13:19,890
怎么了?
What is it?

289
00:13:19,930 --> 00:13:21,700
是警察
The police.

290
00:13:21,730 --> 00:13:24,030
很糟糕的事情
It's awful.

291
00:13:24,070 --> 00:13:25,760
警察有什么事?
What about the police?

292
00:13:26,120 --> 00:13:28,360
他們在屋頂發現一具尸體
They found a body on the roof.

293
00:13:28,660 --> 00:13:30,640
尸體? 誰的?
A body? Who?

294
00:13:30,740 --> 00:13:32,960
他們沒說 但警探來了
They're not saying,but detectives came by.

295
00:13:32,980 --> 00:13:34,320
他們想和你談談
They want to speak with you.

296
00:13:34,700 --> 00:13:35,580
跟我?
With me?

297
00:13:35,660 --> 00:13:37,240
他們會詢問
They're questioning everyone

298
00:13:37,280 --> 00:13:39,760
昨晚參加接待會的每一個人
who was at the reception last night.

299
00:13:47,220 --> 00:13:50,900
顯然 這是不幸的 但工作還得繼續
Clearly, this is tragic, but unfortunately work goes on.

300
00:13:50,960 --> 00:13:52,260
可是你不覺得你應該--
But don't you think you should--

301
00:13:52,290 --> 00:13:55,460
告訴警探他們可以提前預約
Tell them they can set an appointment.

302
00:13:55,500 --> 00:13:58,170
到那時 我會很高興和他們交談
I'd be happy to speak with them then.

303
00:14:01,770 --> 00:14:04,520
噢 還有 伊麗莎白 我需要你幫我聯系
Oh, and, Elizabeth,I need you to connect me

304
00:14:04,540 --> 00:14:05,600
杜勒斯服務器農場
with the Dulles Server Farm.

305
00:14:05,680 --> 00:14:07,420
轉接到我手機
I'll take it on my mobile.

306
00:14:10,140 --> 00:14:11,440
共享文件了嗎?
And the file shares?

307
00:14:11,460 --> 00:14:12,960
因為在我們重新上線之前
'Cause client data is inaccessible

308
00:14:13,000 --> 00:14:13,800
客戶數據無法訪問
until we're back online.

309
00:14:13,820 --> 00:14:15,250
馬上就辦
Jumping on that now.

310
00:14:15,280 --> 00:14:17,120
檢查ASA防火墻日志
Check the logs on the ASA firewall.

311
00:14:17,160 --> 00:14:18,250
我要一份完整報告
I want a full report.

312
00:14:18,290 --> 00:14:20,360
奧利 銷售員
Ollie, sales.

313
00:14:20,380 --> 00:14:21,720
在我另行通知之前
All appointments at Allsafe

314
00:14:21,740 --> 00:14:23,160
取消所有萬安的預約
are cancelled until further notice.

315
00:14:23,180 --> 00:14:24,590
不要向外走漏風聲
Word of this cannot get out.

316
00:14:24,630 --> 00:14:27,430
好的 我們開始吧
All right,let's get to it.

317
00:14:39,880 --> 00:14:43,580
這次攻擊沒什么破壞性 他們已經進入了我們的系統
This hack is far from devastating. They already own us.

318
00:14:43,760 --> 00:14:46,280
但他們并非來尋求有價值的東西
They're not going after anything valuable.

319
00:14:46,380 --> 00:14:48,420
而是轉移我們注意
This is more of a distraction.

320
00:14:48,600 --> 00:14:51,220
但他們試圖讓我們在什么上面分心呢?
But what are they trying to distract us from?

321
00:14:57,940 --> 00:14:59,870
嘿 哥們
Hey, bro.

322
00:15:03,900 --> 00:15:05,760
總是讓我做話匣子
Always the chatterbox.

323
00:15:06,380 --> 00:15:07,960
你在流汗
You're sweating.

324
00:15:08,020 --> 00:15:10,600
噢 是嗎? 有一點
Oh, yeah? Yeah, maybe a little.

325
00:15:10,700 --> 00:15:12,000
東奔西跑的
Been running around.

326
00:15:12,040 --> 00:15:15,520
呃 聽著 我需要你幫我處理一些事情
Um, look, I sorta need you to handle something for me.

327
00:15:15,560 --> 00:15:16,600
他們讓你現在干什么
What have they got you doing here?

328
00:15:16,620 --> 00:15:18,720
試著逆向還原惡意軟件
Trying to reverse engineer the malware.

329
00:15:18,740 --> 00:15:20,960
好的 呃 你得停下手頭工作
Okay, um, I'm gonna need you to stop doing that

330
00:15:21,020 --> 00:15:22,760
把這些被毀壞的惡意驅動軟件
Try and take these engineer corrupted drives malware.

331
00:15:22,800 --> 00:15:24,470
轉存到36號和5號空白磁盤恢復區間
over to Blank's Disk Recovery on 36th and 5th.

332
00:15:26,040 --> 00:15:28,380
為什么找我?這是IT部門的事
Why me? Get one of the IT guys.

333
00:15:28,420 --> 00:15:32,340
每個人都很忙 伊利艾特
Everyone is swamped, Elliot.

334
00:15:34,060 --> 00:15:39,300
老兄 我不是來跟你爭論的
Dude, this isn't, like,a debate.

335
00:15:39,820 --> 00:15:42,100
我一直希望我們之間能相處好一點
I've always wanted things to be cool between us,

336
00:15:42,140 --> 00:15:45,360
但我是你上司
but I outrank you.

337
00:15:45,720 --> 00:15:47,160
所以...
So...

338
00:15:48,800 --> 00:15:50,720
給你硬盤
Here are the drives.

339
00:15:50,960 --> 00:15:52,940
給你安排在2點開始
Your appointment is at 2:00.

340
00:15:52,980 --> 00:15:55,200
不要遲到
You cannot be late.

341
00:15:56,020 --> 00:15:59,720
事實上 呃 不如你現在就去?
In fact, um, how 'bout you leave right now?

342
00:16:00,360 --> 00:16:02,380
現在才12點
It's only 12:00.

343
00:16:02,400 --> 00:16:05,000
伊利艾特 哥們兒 你就--
Elliot, bro, just--

344
00:16:05,060 --> 00:16:08,310
你就幫我這一次 好嗎?
just do me this solid, okay?

345
00:16:21,480 --> 00:16:23,340
他不僅僅只是緊張
He wasn't just stressed.

346
00:16:23,380 --> 00:16:25,160
他感到恐懼
He was scared.

347
00:16:25,600 --> 00:16:27,940
讓我瞧瞧他在隱瞞什么
Let's see what he's hiding.

348
00:16:35,640 --> 00:16:38,810
安吉拉和這一切有什么關系?
What does Angela have to do with this?

349
00:18:13,500 --> 00:18:15,660
你為什么不告訴我?
Why didn't you tell me?

350
00:18:16,120 --> 00:18:17,720
我怎么告訴你?
And say what?

351
00:18:18,220 --> 00:18:20,500
"嘿 艾略特 有群混蛋
"Hey, Elliot, there's a bunch of nude pics of me

352
00:18:20,540 --> 00:18:21,940
要把我的裸照發布在網上"?
that some asshole wants to leak online"?

353
00:18:21,980 --> 00:18:23,140
我能幫助你的
I could have helped.

354
00:18:23,180 --> 00:18:24,850
你不在身邊
You weren't around.

355
00:18:25,280 --> 00:18:26,480
是啊
Yeah.

356
00:18:26,900 --> 00:18:29,820
這個月過的很糟心
Kinda had a rough month.

357
00:18:31,100 --> 00:18:32,950
抱歉
I'm sorry.

358
00:18:33,560 --> 00:18:36,590
告訴我發生什么了
Tell me what happened.

359
00:18:36,740 --> 00:18:38,840
我們被盯上了
We were being pressured.

360
00:18:39,400 --> 00:18:40,660
被誰?
By who?

361
00:18:41,000 --> 00:18:42,460
某些家伙
Some guy.

362
00:18:42,980 --> 00:18:46,140
他給了奧利一張CD 讓他的電腦中毒了
He gave Ollie a CD that infected his laptop,

363
00:18:46,160 --> 00:18:49,940
盜取了他的照片 電郵 還有瀏覽器緩存
stole his pictures, his emails,and browser cache.

364
00:18:50,520 --> 00:18:53,060
他叫他在萬安系統安裝一個磁盤
He said to install the disk at Allsafe,

365
00:18:53,120 --> 00:18:55,360
否則他就在網上曝光我們
or he would leak everything online.

366
00:18:55,940 --> 00:18:57,920
這是前一段時間的事了
It was a while ago.

367
00:18:57,960 --> 00:18:59,460
我以為他把我們忘了
I thought he forgot about us.

368
00:18:59,500 --> 00:19:00,640
我猜對了
I was right.

369
00:19:00,660 --> 00:19:02,320
這次入侵是調虎離山
The hack was a distraction.

370
00:19:02,380 --> 00:19:04,450
這是針對我的 這就是會面
This is about me.This is the meeting.

371
00:19:06,480 --> 00:19:08,480
你應該來找我的
You should have come to me.

372
00:19:08,860 --> 00:19:10,240
我說了
I told you,

373
00:19:10,360 --> 00:19:12,000
我找不到你
you weren't there.

374
00:19:12,100 --> 00:19:13,630
你從來就是心不在焉
You're never there anymore.

375
00:19:15,600 --> 00:19:18,040
你到底怎么了 伊利艾特
Something is going on with you, Elliot.

376
00:19:18,120 --> 00:19:20,280
你過去幾個月一直魂不守舍
You have not been the same the past couple of months,

377
00:19:20,340 --> 00:19:22,140
夏拉死之前你就是這樣了
and this happened before Shayla.

378
00:19:22,180 --> 00:19:23,200
你錯了
You're wrong.

379
00:19:23,260 --> 00:19:24,010
你在欺騙我!
You're lying!

380
00:19:24,540 --> 00:19:27,280
你甚至不和我說話了!
You don't talk to me anymore!

381
00:19:27,400 --> 00:19:29,260
告訴我現在改怎么做!
Just tell me what to do here!

382
00:19:29,260 --> 00:19:31,360
因為我能想到的唯一辦法
Because the only solution I can think of

383
00:19:31,360 --> 00:19:33,650
就是放棄
is to give up.

384
00:19:40,760 --> 00:19:43,480
天啊 說話呀!
God, say something!

385
00:19:47,360 --> 00:19:49,280
你說的對
You're right.

386
00:19:50,120 --> 00:19:52,200
我們不再交流了
We don't talk anymore.

387
00:20:01,760 --> 00:20:04,120
這太奇怪了
It's so strange.

388
00:20:05,160 --> 00:20:07,280
我真的懷念過去的我們
I really miss us.

389
00:20:08,960 --> 00:20:11,600
這有什么奇怪的?
Why is that strange?

390
00:20:15,520 --> 00:20:17,960
因為我從未想過我必須這樣
Because I never thought I'd have to.

391
00:20:21,200 --> 00:20:23,100
黑客
Hackers.

392
00:20:23,130 --> 00:20:25,400
我們天生不相信任何人
We inherently trust no one,

393
00:20:25,800 --> 00:20:27,730
包括對其他黑客
including each other.

394
00:20:27,770 --> 00:20:29,700
我將永遠都不能告訴她
I'll never be able to tell her.

395
00:20:29,740 --> 00:20:31,770
我們之間會永遠存在一道分水嶺
There will always be this divide,

396
00:20:31,810 --> 00:20:34,840
那是她翻越不了的墻
my wall that she can't look over.

397
00:20:36,640 --> 00:20:39,000
她也清楚
And she knows it.

398
00:20:45,800 --> 00:20:48,800
信譽問題 黑暗軍團
Trust issues, the dark army

399
00:20:48,800 --> 00:20:50,680
采取了絕妙的辦法
has taken extraordinary steps

400
00:20:50,680 --> 00:20:53,600
確保會議完美地按照他們的想法進行
to make sure this meeting's exactly how they want it.

401
00:20:53,600 --> 00:20:56,800
難道這就是臭名昭著的白玫瑰成為傳奇的原因?
Is that why the infamous whiterose is such a legend?

402
00:20:56,840 --> 00:21:01,040
因為他比我們其余人都更偏執
Because he's more paranoid than the rest of us.

403
00:21:09,400 --> 00:21:13,160
我是伊利艾特 奧爾德森
I'm Elliot. Alderson.

404
00:21:35,480 --> 00:21:37,640
是個法拉第籠
A Faraday cage.

405
00:21:38,000 --> 00:21:42,640
一個為避免電磁干擾而特殊設計的房間
A room specifically designed to prevent electromagnetic interference

406
00:21:42,640 --> 00:21:48,000
沒有無線電 沒有信號 沒有Wifi 什么都黑不了
No radio, no signal, no WiFi, nothing to hack.

407
00:21:51,880 --> 00:21:54,880
我想我是來找你的
I think I'm here to see you.

408
00:21:59,840 --> 00:22:03,680
我該跟你走嗎?
Am I supposed to follow you?

409
00:22:07,360 --> 00:22:09,360
你打算一直傻站在那
Are you just going to stand there

410
00:22:09,360 --> 00:22:12,040
還是把那些驅動遞給我?
or do you want to hand me those drives?

411
00:22:12,890 --> 00:22:14,960
快快快
Mm-mm-mm.

412
00:22:15,040 --> 00:22:17,680
會議已經開始了
This meeting has started.

413
00:22:17,720 --> 00:22:20,600
我是個時間觀念很強的人 奧爾德森先生
I manage my time very carefully, Mr. Alderson.

414
00:22:20,600 --> 00:22:22,920
表每響一下就代表著
Each beep indicates one minute of my time

415
00:22:22,920 --> 00:22:24,200
我又少了一分鐘
that has passed.

416
00:22:24,200 --> 00:22:26,920
分給你的時間只有不到三分鐘
I have allotted you no more than three minutes.

417
00:22:30,760 --> 00:22:33,080
你確定要這么做嗎?
Are you really gonna do that?

418
00:22:33,080 --> 00:22:35,640
你最好挑一個好一點的話題
I suggest you pick better topics of conversation.

419
00:22:35,640 --> 00:22:38,480
我今天還有十七項日程
I have 17 more items on my agenda today.

420
00:22:38,520 --> 00:22:40,280
我們應該這次
The Evil Corp hack,

421
00:22:40,280 --> 00:22:41,600
把邪惡公司的黑客解決掉
we should go through with it this time.

422
00:22:41,600 --> 00:22:43,760
你會大失所望的
You are turning out to be a grave disappointment.

423
00:22:43,760 --> 00:22:46,040
我們萬事俱備 該有的都有了
We were ready. We had everything set to go.

424
00:22:46,040 --> 00:22:48,200
住處太沒有效率了
Dwelling is so inefficient.

425
00:22:48,200 --> 00:22:49,920
嘿 你上次成功了啊
Hey, you pulled out last time.

426
00:22:49,920 --> 00:22:51,480
別浪費時間在
Wasting more time,

427
00:22:51,520 --> 00:22:53,720
我已經知道了的事情上了
telling me things I already know.

428
00:22:54,040 --> 00:22:55,760
但是我們準備好了
But we were ready.

429
00:22:55,760 --> 00:22:58,040
這是你第三次這么說了
That is the third time that you have expressed that.

430
00:22:58,040 --> 00:23:00,200
她在拖延時間
She's trolling me.

431
00:23:00,230 --> 00:23:03,400
你在這次對話里不占一點上風
You have not advanced this conversation.

432
00:23:03,400 --> 00:23:04,640
一希望占上風么?
Do you intend to?

433
00:23:04,640 --> 00:23:06,000
從上個月起
Since last month,

434
00:23:06,040 --> 00:23:08,280
邪惡公司把他們的磁帶
Evil Corp has moved its tapes to five--

435
00:23:08,320 --> 00:23:09,640
轉移到了五個備用設備里
Backup facilities,

436
00:23:09,680 --> 00:23:11,800
并且你計劃把它們都毀掉
and you have a plan to take them all down.

437
00:23:11,800 --> 00:23:12,920
是的
Yes.

438
00:23:12,920 --> 00:23:15,400
你終于說了點有用的了
Finally, you have communicated something.

439
00:23:15,400 --> 00:23:17,360
所以你到底準備好了沒?
So are you ready to do this or not?

440
00:23:17,360 --> 00:23:19,800
你才是沒準備好的那個
You are the one who is not ready.

441
00:23:19,800 --> 00:23:22,480
一直以來你才總是失敗
It was you who failed all along.

442
00:23:22,520 --> 00:23:24,240
你缺少的是注意力
What you've lacked was focus.

443
00:23:24,240 --> 00:23:27,120
你背離了黑客的道路反而針對泰利 科爾比
You strayed from the hack to target Terry Colby.

444
00:23:27,120 --> 00:23:28,880
這成為了一個安全隱患
This opened a vulnerability.

445
00:23:28,880 --> 00:23:30,080
帶來了猜疑
Suspicion.

446
00:23:30,080 --> 00:23:34,000
尤其是從吉迪恩 戈達德那里
Specifically by Gideon Goddard.

447
00:23:34,480 --> 00:23:37,360
這就是你為什么黑了萬安公司
That's why you hacked Allsafe.

448
00:23:37,400 --> 00:23:39,360
為了監視他的活動
To monitor his activities.

449
00:23:39,360 --> 00:23:41,160
也就是那時我們發現
And that's when we discovered

450
00:23:41,200 --> 00:23:44,880
他把你攻擊的服務器變成了陷阱
that he turned your infected server into a honeypot.

451
00:23:46,400 --> 00:23:49,520
哦 六十秒后會議就結束了
Oh, 60 seconds and this meeting will be over.

452
00:23:49,520 --> 00:23:50,520
等一下
Wait.

453
00:23:50,520 --> 00:23:53,040
我不懂為什么要等一下
The concept of waiting bewilders me.

454
00:23:53,040 --> 00:23:54,400
凡事都有期限
There are always deadlines.

455
00:23:54,400 --> 00:23:56,920
時間總在流逝
There are always ticking clocks.

456
00:23:56,920 --> 00:23:58,840
這就是為什么你必須管理時間
That's why you must manage your time.

457
00:23:58,840 --> 00:24:00,520
我會想辦法消除陷阱的
I'll find a way to remove the honeypot.

458
00:24:00,520 --> 00:24:02,200
直到十六秒前
Until 16 seconds ago,

459
00:24:02,200 --> 00:24:04,120
你還沒察覺有陷阱
you were not aware there was a honeypot.

460
00:24:04,120 --> 00:24:06,560
這對你的信心沒什么好處
This does not inspire confidence.

461
00:24:06,650 --> 00:24:08,080
- 等一下 - 又是這個詞
- Wait.- There's that word again.

462
00:24:08,080 --> 00:24:09,320
我們會處理好的
We'll take care of it.

463
00:24:09,320 --> 00:24:12,320
你知道你本可以幾周前就把陷阱的事告訴我們的
You know you could have told us about the honeypot weeks ago.

464
00:24:12,320 --> 00:24:14,280
術業有專攻
Every hacker has her fixation.

465
00:24:14,280 --> 00:24:16,760
你專攻人類 我專攻時間
You hack people, I hack time.

466
00:24:16,800 --> 00:24:20,040
所以你應該了解 我設下時間線
So you should know that when I set a time line,

467
00:24:20,080 --> 00:24:21,800
總是有原因的
there's a reason.

468
00:24:21,800 --> 00:24:24,840
你還有五十個小時二十三分鐘
You have 50 hours and 23 minutes.

469
00:24:24,840 --> 00:24:27,280
到那時 當所有組織都準備好了
At that point, when all parties are ready,

470
00:24:27,280 --> 00:24:29,600
我們將會發起黑客攻擊
we will initiate the hack.

471
00:24:29,600 --> 00:24:31,800
我們會做的
We'll do it.

472
00:24:32,720 --> 00:24:34,640
可能下次吧
Maybe next time--

473
00:24:34,680 --> 00:24:36,760
你要知道 奧爾德森先生
Understand something, Mr. Alderson.

474
00:24:36,760 --> 00:24:38,360
我走之后
After I leave,

475
00:24:38,560 --> 00:24:40,260
你不會再見到我
you will never see me again.

476
00:24:40,420 --> 00:24:42,780
我的生命中很少有人
There are very few people in my life

477
00:24:42,780 --> 00:24:44,740
能夠讓我有足夠的時間見到第二次
that I have enough time to see more than once,

478
00:24:44,780 --> 00:24:46,200
你不是其中之一
and you are not one of them.

479
00:24:50,880 --> 00:24:52,280
相信我
Trust me,

480
00:24:53,360 --> 00:24:56,050
這不會有任何影響
that's not going to matter.

481
00:24:58,500 --> 00:25:00,160
你為什么要這么做?
Why are you doing all of this?

482
00:25:00,180 --> 00:25:01,740
黑電腦?
The hack?

483
00:25:02,720 --> 00:25:05,660
為什么你和我們一起行動?
Why are you working with us?

484
00:25:15,560 --> 00:25:18,740
還剩50小時20分鐘
50 hours and 20 minutes left.

485
00:25:18,840 --> 00:25:20,180
我需要搞明白這件事
I need to figure this out.

486
00:25:20,220 --> 00:25:22,220
吉迪恩一直都在暗中窺視我
Gideon's been spying on me the whole time.

487
00:25:22,240 --> 00:25:24,120
蜜罐技術 我靠
Honeypot service order, shit.

488
00:25:24,240 --> 00:25:25,720
我現在得行動了
I gotta do that now.

489
00:25:25,800 --> 00:25:28,380
安全令牌 吉迪恩的手機
Security token. Gideon's phone.

490
00:25:28,400 --> 00:25:29,620
我需要他的手機
I need his phone.

491
00:25:29,680 --> 00:25:32,180
還剩50小時19分鐘
50 hours and 19 minutes left.

492
00:25:32,240 --> 00:25:34,780
該死 她的時間偏執癥傳染到我了
Damn, she infected me with her time paranoia.

493
00:25:34,820 --> 00:25:37,280
我們都生活在互相的偏執癥里
We're all living in each other's paranoia.

494
00:25:37,340 --> 00:25:39,420
你肯定無法否定這個
You definitely can't argue that.

495
00:25:39,460 --> 00:25:42,300
這難道就是為什么人們相互回避嗎?
Is that why everyone tries to avoid each other?

496
00:25:42,340 --> 00:25:43,740
我需要冷靜下來
I need to calm down.

497
00:25:43,780 --> 00:25:45,780
我希望我能成為像你那樣的觀察家
I wish I could be an observer like you.

498
00:25:45,820 --> 00:25:47,760
我就能更冷靜的思考
Then I could think more calmly.

499
00:25:57,260 --> 00:25:59,740
這很舒服
This is comfortable.

500
00:25:59,800 --> 00:26:01,700
沒那么多壓力
Less stressful.

501
00:26:01,800 --> 00:26:04,680
事實上 我覺得我能夠看見所有事
In fact, I feel like I can see everything,

502
00:26:04,760 --> 00:26:07,150
了解所有事 以這種舒服的方式
know everything this way.

503
00:26:07,190 --> 00:26:08,590
嗯
Hmm.

504
00:26:09,060 --> 00:26:11,060
你比我知道更多嗎?
Do you know more than me?

505
00:26:11,180 --> 00:26:13,080
這不公平
That wouldn't be fair,

506
00:26:13,120 --> 00:26:16,060
我的想象力比我知道更多
my imaginary friend knowing more than me.

507
00:26:16,180 --> 00:26:18,100
所以你現在可以干什么?
So what would you do now?

508
00:26:18,220 --> 00:26:21,500
我們需要一個干擾來拿到吉迪恩手機
We need a distraction to get Gideon's phone.

509
00:26:28,620 --> 00:26:32,220
戴琳 我需要你做點事
Darlene, I need you to do something for me.

510
00:26:32,300 --> 00:26:33,280
她能幫上忙
She can help.

511
00:26:33,320 --> 00:26:34,920
在Allstate的我老板 吉迪恩
My boss at Allstate, Gideon--

512
00:26:34,960 --> 00:26:36,020
有時候
Sometimes it's hard

513
00:26:36,060 --> 00:26:37,900
聽一個解釋很難
to listen to an explanation,

514
00:26:37,960 --> 00:26:39,920
就算是來自自己的解釋
even when it's from myself.

515
00:26:39,960 --> 00:26:42,280
尤其是自己做出的解釋
Especially when it's from myself.

516
00:26:42,560 --> 00:26:44,560
但是如果只是注意我需要做什么
It would be so much easier

517
00:26:44,580 --> 00:26:46,560
就會簡單很多
to only pay attention when I needed to.

518
00:26:47,080 --> 00:26:48,800
為了
To just--

519
00:26:51,840 --> 00:26:53,840
得出一個結論
Arrive at the conclusion.

520
00:26:56,760 --> 00:26:58,580
這是你所做的事嗎?
Is that what you do?

521
00:27:28,280 --> 00:27:31,400
100份MMS文件傳送到吉迪恩的手機上
100 large MMS files to Gideon's phone.

522
00:27:31,400 --> 00:27:32,400
耗盡它
Drained it.

523
00:27:50,540 --> 00:27:53,560
企業貪婪是一個向下流的欲望
Corporate greed is a trickle down desire

524
00:27:53,600 --> 00:27:55,600
它甚至會留向食物鏈的最低端
that reaches even the bottom of the food chain.

525
00:27:55,660 --> 00:27:58,580
- 為了什么 - 財富? - 什么鬼? - 權利?
- And for what? - Wealth? - What the shit? - Power?

526
00:27:58,960 --> 00:28:00,640
這是個令人悲傷的寓言故事
It's a pathetic fable,

527
00:28:00,700 --> 00:28:03,180
你們 萬安公司 是這個可憐貪婪的辯護人
and you, Allsafe, are a defender of this pitiful avarice.

528
00:28:03,200 --> 00:28:04,680
天啊 F社會知道我們
Holy shit, fsociety knows us.

529
00:28:04,720 --> 00:28:06,420
但是你們的美夢結束了
But your sweet dream is over,

530
00:28:06,460 --> 00:28:08,460
你們的噩夢現在才剛剛開始
and your nightmare is about to begin.

531
00:28:09,740 --> 00:28:12,780
我們已經贏了 讓那些串通一氣的...
We have won.Let those who are complicit...

532
00:28:12,820 --> 00:28:14,280
現在發生了什么?
What the hell's happening now?

533
00:28:14,320 --> 00:28:15,500
那些援助專橫暴君的人
Those who aid the tyrants,

534
00:28:15,540 --> 00:28:17,460
那些接受暴虐的人
those who accept the tyranny

535
00:28:17,520 --> 00:28:19,840
在新的統治下沒有地位
have no place in the new order.

536
00:28:19,880 --> 00:28:21,620
這個干擾是短暫的
The distraction is momentary.

537
00:28:22,180 --> 00:28:23,840
希望我需要的
Hopefully all I need.

538
00:28:23,880 --> 00:28:25,900
他們會知道我們的正義
They will know our justice,

539
00:28:25,940 --> 00:28:27,900
我們不會表現一點仁慈
and we will show no mercy.

540
00:28:27,960 --> 00:28:31,980
吉迪恩 戈達德 你對你的企業
Gideon Goddard, you are a lackey

541
00:28:32,020 --> 00:28:33,620
只是男仆
to your corporate overlords.

542
00:28:33,660 --> 00:28:34,940
來人把它關掉
Someone shut this off.

543
00:28:34,980 --> 00:28:36,000
為壓榨無辜者的人
Defending those

544
00:28:36,040 --> 00:28:38,080
辯護
that bleed the innocent.

545
00:28:38,120 --> 00:28:41,000
為他們服務
Serving them, slave to master.

546
00:28:41,020 --> 00:28:42,360
遙控沒有反應
It's ignoring the remote.

547
00:28:42,480 --> 00:28:43,760
他們黑進了我們的智能電視
They hacked our smart TV.

548
00:28:43,780 --> 00:28:45,500
祝賀你 戈達德先生
Congratulations, Mr. Goddard.

549
00:28:45,540 --> 00:28:46,660
這個被放上了我們的網站
It's posted to our website.

550
00:28:46,700 --> 00:28:47,620
還有YouTube
And YouTube.

551
00:28:47,640 --> 00:28:49,140
你很快會被完結
You will soon be finished.

552
00:28:49,900 --> 00:28:52,720
90秒之內這個密碼會改變
In 90 seconds this code will change.

553
00:28:52,740 --> 00:28:56,060
如果我沒有在那之前用我的電腦登陸
If I don't log in with it on my computer before then,

554
00:28:56,160 --> 00:28:57,800
我會丟失所有東西
I'll lose everything to time.

555
00:28:57,820 --> 00:28:59,720
我們把你的角色公告天下
We are exposing your role to the world.

556
00:28:59,760 --> 00:29:01,300
不 讓它結束
No, let it finish.

557
00:29:01,380 --> 00:29:04,340
整個世界會很生氣
And the world is very angry.

558
00:29:12,180 --> 00:29:14,180
60秒 白玫瑰是對的
60 seconds. Whiterose was right.

559
00:29:14,220 --> 00:29:16,030
我們從一個截止時間到另一個截止時間來回奔波
We run from one deadline to the next.

560
00:29:18,600 --> 00:29:19,660
伊利艾特在哪里?
Where's Elliot?

561
00:29:32,060 --> 00:29:34,060
你在干什么?
What are you doing?

562
00:29:34,140 --> 00:29:36,780
我在做本地備份
I was working on the local backups.

563
00:29:36,840 --> 00:29:38,280
你為什么不和我們一起在那看?
Why weren't you in there with us?

564
00:29:39,740 --> 00:29:41,200
我很擔心--
I was worried about the--

565
00:29:41,240 --> 00:29:42,420
這說不通啊
It just doesn't add up.

566
00:29:42,500 --> 00:29:43,720
這些事一直在發生
All these events keep happening

567
00:29:43,740 --> 00:29:45,500
無論你在不在
around your appearance, your disappearance.

568
00:29:45,520 --> 00:29:46,920
- 吉迪恩 - 別說了
- Gideon-- - Forget it.

569
00:29:47,000 --> 00:29:48,380
我不想聽到
I don't wanna hear it.

570
00:29:48,480 --> 00:29:50,900
這個公司的每個員工站在那里
Every member in this company stood in there,

571
00:29:50,940 --> 00:29:53,220
看著最糟糕的事情發生在萬安公司身上
watching the single worst thing that's happened to Allsafe,

572
00:29:53,240 --> 00:29:54,800
而你在哪里? 在你的小隔間?
and where are you, at your cubicle?

573
00:29:55,480 --> 00:29:57,540
做著什么?
Doing what?

574
00:30:00,820 --> 00:30:02,400
呃 吉迪恩 我不是有意打擾...
Uh, Gideon, I hate to interrupt...

575
00:30:02,400 --> 00:30:02,940
不 現在不行 奧利
No, not now, Ollie.

576
00:30:02,940 --> 00:30:03,940
是邪惡公司的電話
But Evil Corp's on the phone.

577
00:30:06,520 --> 00:30:07,880
我會回來
I'll be back.

578
00:30:07,900 --> 00:30:09,180
我們還沒說完
We're not finished here.

579
00:30:15,440 --> 00:30:16,520
我知道
I know.

580
00:30:16,550 --> 00:30:18,540
你以為我沒有及時的輸入密碼
You thought I didn't put the code in time,

581
00:30:18,540 --> 00:30:21,800
但我得快點把它藏起來在吉迪恩看見之前
but I had to hide it quickly before Gideon saw it.

582
00:30:21,860 --> 00:30:22,960
對不起
Sorry.

583
00:30:32,400 --> 00:30:35,880
我告訴過你我在黑入吉迪恩時看見了什么嗎?
Have I told you what I saw when I hacked Gideon?

584
00:30:35,900 --> 00:30:38,420
當我瞥見他的秘密時?
When I peeked into his secrets?

585
00:30:39,000 --> 00:30:41,910
我看到一善良誠實的人
I saw a good, honest man.

586
00:30:42,460 --> 00:30:44,580
吉迪恩錯了
Gideon was wrong.

587
00:30:44,680 --> 00:30:46,020
我完成了這兒的使命
I am finished here.

588
00:30:46,460 --> 00:30:48,800
我不適合他也不屬于這個地方
I'm no good for him or this place.

589
00:30:48,860 --> 00:30:51,440
他只保護自己的人
He was only protecting his people.

590
00:30:51,820 --> 00:30:53,290
而我呢?
But me?

591
00:30:53,320 --> 00:30:56,960
我所做的一切是為了保護每個人
I'm doing this to protect everyone.

592
00:30:59,930 --> 00:31:02,800
看起來你最近很忙碌啊
Seems you've been very busy lately.

593
00:31:05,920 --> 00:31:08,620
我得知道你計劃是什么
I have to know what you're planning.

594
00:31:08,640 --> 00:31:10,980
我們注定是盟友啊
We were meant to be allies.

595
00:31:12,840 --> 00:31:14,800
或許我們想要的東西是一樣的
We might just want the same thing,

596
00:31:14,820 --> 00:31:16,450
所以我想加入其中
and I need to be involved.

597
00:31:16,480 --> 00:31:19,540
我敢說你大錯特錯了 我的朋友
I'm pretty positive you're dead wrong about that, my friend.

598
00:31:19,580 --> 00:31:22,890
我覺得我們要達成一致是很困難的
I don't think there's anything we could possibly agree on.

599
00:31:24,520 --> 00:31:26,580
我不知道你在玩兒什么把戲
I don't know what game you're playing,

600
00:31:26,600 --> 00:31:28,440
但我勸你廢話少說
but I suggest you cut the bullshit.

601
00:31:28,480 --> 00:31:30,900
如果沒有別的啥事兒 我想我們就聊到這兒吧
If there's nothing else, I think we're done here.

602
00:31:31,160 --> 00:31:35,280
難道你忘記了我可是知道你那骯臟小秘密的人?
Aren't you forgetting that I know your dirty little secret?

603
00:31:35,380 --> 00:31:38,420
你周圍的人要是知道了你的把柄
There are people close to you that wouldn't be happy

604
00:31:38,440 --> 00:31:39,900
恐怕不會太開心吧
if they knew what I know.

605
00:31:45,840 --> 00:31:48,280
我們都是聰明人 不可能受擺布于
We're both too smart to allow pettiness

606
00:31:48,340 --> 00:31:49,380
那些小事的
to dictate our actions.

607
00:31:49,440 --> 00:31:50,810
我們肯定比那有能耐吧
We're better than that.

608
00:31:51,100 --> 00:31:52,700
權衡一下利弊吧
Weigh the pros and cons.

609
00:31:53,160 --> 00:31:54,920
做你該做的
Do what you need to do.

610
00:31:55,000 --> 00:31:56,920
一旦表格的事兒結束
As soon as the tabulations are over with,

611
00:31:56,940 --> 00:31:58,740
你就會知道告訴別人這件事兒
you'll know that telling anyone about that

612
00:31:58,760 --> 00:32:00,420
對我們大家都沒有好處
does neither one of us any good.

613
00:32:01,060 --> 00:32:02,500
實際上 你應該有自覺
In fact, you'll realize

614
00:32:02,500 --> 00:32:04,140
你在你的位置上做任何事兒
that the only thing to do in your position

615
00:32:04,180 --> 00:32:07,480
對我來說都不是事兒
when it comes to me is nothing.

616
00:34:10,680 --> 00:34:13,140
晚上好 威力克先生 我是庫特蘭德警探
Good evening, Mr. Wellick. I'm Detective Quattlander.

617
00:34:13,220 --> 00:34:14,840
這位是瓊斯警探
This is Detective Jones.

618
00:34:15,220 --> 00:34:16,760
你很清楚
As I know you're aware,

619
00:34:16,800 --> 00:34:19,380
我們今天想和你在你的辦公室談談
we were hoping to speak with you at your office today,

620
00:34:19,400 --> 00:34:21,820
但是你的助手說你出去了
but your assistant said you're out.

621
00:34:21,820 --> 00:34:22,860
怎么回事?
What's this about?

622
00:34:23,060 --> 00:34:24,640
我們在調查一個殺手
We're investigating a murder

623
00:34:24,660 --> 00:34:27,440
他出現在你丈夫工作的地方 女士
that occurred at your husband's place of employment, ma'am.

624
00:34:27,880 --> 00:34:29,360
我們能進去談嗎?
May we please come in?

625
00:34:29,380 --> 00:34:30,340
殺手?
A murder?

626
00:34:31,860 --> 00:34:34,480
女士 麻煩你說英語 好嗎?
Ma'am, do you mind speaking in English, please?

627
00:34:34,540 --> 00:34:35,940
我覺得你們這樣不合適吧
I think this is inappropriate,

628
00:34:35,960 --> 00:34:38,160
就這樣唐突地來我家 讓我的妻子擔心
you coming to my house like this, upsetting my wife.

629
00:34:38,180 --> 00:34:39,720
我明天回去我的辦公室--
I will be in my office tomorrow--

630
00:34:39,740 --> 00:34:42,520
威力克先生 要知道現在可是非常時期
Mr. Wellick, as you can imagine this is very time sensitive.

631
00:34:42,540 --> 00:34:44,640
我們只需要問你一些問題
We just need to ask you a few questions.

632
00:34:44,660 --> 00:34:47,360
實際上 你們兩都要問 因為你兩
Actually, both of you, since you were both

633
00:34:47,400 --> 00:34:49,760
都出席了昨晚的招待會
in attendance at the reception last night.

634
00:34:49,860 --> 00:34:53,140
好 我向你保證 我們真的一點點相關信息都沒有
Yeah, I can assure you, we have no information whatsoever.

635
00:34:53,160 --> 00:34:54,480
就一點兒時間
It will only take a moment.

636
00:34:55,300 --> 00:34:58,600
而且你們都認識死者 夏倫 諾斯
And you both did know the deceased, Sharon Knowles.

637
00:34:59,440 --> 00:35:01,060
你確實認識她吧?
You did know her, yes?

638
00:35:01,320 --> 00:35:02,560
莎朗 諾爾斯?
Sharon Knowles?

639
00:35:05,480 --> 00:35:07,660
這真可怕
That's terrible.

640
00:35:07,700 --> 00:35:08,440
呃...
Um...

641
00:35:08,600 --> 00:35:11,180
是 是 我們認識她
Yes, yes, we did know her.

642
00:35:11,320 --> 00:35:13,040
請進
Please, come in.

643
00:35:23,240 --> 00:35:25,060
請坐 需要點兒啥嗎?
Have a seat. Can I get you anything?

644
00:35:25,100 --> 00:35:26,420
咖啡? 茶?
Coffee? Tea?

645
00:35:26,460 --> 00:35:27,540
咖啡就好
Coffee would be great.

646
00:35:27,840 --> 00:35:30,960
茶 如果有草本的更好 謝謝
Tea. Herbal if possible, please.

647
00:35:35,100 --> 00:35:39,060
威力克先生 昨晚你最后一次
Mr. Wellick, what time did you last see

648
00:35:39,080 --> 00:35:41,900
看見夏倫 諾斯是什么時候?
Sharon Knowles last night?

649
00:35:44,040 --> 00:35:45,580
威力克先生?
Mr. Wellick?

650
00:35:46,540 --> 00:35:48,550
你還好嗎?
Are you okay?

651
00:35:51,300 --> 00:35:53,160
喬安娜?
Joanna?

652
00:35:57,960 --> 00:35:59,300
寶寶好像要出生了
I think the baby's coming.

653
00:35:59,320 --> 00:36:01,360
我們得送她去醫院
We gotta get her to the hospital.

654
00:36:22,090 --> 00:36:24,620
氣候控制系統黑得怎么樣了?
How'd it go with the climate control hack?

655
00:36:26,540 --> 00:36:28,440
搞定了
Handled.

656
00:36:28,600 --> 00:36:30,980
我確實聰明又能干
I happen to be really smart and good at things.

657
00:36:31,120 --> 00:36:33,290
但你也不在乎這些
Not like you give a shit.

658
00:36:44,100 --> 00:36:46,970
那我們應該為此慶祝慶祝嘍
We should celebrate then.

659
00:36:54,950 --> 00:36:59,500
再過整整43小時
In 43 hours, exactly,

660
00:36:59,760 --> 00:37:02,740
我們的服務器將不再只是蜜罐系統陷阱
our server will no longer be a honeypot.

661
00:37:04,020 --> 00:37:05,860
而你編的隱匿程序
And that rootkit you wrote

662
00:37:06,780 --> 00:37:09,180
將會打垮邪惡公司
will take down Evil Corp.

663
00:37:10,340 --> 00:37:12,460
戴琳 我們總算成功了
We did it, Darlene.

664
00:37:12,860 --> 00:37:14,800
一定會的
It's gonna happen.

665
00:37:17,540 --> 00:37:20,220
我們真的在這樣做嗎?
We're really doing this?

666
00:37:30,050 --> 00:37:31,950
哦 天哪
Oh, my God!

667
00:37:34,750 --> 00:37:36,790
真是太高興了!
Be happy!

668
00:37:36,820 --> 00:37:38,700
那多虧了你
You did this.

669
00:37:39,000 --> 00:37:40,930
多虧了你啊
You did it.

670
00:37:40,960 --> 00:37:42,260
伊利艾特 你就要
Just like that, Elliot,

671
00:37:42,290 --> 00:37:44,080
改變世界啦
you're gonna change the world.

672
00:37:46,330 --> 00:37:47,930
那是我們一起做到的
We did this.

673
00:37:47,970 --> 00:37:51,760
我本想獨占這個功勞的
I would love to take credit on this one.

674
00:37:51,820 --> 00:37:54,020
但我不能
But I can't.

675
00:37:54,710 --> 00:37:57,040
說真的 這確實是你的功勞啊
No, really, this was you.

676
00:37:59,620 --> 00:38:03,810
毫無置疑 你確實是我見過的最厲害的人
You are seriously the best person I know,

677
00:38:03,850 --> 00:38:05,500
你知道嗎?
you know that?

678
00:38:10,190 --> 00:38:12,620
我真是太愛你了
I love you so much.

679
00:38:17,640 --> 00:38:20,560
哦 天哪 伊利艾特! 你搞什么啊?
Oh, my God, Elliot! What the f---?

680
00:38:21,970 --> 00:38:23,070
我 我很抱歉
I'm--I'm sorry.

681
00:38:23,100 --> 00:38:26,140
你到底是怎么了?
What the hell is wrong with you?

682
00:38:26,170 --> 00:38:27,610
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

683
00:38:27,640 --> 00:38:29,240
我很抱歉 我以為
I'm sorry, I thought--

684
00:38:29,270 --> 00:38:30,980
我只是
I just--

685
00:38:31,010 --> 00:38:32,340
真的很對不起
I'm sorry.

686
00:38:33,880 --> 00:38:36,180
哦 天哪 伊利艾特
Oh, my God, Elliot.

687
00:38:36,210 --> 00:38:39,720
你又忘了么?
Did you forget again?

688
00:38:39,750 --> 00:38:42,720
你忘記我是誰了嗎?
Did you forget who I am?

689
00:38:45,090 --> 00:38:47,020
你在說什么?
What do you mean?

690
00:38:47,630 --> 00:38:48,990
忘記什么?
Forget what?

691
00:38:51,100 --> 00:38:54,700
伊利艾特 我想讓你告訴我你把我看做誰
Elliot, I need you to tell me who you think I am.

692
00:38:56,230 --> 00:38:58,100
你在說什么啊?
What are you talking about?

693
00:38:58,140 --> 00:39:00,570
快點告訴我
Tell me right now.

694
00:39:05,140 --> 00:39:07,110
我不明白你在說什么
What are you saying?

695
00:39:07,150 --> 00:39:09,980
伊利艾特
Elliot.

696
00:39:12,250 --> 00:39:17,120
我當然 當然沒忘記
Of course I didn't-- didn't forget.

697
00:39:17,160 --> 00:39:19,700
你是戴琳
You're Darlene.

698
00:39:24,700 --> 00:39:27,720
你是戴琳啊
You're Darlene.

699
00:39:28,100 --> 00:39:30,000
伊利艾特
Elliot.

700
00:39:31,380 --> 00:39:33,880
你是戴琳
You're Darlene.

701
00:39:39,710 --> 00:39:40,950
我知道的
I know.

702
00:39:40,980 --> 00:39:42,680
我懂她要說什么了
I know what she's going to say.

703
00:39:42,710 --> 00:39:43,680
我是你的
I'm your...

704
00:39:43,720 --> 00:39:46,150
妹妹
Sister.

705
00:39:49,750 --> 00:39:52,620
你是我的妹妹
You're my sister.

706
00:40:14,510 --> 00:40:16,940
戴琳曾和我整天躲在電影院里
Darlene and I'd hide in movie theaters all day.

707
00:40:16,980 --> 00:40:18,140
她總是會唱歌
Darlene would sing

708
00:40:18,220 --> 00:40:19,880
她曾經在我們的家里玩滑板車
She rode her scooter in front of our house.

709
00:40:19,920 --> 00:40:21,450
我要崩潰了 我要瘋了 瘋了
I'm crazy.I'm crazy--crazy.

710
00:40:21,490 --> 00:40:22,990
她三年級時曾試圖逃跑
She tried to run away in the third grade.

711
00:40:23,020 --> 00:40:24,660
我怎么會不記得這些了呢?
How come I didn't remember this?

712
00:40:24,690 --> 00:40:26,760
媽媽對我們不好的時候我們會睡在同一張床上
Slept in the same bed when our mom was mean to us.

713
00:40:26,790 --> 00:40:28,490
我怎么會忘記呢? 我記得她的聲音的
Why did I forget? I remember her voice.

714
00:40:28,530 --> 00:40:30,130
我怎么能夠忘記呢? 我要瘋掉了
How could I forget? I'm crazy.

715
00:40:30,160 --> 00:40:33,700
我要發瘋了 瘋了 我快瘋了 瘋了 我絕對是瘋了
I'm crazy--crazy-- I'm crazy--crazy--I'm crazy.

716
00:40:33,730 --> 00:40:35,130
你難道瘋了嗎?
Are you freaking out?

717
00:40:35,170 --> 00:40:36,870
快告訴我事實
Tell me the truth.

718
00:40:36,900 --> 00:40:38,840
一直以來你都是這樣想的嗎?
Were you in on this the whole time?

719
00:40:38,870 --> 00:40:41,070
是嗎?
Were you?

720
00:40:43,240 --> 00:40:44,680
快想想 該死的 快回想下
Think, God damn it. Think.

721
00:40:44,710 --> 00:40:46,180
我怎么可能就這樣輕易忘記她呢?
How can I just forget her like that?

722
00:40:46,210 --> 00:40:48,150
這可是一個人啊 有著難以改變的關系啊
A whole person. A relationship.

723
00:40:48,180 --> 00:40:49,550
這算是健忘癥嗎?
Is this amnesia?

724
00:40:49,580 --> 00:40:50,610
我還有什么不記得了呢?
What else am I not remembering?

725
00:40:50,650 --> 00:40:51,600
我要崩潰了
I'm crazy.

726
00:40:51,640 --> 00:40:53,150
我本該繼續吃藥的
I should have stayed on the meds.

727
00:40:53,180 --> 00:40:54,690
我要瘋了 我要得失心瘋了
I'm crazy.I'm out of my mind.

728
00:40:54,720 --> 00:40:56,720
我懂 我真是不該把你創造出來
I knew it, I should have never created you.

729
00:40:56,760 --> 00:40:58,960
我應該聽聽克里斯塔的話的
I should have listened to Krista.

730
00:41:02,830 --> 00:41:05,130
我是在逃避自己
I avoid myself.

731
00:41:05,160 --> 00:41:06,530
為什么?
Why?

732
00:41:06,560 --> 00:41:08,170
我好害怕
I'm afraid.

733
00:41:08,200 --> 00:41:09,230
是的
Okay.

734
00:41:09,270 --> 00:41:10,730
害怕什么?
Afraid of what?

735
00:41:10,770 --> 00:41:12,540
害怕發現太多
Finding too much.

736
00:41:12,570 --> 00:41:14,610
太少 發現不了
Too little. Nothing at all.

737
00:41:14,640 --> 00:41:16,670
我真的存在嗎?
Do I even exist?

738
00:41:16,710 --> 00:41:20,210
看著我 伊利艾特 奧爾德森
See me, Elliot Alderson.

739
00:41:20,250 --> 00:41:21,810
我就在你眼前
I am here.

740
00:41:25,050 --> 00:41:27,990
現在我要走了
Now I'm gone.

741
00:41:41,830 --> 00:41:43,970
我們必須深挖一下
We have to hack...

742
00:41:44,000 --> 00:41:46,000
我的信息
me.

743
00:42:08,890 --> 00:42:11,200
什么都沒了
Nothing.

744
00:42:11,230 --> 00:42:13,000
完全沒身份
No identity.

745
00:42:13,030 --> 00:42:16,170
我完全就是個鬼魂啊
I'm a ghost.

746
00:42:28,560 --> 00:42:31,180
我剛剛是不是把自己刪掉了?
Did I erase myself?

747
00:44:25,160 --> 00:44:27,660
我覺得我們有必要談談
I think we should talk.

