7
00:00:03,500 --> 00:00:06,300
機器人先生 前情提要

8
00:00:03,500 --> 00:00:06,300
大家字幕組 傾情譯制

9
00:00:27,000 --> 00:00:29,000
翻譯    墳老絲  Libear

10
00:00:29,000 --> 00:00:31,000
翻譯    墳老絲  Libear

11
00:00:31,000 --> 00:00:33,000
翻譯    子虛烏有  兔八哥

12
00:00:33,000 --> 00:00:35,000
翻譯    子虛烏有  兔八哥

13
00:00:35,000 --> 00:00:37,000
校對    Libear  鑫鑫美少女  Xz

14
00:00:37,000 --> 00:00:39,000
校對    Libear  鑫鑫美少女  Xz

15
00:00:39,000 --> 00:00:41,000
時間軸    嵬森  我在馬路邊

16
00:00:41,000 --> 00:00:43,000
時間軸    嵬森  我在馬路邊

17
00:00:43,000 --> 00:00:45,000
壓制    晟晟

18
00:00:45,000 --> 00:00:47,000
壓制    晟晟

19
00:00:47,000 --> 00:00:49,000
監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森  坑坑

20
00:00:49,000 --> 00:00:51,000
監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森  坑坑

21
00:06:11,200 --> 00:06:21,260
機器人先生

22
00:06:11,200 --> 00:06:21,260
第一季  第七集

23
00:10:44,560 --> 00:10:47,850
禁閉時間:Kevi未經審訊就被美國政府關押了這么長時間

24
00:10:44,560 --> 00:10:47,850
3年，4個月，9天，10小時，42分

25
00:11:05,910 --> 00:11:06,910
我隆鼻了

26
00:11:06,910 --> 00:11:07,880
我隆鼻了

27
00:11:06,910 --> 00:11:07,880
戀足者

28
00:11:09,830 --> 00:11:10,260
我假裝愛我丈夫

29
00:11:10,710 --> 00:11:11,550
我假裝愛我丈夫

30
00:11:10,710 --> 00:11:11,550
我暴飲暴食

31
00:11:08,450 --> 00:11:08,790
性恐懼

32
00:11:08,790 --> 00:11:09,790
性恐懼

33
00:11:10,710 --> 00:11:11,550
性恐懼

34
00:11:11,550 --> 00:11:12,500
我偷竊

35
00:11:12,540 --> 00:11:13,340
我偷竊

36
00:11:13,340 --> 00:11:14,600
我討厭我的家人

37
00:11:15,670 --> 00:11:17,800
我內心空虛

38
00:13:30,220 --> 00:13:31,300
藝術家:

39
00:13:33,600 --> 00:13:35,020
專輯:

40
00:25:29,250 --> 00:25:33,000
赫斯特圖書館

41
00:25:16,300 --> 00:25:17,640
絕壁植入

42
00:31:22,540 --> 00:31:23,510
穩住

43
00:00:00,310 --> 00:00:03,450
那 有什么發現?
So, what do we got?

44
00:00:03,610 --> 00:00:06,100
泰利 科爾比參與了對
Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of

45
00:00:06,120 --> 00:00:08,830
華盛頓區有毒廢棄物丑聞的掩埋
Washington Township toxic waste scandal.

46
00:00:08,850 --> 00:00:11,210
我們需要些什么證據?
What do we need to prove our case?

47
00:00:11,230 --> 00:00:12,770
一個當時在決定制造關于
Someone who was there

48
00:00:12,790 --> 00:00:16,520
化學廢棄物的假消息的時候 在現場的人
when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.

49
00:00:16,540 --> 00:00:17,900
給我滾遠點
Get the hell away from my home.

50
00:00:17,920 --> 00:00:19,090
滾遠點
Get away from my home.

51
00:00:19,110 --> 00:00:21,210
伊利艾特 你到底怎么了
Elliot, what is going on with you.

52
00:00:21,230 --> 00:00:23,860
你什么都不告訴我我沒辦法幫你
I cannot help you if you keep me in the dark.

53
00:00:23,880 --> 00:00:25,280
出問題了
We got problems.

54
00:00:25,310 --> 00:00:27,160
黑暗軍團放鴿子了
The Dark Army is bailing.

55
00:00:27,180 --> 00:00:28,210
這事兒沒完
It's not over.

56
00:00:28,280 --> 00:00:30,360
今晚不行 我們還會找到其它辦法的
We'll find a way, just not tonight.

57
00:00:30,380 --> 00:00:33,150
和這種人結婚你不覺得腦疼嗎?
How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?

58
00:00:33,170 --> 00:00:34,800
你是不是也想看我發火(尿)?
You want to watch me piss too?

59
00:00:34,820 --> 00:00:35,920
斯考特 這中間有誤會--
Scott, a misunderstand--

60
00:00:35,940 --> 00:00:38,450
為了你我很樂意把我的老二掏出來
Happy to pull my dick out for you,

61
00:00:38,820 --> 00:00:39,620
伊利艾特!
Elliot!

62
00:00:40,040 --> 00:00:40,850
她在哪?
Where is she?

63
00:00:40,870 --> 00:00:42,820
說了會把她還給你的 兄弟
Told you you'd get her back, bro.

64
00:01:50,990 --> 00:01:51,990
操!
Shit!

65
00:02:04,110 --> 00:02:05,150
臥槽!
Shit!

66
00:02:09,560 --> 00:02:10,890
開門!
Open up!

67
00:02:11,350 --> 00:02:13,360
我在走廊血流成河了!
I'm bleeding all over the hallway!

68
00:02:15,090 --> 00:02:17,870
生死攸關!
It's a life-or-death situation out here!

69
00:02:18,420 --> 00:02:20,420
聽著 我知道你在里面 我看見你剛進去
Look, I know you're in there. I just saw you go in.

70
00:02:20,450 --> 00:02:22,080
快開門!
Open up!

71
00:02:24,040 --> 00:02:24,850
我找--
I'm lo--

72
00:02:27,600 --> 00:02:29,260
怎么 你就傻傻地站那嗎?
Well, are you just gonna stand there?

73
00:02:29,840 --> 00:02:31,460
給我倒杯水 傻瓜
Get me a glass of water, dummy.

74
00:02:32,490 --> 00:02:34,790
我能接點水嗎? 謝謝
Can I use this? Thanks.

75
00:02:37,310 --> 00:02:38,730
這條魚是我侄女給我的
My niece gave him to me.

76
00:02:39,140 --> 00:02:41,230
天 我還沒給他取名字呢
I haven't even named him yet. God.

77
00:02:41,250 --> 00:02:44,080
你能不能體會到一個六歲熊孩子帶來的壓力?
Do you know the pressure of an ecstatic six-year-old?

78
00:02:44,200 --> 00:02:48,220
我是說 如果那家伙死了的話 她的整個世界都會崩潰
I mean, I kill that thing, and her whole world collapses.

79
00:02:48,240 --> 00:02:49,910
我喜歡你這個房間的布置
I like what you did with the place.

80
00:02:53,150 --> 00:02:56,020
恩 挺不錯的 不過還是更喜歡我的
Yeah, nice setup. Still like mine better though.

81
00:03:08,940 --> 00:03:11,190
嘿 想要高檔貨就跟我說
Yo, let me know if you want a top-shelf hookup.

82
00:03:12,490 --> 00:03:14,000
對了 正好你在...
Actually, now that I have you...

83
00:03:14,840 --> 00:03:18,750
你能幫我搬一下衣柜嗎...肌肉男?
Will you help me move a dresser...Mr. Muscles?

84
00:03:19,670 --> 00:03:21,380
好吧 來 來吧
Okay, come on. Just come on.

85
00:03:33,000 --> 00:03:35,730
車里男搬家公司現在太真格了
Man 'n' van is getting way too legit.

86
00:03:36,270 --> 00:03:37,550
這些家伙以前就是些 鼓手什么的
They used to just be, like, drummers

87
00:03:37,570 --> 00:03:38,970
開著他們老娘的本田奧德賽面包車
with their mom's Honda Odysseys.

88
00:03:38,990 --> 00:03:41,500
現在居然是皇后區的一家真的公司
Now it's an actual company in Queens.

89
00:03:41,520 --> 00:03:44,790
這些人還真是面包車里的男人呀
I mean, the guys are literally men in vans.

90
00:03:44,810 --> 00:03:46,890
我可以從你那買嗎啡
I'd buy morphine from you,

91
00:03:47,310 --> 00:03:49,570
前提是你要給我弄到賽寶松
if you could also get me suboxone.

92
00:03:51,640 --> 00:03:55,550
這個 呃 要弄到賽寶松幾乎不可能
Well, um, it's pretty much impossible to get suboxone.

93
00:03:55,580 --> 00:03:57,090
我的供貨商沒有
My supplier doesn't have it.

94
00:04:02,460 --> 00:04:05,450
我看過一首歌的現場表演 簡直太激動了
I saw this song live once. It was so rad.

95
00:04:05,470 --> 00:04:07,910
簡直太愛現場聽喜歡的歌
Don't you just love hearing your favorite songs in person,

96
00:04:07,930 --> 00:04:10,450
那種 震耳欲聾
like, half deaf from the speakers,

97
00:04:10,470 --> 00:04:12,470
群情鼎沸的感覺 你不喜歡嗎?
everyone going nuts around you?

98
00:04:12,490 --> 00:04:13,350
不喜歡
No.

99
00:04:15,270 --> 00:04:16,880
說話很直 我敬佩這樣的人
Direct. I respect that.

100
00:04:19,490 --> 00:04:21,290
我只是討厭演唱會
I just hate concerts.

101
00:04:22,940 --> 00:04:24,140
太多人
Lots of people.

102
00:04:29,350 --> 00:04:30,920
所以你不喜歡別人 是吧?
You don't like people, huh?

103
00:04:31,910 --> 00:04:33,640
大部分吧 不喜歡
Not most of them, no.

104
00:04:35,940 --> 00:04:36,820
好吧
Okay.

105
00:04:37,370 --> 00:04:39,060
那 按這個理論
Well, so by that rationale,

106
00:04:39,380 --> 00:04:42,120
如果你真的喜歡上一個人 那就 像是
if you were to really like one person, it'd be, like,

107
00:04:42,540 --> 00:04:46,480
一種失常或者是一種異常行為
considered an aberration or an abnormality

108
00:04:46,500 --> 00:04:48,670
甚至可以說是 腦殘了
or special, even.

109
00:04:50,550 --> 00:04:51,470
可以這么說吧
I guess.

110
00:04:52,680 --> 00:04:54,670
其實 我就向往腦殘呢
Well, I aim for special,

111
00:04:54,700 --> 00:04:56,790
咱倆比比吧
so challenge accepted.

112
00:05:04,170 --> 00:05:07,900
如果我們早一點認識就好了
I wish we already knew each other.

113
00:05:09,590 --> 00:05:11,850
現在就不這么尷尬
Would make this feel less awkward.

114
00:05:13,780 --> 00:05:15,960
你現在真的覺得尷尬嗎?
You really feel awkward right now?

115
00:05:18,640 --> 00:05:19,350
有點
Yeah.

116
00:05:22,270 --> 00:05:24,320
好吧 那我也希望我們早點認識呢
Well, then I wish we knew each other too then.

117
00:05:30,150 --> 00:05:31,460
我去
Oh, yikes.

118
00:05:31,480 --> 00:05:34,850
我 呃 我遲到了 約了閨蜜去喝東西
I, um, I'm late. Meeting the girls for drinks.

119
00:05:36,310 --> 00:05:38,230
哦 對了 我叫夏拉
Oh, um, I'm Shayla.

120
00:05:43,260 --> 00:05:44,110
我叫伊利艾特
Elliot.

121
00:05:48,620 --> 00:05:51,880
對了 我倒是認識一個人有賽寶松賣
You know, I do know of a guy who sells Suboxone.

122
00:05:52,070 --> 00:05:53,230
據說他是個瘋子
He's supposed to be a fucking psychopath,

123
00:05:53,250 --> 00:05:54,880
但是如果你需要的話 我可以給他打電話
but if you want, I can call him.

124
00:05:55,280 --> 00:05:56,780
為了你和瘋子打交道可能也是值得的
You might be worth a psychopath.

125
00:05:56,800 --> 00:05:58,200
我也不知道 可能吧
I don't know. Maybe.

126
00:05:59,400 --> 00:06:02,470
對了 魚就交給你了 小家伙
Oh, and keep the fish, you filthy animal.

127
00:06:24,440 --> 00:06:26,620
抱歉 一段時間沒跟你說話了
Sorry I haven't talked to you in a while.

128
00:06:27,270 --> 00:06:29,770
我是說 才一個月
I mean, it's only been a month, which I guess

129
00:06:29,790 --> 00:06:32,450
在宏偉藍圖中可能不顯得太長
in the grand scheme of things isn't that long.

130
00:06:33,850 --> 00:06:35,250
我們的生命在宇宙的歷史中
Isn't our life like a blip

131
00:06:35,270 --> 00:06:37,540
不就像一個光點一樣嗎?
in the cosmic calender or something?

132
00:06:40,450 --> 00:06:41,760
夏拉也是
So that's Shayla.

133
00:06:42,210 --> 00:06:43,000
僅僅是一個光點
A blip.

134
00:06:43,920 --> 00:06:44,870
可能都算不上
Not even.

135
00:06:45,650 --> 00:06:47,770
這一秒還在 下一秒就閃沒了
Here one blip, gone the next.

136
00:06:48,100 --> 00:06:50,470
我狠自己的是 我已經習慣了
Makes me hate myself that I've already gotten used to

137
00:06:50,490 --> 00:06:52,600
她已離去的感覺
the idea of her not being here.

138
00:06:53,430 --> 00:06:55,360
一年之后 我可能會想想她
In a year, I'll maybe think about her

139
00:06:55,380 --> 00:06:56,860
也就是偶爾
every once in a while.

140
00:06:57,150 --> 00:07:00,460
過后她就成了一件軼事 僅僅是一個談資
Then she'll become an anecdote, a thing to say.

141
00:07:00,850 --> 00:07:02,600
"我認識一個已經去世的女孩"
"I knew a girl that died,"

142
00:07:03,150 --> 00:07:06,240
還附帶福利 "她是因我而死"
with the added bonus of, "She died because of me."

143
00:07:08,070 --> 00:07:10,150
也許我是該恨我自己
Maybe I should hate myself.

144
00:07:10,250 --> 00:07:12,600
這是最后兩張表
Here are the last two forms.

145
00:07:12,700 --> 00:07:14,060
她要趕我走了
She's getting rid of me,

146
00:07:14,240 --> 00:07:16,370
萬一你還沒想到的話
in case you're still trying to figure that out.

147
00:07:16,460 --> 00:07:18,100
- 一旦我... - 在最下面簽字
- Once I... - Sign on the bottom.

148
00:07:23,130 --> 00:07:24,110
然后我把這文件送去法庭
Then I'll deliver it to the court,

149
00:07:24,130 --> 00:07:25,630
在兩周內 你會收到
and in two weeks' time, you'll receive

150
00:07:25,650 --> 00:07:28,390
官方的正式取消強制治療指令通知
an official release from the mandate.

151
00:07:29,270 --> 00:07:32,080
第二份表格說明我們已經在這里面談長達一年之久了
That second form means that we've been sitting in this room for a year.

152
00:07:32,100 --> 00:07:35,900
有長達52個小時的克里斯塔的嘮叨聲在這個房間里回蕩
Over 52 hours of Krista's voice bouncing around this room.

153
00:07:36,190 --> 00:07:39,740
她認為她這是在白費力氣 也許還真是
She thinks she's a wasted echo. Maybe she is.

154
00:07:40,030 --> 00:07:41,600
我在想 我花了多少時間
I wonder how much time I've spent

155
00:07:41,620 --> 00:07:43,500
坐在這里 不聽她嘮叨
not listening to her in here.

156
00:07:43,710 --> 00:07:44,740
我很擔心你 伊利艾特
I'm worried about you, Elliot.

157
00:07:44,760 --> 00:07:46,150
我真的很希望你能繼續過來
I really want you to keep coming here.

158
00:07:46,170 --> 00:07:47,670
我們還有很多事要完成
We've got a lot more work to do.

159
00:07:47,690 --> 00:07:48,980
她對我還有要求
She wants more from me

160
00:07:49,000 --> 00:07:50,640
但她又不信任我
but she doesn't believe in me.

161
00:07:50,660 --> 00:07:53,700
我努力嘗試是因為我相信在你心里的某一部分
I tried because I believe some part inside of you

162
00:07:53,920 --> 00:07:55,800
還是想好好做事的
wants to do this right.

163
00:07:56,120 --> 00:07:56,890
你呢?
You?

164
00:07:57,560 --> 00:07:59,040
你同意她的話么?
Are you on her side?

165
00:08:22,310 --> 00:08:24,140
你的電源插口得清理清理了
You should clean your sockets.

166
00:08:36,480 --> 00:08:39,480
聽上去像是童話 但我還是會相信
Sounds too good to be true, but I'll bite.

167
00:08:40,060 --> 00:08:41,150
你們想要什么?
What's the ask?

168
00:08:41,640 --> 00:08:43,040
既然我們的委托人有著
Given my client has information

169
00:08:43,060 --> 00:08:45,080
能幫助你的委托人的案子的信息
that could help your client's case,

170
00:08:45,160 --> 00:08:48,210
我們要求這個會議只有她 科爾比 以及我出席
we want the meeting restricted to her, Colby, and myself,

171
00:08:48,440 --> 00:08:50,320
并且是秘密會議 不得記錄
And we want it conducted off-record.

172
00:08:51,710 --> 00:08:52,890
安塔拉 拜托
Antara, come on.

173
00:08:53,480 --> 00:08:55,360
我的委托人不會同意你出席
My client won't accept your presence.

174
00:08:56,170 --> 00:08:57,680
我們的委托人花錢讓我們出席呢
Our client pays for ours.

175
00:08:57,700 --> 00:08:59,400
那你就有責任來代表他
Then you're duty-bound to present him

176
00:08:59,420 --> 00:09:02,500
為我們的有利證據做出合法開價
with any legitimate offer of beneficial evidence.

177
00:09:03,370 --> 00:09:04,310
那是當然
Of course.

178
00:09:04,880 --> 00:09:08,010
給我們一些真正合法和有利的
Give us something truly legitimate and beneficial.

179
00:09:09,330 --> 00:09:11,700
而你都不肯說 你的委托人手里究竟有什么證據
You won't even tell us what the hell your client has.

180
00:09:12,010 --> 00:09:14,960
賽斯 我們已經在談判桌上
Seth, we've been sitting on opposite sides

181
00:09:14,980 --> 00:09:17,520
面對面談了二十多年了
of the negotiating table for two decades.

182
00:09:17,550 --> 00:09:19,020
我又不是啥逗逼
I'm not some joker come out of the woodwork

183
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:20,920
想從科爾比那兒撈一票
trying to scam Colby for millions.

184
00:09:20,940 --> 00:09:23,330
我是在給他唯一的希望一些曙光
I'm giving him the only glimmer of hope he's had.

185
00:09:26,100 --> 00:09:29,280
我們會轉達你的提議的 謝謝
We'll pass along your offer. Thanks for your time.

186
00:09:46,960 --> 00:09:48,620
羅伊德說你想見我
Lloyd said you wanted to see me.

187
00:09:54,330 --> 00:09:57,430
聽著 我很感謝你如此敬業
Look, I appreciate your commitment to this job.

188
00:09:57,680 --> 00:09:58,720
是真的
I really do.

189
00:10:01,300 --> 00:10:03,440
但我不想看到你如此艱難得
But I don't see how you've plowed through

190
00:10:03,870 --> 00:10:05,610
過著這幾周 所以
these last few weeks, so

191
00:10:05,670 --> 00:10:07,810
我想給你放幾天假
I want to offer you some time off.

192
00:10:08,560 --> 00:10:10,090
- 讓你能... - 我不需要放假
- Just some time to... - I don't need time off.

193
00:10:10,110 --> 00:10:10,960
我沒事
I'm good.

194
00:10:16,480 --> 00:10:19,060
嗯... 嗯 還有一件事
Uh...Uh, one more thing.

195
00:10:25,630 --> 00:10:28,340
對她的離去我很遺憾 伊利艾特
I'm so sorry she was taken away, Elliot,

196
00:10:28,420 --> 00:10:33,180
但是別因為她的離去而完全封閉起來自己
but don't let her death close you off entirely.

197
00:10:33,890 --> 00:10:37,310
去找個能敞開心扉聊一聊的人
Find someone you can be your honest self with,

198
00:10:38,570 --> 00:10:39,440
好嗎?
okay?

199
00:10:40,500 --> 00:10:42,740
我記得我小時候 我是因為抄襲我喜歡的網站
I remember when I was a kid, I got into web design

200
00:10:42,770 --> 00:10:45,090
才喜歡上網頁設計的
by ripping off sites I liked.

201
00:10:45,160 --> 00:10:47,250
你只要在你的瀏覽器上點擊 查看源代碼
All you had to do was view source on your browser

202
00:10:47,270 --> 00:10:49,550
然后就能看到那些代碼了
and there it was, the code.

203
00:10:49,930 --> 00:10:52,960
你可以復制粘貼一下 改點小地方
You could copy-paste it, modify it a little,

204
00:10:53,120 --> 00:10:57,730
寫上你的大名 就這樣 這就是你的網頁了
Put your name on it, and like that, it was your site.

205
00:10:59,160 --> 00:11:00,360
查看源代碼
View source.

206
00:11:00,810 --> 00:11:02,640
要是每個人都有代碼會是怎么樣呢?
What if we had that for people?

207
00:11:04,130 --> 00:11:05,880
人們會不會真的想看到呢?
Would people really want to see?

208
00:11:17,990 --> 00:11:20,670
去找個能敞開心扉聊一聊的人?
Find someone to be your honest self with?

209
00:11:21,760 --> 00:11:22,910
簡直狗屁
Bullshit.

210
00:11:26,920 --> 00:11:29,530
真是不錯的建議 謝啦
Really good advice. Thanks.

211
00:11:33,600 --> 00:11:37,350
原句是 "美國黑客組織 F社會
I quote, "The U.S. contingent of the hacker group fsociety

212
00:11:37,370 --> 00:11:39,070
在世界最大的跨國企業
has remained quiet since the upheaval inflicted

213
00:11:39,090 --> 00:11:41,650
的動蕩之后 一直沒有動靜
upon the world's largest multinational conglomerate.

214
00:11:41,670 --> 00:11:44,120
國土安全部部長 杰 約翰遜
Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson

215
00:11:44,140 --> 00:11:46,130
今天發表聲明說
released a statement today stating that,

216
00:11:46,150 --> 00:11:49,090
'這些團體若是想發起有效攻擊
'these groups lack the resources and knowledge

217
00:11:49,110 --> 00:11:52,400
還缺少很多資源和智力呢'"
of the U.S. cell to successfully mount an attack.'"

218
00:11:52,420 --> 00:11:53,840
引用結束
End quote.

219
00:11:55,390 --> 00:11:56,850
是啊 所以呢?
Yeah, so?

220
00:11:57,800 --> 00:11:59,700
我們得把黑暗軍團找回來
We gotta get the Dark Army back.

221
00:12:00,420 --> 00:12:03,200
老兄 我一直都在嘗試
Dude, I've been trying.

222
00:12:03,790 --> 00:12:06,370
你得要我去攻擊他多少次?
How many times do you want me to hack him?

223
00:12:06,390 --> 00:12:08,870
你知道要黑一個黑客是多難么?
Do you know how hard hacking a hacker is?

224
00:12:08,890 --> 00:12:11,010
思科總是換他們的操作系統啊
Cisco switches OSes, like, all the time.

225
00:12:11,030 --> 00:12:13,040
戴琳 我們得開個會
Darlene, we need one meeting.

226
00:12:13,060 --> 00:12:15,460
是啊 我一直在用思科的口徑
Yeah, well, I've been using Cisco's handle

227
00:12:15,480 --> 00:12:18,030
來發送請求 發了一個月了
to send requests for the past month.

228
00:12:18,410 --> 00:12:19,770
啥都沒有
I got nothing.

229
00:12:20,570 --> 00:12:23,000
他是比我笨 但是沒笨到哪里去
He's slower than me, but not by much.

230
00:12:23,320 --> 00:12:25,000
如果我們能和白玫瑰直接對話...
If we can talk to WhiteRose directly...

231
00:12:25,020 --> 00:12:27,760
白玫瑰? 白玫瑰?
WhiteRose? WhiteRose?

232
00:12:27,780 --> 00:12:28,680
說笑呢?
Really?

233
00:12:30,480 --> 00:12:34,200
好吧 假設--假設這個人真的存在
Okay, if--if the guy even exists,

234
00:12:34,220 --> 00:12:36,920
而且是個特大號的"假設"
and that's a big if,

235
00:12:36,940 --> 00:12:39,380
他也不可能和你見面的啊
no way he's meeting you face-to-face.

236
00:12:39,940 --> 00:12:41,050
我們也可以說...
For all we know...

237
00:12:42,390 --> 00:12:44,420
那個家伙就是白玫瑰
This dude's WhiteRose.

238
00:12:45,260 --> 00:12:46,560
打擾了!
Excuse me!

239
00:12:47,350 --> 00:12:49,540
你是白玫瑰嗎?
Are you WhiteRose?

240
00:12:52,280 --> 00:12:53,760
就是這樣
A likely story.

241
00:12:55,740 --> 00:12:58,650
更何況 那些備份盤已經寄去
'sides, the tape backups already shipped

242
00:12:58,670 --> 00:13:00,720
那些新的鐵山設施了
to all the new Steel Mountain facilities,

243
00:13:00,740 --> 00:13:03,380
而我們還沒找到其他方法
and we still haven't found a way around that.

244
00:13:05,210 --> 00:13:06,860
我已經想好了一個計劃
I got a plan in motion.

245
00:13:08,640 --> 00:13:10,240
老天爺都笑了
And god's laughing.

246
00:13:31,370 --> 00:13:33,490
只剩下這些東西是有關她的了
This is all I have left of her.

247
00:13:39,900 --> 00:13:41,310
我會想念她的
I will miss her.

248
00:13:51,210 --> 00:13:52,670
我得再清理一次了
I need to wipe again.

249
00:14:16,490 --> 00:14:18,270
如果你翻到下一頁
So if you scroll to the next page,

250
00:14:18,290 --> 00:14:20,150
就能看到采購和運營的
you'll see the summary of capital budgets

251
00:14:20,170 --> 00:14:22,380
資本預算總結
for purchasing and operations.

252
00:14:22,400 --> 00:14:23,870
懂了 周一會出來一份
We get it. The goddamn earning reports

253
00:14:23,900 --> 00:14:25,550
看上去很不錯的收益報表
are gonna look good come monday.

254
00:14:25,750 --> 00:14:27,520
我們的目標是推進賬單支付
Our aim is to facilitate bill payment

255
00:14:27,540 --> 00:14:29,180
提高金融安全
and heighten financial security,

256
00:14:29,200 --> 00:14:31,080
所以有額外的2%
so that's an extra 2%.

257
00:14:31,100 --> 00:14:32,600
知道嗎 要是我們的收益并沒有好轉
You know, if we hadn't turned our profits around,

258
00:14:32,630 --> 00:14:34,770
- 我就走人了 - 少騙人
- I was gonna leave. - No way.

259
00:14:35,100 --> 00:14:37,030
去哪兒? 別跟我說去蘋果
Where? Don't tell me apple.

260
00:14:37,120 --> 00:14:39,160
- 谷歌 - 才不信
- Google. - Don't buy it.

261
00:14:39,180 --> 00:14:41,120
在谷歌總部的排球場上
I got a blow job from the hiring executive

262
00:14:41,140 --> 00:14:43,370
人力資源部的主管給我來了個口活
on the Googleplex volleyball court.

263
00:14:43,500 --> 00:14:47,730
哦 她很火辣 有瑪麗莎 梅耶爾的風范
Oh, she was hot. Had a Marissa Mayer thing going on, too.

264
00:14:49,880 --> 00:14:51,410
火辣的主管都是從火辣的助理做起的
Hot execs started as hot assistants

265
00:14:51,430 --> 00:14:53,140
一路陪睡到頂峰
who fucked their way to the top

266
00:14:53,170 --> 00:14:55,130
比我們這些人 升職速度快兩倍
twice as fast as the rest of us.

267
00:14:55,150 --> 00:14:56,850
有些破爛事你知道嗎?
You know something screwed up?

268
00:14:57,320 --> 00:14:59,640
我聽說有些助理為了爬上去
I heard that, some assistants, they're going gay

269
00:14:59,660 --> 00:15:01,700
假裝是基佬
to move up the ladder.

270
00:15:01,640 --> 00:15:02,760
我告訴你件更離奇的吧
I'll do you one better.

271
00:15:02,770 --> 00:15:04,470
有那么一小撮可悲的
There's a special handful

272
00:15:04,490 --> 00:15:07,770
孤注一擲的主管也在做雞雞騎手
of pathetically desperate execs going cock jockey.

273
00:15:07,790 --> 00:15:10,010
不是吧 天了嚕!
No. Oh, my god!

274
00:15:10,510 --> 00:15:13,140
嘿 德懷特 我想問問 你的孩子怎么樣了?
Hey, Dwight, I meant to ask. How are your children?

275
00:15:13,160 --> 00:15:15,530
鬼知道 送去勞倫斯中學了
Hell if I know. Sent 'em off to Lawrence.

276
00:15:15,550 --> 00:15:17,250
貌似茱莉亞喜歡藝術
I think Julia likes art.

277
00:15:17,560 --> 00:15:19,430
哎呀 不可能面面俱到的嘛
Oh, well. Can't win 'em all.

278
00:15:19,760 --> 00:15:21,050
勞倫斯中學?
Lawrence?

279
00:15:21,430 --> 00:15:22,240
那你要是失業了
You'll never be able

280
00:15:22,260 --> 00:15:24,340
肯定就付不起學費了咯
to afford that tuition on unemployment.

281
00:15:24,570 --> 00:15:26,590
- 抱歉? - 你被炒了!
- Sorry? - You're fired!

282
00:15:46,040 --> 00:15:47,280
你們兩個也是
You two as well.

283
00:15:48,150 --> 00:15:51,010
我會確保你們都能收到最低遣散費的
I'm making sure you all receive the minimum severance packages.

284
00:15:52,590 --> 00:15:55,230
威力克先生 我不明白
Mr. Wellick, I-I don't understand.

285
00:15:56,490 --> 00:15:57,670
我們做錯什么了?
What did we do?

286
00:16:04,830 --> 00:16:05,820
啥都沒
Nothing.

287
00:16:09,400 --> 00:16:11,760
- 之后... - 你說有新消息會告訴我
- After... - You said you would update me.

288
00:16:12,310 --> 00:16:13,950
我得把我們的情況
I needed to discuss our situation

289
00:16:13,970 --> 00:16:15,380
和州檢察官討論討論
with the state's attorney.

290
00:16:16,160 --> 00:16:17,510
謝謝你過來 羅伊
Thanks for coming in, Roy.

291
00:16:24,110 --> 00:16:25,360
你坐下吧
I think you should have a seat.

292
00:16:32,450 --> 00:16:34,510
科爾比的律師30分鐘前打來電話
Colby's lawyers called 30 minutes ago.

293
00:16:34,530 --> 00:16:37,220
他們想要我們保證 他在開會前享有豁免權
They wanted a promise of total immunity before the meeting,

294
00:16:37,240 --> 00:16:39,550
我從剛才你見到的這個男人那里拿到這個豁免權了
which I obtained from the man you just met.

295
00:16:39,920 --> 00:16:42,820
所以 是的 科爾比同意了...
So, yes, Colby agreed...

296
00:16:43,990 --> 00:16:45,170
但有附加條件
with a caveat.

297
00:16:47,280 --> 00:16:50,430
我不能參加會議 你要一個人進去
I can't be in the room. You have to go in alone.

298
00:16:55,480 --> 00:16:59,530
聽著 你這么做是很有膽量
Look, you made a ballsy move...

299
00:17:00,020 --> 00:17:01,770
但你要是真那么做了
But you doing what you're about to do...

300
00:17:02,450 --> 00:17:04,710
進到一個非常有權力的男人的家里
entering the home of a very powerful man

301
00:17:04,730 --> 00:17:07,400
冒著很大的風險 還要向他索取...
with a lot at stake and asking him for something...

302
00:17:07,460 --> 00:17:09,780
怎么樣都是件危險的事
That's always a dangerous proposition.

303
00:17:11,390 --> 00:17:13,830
所以我再問最后一次...
So one last time...

304
00:17:14,860 --> 00:17:16,860
你確定你想這么做嗎?
Are you sure you want to do this?

305
00:17:33,130 --> 00:17:34,540
我去
Shit, man.

306
00:17:35,670 --> 00:17:37,160
我還以為你是個那些偷了
Thought you was one of them high schoolers

307
00:17:37,180 --> 00:17:38,970
我媽的躺椅的高中生呢
stole my mom's chaise lounge.

308
00:17:39,640 --> 00:17:41,450
很抱歉告訴你
As heartbreaking as it is to hear that,

309
00:17:41,470 --> 00:17:42,840
你得延期了
you're gonna have to put that off.

310
00:17:42,860 --> 00:17:44,010
把大家都聚集起來
Getting everybody back together.

311
00:17:44,030 --> 00:17:45,640
- 拜托 - 這次不行
- Come on. - No, man, not this time.

312
00:17:45,660 --> 00:17:46,780
我不干了
I'm out.

313
00:17:48,220 --> 00:17:50,100
你不能不干 我們需要你
You can't be out. We need you.

314
00:17:50,280 --> 00:17:53,070
聽著 有一批新的人指望著我呢
Look, man, I got a new set of people depending on me, okay?

315
00:17:53,460 --> 00:17:54,610
成堆的客戶
Clients out the wazoo.

316
00:17:54,630 --> 00:17:56,640
所以 只能祝你好運了
So, you know, I mean, good luck,

317
00:17:56,670 --> 00:17:58,330
幫我跟其他人打聲招呼
and tell the kids I said hi.

318
00:17:59,540 --> 00:18:01,070
這是什么? 你在這里干嘛呢?
What is this? What are you doing here?

319
00:18:01,400 --> 00:18:03,630
我搞清楚了怎么把
Well, I figured out how to insert

320
00:18:03,650 --> 00:18:06,980
四氫大麻酚的基因信息編碼注入酵母細胞
THC's genetic information code into yeast cells.

321
00:18:07,300 --> 00:18:08,540
賺錢速度翻三番
Tripled my earning speed.

322
00:18:08,970 --> 00:18:11,870
植物需要幾周才能長好 微生物只要幾天
Plants need weeks to develop. Microbes need days.

323
00:18:12,450 --> 00:18:14,670
所以你現在是在自家后院
So, what, you got a bath and body works

324
00:18:14,690 --> 00:18:16,890
搞起美體用品的裝瓶設備了?
bottling facility in your backyard?

325
00:18:18,960 --> 00:18:20,110
你試試
Try it.

326
00:18:20,810 --> 00:18:23,230
混合物里的四氫大麻酚值靠近邊界值
The THC level is borderline in that blend,

327
00:18:23,250 --> 00:18:26,490
薰衣草也不會影響致幻效果
and the lavender doesn't mess with the high.

328
00:18:26,520 --> 00:18:28,150
只要涂在皮膚上
You just smooth it on your skin.

329
00:18:28,330 --> 00:18:31,630
所以你是為了芳香物 放棄了一場革命?
So you're rejecting a revolution in favor of aroma profiles?

330
00:18:31,750 --> 00:18:33,040
真是大材小用
What a waste of potential.

331
00:18:33,510 --> 00:18:35,380
聽我說 我知道我腦子好使
Look, man, I know I got a good brain.

332
00:18:35,880 --> 00:18:37,310
而且...
Besides...

333
00:18:38,830 --> 00:18:41,390
我們這個小項目最后又是什么結果呢?
What was our little project in the end, anyway?

334
00:18:42,180 --> 00:18:44,120
要我說的話 就是臭狗屎
Wasted shit, if you ask me.

335
00:18:45,610 --> 00:18:47,790
好了 現在你基本上把我給激怒了
Well, now you're borderline pissing me off.

336
00:18:49,030 --> 00:18:50,080
那是事實嗎?
Is that a fact?

337
00:18:52,810 --> 00:18:54,370
如果我決定把你給激怒
And what exactly are you gonna do

338
00:18:54,390 --> 00:18:56,460
你究竟會做出什么舉動?
if I decide to cross that border?

339
00:18:58,340 --> 00:18:59,860
羅梅羅 看著我
Look at my face, Romero.

340
00:19:00,830 --> 00:19:02,470
你我都知道我是瘋子
You and I both know I'm crazy.

341
00:19:03,200 --> 00:19:04,790
而且不是可愛的那種
Not the cute kind either.

342
00:19:04,870 --> 00:19:06,940
我說的是有病的瘋子!
I'm talking crazy crazy!

343
00:19:12,330 --> 00:19:13,520
你玩失聯
You lost touch.

344
00:19:14,000 --> 00:19:15,500
你忘記了為贏得戰斗
You forgot the feeling of spilling blood

345
00:19:15,520 --> 00:19:17,350
在戰場上灑熱血的感覺
on the battlefield by winning the fight.

346
00:19:18,860 --> 00:19:20,450
我本不想傷害你的 羅梅羅
I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.

347
00:19:21,240 --> 00:19:22,420
我是愛你的
I love you, man.

348
00:19:23,270 --> 00:19:25,190
我只想你跟我回到游樂場
I just wanted you to come back to the arcade with me

349
00:19:25,300 --> 00:19:27,090
那樣我們就能一起改變世界
so we could change the world together.

350
00:19:28,950 --> 00:19:31,870
很顯然你不能對我這個瘋子說不
I am clearly too crazy for you to say no to.

351
00:19:39,420 --> 00:19:41,390
你這表情真是千金難買!
Look on your face is priceless!

352
00:19:43,400 --> 00:19:44,600
你個瘋子
Goddamn lunatic.

353
00:19:46,100 --> 00:19:47,930
我們開始行動的時候 你向我保證過
You gave me your word when we started this thing

354
00:19:47,950 --> 00:19:49,040
你會堅持到最后
that you'd finish it.

355
00:19:49,060 --> 00:19:51,380
我也向你保證 不管你做不做得到 我一定可以
I gave you my word what I'd do if you didn't.

356
00:19:52,330 --> 00:19:53,980
回頭游樂場見
See you back at the arcade.

357
00:20:10,880 --> 00:20:12,510
好了 姑娘把茶給你泡好了
Good. I see the girl got you tea.

358
00:20:17,820 --> 00:20:19,350
那么 我們開始吧
Well, let's get started.

359
00:20:26,220 --> 00:20:27,370
你想要多少?
How much do you want?

360
00:20:31,740 --> 00:20:32,830
報個價
Write your number.

361
00:20:35,070 --> 00:20:36,450
想問我什么請隨意
You can ask me anything you want,

362
00:20:37,660 --> 00:20:39,720
但我可以打包票 一切到了最后
but I promise you, at the end of the day,

363
00:20:39,820 --> 00:20:42,890
不管你要尋找什么答案 其魅力也不會超過金錢
money will always be better than what you're looking for.

364
00:20:46,510 --> 00:20:49,830
科爾比先生 1993年
Mr. Colby, did you attend

365
00:20:49,860 --> 00:20:53,090
董事會你出席了嗎?
the executive board meetings during 1993?

366
00:20:57,220 --> 00:21:00,070
會上決定 對華盛頓鎮有毒廢料的處理方案
Were you in the room when the decision was made

367
00:21:00,090 --> 00:21:02,230
不給予任何處理 當時
to ignore the treatment of hazardous waste

368
00:21:02,250 --> 00:21:03,700
你在場嗎?
in Washington Township?

369
00:21:10,980 --> 00:21:13,040
我有一些對你有利的信息 回答我的問題
I have information which can help you...

370
00:21:13,710 --> 00:21:15,010
我可以告訴你
if you answer my question.

371
00:21:18,620 --> 00:21:19,850
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.

372
00:21:22,810 --> 00:21:25,650
針對你的指控有問題 作為證據的數據鏈有漏洞
If you agree to testify against the executives

373
00:21:25,670 --> 00:21:28,720
如果你肯作證 指認與會的高管們
who covered up the illegal dumping of expoxy resin waste,

374
00:21:30,120 --> 00:21:32,200
試圖掩蓋非法傾倒環氧樹脂廢物這一事實
I will testify that I broke chain of custody

375
00:21:32,220 --> 00:21:34,710
我就可以幫你洗刷罪名
with the dat file central to your case.

376
00:21:41,280 --> 00:21:42,310
你不是那個一個月前
You're that hot little thing

377
00:21:42,330 --> 00:21:44,050
來過的小辣妹嗎
that came by here a month ago.

378
00:21:44,430 --> 00:21:45,790
那個萬安公司的姑娘
The girl from Allsafe.

379
00:21:50,550 --> 00:21:53,020
我記起來了
I remember, yeah.

380
00:21:57,740 --> 00:22:01,370
好吧 讓我來回答你的問題
Okay...I'm gonna answer your question.

381
00:22:03,270 --> 00:22:05,000
但首先 我要你做一件事
But here's what I need from you first.

382
00:22:06,620 --> 00:22:08,210
我把褲子脫下來
So I'm gonna pull down my pants,

383
00:22:09,500 --> 00:22:12,480
你把你那撅起來的小嘴湊過來
and then I'm gonna need you to take that pouty mouth of yours

384
00:22:12,630 --> 00:22:14,380
吞下我的蛋蛋
and swallow up my balls.

385
00:22:14,880 --> 00:22:18,260
它們又大 毛又多 尤其是左邊那顆
Now, they're big and hairy, especially the left one,

386
00:22:18,280 --> 00:22:20,500
但你還是得想辦法
so you're really gonna have to, I don't know,

387
00:22:20,520 --> 00:22:23,270
把它們吞下去
squish 'em up to get 'em inside there.

388
00:22:23,860 --> 00:22:26,320
就算是一個腮幫子塞一個也得咽
You're probably gonna have to do one cheek at a time.

389
00:22:26,660 --> 00:22:31,290
等它們在你嘴里含的又暖又舒服了
But then, once they're all warm and snug in there,

390
00:22:31,590 --> 00:22:34,290
你再把你的問題 清清楚楚得和我
I want you to repeat your question to me

391
00:22:34,860 --> 00:22:36,470
復述一遍
as clearly as you can.

392
00:22:38,030 --> 00:22:40,710
我馬上從實招來
Then, and only then, am I willing to answer.

393
00:22:46,340 --> 00:22:47,290
你看如何
What do you say?

394
00:23:07,100 --> 00:23:08,800
如果你不和我合作
If you don't take this deal...

395
00:23:11,140 --> 00:23:12,500
你也會變得和我一樣
you'll become like me.

396
00:23:14,920 --> 00:23:17,750
當然 你還是有大房子住
Sure, maybe you'll live in this house...

397
00:23:19,560 --> 00:23:20,870
腰包也大概也沒憋多少
Maybe you'll have money,

398
00:23:22,380 --> 00:23:26,870
但就算你花重金請的律師能幫你逃脫罪名
but even if your expensive lawyers find a way to get you off,

399
00:23:26,890 --> 00:23:28,440
群眾的眼睛還是雪亮的
people will still think that you're guilty.

400
00:23:35,400 --> 00:23:38,120
沒人會再尊重你
Losing everyone's respect...

401
00:23:43,310 --> 00:23:47,590
包括你認識和不認識的
the respect of people you know and the people you don't...

402
00:23:52,330 --> 00:23:53,880
這感覺很糟糕
It's a shitty feeling.

403
00:23:57,060 --> 00:23:58,070
相信我
Trust me.

404
00:24:13,400 --> 00:24:15,590
有那姑娘在 不用送了
I'll have "the girl" let me out.

405
00:24:24,000 --> 00:24:26,880
鰭鰭 她身上帶微芯片嗎?
Flipper. Is she microchipped?

406
00:24:34,500 --> 00:24:36,900
好的 很好
Okay, very good.

407
00:24:38,350 --> 00:24:39,480
例行檢查做完了
Housekeeping done.

408
00:24:39,720 --> 00:24:41,200
現在切入正題
Now onto the real business.

409
00:24:42,980 --> 00:24:44,760
你的狗以前吃過垃圾嗎？
Has your dog ever eaten trash before?

410
00:24:45,110 --> 00:24:48,950
沒有 至少我不記得她有過
No. I mean, not that I remember.

411
00:24:49,130 --> 00:24:50,750
為你的銀行賬號感到慶幸的是
Well, lucky for your bank account,

412
00:24:50,770 --> 00:24:53,420
她吃下去的東西不大 能自己排泄出來
The piece is small enough to pass on its own.

413
00:24:53,520 --> 00:24:55,250
但是 說小也不小
Unfortunately, though, it's large enough

414
00:24:55,270 --> 00:24:57,350
能讓她在你的公寓里到處嘔吐
to send her puking all over your apartment.

415
00:24:57,560 --> 00:25:01,040
我要把她留在這兒 觀察幾天
So I would crate her for a few days and monitor her.

416
00:25:01,440 --> 00:25:03,710
就算你對她出于好心 她反正是不會知道的
She won't know what you're doing is good for her.

417
00:25:19,400 --> 00:25:22,030
你說得對 我只不過是想證明...
You were right. I was only trying to prove--

418
00:25:22,050 --> 00:25:24,440
科爾比的律師剛才打來電話了 他同意開口了
Colby's lawyers just called. He wants to talk.

419
00:25:25,910 --> 00:25:26,990
再去趟他家
Get back there.

420
00:25:39,180 --> 00:25:41,620
一大清早就出來發癡可不好
It's a little early in the morning to be nerding out,

421
00:25:41,880 --> 00:25:42,930
你不覺得嗎
don't you think?

422
00:25:44,820 --> 00:25:45,840
多久了
How long?

423
00:25:53,040 --> 00:25:53,970
我知道如果我問你...
I knew if I asked you that--

424
00:25:53,990 --> 00:25:55,040
多久了
How long?

425
00:25:57,510 --> 00:25:58,650
幾個禮拜
Couple weeks.

426
00:26:01,670 --> 00:26:04,680
你膽子還真大 用我作突破口去和WhiteRose聯系?
And you had the balls to ask for WhiteRose with my shit?

427
00:26:05,240 --> 00:26:07,090
你想我們兩個都被做掉嗎
It's like you want to get us both killed.

428
00:26:08,240 --> 00:26:09,680
怎么了 他回復了?
What happened? He responded?

429
00:26:12,820 --> 00:26:13,910
你看
You know,

430
00:26:15,260 --> 00:26:17,880
你真不該弄得我在他們面前抬不起頭
you didn't have to make me look like a shitty foot soldier.

431
00:26:18,190 --> 00:26:19,350
沒人會問的...
Nobody would ever even know--

432
00:26:19,370 --> 00:26:21,560
你入侵我的電腦 找到了我們的IP地址
You got root on my box and found the IP,

433
00:26:21,580 --> 00:26:24,600
然后通過我的資源加入他們的討論組
then you joined their channel with my handle.

434
00:26:30,670 --> 00:26:31,830
我們情分已盡
We're so done.

435
00:26:34,390 --> 00:26:35,640
我再也不想看到你了
I don't want to see you again.

436
00:26:42,730 --> 00:26:44,690
不過你們這幫傻瓜心想事成了
But you fools actually got your wish.

437
00:26:46,830 --> 00:26:47,320
不知為何
I don't know why,

438
00:26:47,340 --> 00:26:48,990
但是你們要的這次會面他居然同意了
but the meeting's actually gonna be on.

439
00:26:49,780 --> 00:26:50,880
我想告訴你 小心點
I'd tell you to be careful,

440
00:26:50,900 --> 00:26:53,620
但我知道你不可能聽得進去
but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.

441
00:27:09,900 --> 00:27:11,720
我的律師們正在看你帶來的文件
My lawyers are looking over the paperwork.

442
00:27:14,900 --> 00:27:17,270
- 你的意思是  - 就像我說過的
- Does that mean that-- - exactly what I said.

443
00:27:18,550 --> 00:27:21,670
我叫你回來是為了確保你確實能在法庭上幫到我
I asked you back here to make sure that you can pull off your testimony,

444
00:27:21,690 --> 00:27:24,840
并檢驗你說的那個監管問題的消息確實屬實
make sure that this chain of custody, story of yours is straight.

445
00:27:24,860 --> 00:27:26,230
我可不想被你陰到
I can't afford any trips.

446
00:27:28,110 --> 00:27:29,620
我不會陰你的
I'm not going to trip.

447
00:27:33,780 --> 00:27:34,880
這事
So, what--

448
00:27:35,950 --> 00:27:37,410
到底對你有什么好處?
What's in this for you, anyway?

449
00:27:37,860 --> 00:27:39,440
我知道你恨我
I know you hate me.

450
00:27:40,830 --> 00:27:43,240
現在你卻打算幫我逃脫懲罰?
So, what, you're gonna just let me off scot-free?

451
00:27:43,280 --> 00:27:44,310
你能得到什么回報?
What do you get out of this?

452
00:27:47,570 --> 00:27:49,570
之前我問了你一個問題
Earlier, I asked you a question.

453
00:27:51,080 --> 00:27:52,320
你沒回答
You never answered it.

454
00:27:54,270 --> 00:27:58,140
既然我同意幫你作證 那么
If I'm agreeing to testify in your case, then,

455
00:27:59,120 --> 00:28:02,240
是的 我確實去過幾次會議
yes, you know, I attended several meetings.

456
00:28:02,270 --> 00:28:05,280
和我講講他們決定忽略泄露的那次會議吧
Tell me about the one when they decided to ignore the leak.

457
00:28:07,410 --> 00:28:09,250
我--我不確定你想問什么
I'm--I'm not sure what you're asking.

458
00:28:09,270 --> 00:28:13,140
你們在決定的時候 是幅什么場景?
What was the meeting like when you decided this?

459
00:28:15,820 --> 00:28:16,870
我懂了
I get it.

460
00:28:18,290 --> 00:28:21,020
你想知道 當時是怎么樣的場景?
You want to know, like, what was it like?

461
00:28:21,290 --> 00:28:25,300
比如 我們是不是都一邊抽著雪茄 一邊瘋笑著
Like, um, did we all have cigars and laugh hysterically

462
00:28:25,320 --> 00:28:27,240
簽了那個邪惡的文件?
as we signed the evil documents?

463
00:28:27,620 --> 00:28:28,810
你腦海里是這個畫面么?
Is that what you pictured?

464
00:28:29,390 --> 00:28:30,470
那抱歉你想錯了 甜心
Well, I'm sorry, hon.

465
00:28:30,490 --> 00:28:32,490
要知道 這世界不是你想的那樣
See, the world doesn't work like that.

466
00:28:33,310 --> 00:28:37,110
那你告訴我 告訴我是怎么樣的
Tell me. Tell me how it works.

467
00:28:40,770 --> 00:28:44,360
哦 天啊... 好吧 好吧
Uh, Jesus, um...All right, all right.

468
00:28:44,380 --> 00:28:48,490
我想想 93年的一月
Let's see. January, '93.

469
00:28:49,400 --> 00:28:51,710
那時我的秘書是伊萊恩
Well, my secretary then was Elaine.

470
00:28:52,090 --> 00:28:54,480
那時伊萊恩在晚餐上給我們點了
So Elaine brought us a platter of shrimp cocktail

471
00:28:54,500 --> 00:28:57,920
一盤雞尾酒蝦 這把我們氣壞了
to tide us to dinner, which pissed us off

472
00:28:58,720 --> 00:29:00,980
因為我們剛剛在節日趴上吃了這玩意兒
because we just had a platter at the holiday party.

473
00:29:02,180 --> 00:29:03,430
吉姆讓我們開懷暢飲
Jim opened the bar.

474
00:29:03,460 --> 00:29:05,870
他現在可真是個人才
Now Jim was a real piece of work.

475
00:29:06,180 --> 00:29:08,540
我是說 他有時娘炮有時屌
I mean, half pansy, half Mafia.

476
00:29:08,660 --> 00:29:11,520
一旦遇到艱難抉擇的時刻 他就各種抽煙
First sign of a tight decision, he'd be chain smoking

477
00:29:11,940 --> 00:29:13,380
各種喝酒
down a river of Scotch.

478
00:29:18,200 --> 00:29:19,620
而且 那天還下雨了
You know, it rained.

479
00:29:19,790 --> 00:29:21,410
那天下雨了 我記得的 對
It rained. I remember that, yeah.

480
00:29:26,890 --> 00:29:28,230
那么...
So...

481
00:29:29,270 --> 00:29:33,320
你們喝得爛醉 吃著雞尾蝦
You were drunk, eating shrimp cockail,

482
00:29:34,900 --> 00:29:37,810
然后當時還下著雨 你們就決定讓我媽去死了么?
and it was raining when you decided my mother would die?

483
00:29:46,650 --> 00:29:47,870
看來就是了
That's why.

484
00:29:49,860 --> 00:29:52,820
所以像你這樣的人就不會總是在高處掌權
So people like you won't keep sitting in rooms together.

485
00:30:01,270 --> 00:30:04,370
你們在做這些個決定的時候
Did any of it ever give you or anyone pause

486
00:30:05,940 --> 00:30:07,640
有過一點點的遲疑嗎?
when you made those decisions?

487
00:30:11,290 --> 00:30:11,930
有
Yeah.

488
00:30:14,480 --> 00:30:16,570
有 當然有
Yeah, sure.

489
00:30:19,680 --> 00:30:20,800
但是...
But, um...

490
00:30:23,790 --> 00:30:27,530
之后就各回各家了 然后呢 吃個飯
then you go home, and, uh, and you have dinner,

491
00:30:28,270 --> 00:30:31,640
對吧 然后--然后第二天早上還是照樣醒來
you know, and--and you wake up the next morning.

492
00:30:40,610 --> 00:30:43,980
我們敬這個有著光明前途的同事一杯
Here's to a man who has a bright future at our company,

493
00:30:44,180 --> 00:30:45,350
一個你們都認識的人
a man you all know,

494
00:30:46,530 --> 00:30:50,210
一個能帶我們公司走向成功的人
a man who is going to change this company for the good,

495
00:30:51,330 --> 00:30:55,400
一個能與一位和他同樣聰明的女人結婚的人...
a man smart enough to marry a woman every bit his equal...

496
00:30:56,870 --> 00:31:01,640
我們的新任首席技術官 斯考特 諾斯
Our new Chief Technology Officer, Scott Knowles.

497
00:31:01,790 --> 00:31:03,000
沒錯 沒錯!
Here, here!

498
00:31:03,600 --> 00:31:05,260
謝謝 謝謝
Thank you. Thank you.

499
00:31:05,280 --> 00:31:06,830
- 謝謝 菲利普 - 不客氣
- Thank you, Phillip. - Welcome.

500
00:31:06,850 --> 00:31:08,000
- 非常感謝 - 開始了
- Thank you very much. - Here we go.

501
00:31:08,020 --> 00:31:09,800
很高興能在這里 這里沒事了
It's great to be here. And we're off.

502
00:31:09,970 --> 00:31:11,530
- 謝謝 菲利普 - 小事小事
- Thanks, Phillip. - You're very welcome.

503
00:31:11,550 --> 00:31:13,160
- 恭喜啊 親愛的 - 謝謝 謝謝
- Congratulations, darling. - Thank you, thank you.

504
00:31:16,720 --> 00:31:18,660
嘿 喬 你好嗎?
Hey, Joe, how are you?

505
00:31:39,350 --> 00:31:39,990
謝謝
Thank you.

506
00:31:46,900 --> 00:31:49,130
提瑞爾 很高興見到你
Tyrell, nice to see you.

507
00:31:49,230 --> 00:31:50,020
是嗎?
Is it?

508
00:31:50,480 --> 00:31:52,640
我聽說你跟你丈夫說了我們的事
I hear you shared our moment with your husband.

509
00:31:54,100 --> 00:31:56,060
哦 拜托 都過去一個月了
Oh, come on. That was over a month ago.

510
00:31:56,200 --> 00:31:57,660
別告訴我你現在腰還酸著呢
Don't tell me you're still sore.

511
00:31:59,180 --> 00:32:01,270
誒 我看出了一縷憂傷
Hmm, I sense some defeat.

512
00:32:09,560 --> 00:32:13,280
其實 至少 我覺得我自己受到了譴責
Well, I considered myself, at the very least, reprimanded.

513
00:32:14,590 --> 00:32:15,760
真叫人失望
How disappointing.

514
00:32:16,240 --> 00:32:18,040
一點兒小挫折你就放棄了
One tiny curveball and you gave up.

515
00:32:18,790 --> 00:32:19,490
女士
Miss.

516
00:32:19,940 --> 00:32:20,670
謝謝
Thank you.

517
00:32:22,320 --> 00:32:25,580
早就該知道你虎頭蛇尾
Should have known that you were nothing more than a bold entrance.

518
00:32:26,580 --> 00:32:28,930
你是說 你一點兒都不渴望那種"虎頭"的感覺嗎
Are you saying you don't crave a bold entrance

519
00:32:28,950 --> 00:32:32,490
一次又一次 堅持不懈么?
every time, over and over, sustained?

520
00:32:33,360 --> 00:32:34,370
晚上見一面吧
Meet me tonight.

521
00:32:35,450 --> 00:32:36,540
我有點忙啊
I'm a little busy.

522
00:32:37,160 --> 00:32:38,520
現在就去我的辦公室
Come to my office now.

523
00:32:38,540 --> 00:32:40,140
你說真的么?
Are you really asking me that?

524
00:32:40,160 --> 00:32:42,410
我可不是在問你 是在命令你
I don't recall phrasing it as a question, no.

525
00:32:43,520 --> 00:32:45,630
行啊 那我就不出現就好了
Fine, then I just won't show up.

526
00:32:46,530 --> 00:32:47,640
那就去房頂
Then the roof.

527
00:32:48,630 --> 00:32:50,040
從后邊的樓梯上去
Take the back stairwell.

528
00:32:51,040 --> 00:32:52,870
那里的監控三月份就壞了
The cameras have been out since March.

529
00:32:53,230 --> 00:32:54,290
沒人會知道的
No one will know.

530
00:33:01,470 --> 00:33:02,960
你把復雜的事弄得更復雜了
Well, you just made a long day longer.

531
00:33:02,990 --> 00:33:04,710
我知道萬安公司很快就得把我開除了
I know that Allsafe will have to fire me,

532
00:33:04,740 --> 00:33:06,590
但是出庭作證是個正確的選擇
but testifying was the right thing to do.

533
00:33:06,610 --> 00:33:09,190
老子花了很大的力氣來照顧你
I have worked my ass off to take care of you

534
00:33:09,480 --> 00:33:11,070
也照顧這個公司每一個人
and of every person in this company.

535
00:33:11,090 --> 00:33:13,230
你知道這意味著什么嗎?
Do you know what that means?

536
00:33:13,250 --> 00:33:15,290
你一直是個很棒的老板 吉迪恩--
You've been a great boss, Gideon--

537
00:33:15,610 --> 00:33:18,320
你看 一旦這份供詞被公布
See, once this confession goes public,

538
00:33:18,340 --> 00:33:20,250
就不會有人想和我們合作了
no one will want to do business with us.

539
00:33:20,270 --> 00:33:21,910
公司就垮了
The company will go under.

540
00:33:21,930 --> 00:33:23,880
我不能讓科爾比
I couldn't let Colby take the fall

541
00:33:23,900 --> 00:33:24,810
- 為我的過失埋單 - 哦拜托!
- for something that I did. - Oh, come on!

542
00:33:24,830 --> 00:33:26,710
你我都知道 你沒有在監管上做錯什么
You and I both know you didn't break chain of custody.

543
00:33:26,730 --> 00:33:28,780
我有做錯 而且我感覺很糟糕--
I did and I feel terrible--

544
00:33:28,800 --> 00:33:32,630
安吉拉! 求你了! 別撒謊了
Angela! Please! Stop lying.

545
00:33:36,460 --> 00:33:40,970
你要是這么做... 這里所有的人就都完了
You do this... All these people go down,

546
00:33:42,020 --> 00:33:43,170
他們的家庭
all their families

547
00:33:44,200 --> 00:33:46,810
他們需要這個公司所帶給他們的一切
that rely on what this company provides for them.

548
00:34:10,160 --> 00:34:12,130
啊 原來那條小樓梯能通到這兒啊?
So this is where the rabbit hole leads?

549
00:34:14,740 --> 00:34:15,380
說真的
Got to be honest,

550
00:34:15,410 --> 00:34:17,410
我覺得你出現的可能性也就一半
I half-expected you not to show up.

551
00:34:18,770 --> 00:34:21,320
我還覺得你有一半兒可能去打小報告呢
And I half-expected you to be a tattletale.

552
00:34:22,600 --> 00:34:24,190
看來你是累了
So you are sore.

553
00:34:24,300 --> 00:34:26,990
哦 不是吧 你迷住我了
Oh, come on. You intrigued me.

554
00:34:27,010 --> 00:34:28,820
我也得迷回來
I intrigued back.

555
00:34:29,520 --> 00:34:31,620
咱們就不能直接一點嗎?
Can't we just be more straightforward?

556
00:34:31,650 --> 00:34:34,600
哦 那可不好玩啊 但既然你堅持的話
Oh, that's no fun, but if you insist,

557
00:34:35,870 --> 00:34:37,600
我只是上樓看看看你是不是真的
I just came up here to see if you were really

558
00:34:37,620 --> 00:34:39,240
像看上去那樣容易上當
as gullible as you seem.

559
00:34:40,610 --> 00:34:42,930
我丈夫在樓下爭取著你要的那個位置
My husband's downstairs getting the job that you want,

560
00:34:42,950 --> 00:34:44,970
而你卻在想方設法勾引我
and you're up here trying to fuck me.

561
00:34:44,990 --> 00:34:48,700
不管你這么做是純粹出于欲望還是在釣我上鉤
Now whether that's you being straightforward or a game,

562
00:34:49,320 --> 00:34:51,820
你都沒能提起我的興趣
either way, it's played pretty poorly, if you ask me.

563
00:34:52,610 --> 00:34:54,590
我有問過你什么問題嗎
Again, I asked no question.

564
00:34:55,090 --> 00:34:57,410
我這么做是因為我看出來
All I can tell you is you need this

565
00:34:57,480 --> 00:34:59,080
你欲求不滿 想滿足你
'cause you're dissatisfied.

566
00:35:00,260 --> 00:35:02,350
斯考特要解雇你
Scott plans on firing you,

567
00:35:02,370 --> 00:35:05,530
你現在已經走投無路 狗急跳墻了
and you are clinging on t了o any chance you can get.

568
00:35:06,390 --> 00:35:07,700
你看上去真絕望
You seem desperate.

569
00:35:59,390 --> 00:36:01,180
你干什么 放開我
What do you-- get off of me!

570
00:36:01,780 --> 00:36:03,000
停下
Stop!

571
00:38:02,330 --> 00:38:04,210
我們和WhiteRose接過頭了
We connected with WhiteRose.

572
00:38:04,490 --> 00:38:05,760
計劃又重回正軌
The plan is back on.

573
00:38:08,740 --> 00:38:13,210
我可以哄你 說你是F社會的核心人物
I could bullshit you, tell you you're the only person

574
00:38:13,230 --> 00:38:16,360
缺你不行 沒人能取代你在團隊里的位置
who can fill the exact void we have at fsociety.

575
00:38:17,800 --> 00:38:19,950
但事實是 我需要這支團隊的每一個人都回來
The truth is, I need this group back together.

576
00:38:25,410 --> 00:38:28,310
你有沒有想過 我們的計劃哪一部分最吸引你
Have you ever considered which part of our scheme motivates you?

577
00:38:29,540 --> 00:38:30,860
當黑暗軍團發力
When the Dark Army bailed,

578
00:38:30,940 --> 00:38:32,170
按下一個鍵就能引發一場經濟革命
you didn't care if pushing a button

579
00:38:32,190 --> 00:38:34,100
這些你都不感興趣
would bring an economic revolution.

580
00:38:34,630 --> 00:38:36,460
你要的是瞬間的無政府狀態
You want momentary anarchy.

581
00:38:37,940 --> 00:38:38,810
其他人呢
The others?

582
00:38:39,370 --> 00:38:41,130
莫布里享受大家并肩作戰的感覺
Mobley likes palling around.

583
00:38:41,490 --> 00:38:43,420
羅梅羅一心想要出名
Romero wants a whiff of fame.

584
00:38:44,040 --> 00:38:45,740
他們的理由讓我厭倦
Those reasons depress me.

585
00:38:50,620 --> 00:38:54,020
- 那你是出于什么目的?  - 你不會不關心的
- What's the part you want? - You don't care.

586
00:39:02,040 --> 00:39:03,640
我父母出生于伊朗
My parents were born in Iran.

587
00:39:04,630 --> 00:39:06,390
他們像所有人那樣向往自由
They came here like everybody else,

588
00:39:06,410 --> 00:39:07,300
而來到這里
for freedom,

589
00:39:07,330 --> 00:39:09,770
我父親每周工作60小時
but my dad works 60-hour weeks

590
00:39:09,790 --> 00:39:13,200
絞盡腦汁幫一個身家百萬的藝術品經紀人設法逃稅
to determine tax loopholes for a millionaire art dealer.

591
00:39:13,830 --> 00:39:16,650
我母親 為了一個網絡大學的文憑
My mom, she ran up loans into five digits

592
00:39:16,670 --> 00:39:18,190
欠下了5位數的債
to get an online degree.

593
00:39:19,110 --> 00:39:21,180
縱然如此 他們任然稱頌美國的偉大
They won't shut up about how great America is.

594
00:39:23,310 --> 00:39:25,190
他們就將這樣 欠下一屁股債
But they're gonna die in debt

595
00:39:25,420 --> 00:39:27,350
干不想干的活 了卻此生
doing things they never wanted to do.

596
00:39:35,180 --> 00:39:38,010
這個世界上有多少人?
There are how many billion people in this world?

597
00:39:39,230 --> 00:39:40,420
73億
7.3.

598
00:39:40,960 --> 00:39:43,900
命運讓我們走到一起
Somehow you and I landed together...

599
00:39:44,690 --> 00:39:47,360
在這個特定的歷史時刻 擁有特定的條件
Doing something impossible if we were alone,

600
00:39:47,840 --> 00:39:51,390
去完成我們靠單打獨斗無法完成的壯舉
not to mention at the right point in history with the right resources.

601
00:39:52,100 --> 00:39:55,530
我們付出那么多努力 眼看就要有所回報
We have what we've worked for right there for the taking.

602
00:39:56,600 --> 00:39:58,890
我們現在只需再度攜手 就能完成它
We just need each other to see this through.

603
00:40:14,120 --> 00:40:15,870
你再靠近 我就叫警察了
You come any closer, I'm calling the cops.

604
00:40:21,910 --> 00:40:25,580
嗨 接線員 我要報警
Hi, operator. I'd like to report an emergency.

605
00:40:25,950 --> 00:40:28,490
我在家里的電腦里插入了含有惡意軟件的CD
I placed a malicious cd in my work computer,

606
00:40:28,520 --> 00:40:31,040
現在這個給我CD的家伙就站在我面前
and now this guy at the gym is saying hi to me.

607
00:40:32,350 --> 00:40:33,140
我要回家了
I'm going home.

608
00:40:33,160 --> 00:40:34,640
我要你為我做件事
I need you to do something for me.

609
00:40:34,660 --> 00:40:37,220
叫那些愿意來的女生 好嗎?
Call the girl who wants to be involved, okay?

610
00:40:37,240 --> 00:40:38,580
她叫安吉拉 莫斯
Her name is Angela Moss.

611
00:40:38,600 --> 00:40:39,350
我給你她的電話吧
Let me give you her phone number.

612
00:40:39,370 --> 00:40:41,820
聽著軟蛋 如果你不按我說的做
Listen, pussy. If you don't do what I say,

613
00:40:41,850 --> 00:40:44,510
那我就會讓米田共
then the giant shit storm that rains turds later

614
00:40:44,530 --> 00:40:48,100
在空中劃過一道云彩 寫著你的芳名
will leave a trail of clouds in the sky spelling out your name.

615
00:40:56,990 --> 00:41:00,860
伊利艾特? 你怎么來了?
Elliot? I wasn't expecting you.

616
00:41:02,070 --> 00:41:03,670
我來赴約看病
I'm here for my appointment.

617
00:41:06,490 --> 00:41:08,860
好吧　你可以在我的第一個病人來之前先看
Well, you can slip in before my first patient.

618
00:41:29,290 --> 00:41:31,160
你說我得告訴你實情
You told me I should tell you the truth.

619
00:41:32,560 --> 00:41:33,270
是的
Yes.

620
00:41:35,610 --> 00:41:40,300
我所說的話 你會保密嗎?
Everything I say will still be protected and confidential?

621
00:41:46,520 --> 00:41:47,790
我之前在說謊
I've been lying to you.

622
00:41:50,990 --> 00:41:52,380
我沒按時吃藥
I don't take my pills.

623
00:41:53,600 --> 00:41:54,620
你也沒有
But you don't either.

624
00:41:56,900 --> 00:41:59,040
你對安定的購買次數與
Your refill frequency for ativan doesn't match

625
00:41:59,060 --> 00:42:01,120
你開藥量除以劑量不符
your prescription divided by the dosage.

626
00:42:06,450 --> 00:42:07,430
今天早上...
This morning...

627
00:42:10,060 --> 00:42:12,460
你買了中杯的榛子拿鐵
You bought a tall hazelnut latte.

628
00:42:12,920 --> 00:42:14,980
用你的邪惡公司的卡付賬
Paid for it on your evil corp card.

629
00:42:15,870 --> 00:42:18,490
你給你妹妹的錢多了
By text, you justified the indulgence to your sister

630
00:42:18,510 --> 00:42:21,040
因為邪惡公司給你的獎勵翻倍了
because evil corp gives you double rewards.

631
00:42:21,130 --> 00:42:24,230
可你不知道這些獎勵只能用在差旅費上
But those points only accumulate on travel expenses.

632
00:42:24,700 --> 00:42:25,910
你對錢不是很敏感啊
You're not good with money.

633
00:42:27,410 --> 00:42:31,710
在紙上 周四下午兩點來的那個瑪里琳 奧布賴恩
On paper, your Thursday 2:00, Marilyn O'Brien,

634
00:42:31,820 --> 00:42:33,290
和你有著很相近的經歷
is your doppelganger.

635
00:42:34,410 --> 00:42:37,810
我覺得你是在鼓勵她
I think you're encouraging her

636
00:42:37,830 --> 00:42:39,140
離開她的丈夫...
to leave her husband...

637
00:42:41,940 --> 00:42:44,040
因為你知道被甩的滋味
Because you're tired of being dumped.

638
00:42:47,920 --> 00:42:49,810
你喜歡情色 尤其是走后門的
You like porn, especially anal.

639
00:42:49,830 --> 00:42:51,070
不知道是不是你自己喜歡這樣
Whether you like it yourself, I don't know.

640
00:42:51,090 --> 00:42:53,000
和我沒關系
That's not relevant to me.

641
00:42:53,880 --> 00:42:55,720
你告訴你最好的朋友詹尼弗
You've told your best friend Jennifer

642
00:42:55,750 --> 00:42:58,780
說你希望你媽媽早點死
that you wish your mom would die.

643
00:43:01,830 --> 00:43:03,950
有時候我會通過你的攝像頭看你
I sometimes watch you on your webcam.

644
00:43:05,290 --> 00:43:06,790
有時候你會哭...
You cry sometimes...

645
00:43:09,500 --> 00:43:10,610
和我一樣
Just like me.

646
00:43:13,760 --> 00:43:15,500
因為你很孤單
Because you're lonely.

647
00:43:22,480 --> 00:43:24,250
我不只是黑你的電腦 克里斯塔
I don't just hack you, Krista.

648
00:43:24,270 --> 00:43:25,560
我黑所有人的
I hack everyone--

649
00:43:27,240 --> 00:43:30,010
我的朋友 同事
My friends, coworkers.

650
00:43:35,650 --> 00:43:37,420
但是我已經幫助了很多人了
But I've helped a lot of people.

651
00:43:44,470 --> 00:43:45,250
我想要...
I want...

652
00:43:48,470 --> 00:43:50,700
一個能走出孤單的方法...
A way out of loneliness...

653
00:43:53,420 --> 00:43:54,630
就像你一樣
Just like you.

654
00:44:07,410 --> 00:44:09,330
這是你想要聽到的嗎?
Is that what you wanted to hear?

655
00:44:13,000 --> 00:44:23,000
本字幕由大家字幕組原創翻譯
僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
彼以國士待我 我以國士待之
用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人
有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們
請聯系：dajiazimuzu@163.com

