[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.8,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 机器人先生,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 机器人先生1,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 前情提要,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效标记,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.5,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 集数,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00C6CDC2,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,3,0,0.1,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 微信,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 标题,汉仪双线体简,40,&H001C1DB6,&H0021218D,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,14,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(377.2,287.467)\c&H240F9F&\i1\b0}9
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.00,0:00:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(150,500)\fscx113\fscy145\c&H000000&\move(39.471,236.557,32.2,245.8,0,2000)}m 0 20 l 39 20 l 39 59 l 0 59
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.00,0:00:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(150,500)\\fscx113\fscy145\move(22.1,258.914,29.829,249,0,2000)}m 0 20 l 39 20 l 39 59 l 0 59
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.12,0:00:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(1000,500)\\fscx113\fscy145\c&H000000&\\move(40.5,237.943,30.99,248.8,0,2000)}m 32 26 l 32 26 l 32 28 l 31 28 l 31 27 l 30 27 l 30 28 l 29 28 l 29 29 l 28 29 l 28 30 l 27 30 l 27 31 l 26 31 l 26 32 l 28 32 l 28 31 l 30 31 l 30 32 l 28 32 l 28 33 l 27 33 l 27 35 l 26 35 l 26 36 l 25 36 l 25 35 l 24 35 l 24 32 l 22 32 l 22 31 l 23 31 l 23 30 l 22 30 l 22 29 l 24 29 l 24 30 l 26 30 l 26 29 l 24 29 l 24 27 l 23 27 l 23 28 l 22 28 l 22 29 l 21 29 l 21 30 l 19 30 l 19 31 l 20 31 l 20 32 l 19 32 l 19 31 l 18 31 l 18 32 l 17 32 l 17 31 l 18 31 l 18 30 l 17 30 l 17 29 l 19 29 l 19 28 l 19 28 l 20 28 l 20 29 l 21 29 l 21 28 l 20 28 l 20 27 l 22 27 l 22 26 l 27 26 l 27 27 l 25 27 l 25 28 l 28 28 l 28 24 l 27 24 l 27 25 l 26 25 l 26 24 l 27 24 l 27 23 l 28 23 l 28 22 l 27 22 l 27 21 l 29 21 l 29 26 l 32 26 m 16 28 l 17 28 l 17 27 l 16 27 l 16 28 m 17 25 l 16 25 l 16 24 l 17 24 l 17 25 m 18 28 l 18 26 l 19 26 l 19 25 l 20 25 l 20 24 l 19 24 l 19 25 l 18 25 l 18 24 l 19 24 l 19 23 l 20 23 l 20 21 l 21 21 l 21 20 l 22 20 l 22 23 l 20 23 l 20 24 l 21 24 l 21 26 l 20 26 l 20 27 l 19 27 l 19 28 l 18 28 m 23 25 l 22 25 l 22 24 l 23 24 l 23 25 m 24 25 l 24 23 l 23 23 l 23 20 l 24 20 l 24 21 l 26 21 l 26 23 l 25 23 l 25 25 m 0 27 l 0 29 l 1 29 l 1 28 l 2 28 l 2 29 l 3 29 l 3 32 l 2 32 l 2 33 l 1 33 l 1 32 l 0 32 l 0 33 l 1 33 l 1 34 l 2 34 l 2 36 l 1 36 l 1 35 l 0 35 l 0 37 l 2 37 l 2 38 l 5 38 l 5 39 l 7 39 l 7 38 l 6 38 l 6 37 l 8 37 l 8 36 l 9 36 l 9 35 l 10 35 l 10 36 l 11 36 l 11 35 l 10 35 l 10 33 l 9 33 l 9 35 l 8 35 l 8 33 l 9 33 l 9 32 l 6 32 l 6 31 l 5 31 l 5 30 l 6 30 l 6 31 l 8 31 l 8 30 l 6 30 l 6 29 l 8 29 l 8 27 l 7 27 l 7 28 l 6 28 l 6 29 l 4 29 l 4 27 l 5 27 l 5 28 l 6 28 l 6 27 l 7 27 l 7 26 l 6 26 l 6 27 l 5 27 l 5 26 l 2 26 l 2 27 l 3 27 l 3 28 l 2 28 l 2 27 l 1 27 m 0 30 l 2 30 l 2 31 l 0 31 m 9 30 l 10 30 l 10 31 l 9 31 l 9 30 m 21 31 l 22 31 l 22 30 l 21 30 l 21 31 m 37 26 l 34 26 l 34 27 l 33 27 l 33 28 l 32 28 l 32 29 l 31 29 l 31 28 l 30 28 l 30 31 l 31 31 l 31 32 l 30 32 l 30 33 l 29 33 l 29 35 l 28 35 l 28 36 l 26 36 l 26 39 l 25 39 l 25 40 l 24 40 l 24 38 l 23 38 l 23 40 l 24 40 l 24 42 l 22 42 l 22 41 l 19 41 l 19 42 l 20 42 l 20 43 l 21 43 l 21 44 l 19 44 l 19 45 l 22 45 l 22 43 l 25 43 l 25 40 l 26 40 l 26 43 l 27 43 l 27 41 l 28 41 l 28 43 l 30 43 l 30 44 l 32 44 l 32 45 l 33 45 l 33 44 l 34 44 l 34 43 l 35 43 l 35 42 l 33 42 l 33 44 l 32 44 l 32 43 l 32 41 l 31 41 l 31 42 l 30 42 l 30 41 l 29 41 l 29 40 l 26 40 l 26 39 l 27 39 l 27 37 l 28 37 l 28 38 l 29 38 l 29 40 l 30 40 l 30 41 l 31 41 l 31 40 l 32 40 l 32 39 l 34 39 l 34 40 l 34 41 l 36 41 l 36 43 l 37 43 l 37 42 l 37 39 l 36 39 l 36 40 l 35 40 l 35 38 l 36 38 l 36 37 l 37 37 l 37 36 l 35 36 l 35 34 l 34 34 l 34 35 l 33 35 l 33 36 l 35 36 l 35 38 l 33 38 l 33 36 l 32 36 l 32 37 l 30 37 l 30 38 l 29 38 l 29 37 l 28 37 l 28 36 l 30 36 l 30 35 l 31 35 l 31 36 l 32 36 l 32 35 l 33 35 l 33 33 l 34 33 l 34 32 l 35 32 l 35 33 l 36 33 l 36 34 l 37 34 l 37 32 l 35 32 l 35 30 l 32 30 l 32 29 l 33 29 l 33 28 l 35 28 l 35 27 l 37 27 l 37 26 m 33 31 l 33 32 l 32 32 l 32 31 m 31 33 l 32 33 l 32 34 l 31 34 m 25 34 l 26 34 l 26 33 l 25 33 m 36 28 l 36 28 l 37 28 l 37 29 l 36 29 m 36 30 l 37 30 l 37 31 l 36 31 m 14 35 l 14 33 l 13 33 l 13 34 l 12 34 l 12 37 l 13 37 l 13 35 m 4 37 l 4 36 l 3 36 l 3 37 l 2 37 l 2 36 l 3 36 l 3 32 l 5 32 l 5 33 l 4 33 l 4 34 l 6 34 l 6 33 l 7 33 l 7 34 l 6 34 l 6 35 l 7 35 l 7 36 l 6 36 l 6 37 l 4 37 m 4 35 l 5 35 l 5 36 l 4 36 m 37 45 l 37 44 l 36 44 l 36 43 l 35 43 l 35 44 l 34 44 l 34 45 l 35 45 l 35 46 l 34 46 l 34 47 l 35 47 l 35 50 l 34 50 l 34 52 l 33 52 l 33 54 l 31 54 l 31 53 l 32 53 l 32 52 l 33 52 l 33 49 l 34 49 l 34 48 l 33 48 l 33 46 l 29 46 l 29 45 l 28 45 l 28 46 l 27 46 l 27 45 l 28 45 l 28 44 l 26 44 l 26 46 l 25 46 l 25 47 l 24 47 l 24 45 l 25 45 l 25 44 l 23 44 l 23 46 l 21 46 l 21 47 l 20 47 l 20 46 l 19 46 l 19 49 l 21 49 l 21 52 l 19 52 l 19 53 l 21 53 l 21 55 l 23 55 l 23 54 l 22 54 l 22 53 l 23 53 l 23 52 l 22 52 l 22 51 l 24 51 l 24 52 l 25 52 l 25 51 l 26 51 l 26 50 l 25 50 l 25 49 l 24 49 l 24 50 l 22 50 l 22 49 l 23 49 l 23 48 l 26 48 l 26 47 l 28 47 l 28 48 l 28 48 l 26 48 l 26 50 l 27 50 l 27 49 l 28 49 l 28 50 l 27 50 l 27 51 l 28 51 l 28 53 l 27 53 l 27 52 l 26 52 l 26 55 l 28 55 l 28 54 l 29 54 l 29 51 l 30 51 l 30 52 l 31 52 l 31 51 l 32 51 l 32 52 l 31 52 l 31 53 l 30 53 l 30 54 l 29 54 l 29 55 l 37 55 l 37 52 l 36 52 l 36 54 l 34 54 l 34 53 l 35 53 l 35 50 l 37 50 l 37 48 l 36 48 l 36 45 m 29 47 l 32 47 l 32 50 l 29 50 m 30 48 l 31 48 l 31 49 l 30 49 m 13 49 l 15 49 l 15 46 l 16 46 l 16 45 l 17 45 l 17 44 l 18 44 l 18 42 l 17 42 l 17 41 l 14 41 l 14 42 l 16 42 l 16 45 l 15 45 l 15 43 l 14 43 l 14 42 l 13 42 l 13 44 l 11 44 l 11 43 l 12 43 l 12 42 l 9 42 l 9 44 l 8 44 l 8 42 l 6 42 l 6 41 l 10 41 l 10 39 l 11 39 l 11 41 l 13 41 l 13 40 l 14 40 l 14 39 l 13 39 l 13 40 l 12 40 l 12 39 l 11 39 l 11 37 l 9 37 l 9 38 l 8 38 l 8 40 l 5 40 l 5 41 l 3 41 l 3 40 l 0 40 l 0 42 l 1 42 l 1 41 l 2 41 l 2 43 l 0 43 l 0 47 l 1 47 l 1 44 l 2 44 l 2 46 l 3 46 l 3 44 l 2 44 l 2 43 l 3 43 l 3 42 l 4 42 l 4 47 l 5 47 l 5 46 l 6 46 l 6 45 l 7 45 l 7 44 l 6 44 l 6 43 l 5 43 l 5 42 l 6 42 l 6 43 l 7 43 l 7 44 l 8 44 l 8 46 l 6 46 l 6 47 l 8 47 l 8 48 l 9 48 l 9 45 l 10 45 l 10 44 l 11 44 l 11 45 l 10 45 l 10 46 l 11 46 l 11 47 l 10 47 l 10 48 l 11 48 l 11 47 l 14 47 l 14 48 l 13 48 m 13 46 l 12 46 l 12 45 l 13 45 m 15 55 l 11 55 l 11 54 l 9 54 l 9 53 l 8 53 l 8 50 l 9 50 l 9 52 l 10 52 l 10 49 l 11 49 l 11 53 l 12 53 l 12 51 l 13 51 l 13 50 l 14 50 l 14 51 l 13 51 l 13 53 l 12 53 l 12 54 l 15 54 l 15 54 m 15 53 l 15 52 l 17 52 l 17 53 l 18 53 l 18 55 l 16 55 l 16 53 m 17 47 l 18 47 l 18 49 l 16 49 l 16 48 l 17 48 m 17 50 l 18 50 l 18 51 l 17 51 m 19 50 l 20 50 l 20 51 l 19 51 m 19 54 l 20 54 l 20 55 l 19 55 m 0 38 l 1 38 l 1 39 l 0 39 m 0 48 l 7 48 l 7 55 l 0 55 l 0 55 m 1 49 l 1 54 l 1 54 l 6 54 l 6 49 m 2 50 l 5 50 l 5 53 l 2 53 m 30 18 l 30 25 l 37 25 l 37 18 m 31 19 l 36 19 l 36 24 l 31 24 m 32 20 l 32 23 l 35 23 l 35 20 m 0 18 l 7 18 l 7 25 l 0 25 m 1 19 l 1 24 l 6 24 l 6 19 m 2 20 l 2 23 l 5 23 l 5 20 m 8 18 l 8 21 l 11 21 l 11 22 l 10 22 l 10 23 l 8 23 l 8 27 l 10 27 l 10 28 l 12 28 l 12 32 l 10 32 l 10 33 l 11 33 l 11 34 l 12 34 l 12 33 l 13 33 l 13 32 l 15 32 l 15 31 l 16 31 l 16 29 l 15 29 l 15 30 l 14 30 l 14 29 l 15 29 l 15 28 l 14 28 l 14 27 l 13 27 l 13 23 l 15 23 l 15 24 l 14 24 l 14 26 l 15 26 l 15 27 l 16 27 l 16 25 l 15 25 l 15 24 l 16 24 l 16 23 l 17 23 l 17 24 l 18 24 l 18 22 l 19 22 l 19 20 l 21 20 l 21 19 l 23 19 l 23 18 l 21 18 l 21 19 l 19 19 l 19 18 l 18 18 l 18 20 l 17 20 l 17 22 l 15 22 l 15 21 l 16 21 l 16 20 l 17 20 l 17 19 l 16 19 l 16 20 l 15 20 l 15 19 l 16 19 l 16 18 l 14 18 l 14 20 l 15 20 l 15 21 l 14 21 l 14 20 l 13 20 l 13 21 l 12 21 l 12 19 l 13 19 l 13 18 l 11 18 l 11 19 l 9 19 l 9 18 m 9 26 l 9 24 l 10 24 l 10 23 l 11 23 l 11 22 l 12 22 l 12 27 l 11 27 l 11 26 m 10 25 l 10 24 l 11 24 l 11 25 m 25 18 l 25 19 l 26 19 l 26 18 m 28 18 l 29 18 l 29 20 l 27 20 l 27 19 l 28 19
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.12,0:00:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fad(1000,500)\c&H000000&\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&\fscx16\fscy26\\move(41,237.9,31.372,248.87,0,2000)}m 56 35 l 43 41 l 52 41 l 52 39 l 56 39 m 73 28 l 77 41 l 82 41 m 69 21 l 61 21 l 64 23 l 64 39 l 63 41 l 70 41 l 65 28 l 67 23 l 71 23 m 25 28 l 17 41 l 33 41 m 31 21 l 52 21 l 42 25 l 42 29 l 53 24 l 55 26 l 42 32 l 42 35 l 56 29 l 56 31 l 42 37 l 41 39 m 29 9 l 55 9 l 55 11 l 41 11 l 41 17 l 51 17 l 51 14 l 65 14 l 68 18 l 29 18 m 20 11 l 16 18 l 20 18 m 14 21 l 19 21 l 8 39 l 7 39 l 7 41 l 1 41
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.00,0:00:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs9\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,300)\\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscy100)\\pos(30.343,286.457)}dajiazimuzu
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.00,0:00:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs9\fn微软雅黑\fad(0,100)\\fscy0\t(0,500,\fscy100)\\pos(30.343,286.457)}dajiazimuzu
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.86,0:00:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Exciting time in the world right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.46,0:00:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Exciting time.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.76,0:00:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you agree to testify,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.49,0:00:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will testify that I broke chain of custody
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.78,0:00:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with the .DAT file.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.52,0:00:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We've implemented a honey pot, CS30.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.08,0:00:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd like to look over your findings,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.74,0:00:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}especially this server.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.75,0:00:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Detectives came by. They want to speak with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.83,0:00:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They found a body on the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.54,0:00:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And you both did know the deceased.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.37,0:00:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sharon Knowles.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.96,0:00:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sharon Knowles?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.24,0:00:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.86,0:00:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think the baby's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.16,0:00:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We got to get her to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.37,0:00:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tell me about your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.04,0:00:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I remember I tried to hug him, tell him I'm sorry,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.51,0:00:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and he shoved me so hard, I fell backwards out the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.22,0:00:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, my God, Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.72,0:00:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Did you forget again? Did you forget who I am?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.22,0:00:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-I'm your... - Sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.56,0:00:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- I think we should talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.33,0:00:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- It hasn't happened since 1904
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.43,0:00:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the year John McGraw decided to take his bat and ball
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.02,0:00:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and go home. Here we are 90 years later,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.36,0:01:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I want to get your thoughts on what it was like
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.28,0:01:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to be without the 1994 World Series.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.16,0:01:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's right, the 1994 World Series cancelled....
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.33,0:01:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you would have told me
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.75,0:01:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}back in August when the players voted to walk out
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.96,0:01:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that we would be here where we are today,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.70,0:01:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I would have told you no way, no how,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.38,0:01:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.09,0:01:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But hey, if I ever get it wrong, I admit it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.89,0:01:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what happened? I want to hear from you...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.72,0:01:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mr. Robot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.10,0:01:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Um, well, I'd recommend the Pentium 90.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.74,0:01:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're lighting fast, and we've got some in stock now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.07,0:01:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}With an 800 megabyte hard drive, you'll be all set.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.44,0:01:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Or we could save you a few bucks
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.04,0:01:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and upgrade what you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.44,0:01:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Once we swap out that motherboard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.91,0:01:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and hard drive, you'll be better than new.\N{\fs14}Once we swap out that motherboard
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.12,0:01:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and hard drive, you'll be better than new.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.11,0:01:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why don't you bring it on by, and we'll take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.45,0:01:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.59,0:01:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.70,0:01:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.82,0:01:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What happened? That new mouse not work out for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.12,0:01:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your son, he stole money from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.29,0:01:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Uh, excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.74,0:01:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your son stole money from me. I pulled out my wallet,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.32,0:02:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I specifically remembered I had three 20s.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.43,0:02:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now I only have one.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.80,0:02:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}{\i1}I used one to pay for the mouse,{\i}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.47,0:02:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}{\i1}and then I had two left.{\i}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.77,0:02:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your son was standing right behind me
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.47,0:02:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}when I had my money out on the counter.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.53,0:02:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14} I--just calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.11,0:02:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm sure there's an explanation for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.54,0:02:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-I don't want an explanation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.16,0:02:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The only thing I want from you is my money
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.08,0:02:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and a f---ing apology.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.29,0:02:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There's no need for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.54,0:02:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm just trying to figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.80,0:02:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can you tell how much of a shit I give about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.96,0:02:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Ugh. I don't have time for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.46,0:02:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you giving me my money or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.55,0:02:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, do the right thing here guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.84,0:02:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.17,0:02:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14} Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14} The answer's no.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.81,0:02:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14} Are you-- you being serious right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.43,0:02:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.84,0:02:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You--you're really just\N{\fs14}gonna sit there and lie?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.69,0:03:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I should call the cops!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.28,0:03:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What an example you're setting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.33,0:03:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I--I earn my money,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.75,0:03:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and you're just teaching him how to steal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.04,0:03:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're a terrible father.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.74,0:03:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.09,0:03:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're a nobody.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.68,0:03:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're a middle-aged man doing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.68,0:03:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}what my retarded nephew could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.68,0:03:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.27,0:03:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know what? Keep your 20.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.35,0:03:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll just go to Best Buy from now on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.98,0:03:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}God...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.41,0:03:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.76,0:04:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Dad, I didn't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.93,0:04:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Let me see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.46,0:04:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}"Timecop" or "Stargate"?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.13,0:04:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What? 20 bucks ought to cover the both of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.36,0:04:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}"Pulp Fiction"? Never heard of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.20,0:05:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sure I can take you to that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.31,0:05:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All right, get your jacket.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.72,0:05:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.23,0:05:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How come I'm not in trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.57,0:05:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Even though what you did was wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.32,0:05:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you're still a good kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.49,0:05:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and that guy was a prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.36,0:05:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sometimes that matters more.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.00,0:05:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on, let's go. It starts in 15 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.87,0:05:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want to get some popcorn. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.75,0:06:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's really him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.43,0:06:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's really you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.77,0:07:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Never been to your apartment before.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.44,0:07:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.74,0:07:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A little messy, but that's not Earth-shattering news.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.95,0:07:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You never really did like cleaning your room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.84,0:07:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jesus f---ing Christ.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.96,0:07:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't believe it's really you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.09,0:07:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was beginning to wonder how long
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.60,0:07:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}it was gonna take before you recognized me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.43,0:07:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The fact that you stopped recognizing Darlene too, well...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.19,0:07:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got to be honest, that's a little disconcerting.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.61,0:07:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why didn't you say anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.81,0:07:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why didn't you tell me? - Okay, Elliot--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.82,0:07:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- This whole time?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.82,0:07:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Elliot, you are not well.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.37,0:07:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was trying to handle it gently.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.16,0:07:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Gently?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.30,0:08:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Gently?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.46,0:08:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Gently?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.16,0:08:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that what the last three months have been?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.05,0:08:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No. It's been about us doing something important,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.56,0:08:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and that's what it still needs to be about.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.34,0:08:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You died.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.43,0:08:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You died.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.35,0:08:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're dead!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.19,0:08:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I suggest you lower your voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.24,0:08:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Lower my voice?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.99,0:08:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want me to lower my voice after appearing at my door
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.53,0:08:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}20 years after your supposed death?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.84,0:08:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think this is a perfect f---ing volume!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.55,0:08:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, you don't want them to hear us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.72,0:09:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Especially after my impromptu visit from
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.26,0:09:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tyrell Wellick last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.11,0:09:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, there are people out there
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.90,0:09:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}who do not want us to work together.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.73,0:09:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that why they've been following me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.54,0:09:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that why, because of you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.74,0:09:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Think about it. You don't remember me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.88,0:09:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You don't remember your own God damn sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.00,0:09:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You see that shrink, pop their pills.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.47,0:09:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They intentionally put you in this haze, fog,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.88,0:09:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}or whatever brain matter you have left in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.72,0:09:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so you forget what they want you to forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.76,0:09:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're trying to control you, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.89,0:09:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They've been trying to control you all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.76,0:09:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is crazy. I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.98,0:09:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm crazy. You're crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.42,0:09:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.44,0:09:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.40,0:09:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who's trying to control me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.41,0:09:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The people out there who don't want me alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.66,0:09:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The people who are afraid of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.78,0:10:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We have to be more careful, now more than ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.28,0:10:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And Darlene, she knew about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.51,0:10:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, I will explain everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.46,0:10:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but right now, tonight, we have to stick to the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.18,0:10:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you kidding me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.96,0:10:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want me to put this on hold?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.52,0:10:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you out of your God damn mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.80,0:10:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's not safe to discuss this here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.11,0:10:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't give a shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.19,0:10:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tell me what the f--- is going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.98,0:10:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All right. Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.54,0:10:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.87,0:10:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want answers?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.96,0:10:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Stop asking questions and follow me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.62,0:11:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, that's sweet. I--I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.58,0:11:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're going too fast.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.88,0:11:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Trust me, don't think that's the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.17,0:11:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.33,0:11:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you didn't want to talk last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.00,0:11:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, Harry, I can't right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.14,0:11:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have to-- - Breathe...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.64,0:11:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and have some breakfast in bed with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.49,0:11:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How are you enjoying anything like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.25,0:11:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mm.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.68,0:11:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Honey, I appreciate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.12,0:11:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I...God, if you only knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.08,0:11:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tell me. I would love to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.70,0:11:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They hacked us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.87,0:11:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know that. It's all over the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.42,0:11:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now, normally a company can get through this,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.44,0:11:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but we're a cyber security company.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.76,0:11:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can you appreciate how bad that is?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.68,0:11:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We're hanging on by our fingernails.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.94,0:12:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Ugh, who knows?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.32,0:12:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe we've already fallen off a cliff,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.84,0:12:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I'm still trying to grasp on to something.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.78,0:12:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm a failure.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.20,0:12:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.41,0:12:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look at this person who loves you so much
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.86,0:12:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he would die a happy man right now just 'cause
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he had this, us, sitting down and having breakfast.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.59,0:12:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't think failing looks like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.40,0:12:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Make sure you go through all those emails again,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.28,0:12:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}everything from '91 to '95,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.92,0:12:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and let's start building a table
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.30,0:12:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that cross-references our calendar.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.40,0:13:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Yes, ma'am. - Hey, good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.80,0:13:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, you should be proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.54,0:13:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}News of Colby's confession is breaking today.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.67,0:13:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So far we are firing on all cylinders, so what's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.12,0:13:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I came to help out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.30,0:13:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, can you rescan these and email the .PDFs to me
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.54,0:13:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and copy Ry on them?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.62,0:13:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shouldn't you be at work?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.14,0:13:33.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Angela, you can't work here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.28,0:13:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why not? I gave up everything for this case.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.36,0:13:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't want you to.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.65,0:13:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I am not here to help you find purpose in your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.14,0:13:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you need something to do, take a jewelry class,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.66,0:13:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but you can't work here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.88,0:13:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}After what I did,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.21,0:13:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I won't be able to find another job in tech.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.22,0:13:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm broke.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.67,0:13:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The lawsuit money won't come in for years.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.78,0:13:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Which is why you need to find something you can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.67,0:14:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But this is not it,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.34,0:14:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}not at this level for what we're trying to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.18,0:14:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.18,0:14:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}John. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.68,0:14:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.85,0:14:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Um...four?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.02,0:14:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, no, no, we're not going down that road.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.94,0:14:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Absolutely not.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.52,0:14:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's not happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.53,0:14:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, it's gonna be six or nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.53,0:14:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Who is this? - It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.24,0:14:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm looking for Elliot He's not at work.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.76,0:14:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- I think he's flipping out again.- What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.96,0:14:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He tried to kiss me last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.76,0:14:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're the one that found him last time he was like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.38,0:14:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I really need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.39,0:14:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.24,0:15:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.54,0:15:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Let's keep thinking then.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.58,0:15:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have been.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.58,0:15:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This was our runaway hideout.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.56,0:15:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He always came here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.22,0:15:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, let's spitball together.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.47,0:15:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.76,0:15:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.64,0:15:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- It means...I don't really know Elliot any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.60,0:15:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He has gone psycho legit this time, Angela.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.52,0:15:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We are in a state of 911.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.02,0:15:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We just need to talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.66,0:15:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, well, he doesn't want to talk back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.44,0:15:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And if he does, it's usually with a bunch of lies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.41,0:15:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We can't keep protecting him from himself, Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.44,0:15:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He has saved our asses multiple times,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.94,0:15:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and you're just gonna do him like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.98,0:15:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why do you even care?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.92,0:15:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What is that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.50,0:15:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It means you guys were never that close.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.34,0:15:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}In fact,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.17,0:16:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he's been doing just fine until you moved back to the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.30,0:16:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why are you even here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.85,0:16:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why have you and Elliot been spending so much time together?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.12,0:16:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, you need to back off, babe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.14,0:16:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He is my brother, and I'm just trying to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.44,0:16:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That requires no explanation.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.31,0:16:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You don't want to tell me what's really going on here,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.64,0:16:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that's fine, but then stop asking me for my help.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.36,0:16:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think we're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.51,0:16:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Remember this?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.68,0:16:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Of course I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.72,0:16:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think it's reasonable for me to confirm given your--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.04,0:16:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I even remember my game.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.15,0:17:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd calculate the statistical probability
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.65,0:17:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of safety for each car on the train
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.19,0:17:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}based on how often they would derail.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.19,0:17:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}On the way there, I'd always pick the safest car
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.60,0:17:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}'cause I looked forward to our trips to the city so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.75,0:17:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then on the way back, I'd pick the most dangerous ones...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.87,0:17:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}'cause I hated going home.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.04,0:17:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She's not there any more, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.21,0:17:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Look, I don't know where we're going,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.93,0:17:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but we need to find Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.43,0:17:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They may be after her-  Shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.39,0:17:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I thought that was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.06,0:17:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, my God. I haven't seen you in forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.04,0:17:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We can't see Darlene right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.08,0:17:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's too risky.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.63,0:18:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you're confused, Elliot, but I'm gonna show you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.36,0:18:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm gonna show you exactly where I've been this whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.73,0:18:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.43,0:18:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll figure this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.60,0:18:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you don't trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.32,0:18:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wouldn't either, but I'm telling you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.24,0:18:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm remembering more and more now as time goes on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.99,0:18:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's a plus.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.83,0:18:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's all starting to come back,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.45,0:18:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and once we get all the answers,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.66,0:18:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll be back to normal,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.45,0:18:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}except for the fact that my dead father
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.78,0:18:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}isn't really dead and is sitting across from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.68,0:19:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm gonna step outside and give you guys a moment to yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.04,0:19:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,We'll try feeding him again later, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.72,0:19:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Okay
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.08,0:21:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, I know the owner. Freddy
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.96,0:21:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you okay? Is everyone okay? What the hell happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.88,0:21:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm still trying to figure that one out myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.40,0:21:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was gone one day upstate.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.20,0:21:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're saying it was electrical, but who knows?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.56,0:22:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}On hold with the insurance.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.04,0:22:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Cocksuckers are doing their typical dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.20,0:22:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, I was on hold?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.40,0:22:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, wait, not again.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.76,0:22:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, I just came by to pick up some drives
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.68,0:22:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}one of my employees dropped off yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.56,0:22:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm sorry you wasted the trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.56,0:22:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Everything's gone. I'm sorry you wasted the trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.60,0:22:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Everything's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.96,0:22:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tyrell.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.72,0:22:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What was it?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.88,0:22:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.96,0:22:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.96,0:22:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.40,0:22:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you for the flowers, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.16,0:22:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If I'm being honest,it was Anwar
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.12,0:22:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}who sent the flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.68,0:22:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He has a way with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.08,0:22:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tyrell, you don't know me to beat around the bush,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.04,0:22:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so I'll get right to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.28,0:23:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.38,0:23:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You understand the delicate state we're in these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.40,0:23:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}As I'm sure you're aware,this situation
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.88,0:23:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with Sharon Knowles is...it's horrific.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.44,0:23:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Scott is understandably devastated by it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.92,0:23:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, my heart goes out to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.16,0:23:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know what I'd do if--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.44,0:23:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, yeah,I know, I know, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.72,0:23:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The thing is that the police
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.85,0:23:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}have indicated to Scott and to me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.16,0:23:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that you are a person of interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.84,0:23:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're suspicions are based on information Scott
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.12,0:23:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}gave them about advances you made on Sharon?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.68,0:23:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, Tyrell,it was not lost on me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.72,0:23:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that you and Scott had your own competitive frictions.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.52,0:23:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hell, the man nabbed CTO right out from under you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.64,0:23:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm sure his distress is just causing him to lash out,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.00,0:23:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and you're an easy target for him,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.88,0:24:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and of course I doubt you're involvement in this mishap,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.68,0:24:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but...but...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.73,0:24:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The problem remains.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.32,0:24:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Scott will continue here,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.24,0:24:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but you, I'm afraid, can not.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.08,0:24:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm not sure what you're saying, Phillip.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.10,0:24:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know exactly what I'm saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.76,0:24:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Phillip, you can't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.11,0:24:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.49,0:24:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.11,0:25:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've killed myself for this company!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.72,0:25:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've been promoted faster than anyone else!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.00,0:25:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't deny I tried picturing your reaction.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.12,0:25:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I seldom have time for such imaginings.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.29,0:25:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}For you, I was curious.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.36,0:25:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It could've gone any number of ways,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.16,0:25:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I found all the different versions quite interesting,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.28,0:25:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I admit, but now...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.00,0:25:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}confronted with the reality...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.97,0:25:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have to say I'm disappointed.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.98,0:25:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Phillip, please don't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.00,0:25:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was on a track.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.44,0:25:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There was a moment, Tyrell,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.32,0:25:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a point in your recent past,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.32,0:25:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a mistake,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.80,0:25:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a compulsion, decision,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.68,0:26:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}something, that led you to this point right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.24,0:26:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My only advice to you is...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.68,0:26:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}find that moment,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.72,0:26:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}understand it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.49,0:26:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's the only way to reconcile this...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.16,0:26:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}this failure with yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.36,0:26:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please, sir, don't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.16,0:26:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm begging you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.50,0:26:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I...I love this company.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.90,0:27:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mr. Wellick,you can't keep ignoring us.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.36,0:27:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you have any questions,contact my lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.44,0:27:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you have evidence against me, charge me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.44,0:27:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know I brought you back to township,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.80,0:27:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but stopping by our old house is not part of the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.44,0:27:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on, these people are gonna be home soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.48,0:27:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not the best time for a B and E.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.80,0:27:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is where it happened,isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.20,0:27:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What? Where what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.76,0:27:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You remember anything about that window?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.60,0:27:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.24,0:27:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Like I said, we should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.94,0:27:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, what are you doing?Calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.64,0:27:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah!Ugh!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.04,0:27:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-You pushed me out this window.- Elliot...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.48,0:27:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-You pushed me off the boardwalk.- Hey, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.40,0:27:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No. Maybe you're the one who needs some pushing now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.60,0:27:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Calm down.It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.08,0:27:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Bullshit! I was eight years old.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.16,0:27:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You thought I deserved it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.36,0:27:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-That's what you said, isn't it? -No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.76,0:27:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-Yeah, right before you pushed me again! -No, no, no, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.36,0:28:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you thought you deserved it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.04,0:28:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You felt guilty about this your whole life,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.04,0:28:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}about telling people my secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.68,0:28:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This anger was never at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.24,0:28:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It was at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.64,0:28:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.08,0:28:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you don't have to be angry at yourself any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.48,0:28:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Just let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.76,0:28:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please let it go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.24,0:28:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're right.I was angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.68,0:28:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was angry at myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.88,0:28:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I hated myself for doing what I did to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.81,0:28:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm ready to let go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.65,0:28:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.08,0:29:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Gonna work in the garden a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.40,0:29:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It'd be nice if you wanted to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.52,0:29:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, by the way, you didn't tell me Darlene was back in town.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.84,0:29:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I haven't seen her back here in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.20,0:29:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.65,0:29:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Darlene. At least, I think it was her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.03,0:29:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You saw her? Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.29,0:29:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm telling you,I did not get notification of the request.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.96,0:29:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That server needs to remain a honey pot, off the network.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.80,0:29:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sir, I have the request right here from yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.32,0:29:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm trying to tell you, Jim,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.80,0:29:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}our network was compromised yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.88,0:29:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I did not make the request.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.20,0:29:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Someone else obviously did,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.56,0:29:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so you need to take the server off the network,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.52,0:29:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}or something's gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.88,0:29:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I just can't do that, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.97,0:29:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We have specific orders from Tyrell Wellick
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.68,0:29:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to keep the request as is.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.52,0:29:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That just doesn't make any sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.56,0:29:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, I need to speak to your supervisor.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.69,0:30:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.36,0:30:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is anyone here?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.43,0:30:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.32,0:30:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.68,0:30:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I ran out of places to look,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.00,0:30:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so I figured I'd try the last place he'd ever be.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.96,0:30:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Struck out again.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.28,0:30:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.39,0:30:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I haven't been here in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.23,0:30:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The new family that just moved in is so weird,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.16,0:30:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}especially the dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.37,0:30:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They really change much.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.38,0:30:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.92,0:30:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.30,0:31:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.42,0:31:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Weird new dad's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.40,0:31:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm sorry, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.32,0:31:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.24,0:31:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I should be more open with you, your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.95,0:31:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.64,0:31:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't get all mushy on me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.92,0:31:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.51,0:31:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Wasn't that Elliot's room?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.12,0:32:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We're almost there.Almost there.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.44,0:32:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why?Why are we here?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.31,0:32:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I thought you said we were going somewhere safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.76,0:32:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.37,0:32:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.54,0:32:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.32,0:32:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.12,0:32:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What the hell are they doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.82,0:32:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Won't be long now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.99,0:32:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I tried to protect you, son,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.80,0:32:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but they caught up to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.40,0:32:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-Elliot!- What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.67,0:32:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's Darlene and Angela.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.40,0:32:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Trust me, son,I wanted to tell you sooner.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.36,0:32:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Things got too accelerated at the end there.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.39,0:32:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You have to believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.34,0:32:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No matter what anyone tries to do, I will never leave you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.92,0:32:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will always be right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.80,0:32:41.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you understand that? They are not going to break us apart again.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.04,0:32:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.96,0:32:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Listen to me. - Tell me right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.40,0:32:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen to me because we don't have much time.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.84,0:32:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're gonna try and get rid of me again,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.82,0:32:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I need you to not let them!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.88,0:32:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why would they get rid of you?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.04,0:32:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please, Elliot, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.24,0:32:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will never leave you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.26,0:32:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will never leave you alone again.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.20,0:33:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I love you, son.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.98,0:33:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's he talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.16,0:33:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's he talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.65,0:33:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, I want to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.90,0:33:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.16,0:33:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want to know!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.49,0:33:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, who are you talking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.53,0:33:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you mean? I'm talking to
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.13,0:33:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Stay back. Stay back.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.38,0:33:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, you're bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.55,0:33:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.89,0:33:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.77,0:33:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.11,0:34:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.07,0:34:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You didn't see him?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.07,0:34:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.24,0:34:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.74,0:34:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This can't be happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.58,0:34:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-This can't be happening. -No...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.06,0:34:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is happening, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.73,0:34:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You knew all along, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.74,0:34:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, who do you think you've been talking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.12,0:34:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're gonnamake me say it, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.09,0:35:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm Mr. Robot.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.37,0:35:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.54,0:35:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think I'm pretty f---ing far from okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.75,0:35:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't take this the wrong way,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.25,0:35:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but I envy you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.48,0:35:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wish I could talk to my mom again,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.40,0:35:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}even if she isn't real.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.12,0:36:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Take care of yourself, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.14,0:36:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you don't feel like talking about it...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.77,0:36:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're right, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.44,0:36:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Unfortunately I need to know, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.81,0:36:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}given what we've been doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.82,0:36:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I just need to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.62,0:36:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you remember any of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.16,0:36:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Remember what?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.05,0:36:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}When we first started fsociety.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.14,0:37:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is Mr. Wellick in?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.64,0:37:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, hi, Mr. Goddard.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.18,0:37:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, he's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.35,0:37:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He was, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.18,0:37:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He was let go today.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.65,0:37:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.02,0:37:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.33,0:37:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He wasn't always the easiest person to deal with.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.66,0:37:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I--I'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.36,0:37:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Uh, do you think you can get me in to see Scott Knowles?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.37,0:37:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}-It's urgent. - Oh, no, definitely not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.87,0:37:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You haven't heard?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.87,0:38:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Dad, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.24,0:38:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll let you two talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.46,0:38:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know, I know, but hey, you popped in over at my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.46,0:38:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I figured I'd return the favor.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.09,0:38:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.97,0:38:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}To offer you something you may want.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.73,0:38:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on in.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.73,0:38:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If this is about the case--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.23,0:38:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please. I don't care about the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.60,0:38:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't even understand the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.82,0:38:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have lawyers for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.82,0:38:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.16,0:38:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You boys can wait outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.45,0:38:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So I got to be honest, I was impressed by you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.17,0:38:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sure, your career's finished,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.09,0:38:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but you played a great short game.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.29,0:38:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You took a big gamble, and you got what you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.96,0:39:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It was just, you know, the wrong thing to want.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.43,0:39:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you care?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.35,0:39:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, I looked into you over there at Allsafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.31,0:39:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, lots of people
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.94,0:39:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}would've settled into middle management bliss
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.78,0:39:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}after all the shit you've taken,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.14,0:39:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.81,0:39:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're relentless and smart, and that combination
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.48,0:39:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}is very valuable to a lot of important people,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.32,0:39:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}people I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.82,0:39:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where are you going with all of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.32,0:39:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think I can land you a pretty lucrative gig.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.83,0:39:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A gig? Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.55,0:39:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your favorite place, where else?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.14,0:39:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You slummed it all the way down to Jersey in person
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.90,0:39:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to offer me a job at the company I'm currently suing?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.18,0:40:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's the real ask here?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.40,0:40:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think you'd make a great business woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.52,0:40:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm afraid it's nothing more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.49,0:40:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Is this a joke? - It's no joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.03,0:40:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My pals think you can bring a lot to the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.99,0:40:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't be offering me a job there.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.20,0:40:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're testifying against them.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.25,0:40:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, you'll find this out fairly soon,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.08,0:40:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but in business, grudges aren't really a thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.25,0:40:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's too emotional.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.67,0:40:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's because you pulled off
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.37,0:40:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}what you pulled off that they called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.26,0:40:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is a huge class action lawsuit.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.38,0:40:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They are going to pay millions.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.38,0:40:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Roughly 75 to 100 million.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.05,0:40:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, that's what their lawyers will settle for
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.35,0:40:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}after they exhaust most of your legal team's funds
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.60,0:40:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}for the next seven years.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.69,0:40:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And sure, that is-- that's a lot of money,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.44,0:40:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but not to them, not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.56,0:40:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We started a rainy-day fund
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.28,0:40:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}when the leak happened just for this occasion.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.78,0:40:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The fund itself has already made five times that amount.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.63,0:40:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd like to ask you to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.74,0:41:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shall I pass your name along then?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.05,0:41:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm not working there.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.88,0:41:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They killed my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.47,0:41:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And every fast food joint around the corner
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.30,0:41:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}delivers diabetes to millions of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.97,0:41:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Phillip Morris hands out lung cancer on the hour, every hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.59,0:41:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, hell,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.12,0:41:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}everyone's destroying the planet beyond the point of no return.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.59,0:41:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you really gonna start taking all of these things
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.98,0:41:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so personally?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.15,0:41:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.73,0:41:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe someone has to.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.32,0:41:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A suggestion:
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.49,0:41:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you want to change things,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.27,0:41:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}perhaps you should try from within,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.99,0:41:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}because this is what happens from the outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.28,0:41:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}These guys don't wait on anyone,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.00,0:41:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so you'll have to let them know by tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.00,0:41:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll show myself out.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.57,0:42:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}These are all empty.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.17,0:42:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you just filling them and dumping them?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.73,0:42:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where are your new 'scrips?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.68,0:42:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What does it matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.40,0:42:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't even know what's real any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.02,0:42:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, I know you feel shitty right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.07,0:42:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but once you take your meds--
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.52,0:42:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe we should stop it, Darlene.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.83,0:42:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Stop what?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.03,0:42:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.92,0:42:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The hack. Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.50,0:42:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe we shouldn't execute it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.75,0:42:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.04,0:42:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The minute our infected server gets back on the main network,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.71,0:42:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- we're set. - It wasn't me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.93,0:42:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The whole time, it wasn't really me doing all of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.55,0:43:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, the reasons we wanted to do this,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.72,0:43:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the reasons why we all wanted to do this,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.06,0:43:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}are real.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.06,0:43:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe you don't realize this, but this was your idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:12.56,0:43:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You came up with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.24,0:43:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There is a part of you. somewhere deep down inside,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.29,0:43:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that knows this is the right thing to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.75,0:43:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm gonna get your meds.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.41,0:43:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll talk more when I get back, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.55,0:43:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.27,0:43:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What would you do if you were in my shoes?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.74,0:43:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know. I know, I'm officially crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.77,0:43:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but the plan isn't, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.28,0:44:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What the hell are you--
Dialogue: 0,0:44:06.29,0:44:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shh.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.97,0:44:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've been waiting outside your apartment until she left.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.47,0:44:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Didn't want anyone to know I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.69,0:44:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you're behind it,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.64,0:44:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}all of it, F society, the server,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:36.53,0:44:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Colby, Allsafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.03,0:44:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're the one constant in a sea of variables.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.50,0:44:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:54.47,0:44:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}now, I don't know what your grand plan is,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.55,0:45:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but I need to, and you're going to tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.98,0:45:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Two days ago I strangled a woman to death just with my hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.86,0:45:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's a strange sensation.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.45,0:45:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Something so tremendous done
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.37,0:45:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}by something so simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.17,0:45:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The first ten seconds were...uncomfortable,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.21,0:45:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a feeling of limbo,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:40.88,0:45:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but then your muscles tense,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.60,0:45:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and she struggles and fights,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.27,0:45:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but it almost disappears in the background
Dialogue: 0,0:45:48.27,0:45:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}along with everything else in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:52.89,0:45:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}At that moment it's just you and absolute power,
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.56,0:46:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}nothing else.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:03.54,0:46:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That moment stayed with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.08,0:46:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I thought I'd feel guilty for being a murderer,
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.96,0:46:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but...I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.64,0:46:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I feel wonder.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:43.59,0:46:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How long has this been going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.00,0:46:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:46:56.34,0:46:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And what is it that you're doing exactly?
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.02,0:47:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Encrypting all the files.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:03.04,0:47:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All of Evil Corp's financial records
Dialogue: 0,0:47:05.20,0:47:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}will be impossible to access.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.74,0:47:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The encryption key will self-delete
Dialogue: 0,0:47:09.41,0:47:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}after the process completes.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:11.40,0:47:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What about the backups?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:12.33,0:47:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I took care of that too.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:14.64,0:47:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}China. Steel Mountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:17.34,0:47:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Of course, even when we went redundant.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.53,0:47:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I hacked the Air Dream network.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.12,0:47:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was in all of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.62,0:47:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You really thought of everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.56,0:47:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who else was involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:32.88,0:47:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Just me.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:38.30,0:47:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, now it's you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:41.72,0:47:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've always told you we'd end up working together, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:48.25,0:47:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But still, I have to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:47:52.85,0:47:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why did you do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.54,0:48:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What did you hope to accomplish by doing all of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.24,0:48:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:48:17.00,0:48:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wanted to save the world.
