10
00:00:00,860 --> 00:00:02,440
Exciting time in the world right now.

11
00:00:02,460 --> 00:00:03,760
Exciting time.

12
00:00:03,760 --> 00:00:05,490
If you agree to testify,

13
00:00:05,490 --> 00:00:07,760
I will testify that I broke chain of custody

14
00:00:07,780 --> 00:00:08,500
with the .DAT file.

15
00:00:08,520 --> 00:00:11,020
We've implemented a honey pot, CS30.

16
00:00:11,080 --> 00:00:12,690
I'd like to look over your findings,

17
00:00:12,740 --> 00:00:14,690
especially this server.

18
00:00:14,750 --> 00:00:16,780
Detectives came by. They want to speak with you.

19
00:00:16,830 --> 00:00:18,520
They found a body on the roof.

20
00:00:18,540 --> 00:00:20,330
And you both did know the deceased.

21
00:00:20,370 --> 00:00:21,900
Sharon Knowles.

22
00:00:21,960 --> 00:00:23,180
Sharon Knowles?

23
00:00:23,240 --> 00:00:23,820
Aah!

24
00:00:23,860 --> 00:00:25,120
I think the baby's coming.

25
00:00:25,160 --> 00:00:26,370
We got to get her to the hospital.

26
00:00:26,370 --> 00:00:28,040
Tell me about your father.

27
00:00:28,040 --> 00:00:30,460
I remember I tried to hug him, tell him I'm sorry,

28
00:00:30,510 --> 00:00:33,880
and he shoved me so hard, I fell backwards out the window.

29
00:00:35,220 --> 00:00:36,680
Oh, my God, Elliot!

30
00:00:36,720 --> 00:00:39,220
Did you forget again? Did you forget who I am?

31
00:00:39,220 --> 00:00:41,050
-I'm your... - Sister.

32
00:00:47,560 --> 00:00:49,360
- I think we should talk.

33
00:00:52,330 --> 00:00:54,400
- It hasn't happened since 1904

34
00:00:54,430 --> 00:00:57,000
the year John McGraw decided to take his bat and ball

35
00:00:57,020 --> 00:00:59,340
and go home. Here we are 90 years later,

36
00:00:59,360 --> 00:01:01,240
and I want to get your thoughts on what it was like

37
00:01:01,280 --> 00:01:04,130
to be without the 1994 World Series.

38
00:01:04,160 --> 00:01:07,300
That's right, the 1994 World Series cancelled....

39
00:01:07,330 --> 00:01:08,750
If you would have told me

40
00:01:08,750 --> 00:01:10,920
back in August when the players voted to walk out

41
00:01:10,960 --> 00:01:12,660
that we would be here where we are today,

42
00:01:12,700 --> 00:01:14,340
I would have told you no way, no how,

43
00:01:14,380 --> 00:01:16,090
that's not gonna happen.

44
00:01:16,090 --> 00:01:17,840
But hey, if I ever get it wrong, I admit it.

45
00:01:17,890 --> 00:01:20,430
So, what happened? I want to hear from you...

46
00:01:20,720 --> 00:01:22,420
Mr. Robot.

47
00:01:24,100 --> 00:01:26,700
Um, well, I'd recommend the Pentium 90.

48
00:01:26,740 --> 00:01:29,020
They're lighting fast, and we've got some in stock now.

49
00:01:29,070 --> 00:01:32,600
With an 800 megabyte hard drive, you'll be all set.

50
00:01:33,440 --> 00:01:35,020
Or we could save you a few bucks

51
00:01:35,040 --> 00:01:36,410
and upgrade what you have.

52
00:01:36,440 --> 00:01:37,910
Once we swap out that motherboard

53
00:01:37,910 --> 00:01:38,120
and hard drive, you'll be better than new.
Once we swap out that motherboard

54
00:01:38,120 --> 00:01:41,080
and hard drive, you'll be better than new.

55
00:01:41,110 --> 00:01:44,450
Why don't you bring it on by, and we'll take a look.

56
00:01:44,450 --> 00:01:45,530
Okay.

57
00:01:45,590 --> 00:01:46,670
Thank you.

58
00:01:46,700 --> 00:01:47,820
Bye-bye.

59
00:01:48,820 --> 00:01:51,120
What happened? That new mouse not work out for you?

60
00:01:51,120 --> 00:01:53,460
Your son, he stole money from me.

61
00:01:54,290 --> 00:01:55,680
Uh, excuse me?

62
00:01:55,740 --> 00:01:58,280
Your son stole money from me. I pulled out my wallet,

63
00:01:58,320 --> 00:02:00,380
and I specifically remembered I had three 20s.

64
00:02:00,430 --> 00:02:01,800
Now I only have one.

65
00:02:01,800 --> 00:02:03,440
I used one to pay for the mouse,

66
00:02:03,470 --> 00:02:04,720
and then I had two left.

67
00:02:04,770 --> 00:02:07,440
Your son was standing right behind me

68
00:02:07,470 --> 00:02:09,470
when I had my money out on the counter.

69
00:02:09,530 --> 00:02:11,060
I--just calm down.

70
00:02:11,110 --> 00:02:12,500
I'm sure there's an explanation for this.

71
00:02:12,540 --> 00:02:14,140
-I don't want an explanation.

72
00:02:14,160 --> 00:02:16,040
The only thing I want from you is my money

73
00:02:16,080 --> 00:02:17,820
and a f---ing apology.

74
00:02:18,290 --> 00:02:19,480
There's no need for that.

75
00:02:19,540 --> 00:02:20,760
I'm just trying to figure it out.

76
00:02:20,800 --> 00:02:23,910
Can you tell how much of a shit I give about that?

77
00:02:23,960 --> 00:02:26,410
Ugh. I don't have time for this.

78
00:02:26,460 --> 00:02:28,780
Are you giving me my money or not?

79
00:02:29,550 --> 00:02:32,380
Look, do the right thing here guy.

80
00:02:36,840 --> 00:02:38,420
Then, no.

81
00:02:39,170 --> 00:02:40,670
Excuse me?

82
00:02:40,720 --> 00:02:42,040
The answer's no.

83
00:02:47,810 --> 00:02:50,400
Are you-- you being serious right now?

84
00:02:50,430 --> 00:02:52,440
I can't help you.

85
00:02:53,840 --> 00:02:58,240
You--you're really just
gonna sit there and lie?

86
00:02:58,690 --> 00:03:00,500
I should call the cops!

87
00:03:03,280 --> 00:03:05,280
What an example you're setting.

88
00:03:05,330 --> 00:03:06,700
I--I earn my money,

89
00:03:06,750 --> 00:03:10,000
and you're just teaching him how to steal.

90
00:03:10,040 --> 00:03:11,720
You're a terrible father.

91
00:03:11,740 --> 00:03:13,040
- I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.

92
00:03:13,090 --> 00:03:14,620
You're a nobody.

93
00:03:14,680 --> 00:03:16,630
You're a middle-aged man doing

94
00:03:16,680 --> 00:03:20,160
what my retarded nephew could do.

95
00:03:20,680 --> 00:03:22,080
That's your life.

96
00:03:24,270 --> 00:03:27,300
You know what? Keep your 20.

97
00:03:27,350 --> 00:03:29,690
I'll just go to Best Buy from now on.

98
00:03:29,980 --> 00:03:31,520
God...

99
00:03:48,410 --> 00:03:49,980
Come on out.

100
00:04:02,760 --> 00:04:05,760
Dad, I didn't do it.

101
00:04:13,930 --> 00:04:15,570
Let me see it.

102
00:04:40,460 --> 00:04:42,460
"Timecop" or "Stargate"?

103
00:04:47,130 --> 00:04:49,630
What? 20 bucks ought to cover the both of us.

104
00:04:55,360 --> 00:04:58,140
"Pulp Fiction"? Never heard of it.

105
00:04:58,200 --> 00:05:00,280
Sure I can take you to that?

106
00:05:00,310 --> 00:05:01,980
All right, get your jacket.

107
00:05:26,720 --> 00:05:27,890
What?

108
00:05:30,230 --> 00:05:33,010
How come I'm not in trouble?

109
00:05:37,570 --> 00:05:40,270
Even though what you did was wrong,

110
00:05:40,320 --> 00:05:41,900
you're still a good kid,

111
00:05:44,490 --> 00:05:46,360
and that guy was a prick.

112
00:05:46,360 --> 00:05:48,720
Sometimes that matters more.

113
00:05:51,000 --> 00:05:52,830
Come on, let's go. It starts in 15 minutes.

114
00:05:52,870 --> 00:05:54,750
I want to get some popcorn. Come on.

115
00:06:42,750 --> 00:06:45,420
It's really him.

116
00:06:52,430 --> 00:06:54,980
It's really you.

117
00:07:00,770 --> 00:07:04,400
Never been to your apartment before.

118
00:07:04,440 --> 00:07:06,690
It's nice.

119
00:07:06,740 --> 00:07:11,940
A little messy, but that's not Earth-shattering news.

120
00:07:11,950 --> 00:07:14,780
You never really did like cleaning your room.

121
00:07:19,840 --> 00:07:22,790
Jesus f---ing Christ.

122
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:27,120
I can't believe it's really you.

123
00:07:28,090 --> 00:07:29,540
I was beginning to wonder how long

124
00:07:29,600 --> 00:07:32,380
it was gonna take before you recognized me.

125
00:07:32,430 --> 00:07:37,380
The fact that you stopped recognizing Darlene too, well...

126
00:07:38,190 --> 00:07:41,690
I got to be honest, that's a little disconcerting.

127
00:07:44,610 --> 00:07:46,780
Why didn't you say anything?

128
00:07:46,810 --> 00:07:48,780
Why didn't you tell me? - Okay, Elliot--

129
00:07:48,820 --> 00:07:49,780
- This whole time?

130
00:07:49,820 --> 00:07:51,920
- Elliot, you are not well.

131
00:07:52,370 --> 00:07:57,160
I was trying to handle it gently.

132
00:07:57,160 --> 00:07:59,120
Gently?

133
00:07:59,300 --> 00:08:01,020
Gently?

134
00:08:01,460 --> 00:08:03,020
Gently?

135
00:08:04,160 --> 00:08:07,000
Is that what the last three months have been?

136
00:08:07,050 --> 00:08:12,500
No. It's been about us doing something important,

137
00:08:12,560 --> 00:08:16,310
and that's what it still needs to be about.

138
00:08:16,340 --> 00:08:18,390
You died.

139
00:08:18,430 --> 00:08:19,540
You died.

140
00:08:21,350 --> 00:08:23,150
You're dead!

141
00:08:25,190 --> 00:08:28,150
I suggest you lower your voice.

142
00:08:32,240 --> 00:08:33,760
Lower my voice?

143
00:08:33,990 --> 00:08:37,500
You want me to lower my voice after appearing at my door

144
00:08:37,530 --> 00:08:41,700
20 years after your supposed death?

145
00:08:43,840 --> 00:08:49,710
I think this is a perfect f---ing volume!

146
00:08:54,550 --> 00:08:56,700
Elliot, you don't want them to hear us.

147
00:08:57,720 --> 00:09:00,240
Especially after my impromptu visit from

148
00:09:00,260 --> 00:09:02,050
Tyrell Wellick last night.

149
00:09:06,110 --> 00:09:08,860
Elliot, there are people out there

150
00:09:08,900 --> 00:09:10,780
who do not want us to work together.

151
00:09:14,730 --> 00:09:16,820
Is that why they've been following me?

152
00:09:18,540 --> 00:09:21,640
Is that why, because of you?

153
00:09:22,740 --> 00:09:25,830
Think about it. You don't remember me.

154
00:09:25,880 --> 00:09:27,910
You don't remember your own God damn sister.

155
00:09:28,000 --> 00:09:31,380
You see that shrink, pop their pills.

156
00:09:31,470 --> 00:09:33,840
They intentionally put you in this haze, fog,

157
00:09:33,880 --> 00:09:35,670
or whatever brain matter you have left in there,

158
00:09:35,720 --> 00:09:38,720
so you forget what they want you to forget.

159
00:09:38,760 --> 00:09:40,840
They're trying to control you, Elliot.

160
00:09:40,890 --> 00:09:43,730
They've been trying to control you all along.

161
00:09:43,760 --> 00:09:46,930
This is crazy. I'm crazy.

162
00:09:46,980 --> 00:09:48,360
I'm crazy. You're crazy.

163
00:09:48,420 --> 00:09:49,430
This is crazy.

164
00:09:49,440 --> 00:09:51,350
What are you talking about?

165
00:09:51,400 --> 00:09:53,350
Who's trying to control me?

166
00:09:53,410 --> 00:09:56,610
The people out there who don't want me alive.

167
00:09:56,660 --> 00:09:58,940
The people who are afraid of us.

168
00:09:59,780 --> 00:10:03,250
We have to be more careful, now more than ever.

169
00:10:03,280 --> 00:10:06,900
And Darlene, she knew about this?

170
00:10:08,510 --> 00:10:11,460
Elliot, I will explain everything,

171
00:10:11,460 --> 00:10:15,020
but right now, tonight, we have to stick to the plan.

172
00:10:16,180 --> 00:10:17,960
Are you kidding me?

173
00:10:17,960 --> 00:10:20,470
You want me to put this on hold?

174
00:10:20,520 --> 00:10:22,800
Are you out of your God damn mind?

175
00:10:22,800 --> 00:10:25,050
It's not safe to discuss this here.

176
00:10:25,110 --> 00:10:27,400
I don't give a shit!

177
00:10:29,190 --> 00:10:31,640
Tell me what the f--- is going on.

178
00:10:34,980 --> 00:10:38,180
All right. Come on, let's go.

179
00:10:38,540 --> 00:10:39,820
Where?

180
00:10:42,870 --> 00:10:44,910
You want answers?

181
00:10:44,960 --> 00:10:47,460
Stop asking questions and follow me.

182
00:10:59,620 --> 00:11:01,540
Oh, that's sweet. I--I can't.

183
00:11:01,580 --> 00:11:02,840
You're going too fast.

184
00:11:02,880 --> 00:11:05,130
Trust me, don't think that's the problem.

185
00:11:05,170 --> 00:11:07,000
Hey.

186
00:11:07,330 --> 00:11:09,970
I know you didn't want to talk last night.

187
00:11:10,000 --> 00:11:12,120
No, Harry, I can't right now.

188
00:11:12,140 --> 00:11:13,590
I have to-- - Breathe...

189
00:11:13,640 --> 00:11:15,500
and have some breakfast in bed with me.

190
00:11:30,490 --> 00:11:32,940
How are you enjoying anything like that?

191
00:11:35,250 --> 00:11:36,360
Mm.

192
00:11:36,680 --> 00:11:38,040
Honey, I appreciate it.

193
00:11:38,120 --> 00:11:41,030
I...God, if you only knew.

194
00:11:41,080 --> 00:11:42,670
Tell me. I would love to know.

195
00:11:42,700 --> 00:11:43,870
They hacked us.

196
00:11:43,870 --> 00:11:46,370
You know that. It's all over the news.

197
00:11:46,420 --> 00:11:48,400
Now, normally a company can get through this,

198
00:11:48,440 --> 00:11:50,710
but we're a cyber security company.

199
00:11:50,760 --> 00:11:54,630
Can you appreciate how bad that is?

200
00:11:54,680 --> 00:11:58,020
We're hanging on by our fingernails.

201
00:11:58,940 --> 00:12:01,970
Ugh, who knows?

202
00:12:02,320 --> 00:12:04,800
Maybe we've already fallen off a cliff,

203
00:12:04,840 --> 00:12:07,180
and I'm still trying to grasp on to something.

204
00:12:12,780 --> 00:12:14,900
I'm a failure.

205
00:12:16,200 --> 00:12:18,040
Look at me.

206
00:12:22,410 --> 00:12:25,800
Look at this person who loves you so much

207
00:12:25,860 --> 00:12:27,720
he would die a happy man right now just 'cause

208
00:12:27,780 --> 00:12:33,590
he had this, us, sitting down and having breakfast.

209
00:12:33,590 --> 00:12:37,590
I don't think failing looks like this.

210
00:12:50,400 --> 00:12:52,240
Make sure you go through all those emails again,

211
00:12:52,280 --> 00:12:53,860
everything from '91 to '95,

212
00:12:53,920 --> 00:12:55,240
and let's start building a table

213
00:12:55,300 --> 00:12:57,180
that cross-references our calendar.

214
00:12:57,400 --> 00:13:00,530
- Yes, ma'am. - Hey, good to see you.

215
00:13:00,800 --> 00:13:02,520
Oh, you should be proud.

216
00:13:02,540 --> 00:13:04,620
News of Colby's confession is breaking today.

217
00:13:04,670 --> 00:13:09,090
So far we are firing on all cylinders, so what's up?

218
00:13:09,120 --> 00:13:11,790
I came to help out.

219
00:13:16,300 --> 00:13:19,520
Yeah, can you rescan these and email the .PDFs to me

220
00:13:19,540 --> 00:13:20,560
and copy Ry on them?

221
00:13:20,620 --> 00:13:22,130
Shouldn't you be at work?

222
00:13:22,140 --> 00:13:23,970
I quit.

223
00:13:29,140 --> 00:13:33,230
Angela, you can't work here.

224
00:13:33,280 --> 00:13:36,300
Why not? I gave up everything for this case.

225
00:13:36,360 --> 00:13:38,620
I don't want you to.

226
00:13:38,650 --> 00:13:42,060
I am not here to help you find purpose in your life.

227
00:13:42,140 --> 00:13:44,580
If you need something to do, take a jewelry class,

228
00:13:44,660 --> 00:13:46,840
but you can't work here.

229
00:13:47,880 --> 00:13:50,160
After what I did,

230
00:13:50,210 --> 00:13:53,160
I won't be able to find another job in tech.

231
00:13:53,220 --> 00:13:54,670
I'm broke.

232
00:13:54,670 --> 00:13:56,740
The lawsuit money won't come in for years.

233
00:13:56,780 --> 00:13:59,670
Which is why you need to find something you can get.

234
00:13:59,670 --> 00:14:01,310
But this is not it,

235
00:14:01,340 --> 00:14:04,180
not at this level for what we're trying to do.

236
00:14:06,180 --> 00:14:07,180
Hello?

237
00:14:07,180 --> 00:14:08,600
John. Yeah, yeah, yeah.

238
00:14:08,680 --> 00:14:09,850
No, tell me.

239
00:14:09,850 --> 00:14:12,980
Um...four?

240
00:14:13,020 --> 00:14:14,860
No, no, no, we're not going down that road.

241
00:14:14,940 --> 00:14:16,490
Absolutely not.

242
00:14:16,520 --> 00:14:18,490
It's not happening.

243
00:14:18,530 --> 00:14:20,740
No, it's gonna be six or nothing.

244
00:14:27,530 --> 00:14:29,220
- Who is this? - It's me.

245
00:14:29,240 --> 00:14:31,700
I'm looking for Elliot He's not at work.

246
00:14:31,760 --> 00:14:34,860
- I think he's flipping out again.- What do you mean?

247
00:14:34,960 --> 00:14:38,710
He tried to kiss me last night.

248
00:14:38,760 --> 00:14:41,380
You're the one that found him last time he was like this.

249
00:14:41,380 --> 00:14:43,720
I really need your help.

250
00:14:46,390 --> 00:14:48,220
Okay, where are you?

251
00:15:06,240 --> 00:15:08,490
He's not here.

252
00:15:08,540 --> 00:15:10,540
Let's keep thinking then.

253
00:15:10,580 --> 00:15:12,540
I have been.

254
00:15:12,580 --> 00:15:14,500
This was our runaway hideout.

255
00:15:14,560 --> 00:15:16,580
He always came here.

256
00:15:17,220 --> 00:15:20,420
Okay, let's spitball together.

257
00:15:20,470 --> 00:15:22,500
I can't help you.

258
00:15:23,760 --> 00:15:25,590
What does that mean?

259
00:15:25,640 --> 00:15:30,120
- It means...I don't really know Elliot any more.

260
00:15:30,600 --> 00:15:33,480
He has gone psycho legit this time, Angela.

261
00:15:33,520 --> 00:15:34,980
We are in a state of 911.

262
00:15:35,020 --> 00:15:36,620
We just need to talk to him.

263
00:15:36,660 --> 00:15:38,440
Yeah, well, he doesn't want to talk back.

264
00:15:38,440 --> 00:15:41,360
And if he does, it's usually with a bunch of lies.

265
00:15:41,410 --> 00:15:44,440
We can't keep protecting him from himself, Darlene.

266
00:15:44,440 --> 00:15:46,900
He has saved our asses multiple times,

267
00:15:46,940 --> 00:15:48,750
and you're just gonna do him like this?

268
00:15:48,980 --> 00:15:51,040
Why do you even care?

269
00:15:51,920 --> 00:15:53,450
What is that supposed to mean?

270
00:15:53,500 --> 00:15:56,290
It means you guys were never that close.

271
00:15:56,340 --> 00:15:58,120
In fact,

272
00:15:58,170 --> 00:16:01,600
he's been doing just fine until you moved back to the city.

273
00:16:03,300 --> 00:16:05,800
Why are you even here?

274
00:16:05,850 --> 00:16:08,920
Why have you and Elliot been spending so much time together?

275
00:16:09,120 --> 00:16:11,140
Okay, you need to back off, babe.

276
00:16:11,140 --> 00:16:13,390
He is my brother, and I'm just trying to help.

277
00:16:13,440 --> 00:16:15,310
That requires no explanation.

278
00:16:15,310 --> 00:16:17,580
You don't want to tell me what's really going on here,

279
00:16:17,640 --> 00:16:20,810
that's fine, but then stop asking me for my help.

280
00:16:44,360 --> 00:16:46,000
I think we're good.

281
00:16:49,510 --> 00:16:51,680
Remember this?

282
00:16:51,680 --> 00:16:53,660
Of course I do.

283
00:16:53,720 --> 00:16:56,020
I think it's reasonable for me to confirm given your--

284
00:16:56,040 --> 00:16:59,100
I even remember my game.

285
00:16:59,150 --> 00:17:01,600
I'd calculate the statistical probability

286
00:17:01,650 --> 00:17:04,190
of safety for each car on the train

287
00:17:04,190 --> 00:17:07,190
based on how often they would derail.

288
00:17:07,190 --> 00:17:09,560
On the way there, I'd always pick the safest car

289
00:17:09,600 --> 00:17:13,700
'cause I looked forward to our trips to the city so much.

290
00:17:13,750 --> 00:17:17,360
Then on the way back, I'd pick the most dangerous ones...

291
00:17:18,870 --> 00:17:21,370
'cause I hated going home.

292
00:17:24,040 --> 00:17:27,210
She's not there any more, Elliot.

293
00:17:27,210 --> 00:17:28,880
- Look, I don't know where we're going,

294
00:17:28,930 --> 00:17:30,380
but we need to find Darlene.

295
00:17:30,430 --> 00:17:32,100
They may be after her-  Shh.

296
00:17:39,390 --> 00:17:41,530
I thought that was you.

297
00:17:45,060 --> 00:17:48,730
Oh, my God. I haven't seen you in forever.

298
00:17:53,040 --> 00:17:55,040
We can't see Darlene right now.

299
00:17:55,080 --> 00:17:57,280
It's too risky.

300
00:17:58,630 --> 00:18:01,260
I know you're confused, Elliot, but I'm gonna show you.

301
00:18:01,360 --> 00:18:06,080
I'm gonna show you exactly where I've been this whole time.

302
00:18:19,730 --> 00:18:21,430
Look, calm down.

303
00:18:21,430 --> 00:18:23,570
I'll figure this out.

304
00:18:23,600 --> 00:18:25,270
I know you don't trust me.

305
00:18:25,320 --> 00:18:27,190
I wouldn't either, but I'm telling you,

306
00:18:27,240 --> 00:18:29,940
I'm remembering more and more now as time goes on.

307
00:18:29,990 --> 00:18:31,780
That's a plus.

308
00:18:31,830 --> 00:18:34,450
It's all starting to come back,

309
00:18:34,450 --> 00:18:36,560
and once we get all the answers,

310
00:18:36,660 --> 00:18:39,420
I'll be back to normal,

311
00:18:39,450 --> 00:18:41,760
except for the fact that my dead father

312
00:18:41,780 --> 00:18:45,120
isn't really dead and is sitting across from me.

313
00:19:00,680 --> 00:19:04,040
I'm gonna step outside and give you guys a moment to yourselves.

314
00:19:04,040 --> 00:19:06,560
We'll try feeding him again later, okay?

315
00:19:06,720 --> 00:19:08,120
Okay

316
00:21:47,080 --> 00:21:50,280
No, I know the owner. Freddy

317
00:21:50,960 --> 00:21:53,880
Are you okay? Is everyone okay? What the hell happened?

318
00:21:53,880 --> 00:21:55,400
I'm still trying to figure that one out myself.

319
00:21:55,400 --> 00:21:57,200
I was gone one day upstate.

320
00:21:57,200 --> 00:21:58,560
They're saying it was electrical, but who knows?

321
00:21:58,560 --> 00:22:00,000
On hold with the insurance.

322
00:22:00,040 --> 00:22:02,200
Cocksuckers are doing their typical dance.

323
00:22:02,200 --> 00:22:04,120
Yeah, I was on hold?

324
00:22:04,400 --> 00:22:07,760
No, wait, not again.

325
00:22:07,760 --> 00:22:10,680
Well, I just came by to pick up some drives

326
00:22:10,680 --> 00:22:12,320
one of my employees dropped off yesterday.

327
00:22:12,560 --> 00:22:14,560
I'm sorry you wasted the trip.

328
00:22:14,560 --> 00:22:14,600
Everything's gone. I'm sorry you wasted the trip.

329
00:22:14,600 --> 00:22:16,840
Everything's gone.

330
00:22:30,960 --> 00:22:33,520
Tyrell.

331
00:22:33,720 --> 00:22:34,880
What was it?

332
00:22:34,880 --> 00:22:36,200
Boy?

333
00:22:36,960 --> 00:22:38,680
Yeah.

334
00:22:38,960 --> 00:22:40,280
Good.

335
00:22:40,400 --> 00:22:42,080
Thank you for the flowers, sir.

336
00:22:42,160 --> 00:22:44,120
If I'm being honest,it was Anwar

337
00:22:44,120 --> 00:22:46,120
who sent the flowers.

338
00:22:46,680 --> 00:22:49,240
He has a way with them.

339
00:22:52,080 --> 00:22:56,920
Tyrell, you don't know me to beat around the bush,

340
00:22:57,040 --> 00:22:59,200
so I'll get right to it.

341
00:22:59,280 --> 00:23:01,320
Have a seat.

342
00:23:01,380 --> 00:23:07,360
You understand the delicate state we're in these days.

343
00:23:07,400 --> 00:23:09,840
As I'm sure you're aware,this situation

344
00:23:09,880 --> 00:23:13,200
with Sharon Knowles is...it's horrific.

345
00:23:13,440 --> 00:23:16,640
Scott is understandably devastated by it.

346
00:23:16,920 --> 00:23:19,160
Yeah, my heart goes out to him.

347
00:23:19,160 --> 00:23:20,440
I don't know what I'd do if--

348
00:23:20,440 --> 00:23:22,680
Yeah, yeah,I know, I know, but...

349
00:23:22,720 --> 00:23:25,480
The thing is that the police

350
00:23:25,850 --> 00:23:29,850
have indicated to Scott and to me

351
00:23:30,160 --> 00:23:34,480
that you are a person of interest.

352
00:23:34,840 --> 00:23:38,120
They're suspicions are based on information Scott

353
00:23:38,120 --> 00:23:43,370
gave them about advances you made on Sharon?

354
00:23:43,680 --> 00:23:46,680
Look, Tyrell,it was not lost on me

355
00:23:46,720 --> 00:23:50,360
that you and Scott had your own competitive frictions.

356
00:23:50,520 --> 00:23:54,440
Hell, the man nabbed CTO right out from under you.

357
00:23:54,640 --> 00:23:58,000
I'm sure his distress is just causing him to lash out,

358
00:23:58,000 --> 00:23:59,840
and you're an easy target for him,

359
00:23:59,880 --> 00:24:03,680
and of course I doubt you're involvement in this mishap,

360
00:24:03,680 --> 00:24:06,110
but...but...

361
00:24:08,730 --> 00:24:12,560
The problem remains.

362
00:24:15,320 --> 00:24:18,200
Scott will continue here,

363
00:24:18,240 --> 00:24:21,400
but you, I'm afraid, can not.

364
00:24:37,080 --> 00:24:40,680
I'm not sure what you're saying, Phillip.

365
00:24:45,100 --> 00:24:48,600
You know exactly what I'm saying.

366
00:24:50,760 --> 00:24:55,070
Phillip, you can't do this.

367
00:24:55,110 --> 00:24:57,440
You can't do this.

368
00:24:57,490 --> 00:24:59,110
You can't!

369
00:24:59,110 --> 00:25:01,720
I've killed myself for this company!

370
00:25:01,720 --> 00:25:05,280
I've been promoted faster than anyone else!

371
00:25:07,000 --> 00:25:11,200
I can't deny I tried picturing your reaction.

372
00:25:12,120 --> 00:25:15,260
I seldom have time for such imaginings.

373
00:25:15,290 --> 00:25:17,320
For you, I was curious.

374
00:25:17,360 --> 00:25:19,160
It could've gone any number of ways,

375
00:25:19,160 --> 00:25:22,240
and I found all the different versions quite interesting,

376
00:25:22,280 --> 00:25:24,630
I admit, but now...

377
00:25:25,000 --> 00:25:28,160
confronted with the reality...

378
00:25:28,970 --> 00:25:32,000
I have to say I'm disappointed.

379
00:25:32,980 --> 00:25:37,000
Phillip, please don't do this.

380
00:25:37,000 --> 00:25:39,240
I was on a track.

381
00:25:49,440 --> 00:25:52,320
There was a moment, Tyrell,

382
00:25:52,320 --> 00:25:55,830
a point in your recent past,

383
00:25:56,320 --> 00:25:57,720
a mistake,

384
00:25:57,800 --> 00:25:59,640
a compulsion, decision,

385
00:25:59,680 --> 00:26:04,670
something, that led you to this point right now.

386
00:26:05,240 --> 00:26:07,280
My only advice to you is...

387
00:26:07,680 --> 00:26:10,360
find that moment,

388
00:26:10,720 --> 00:26:13,080
understand it.

389
00:26:15,490 --> 00:26:18,120
It's the only way to reconcile this...

390
00:26:18,160 --> 00:26:20,720
this failure with yourself.

391
00:26:22,360 --> 00:26:26,610
Please, sir, don't do this.

392
00:26:27,160 --> 00:26:29,600
I'm begging you.

393
00:26:30,500 --> 00:26:36,040
I...I love this company.

394
00:27:00,900 --> 00:27:04,360
Mr. Wellick,you can't keep ignoring us.

395
00:27:04,360 --> 00:27:06,440
If you have any questions,contact my lawyer.

396
00:27:06,440 --> 00:27:08,900
If you have evidence against me, charge me.

397
00:27:18,440 --> 00:27:20,800
I know I brought you back to township,

398
00:27:20,800 --> 00:27:24,440
but stopping by our old house is not part of the plan.

399
00:27:24,440 --> 00:27:26,480
Come on, these people are gonna be home soon.

400
00:27:26,480 --> 00:27:27,800
Not the best time for a B and E.

401
00:27:27,800 --> 00:27:29,200
This is where it happened,isn't it?

402
00:27:29,200 --> 00:27:32,430
What? Where what happened?

403
00:27:32,760 --> 00:27:35,560
You remember anything about that window?

404
00:27:35,600 --> 00:27:37,180
Come on, Elliot.

405
00:27:37,240 --> 00:27:38,930
Like I said, we should go.

406
00:27:38,940 --> 00:27:42,120
Elliot, what are you doing?Calm down.

407
00:27:42,640 --> 00:27:44,000
Aah!Ugh!

408
00:27:44,040 --> 00:27:45,480
-You pushed me out this window.- Elliot...

409
00:27:45,480 --> 00:27:47,400
-You pushed me off the boardwalk.- Hey, come on.

410
00:27:47,400 --> 00:27:49,560
No. Maybe you're the one who needs some pushing now.

411
00:27:49,600 --> 00:27:51,080
Calm down.It was an accident.

412
00:27:51,080 --> 00:27:53,160
Bullshit! I was eight years old.

413
00:27:53,160 --> 00:27:54,360
You thought I deserved it.

414
00:27:54,360 --> 00:27:55,760
-That's what you said, isn't it? -No, no.

415
00:27:55,760 --> 00:27:57,320
-Yeah, right before you pushed me again! -No, no, no, Elliot,

416
00:27:57,360 --> 00:28:00,040
you thought you deserved it.

417
00:28:00,040 --> 00:28:02,000
You felt guilty about this your whole life,

418
00:28:02,040 --> 00:28:03,640
about telling people my secret.

419
00:28:03,680 --> 00:28:05,200
This anger was never at me.

420
00:28:05,240 --> 00:28:06,640
It was at you.

421
00:28:06,640 --> 00:28:08,040
Please, Elliot,

422
00:28:08,080 --> 00:28:10,480
you don't have to be angry at yourself any more.

423
00:28:10,480 --> 00:28:11,720
Just let it go.

424
00:28:11,760 --> 00:28:13,160
Please let it go.

425
00:28:13,240 --> 00:28:15,640
You're right.I was angry.

426
00:28:15,680 --> 00:28:16,840
I was angry at myself.

427
00:28:16,880 --> 00:28:20,400
I hated myself for doing what I did to you.

428
00:28:21,810 --> 00:28:23,610
I'm ready to let go.

429
00:28:23,650 --> 00:28:24,810
Aah!

430
00:29:03,080 --> 00:29:06,360
Gonna work in the garden a little.

431
00:29:06,400 --> 00:29:08,350
It'd be nice if you wanted to help.

432
00:29:11,520 --> 00:29:14,840
Oh, by the way, you didn't tell me Darlene was back in town.

433
00:29:14,840 --> 00:29:17,200
I haven't seen her back here in a while.

434
00:29:17,200 --> 00:29:18,610
What did you say?

435
00:29:18,650 --> 00:29:21,980
Darlene. At least, I think it was her.

436
00:29:22,030 --> 00:29:26,240
You saw her? Where?

437
00:29:26,290 --> 00:29:29,960
I'm telling you,I did not get notification of the request.

438
00:29:29,960 --> 00:29:32,760
That server needs to remain a honey pot, off the network.

439
00:29:32,800 --> 00:29:34,280
Sir, I have the request right here from yesterday.

440
00:29:34,320 --> 00:29:35,800
I'm trying to tell you, Jim,

441
00:29:35,800 --> 00:29:37,840
our network was compromised yesterday.

442
00:29:37,880 --> 00:29:39,160
I did not make the request.

443
00:29:39,200 --> 00:29:40,520
Someone else obviously did,

444
00:29:40,560 --> 00:29:42,520
so you need to take the server off the network,

445
00:29:42,520 --> 00:29:43,840
or something's gonna happen.

446
00:29:43,880 --> 00:29:44,960
I just can't do that, sir.

447
00:29:44,970 --> 00:29:46,670
We have specific orders from Tyrell Wellick

448
00:29:46,680 --> 00:29:48,520
to keep the request as is.

449
00:29:48,520 --> 00:29:50,520
That just doesn't make any sense.

450
00:29:50,560 --> 00:29:53,840
Look, I need to speak to your supervisor.

451
00:30:01,690 --> 00:30:03,400
Hello?

452
00:30:05,360 --> 00:30:07,480
Is anyone here?

453
00:30:21,430 --> 00:30:23,160
Hello?

454
00:30:24,320 --> 00:30:26,800
Oh, Jesus.

455
00:30:27,680 --> 00:30:30,000
I ran out of places to look,

456
00:30:30,000 --> 00:30:32,640
so I figured I'd try the last place he'd ever be.

457
00:30:32,960 --> 00:30:35,120
Struck out again.

458
00:30:35,280 --> 00:30:37,040
Oh, God.

459
00:30:37,390 --> 00:30:40,640
I haven't been here in years.

460
00:30:41,230 --> 00:30:45,080
The new family that just moved in is so weird,

461
00:30:45,160 --> 00:30:47,450
especially the dad.

462
00:30:50,370 --> 00:30:53,040
They really change much.

463
00:30:54,380 --> 00:30:56,400
You okay?

464
00:30:56,920 --> 00:30:58,250
Yeah.

465
00:30:59,300 --> 00:31:00,410
Shit.

466
00:31:00,420 --> 00:31:02,250
Weird new dad's back.

467
00:31:19,400 --> 00:31:22,270
I'm sorry, by the way.

468
00:31:22,320 --> 00:31:24,160
For what?

469
00:31:25,240 --> 00:31:29,990
I should be more open with you, your family.

470
00:31:33,950 --> 00:31:35,640
Okay, okay.

471
00:31:35,640 --> 00:31:38,160
Don't get all mushy on me now.

472
00:31:43,920 --> 00:31:46,160
Do you see that?

473
00:31:47,510 --> 00:31:49,720
Wasn't that Elliot's room?

474
00:31:57,120 --> 00:32:01,400
We're almost there.Almost there.

475
00:32:01,440 --> 00:32:03,280
Why?Why are we here?

476
00:32:03,310 --> 00:32:05,720
I thought you said we were going somewhere safe.

477
00:32:05,760 --> 00:32:07,000
Aah!

478
00:32:07,370 --> 00:32:09,480
Elliot!

479
00:32:09,540 --> 00:32:11,320
Elliot!

480
00:32:11,320 --> 00:32:13,070
Shit.

481
00:32:13,120 --> 00:32:15,820
What the hell are they doing here?

482
00:32:15,820 --> 00:32:17,960
Won't be long now.

483
00:32:17,990 --> 00:32:19,760
I tried to protect you, son,

484
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:21,400
but they caught up to us.

485
00:32:21,400 --> 00:32:23,660
-Elliot!- What are you talking about?

486
00:32:23,670 --> 00:32:26,360
That's Darlene and Angela.

487
00:32:26,400 --> 00:32:29,280
Trust me, son,I wanted to tell you sooner.

488
00:32:29,360 --> 00:32:31,340
Things got too accelerated at the end there.

489
00:32:31,390 --> 00:32:33,340
You have to believe that.

490
00:32:33,340 --> 00:32:36,880
No matter what anyone tries to do, I will never leave you.

491
00:32:36,920 --> 00:32:38,720
I will always be right here.

492
00:32:38,800 --> 00:32:41,040
Do you understand that? They are not going to break us apart again.

493
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:41,960
What's going on?

494
00:32:41,960 --> 00:32:43,400
- Listen to me. - Tell me right now!

495
00:32:43,400 --> 00:32:44,840
Listen to me because we don't have much time.

496
00:32:44,840 --> 00:32:46,160
They're gonna try and get rid of me again,

497
00:32:46,820 --> 00:32:47,820
and I need you to not let them!

498
00:32:47,880 --> 00:32:49,000
Why would they get rid of you?

499
00:32:49,040 --> 00:32:49,880
Please, Elliot, listen to me.

500
00:32:50,240 --> 00:32:51,740
I will never leave you.

501
00:32:53,260 --> 00:32:56,320
I will never leave you alone again.

502
00:32:58,200 --> 00:33:00,240
I love you, son.

503
00:33:11,980 --> 00:33:13,940
What's he talking about?

504
00:33:14,160 --> 00:33:16,140
What's he talking about?

505
00:33:16,650 --> 00:33:18,850
Hey, I want to know.

506
00:33:18,900 --> 00:33:21,100
I want to know.

507
00:33:21,160 --> 00:33:23,440
I want to know!

508
00:33:23,490 --> 00:33:27,080
Elliot, who are you talking to?

509
00:33:29,530 --> 00:33:32,080
What do you mean? I'm talking to

510
00:33:40,130 --> 00:33:45,380
Stay back. Stay back.

511
00:33:45,380 --> 00:33:47,210
Elliot, you're bleeding.

512
00:33:49,550 --> 00:33:52,890
Aah.

513
00:33:52,890 --> 00:33:54,720
Elliot...

514
00:33:55,770 --> 00:33:57,220
Aah.

515
00:34:02,110 --> 00:34:06,070
Elliot, what are you doing here?

516
00:34:06,070 --> 00:34:10,070
You didn't see him?

517
00:34:10,070 --> 00:34:13,240
Who?

518
00:34:13,240 --> 00:34:15,710
Aah!

519
00:34:15,740 --> 00:34:18,580
This can't be happening.

520
00:34:18,580 --> 00:34:20,960
-This can't be happening. -No...

521
00:34:29,060 --> 00:34:31,760
This is happening, isn't it?

522
00:34:36,730 --> 00:34:40,270
You knew all along, didn't you?

523
00:34:47,740 --> 00:34:53,500
Elliot, who do you think you've been talking to?

524
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:58,840
You're gonnamake me say it, aren't you?

525
00:35:03,090 --> 00:35:05,120
I'm Mr. Robot.

526
00:35:20,370 --> 00:35:25,490
You're gonna be okay.

527
00:35:25,540 --> 00:35:28,750
I think I'm pretty f---ing far from okay.

528
00:35:31,750 --> 00:35:35,250
Don't take this the wrong way,

529
00:35:35,250 --> 00:35:37,050
but I envy you.

530
00:35:40,480 --> 00:35:44,340
I wish I could talk to my mom again,

531
00:35:44,400 --> 00:35:46,730
even if she isn't real.

532
00:36:09,120 --> 00:36:12,620
Take care of yourself, okay?

533
00:36:27,140 --> 00:36:29,720
I know you don't feel like talking about it...

534
00:36:29,770 --> 00:36:32,390
You're right, I don't.

535
00:36:32,440 --> 00:36:35,810
Unfortunately I need to know, Elliot,

536
00:36:35,810 --> 00:36:39,780
given what we've been doing.

537
00:36:39,820 --> 00:36:42,450
I just need to know.

538
00:36:44,620 --> 00:36:46,790
Do you remember any of it?

539
00:36:50,160 --> 00:36:53,000
Remember what?

540
00:36:53,050 --> 00:36:55,670
When we first started fsociety.

541
00:37:04,140 --> 00:37:06,590
Is Mr. Wellick in?

542
00:37:06,640 --> 00:37:09,150
Oh, hi, Mr. Goddard.

543
00:37:09,180 --> 00:37:10,350
No, he's gone.

544
00:37:10,350 --> 00:37:12,150
He was, um...

545
00:37:12,180 --> 00:37:13,600
He was let go today.

546
00:37:13,650 --> 00:37:18,020
What? Why?

547
00:37:18,020 --> 00:37:20,270
I don't know.

548
00:37:20,330 --> 00:37:22,610
He wasn't always the easiest person to deal with.

549
00:37:22,660 --> 00:37:24,360
I--I'm sure.

550
00:37:24,360 --> 00:37:29,330
Uh, do you think you can get me in to see Scott Knowles?

551
00:37:29,370 --> 00:37:33,840
-It's urgent. - Oh, no, definitely not now.

552
00:37:33,870 --> 00:37:35,710
You haven't heard?

553
00:38:05,870 --> 00:38:08,240
Dad, what's going on?

554
00:38:08,240 --> 00:38:11,070
I'll let you two talk.

555
00:38:16,460 --> 00:38:19,050
I know, I know, but hey, you popped in over at my home.

556
00:38:19,460 --> 00:38:23,090
I figured I'd return the favor.

557
00:38:23,090 --> 00:38:24,920
What do you want?

558
00:38:24,970 --> 00:38:27,670
To offer you something you may want.

559
00:38:27,730 --> 00:38:30,680
Come on in.

560
00:38:30,730 --> 00:38:32,180
If this is about the case--

561
00:38:32,230 --> 00:38:33,600
Please. I don't care about the case.

562
00:38:33,600 --> 00:38:34,760
I don't even understand the case.

563
00:38:34,820 --> 00:38:36,770
I have lawyers for that.

564
00:38:36,820 --> 00:38:39,070
Then what?

565
00:38:41,160 --> 00:38:43,940
You boys can wait outside.

566
00:38:48,450 --> 00:38:52,110
So I got to be honest, I was impressed by you.

567
00:38:52,170 --> 00:38:54,030
Sure, your career's finished,

568
00:38:54,090 --> 00:38:56,290
but you played a great short game.

569
00:38:56,290 --> 00:38:58,920
You took a big gamble, and you got what you wanted.

570
00:38:58,960 --> 00:39:02,170
It was just, you know, the wrong thing to want.

571
00:39:09,430 --> 00:39:11,300
What do you care?

572
00:39:11,350 --> 00:39:14,270
You know, I looked into you over there at Allsafe.

573
00:39:14,310 --> 00:39:15,890
I mean, lots of people

574
00:39:15,940 --> 00:39:17,720
would've settled into middle management bliss

575
00:39:17,780 --> 00:39:19,140
after all the shit you've taken,

576
00:39:19,140 --> 00:39:20,810
but you didn't.

577
00:39:20,810 --> 00:39:22,450
You're relentless and smart, and that combination

578
00:39:22,480 --> 00:39:26,320
is very valuable to a lot of important people,

579
00:39:26,320 --> 00:39:28,820
people I know.

580
00:39:28,820 --> 00:39:32,320
Where are you going with all of this?

581
00:39:32,320 --> 00:39:36,880
I think I can land you a pretty lucrative gig.

582
00:39:39,830 --> 00:39:43,500
A gig? Where?

583
00:39:43,550 --> 00:39:46,670
Your favorite place, where else?

584
00:39:50,140 --> 00:39:53,840
You slummed it all the way down to Jersey in person

585
00:39:53,900 --> 00:39:58,180
to offer me a job at the company I'm currently suing?

586
00:39:58,180 --> 00:40:00,350
What's the real ask here?

587
00:40:00,400 --> 00:40:02,520
I think you'd make a great business woman.

588
00:40:02,520 --> 00:40:05,440
I'm afraid it's nothing more than that.

589
00:40:05,490 --> 00:40:07,020
- Is this a joke? - It's no joke.

590
00:40:07,030 --> 00:40:08,940
My pals think you can bring a lot to the table.

591
00:40:08,990 --> 00:40:11,190
You can't be offering me a job there.

592
00:40:11,200 --> 00:40:13,200
You're testifying against them.

593
00:40:13,250 --> 00:40:15,030
So, you'll find this out fairly soon,

594
00:40:15,080 --> 00:40:18,200
but in business, grudges aren't really a thing.

595
00:40:18,250 --> 00:40:19,620
It's too emotional.

596
00:40:19,670 --> 00:40:21,340
It's because you pulled off

597
00:40:21,370 --> 00:40:23,210
what you pulled off that they called me.

598
00:40:23,260 --> 00:40:26,340
This is a huge class action lawsuit.

599
00:40:26,380 --> 00:40:28,380
They are going to pay millions.

600
00:40:28,380 --> 00:40:31,050
Roughly 75 to 100 million.

601
00:40:31,050 --> 00:40:33,300
I mean, that's what their lawyers will settle for

602
00:40:33,350 --> 00:40:35,550
after they exhaust most of your legal team's funds

603
00:40:35,600 --> 00:40:37,640
for the next seven years.

604
00:40:37,690 --> 00:40:39,390
And sure, that is-- that's a lot of money,

605
00:40:39,440 --> 00:40:41,560
but not to them, not really.

606
00:40:41,560 --> 00:40:43,230
We started a rainy-day fund

607
00:40:43,280 --> 00:40:45,730
when the leak happened just for this occasion.

608
00:40:45,780 --> 00:40:48,900
The fund itself has already made five times that amount.

609
00:40:57,630 --> 00:40:59,710
I'd like to ask you to leave.

610
00:40:59,740 --> 00:41:00,990
Shall I pass your name along then?

611
00:41:01,050 --> 00:41:02,830
I'm not working there.

612
00:41:02,880 --> 00:41:04,410
They killed my mother.

613
00:41:04,470 --> 00:41:06,250
And every fast food joint around the corner

614
00:41:06,300 --> 00:41:08,920
delivers diabetes to millions of people.

615
00:41:08,970 --> 00:41:11,550
Phillip Morris hands out lung cancer on the hour, every hour.

616
00:41:11,590 --> 00:41:12,960
I mean, hell,

617
00:41:13,120 --> 00:41:16,560
everyone's destroying the planet beyond the point of no return.

618
00:41:16,590 --> 00:41:18,930
Are you really gonna start taking all of these things

619
00:41:18,980 --> 00:41:20,100
so personally?

620
00:41:20,150 --> 00:41:21,680
Maybe I will.

621
00:41:21,730 --> 00:41:23,270
Maybe someone has to.

622
00:41:23,320 --> 00:41:24,430
A suggestion:

623
00:41:24,490 --> 00:41:26,240
If you want to change things,

624
00:41:26,270 --> 00:41:30,940
perhaps you should try from within,

625
00:41:30,990 --> 00:41:36,250
because this is what happens from the outside.

626
00:41:36,280 --> 00:41:37,950
These guys don't wait on anyone,

627
00:41:38,000 --> 00:41:40,450
so you'll have to let them know by tomorrow.

628
00:41:42,000 --> 00:41:44,250
I'll show myself out.

629
00:42:08,570 --> 00:42:11,130
These are all empty.

630
00:42:11,170 --> 00:42:16,670
Are you just filling them and dumping them?

631
00:42:16,730 --> 00:42:19,680
Where are your new 'scrips?

632
00:42:19,680 --> 00:42:22,350
What does it matter?

633
00:42:22,400 --> 00:42:27,980
I don't even know what's real any more.

634
00:42:28,020 --> 00:42:31,020
Look, I know you feel shitty right now,

635
00:42:31,070 --> 00:42:32,520
but once you take your meds--

636
00:42:32,520 --> 00:42:35,780
Maybe we should stop it, Darlene.

637
00:42:35,830 --> 00:42:38,030
Stop what?

638
00:42:38,030 --> 00:42:39,860
The plan.

639
00:42:39,920 --> 00:42:41,450
The hack. Everything.

640
00:42:41,500 --> 00:42:43,700
Maybe we shouldn't execute it.

641
00:42:43,750 --> 00:42:46,040
What? Why?

642
00:42:46,040 --> 00:42:48,710
The minute our infected server gets back on the main network,

643
00:42:48,710 --> 00:42:51,880
- we're set. - It wasn't me.

644
00:42:51,930 --> 00:42:57,510
The whole time, it wasn't really me doing all of that.

645
00:42:57,550 --> 00:43:02,690
Elliot, the reasons we wanted to do this,

646
00:43:02,720 --> 00:43:05,020
the reasons why we all wanted to do this,

647
00:43:05,060 --> 00:43:08,060
are real.

648
00:43:08,060 --> 00:43:12,560
Maybe you don't realize this, but this was your idea.

649
00:43:12,560 --> 00:43:16,230
You came up with this.

650
00:43:16,240 --> 00:43:19,240
There is a part of you. somewhere deep down inside,

651
00:43:19,290 --> 00:43:22,620
that knows this is the right thing to do.

652
00:43:26,750 --> 00:43:28,410
I'm gonna get your meds.

653
00:43:28,410 --> 00:43:30,580
We'll talk more when I get back, okay?

654
00:43:35,550 --> 00:43:36,890
Come on.

655
00:43:46,270 --> 00:43:49,680
What would you do if you were in my shoes?

656
00:43:49,740 --> 00:43:52,770
I know. I know, I'm officially crazy,

657
00:43:52,770 --> 00:43:56,410
but the plan isn't, is it?

658
00:44:05,280 --> 00:44:06,250
What the hell are you--

659
00:44:06,290 --> 00:44:07,670
Shh.

660
00:44:23,970 --> 00:44:27,440
I've been waiting outside your apartment until she left.

661
00:44:27,470 --> 00:44:30,640
Didn't want anyone to know I'm here.

662
00:44:30,690 --> 00:44:32,640
I know you're behind it,

663
00:44:32,640 --> 00:44:36,480
all of it, F society, the server,

664
00:44:36,530 --> 00:44:38,980
Colby, Allsafe.

665
00:44:39,030 --> 00:44:42,490
You're the one constant in a sea of variables.

666
00:44:50,500 --> 00:44:54,410
Elliot...

667
00:44:54,470 --> 00:44:58,500
now, I don't know what your grand plan is,

668
00:44:58,550 --> 00:45:00,840
but I need to, and you're going to tell me.

669
00:45:11,980 --> 00:45:17,820
Two days ago I strangled a woman to death just with my hands.

670
00:45:17,860 --> 00:45:20,820
That's a strange sensation.

671
00:45:25,450 --> 00:45:27,360
Something so tremendous done

672
00:45:27,370 --> 00:45:30,370
by something so simple.

673
00:45:33,170 --> 00:45:38,210
The first ten seconds were...uncomfortable,

674
00:45:38,210 --> 00:45:40,840
a feeling of limbo,

675
00:45:40,880 --> 00:45:42,550
but then your muscles tense,

676
00:45:42,600 --> 00:45:46,220
and she struggles and fights,

677
00:45:46,270 --> 00:45:48,220
but it almost disappears in the background

678
00:45:48,270 --> 00:45:52,860
along with everything else in the world.

679
00:45:52,890 --> 00:45:58,560
At that moment it's just you and absolute power,

680
00:45:58,560 --> 00:46:03,480
nothing else.

681
00:46:03,540 --> 00:46:05,900
That moment stayed with me.

682
00:46:11,080 --> 00:46:14,910
I thought I'd feel guilty for being a murderer,

683
00:46:14,960 --> 00:46:19,580
but...I don't.

684
00:46:19,640 --> 00:46:21,970
I feel wonder.

685
00:46:43,590 --> 00:46:45,560
How long has this been going on?

686
00:46:48,000 --> 00:46:48,720
I don't know.

687
00:46:56,340 --> 00:46:58,240
And what is it that you're doing exactly?

688
00:46:59,020 --> 00:47:00,480
Encrypting all the files.

689
00:47:03,040 --> 00:47:05,150
All of Evil Corp's financial records

690
00:47:05,200 --> 00:47:07,000
will be impossible to access.

691
00:47:07,740 --> 00:47:09,400
The encryption key will self-delete

692
00:47:09,410 --> 00:47:11,120
after the process completes.

693
00:47:11,400 --> 00:47:12,320
What about the backups?

694
00:47:12,330 --> 00:47:13,420
I took care of that too.

695
00:47:14,640 --> 00:47:15,760
China. Steel Mountain.

696
00:47:17,340 --> 00:47:19,520
Of course, even when we went redundant.

697
00:47:19,530 --> 00:47:21,160
I hacked the Air Dream network.

698
00:47:22,120 --> 00:47:23,300
I was in all of them.

699
00:47:24,620 --> 00:47:26,060
You really thought of everything.

700
00:47:28,560 --> 00:47:29,740
Who else was involved?

701
00:47:32,880 --> 00:47:34,000
Just me.

702
00:47:38,300 --> 00:47:40,280
Well, now it's you and me.

703
00:47:41,720 --> 00:47:44,130
I've always told you we'd end up working together, Elliot.

704
00:47:48,250 --> 00:47:51,770
But still, I have to know.

705
00:47:52,850 --> 00:47:54,360
Why did you do it?

706
00:47:58,540 --> 00:48:01,470
What did you hope to accomplish by doing all of this?

707
00:48:07,240 --> 00:48:07,860
I don't know.

708
00:48:17,000 --> 00:48:18,480
I wanted to save the world.

