7
00:00:02,220 --> 00:00:04,140
Did you have something to do with Vera getting busted?

8
00:00:04,140 --> 00:00:05,400
Who told you to put your business

9
00:00:05,400 --> 00:00:07,150
anywhere near social media?

10
00:00:07,210 --> 00:00:09,550
My aspirational little brother.

11
00:00:10,110 --> 00:00:11,880
Someone's gonna get hurt for this.

12
00:00:12,030 --> 00:00:13,000
What happened to Angela?

13
00:00:13,000 --> 00:00:15,660
She's not going to work out for us, not on this level.

14
00:00:15,820 --> 00:00:17,480
You didn't have to stick up for me in there.

15
00:00:17,560 --> 00:00:18,540
Don't do it again.

16
00:00:18,600 --> 00:00:21,530
Evil corp tapped you for CTO, yes?

17
00:00:22,760 --> 00:00:23,550
You're ruining your life.

18
00:00:23,550 --> 00:00:25,220
I also ruined yours.

19
00:00:25,390 --> 00:00:28,120
Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of

20
00:00:28,200 --> 00:00:31,290
The Washington Township toxic waste scandal.

21
00:00:31,370 --> 00:00:31,950
Sharon?

22
00:00:32,010 --> 00:00:34,970
How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?

23
00:00:35,050 --> 00:00:36,220
I'm in here.

24
00:00:38,860 --> 00:00:40,670
Would you mind sleeping here tonight?

25
00:00:40,870 --> 00:00:42,600
That girl in there is mine.

26
00:00:42,650 --> 00:00:43,630
If you're around tonight,

27
00:00:43,680 --> 00:00:45,260
come over and tell me about it.

28
00:00:49,160 --> 00:00:50,020
Shayla?

29
00:00:50,590 --> 00:00:53,630
Sometimes the universe aligns perfectly.

30
00:00:53,870 --> 00:00:55,520
Here I am, locked away.

31
00:00:55,680 --> 00:00:58,060
Still, it brings you right to me.

32
00:01:07,380 --> 00:01:08,810
I feel the sensation.

33
00:01:09,020 --> 00:01:10,190
Fight or flight.

34
00:01:10,490 --> 00:01:11,710
It's constant.

35
00:01:12,890 --> 00:01:14,110
I should just pick one.

36
00:01:15,310 --> 00:01:18,490
I, Elliot Alderson, am flight.

37
00:01:19,200 --> 00:01:20,120
I am fear.

38
00:01:20,520 --> 00:01:23,720
I am anxiety, terror, panic.

39
00:01:41,480 --> 00:01:42,880
Doesn't feel real.

40
00:01:48,190 --> 00:01:49,040
You should eat.

41
00:01:51,290 --> 00:01:52,330
Not hungry.

42
00:01:52,430 --> 00:01:54,250
I don't know what I ordered.

43
00:01:57,640 --> 00:01:59,180
I'm sorry.

44
00:02:09,070 --> 00:02:10,600
You don't like the guisado?

45
00:02:11,130 --> 00:02:13,320
No, it's--it's good.

46
00:02:13,370 --> 00:02:14,440
Thank you.

47
00:02:27,110 --> 00:02:28,440
What are you thinking about?

48
00:02:31,500 --> 00:02:32,810
First time we met.

49
00:02:35,440 --> 00:02:37,080
Doesn't feel that long ago.

50
00:02:40,040 --> 00:02:41,600
Now look at us.

51
00:02:42,600 --> 00:02:43,840
Who would have thought?

52
00:02:47,630 --> 00:02:49,790
If I could go back and undo this--

53
00:02:49,840 --> 00:02:50,820
You can't.

54
00:02:53,980 --> 00:02:55,470
You promised me.

55
00:02:56,280 --> 00:02:58,240
I'm gonna get you out of this, okay?

56
00:02:58,300 --> 00:02:59,310
Time's up.

57
00:03:00,370 --> 00:03:01,210
Let's go.

58
00:03:01,260 --> 00:03:02,240
Elliot!

59
00:03:02,510 --> 00:03:04,520
Sit down. Sit down.

60
00:03:12,480 --> 00:03:13,320
Come with me.

61
00:03:15,370 --> 00:03:16,260
Let's go.

62
00:03:47,980 --> 00:03:49,890
- Hello? - The origin of your name.

63
00:03:49,980 --> 00:03:51,490
I looked it up for you, bruh.

64
00:03:51,550 --> 00:03:52,870
Where are you taking her?

65
00:03:53,640 --> 00:03:54,640
Elliot.

66
00:03:55,040 --> 00:03:57,480
"Brave and true."

67
00:03:58,170 --> 00:04:01,750
Did you know the origin of "Brave" Evolved from "Savage"?

68
00:04:01,820 --> 00:04:03,900
I don't know what you think this is about,

69
00:04:04,370 --> 00:04:05,960
but you need to let her go.

70
00:04:06,040 --> 00:04:07,310
You know, funny thing.

71
00:04:07,570 --> 00:04:09,510
My name means something similar.

72
00:04:09,570 --> 00:04:11,280
Brave traveler.

73
00:04:11,650 --> 00:04:12,830
Adventurer.

74
00:04:12,970 --> 00:04:16,470
Savage traveler becomes brave traveler.

75
00:04:16,700 --> 00:04:20,540
Are we savages, or are we brave?

76
00:04:21,280 --> 00:04:22,510
Don't know, bro.

77
00:04:22,590 --> 00:04:24,210
Listen to me, man.

78
00:04:26,380 --> 00:04:29,990
When I found out you did this, I didn't get angry.

79
00:04:30,150 --> 00:04:32,700
I got impressed.

80
00:04:32,920 --> 00:04:33,930
Your power.

81
00:04:34,640 --> 00:04:36,100
I want it, Elliot.

82
00:04:36,200 --> 00:04:38,480
And I want it so bad it makes my dick hard.

83
00:04:38,580 --> 00:04:39,930
And I want it today.

84
00:04:41,070 --> 00:04:42,250
I don't know what you think I can do.

85
00:04:42,400 --> 00:04:44,380
I can't just hack you out of prison.

86
00:04:45,140 --> 00:04:48,090
Not all prisons are networked, and even if yours is,

87
00:04:48,160 --> 00:04:50,800
it would take weeks to find security holes.

88
00:04:50,890 --> 00:04:51,970
Has to be tonight.

89
00:04:52,590 --> 00:04:54,480
I got crosshairs on my heart.

90
00:04:54,630 --> 00:04:55,710
I don't make it out,

91
00:04:55,910 --> 00:04:58,420
I'm dead, and that ain't meant to be just yet.

92
00:04:59,440 --> 00:05:00,820
You do your thing, bro.

93
00:05:01,240 --> 00:05:03,060
You're asking the impossible.

94
00:05:03,610 --> 00:05:07,380
When we cross paths tonight, Elliot, I'ma hug you.

95
00:05:08,390 --> 00:05:09,920
Please listen, man.

96
00:05:10,430 --> 00:05:13,070
Shayla--this is on me.

97
00:05:13,240 --> 00:05:14,130
Okay?

98
00:05:14,230 --> 00:05:15,650
You got to let her go.

99
00:05:16,120 --> 00:05:17,060
Oh, that?

100
00:05:17,400 --> 00:05:18,620
She cool, bro.

101
00:05:19,010 --> 00:05:20,540
Trust me, she cool.

102
00:05:20,910 --> 00:05:22,510
She'll be there tonight too.

103
00:05:23,020 --> 00:05:24,940
It'll be one big happy happy.

104
00:05:28,430 --> 00:05:29,350
Hey, Elliot.

105
00:05:30,550 --> 00:05:31,650
I love you, bro.

106
00:05:52,790 --> 00:05:53,780
Where's Shayla?

107
00:05:53,970 --> 00:05:55,100
Man, I'm not gonna tell you again.

108
00:05:55,200 --> 00:05:57,140
Stop asking so many questions.

109
00:05:58,930 --> 00:05:59,770
Come on.

110
00:06:04,990 --> 00:06:06,840
Vera may be out of his mind,

111
00:06:07,150 --> 00:06:10,440
but yes, it is possible to hack into a prison's network.

112
00:06:10,810 --> 00:06:13,770
Most of them use regular industrial control systems.

113
00:06:17,230 --> 00:06:19,640
I'm a blind man to what Vera sees in this dude.

114
00:06:19,710 --> 00:06:23,880
Amen. Techie computer hacker genius, my thick Dominican dick.

115
00:06:25,990 --> 00:06:27,340
When you have control of that,

116
00:06:28,000 --> 00:06:30,360
you basically have control of the cell doors.

117
00:06:33,150 --> 00:06:35,550
But what these morons don't know is,

118
00:06:35,930 --> 00:06:38,990
it's almost impossible without any research.

119
00:06:39,520 --> 00:06:41,560
Time to shine your cojones and get to work.

120
00:06:42,840 --> 00:06:44,030
Our only rule:

121
00:06:44,400 --> 00:06:46,340
do what we say.

122
00:06:46,430 --> 00:06:49,440
You violate that dictate, we kill your sweetheart.

123
00:06:50,070 --> 00:06:51,310
Yo, Isaac.

124
00:06:51,450 --> 00:06:52,770
How my dic-tate?

125
00:06:53,530 --> 00:06:54,650
Shut up, bitch.

126
00:06:56,160 --> 00:06:57,420
Dictate.

127
00:07:04,360 --> 00:07:05,920
Vera's bro, Isaac.

128
00:07:06,530 --> 00:07:08,220
Something about him bugs me,

129
00:07:08,770 --> 00:07:11,090
and you know what I like to do when that happens?

130
00:07:48,480 --> 00:07:51,000
Hi, I'm trying to reach Mr. Beckett.

131
00:07:52,620 --> 00:07:54,720
When would Mr. Lattimer be available?

132
00:07:54,780 --> 00:07:56,010
I can come in today.

133
00:07:56,160 --> 00:07:58,530
I already told you what it's in reference to.

134
00:07:59,590 --> 00:08:01,570
I'm trying again for Mrs. Nayar.

135
00:08:02,670 --> 00:08:05,200
Regarding the Washington Township Scandal.

136
00:08:05,290 --> 00:08:07,130
I may have found some information.

137
00:08:07,160 --> 00:08:08,750
Please don't put me on hold again.

138
00:08:23,260 --> 00:08:24,770
Happy Monday, Angela.

139
00:08:26,710 --> 00:08:27,970
How fun.

140
00:08:30,060 --> 00:08:31,220
Thanks.

141
00:09:13,520 --> 00:09:15,420
I'm Emily Moss's daughter.

142
00:09:16,320 --> 00:09:18,250
Angela Moss. I called--

143
00:09:18,320 --> 00:09:19,550
Six times.

144
00:09:20,190 --> 00:09:21,120
Yes.

145
00:09:21,220 --> 00:09:24,120
I'm here to discuss the Washington Township case.

146
00:09:27,880 --> 00:09:28,880
I'm listening.

147
00:09:31,270 --> 00:09:33,260
You represented the victim's families.

148
00:09:33,290 --> 00:09:35,390
26 families, mine included.

149
00:09:35,780 --> 00:09:38,000
I thought with the latest news in the data dumps--

150
00:09:38,090 --> 00:09:39,640
the Terry Colby scandal,

151
00:09:39,740 --> 00:09:41,570
his covering up the chemical waste spill.

152
00:09:41,680 --> 00:09:42,560
Alleged.

153
00:09:43,460 --> 00:09:45,430
Well, and documents.

154
00:09:45,500 --> 00:09:46,840
Superficial.

155
00:09:47,210 --> 00:09:50,840
But if we bring this stronger, more concrete case--

156
00:09:51,760 --> 00:09:54,170
You'll see that I have the evidence from the data dumps.

157
00:09:54,640 --> 00:09:56,240
Along with further research.

158
00:09:56,320 --> 00:09:57,520
Stickies.

159
00:09:57,660 --> 00:10:00,080
Oh, and you've highlighted and underlined.

160
00:10:00,720 --> 00:10:02,120
This is serious.

161
00:10:06,220 --> 00:10:10,300
So, you want to take internet gossip to federal court

162
00:10:10,380 --> 00:10:12,610
and throw it at the strongest conglomerate

163
00:10:12,700 --> 00:10:14,430
in the history of civilization?

164
00:10:27,390 --> 00:10:28,620
Guy in the suit.

165
00:10:30,070 --> 00:10:32,250
Twice convicted of sexual assault,

166
00:10:32,400 --> 00:10:34,170
charged again this past weekend.

167
00:10:34,350 --> 00:10:35,830
Raped his pregnant girlfriend.

168
00:10:35,900 --> 00:10:37,980
Bashed her head in with an xbox.

169
00:10:38,060 --> 00:10:39,960
Claims she cheated during Halo.

170
00:10:40,720 --> 00:10:43,340
Yet I have a better chance of defending him.

171
00:10:56,460 --> 00:10:57,480
You called back.

172
00:10:59,230 --> 00:11:01,240
I called every lawyer from this case,

173
00:11:01,340 --> 00:11:03,650
and you're the only one that called me back.

174
00:12:00,730 --> 00:12:02,630
Shit. Shit, shit.

175
00:12:08,390 --> 00:12:10,620
Connection closed by remote host.

176
00:12:10,680 --> 00:12:12,670
But we had a fish. I was in.

177
00:12:13,400 --> 00:12:16,970
The exploit started to run, and then--was it the code?

178
00:12:17,040 --> 00:12:18,330
Brah, what's the deal?

179
00:12:26,090 --> 00:12:27,520
I got to take her for a walk.

180
00:12:27,750 --> 00:12:28,460
Why?

181
00:12:29,500 --> 00:12:30,930
'Cause she'll piss on the floor if I don't.

182
00:12:30,930 --> 00:12:33,240
You think I give a shit about your goddamn floor?

183
00:12:41,820 --> 00:12:43,120
I'm just playing, brah.

184
00:12:43,530 --> 00:12:44,780
Yeah, you can take her.

185
00:12:48,130 --> 00:12:49,240
You hear what I said?

186
00:12:49,550 --> 00:12:50,800
I said you can take her.

187
00:13:02,050 --> 00:13:02,820
Come on.

188
00:13:15,640 --> 00:13:16,380
It's out.

189
00:13:16,380 --> 00:13:17,540
Okay, got you.

190
00:13:39,010 --> 00:13:40,640
Did she like my little toy?

191
00:13:42,110 --> 00:13:44,140
Did you write that exploit yourself?

192
00:13:45,560 --> 00:13:46,670
I had an hour.

193
00:13:46,940 --> 00:13:49,270
So what, you just pulled code from rapid nine or some shit?

194
00:13:49,360 --> 00:13:51,590
Since when did you become a script kiddie?

195
00:13:52,230 --> 00:13:54,320
I repeat, I had an hour.

196
00:13:55,130 --> 00:13:57,090
Malware detection must have caught it.

197
00:13:58,150 --> 00:13:59,340
You fucked me.

198
00:13:59,420 --> 00:14:00,800
Hey, don't put this on me, okay?

199
00:14:00,860 --> 00:14:02,180
This is a shit show

200
00:14:02,240 --> 00:14:04,310
and you gave me no time to do it right.

201
00:14:04,400 --> 00:14:07,230
I can run circles around an ics given the proper whitepapers and time.

202
00:14:10,220 --> 00:14:11,580
Where the hell are you going?

203
00:14:11,990 --> 00:14:14,120
I have no problem telling these two douchetools

204
00:14:14,170 --> 00:14:15,140
they're gonna have to sit on their pricks

205
00:14:15,230 --> 00:14:16,930
till we can find a better solution.

206
00:14:17,000 --> 00:14:18,710
You don't understand. These guys are--

207
00:14:18,810 --> 00:14:21,370
Assholes? Yeah, I'm gonna tell them what's up.

208
00:14:24,920 --> 00:14:26,080
That's what's up, girl.

209
00:14:27,970 --> 00:14:28,930
Now, let's go.

210
00:14:39,470 --> 00:14:42,550
So none of those guys called you back, not even lattimer?

211
00:14:43,010 --> 00:14:44,030
Pussies.

212
00:14:44,100 --> 00:14:46,440
I bet they didn't even bother to read the data dumps.

213
00:14:46,590 --> 00:14:47,610
But you read them.

214
00:14:49,160 --> 00:14:51,040
You know it took me eight years

215
00:14:51,130 --> 00:14:54,160
to rebuild my career after our case was dismissed?

216
00:14:54,720 --> 00:15:00,390
So, as much as I think this company is evil incarnate--

217
00:15:00,570 --> 00:15:01,980
and trust me, they are--

218
00:15:02,640 --> 00:15:04,400
you know, it's not worth it.

219
00:15:09,500 --> 00:15:10,940
What would it take,

220
00:15:12,350 --> 00:15:13,980
hypothetically...

221
00:15:15,050 --> 00:15:17,280
what do we need to prove our case?

222
00:15:17,340 --> 00:15:19,720
Hypothetically, a reliable eye witness.

223
00:15:20,040 --> 00:15:21,850
You know, if you miraculously find someone

224
00:15:21,920 --> 00:15:23,420
on the inside to flip.

225
00:15:23,760 --> 00:15:25,480
Someone who was there

226
00:15:25,560 --> 00:15:30,540
when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.

227
00:15:30,800 --> 00:15:31,930
So,

228
00:15:32,030 --> 00:15:36,060
unless you're facebook friends with one of those assholes,

229
00:15:36,470 --> 00:15:39,210
this hypothetical is just that.

230
00:15:42,320 --> 00:15:43,710
Let's move on.

231
00:15:44,320 --> 00:15:46,110
Where are you working these days?

232
00:15:47,000 --> 00:15:48,240
You have a boyfriend?

233
00:15:48,640 --> 00:15:49,840
How's your dad?

234
00:15:51,530 --> 00:15:54,690
I work for a company that doesn't respect me,

235
00:15:55,050 --> 00:15:57,560
my boyfriend recently cheated on me,

236
00:15:57,760 --> 00:16:02,020
and my father is drowning in debt.

237
00:16:09,130 --> 00:16:10,810
- I'll see you next time. - Okay.

238
00:16:18,320 --> 00:16:20,300
Fluorescent lights are hell, no?

239
00:16:23,690 --> 00:16:25,240
Was there a change in schedule?

240
00:16:25,440 --> 00:16:27,260
I thought I had Spencer next.

241
00:16:28,470 --> 00:16:32,010
These interviews, they're just a waste of your time.

242
00:16:32,110 --> 00:16:35,690
I mean, you know our regulatory and IP issues inside out.

243
00:16:36,300 --> 00:16:38,180
I was thinking we play hooky the rest of the day,

244
00:16:38,240 --> 00:16:39,510
hit the back nine.

245
00:16:44,000 --> 00:16:45,400
Is that a vacheron?

246
00:16:46,540 --> 00:16:47,940
Patek Philippe tourbillon.

247
00:16:48,030 --> 00:16:52,410
A gift from the prince of, uh...

248
00:16:55,530 --> 00:16:57,020
Oh, does it even matter?

249
00:17:03,370 --> 00:17:05,670
But I'm not blowing off my remaining interviews.

250
00:17:06,830 --> 00:17:07,790
Look.

251
00:17:09,770 --> 00:17:13,040
I know you think you were a shoo-in for CTO,

252
00:17:13,860 --> 00:17:15,310
And you're pissed.

253
00:17:16,710 --> 00:17:19,240
Probably wishing I'd fall into the subway tracks.

254
00:17:20,890 --> 00:17:23,150
So how about you cut the bullshit?

255
00:17:25,500 --> 00:17:28,410
I'm afraid your paranoia has gotten the best of you, but,

256
00:17:28,810 --> 00:17:30,590
nevertheless, please excuse me.

257
00:17:30,670 --> 00:17:32,090
I'll leave you to review your notes

258
00:17:32,200 --> 00:17:33,740
before Spencer arrives.

259
00:17:33,840 --> 00:17:36,110
Oh, and thank you for dinner.

260
00:17:38,690 --> 00:17:39,890
The entire evening was enchanting.

261
00:17:39,980 --> 00:17:42,840
The food, the wine, the lovely Sharon.

262
00:17:45,100 --> 00:17:46,700
Please tell her I say hello.

263
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:51,410
Did you enjoy the view?

264
00:17:56,130 --> 00:18:00,380
What, do you think she wouldn't tell me?

265
00:18:03,960 --> 00:18:05,690
I'm not sure what you're trying...

266
00:18:05,770 --> 00:18:07,390
You want to watch me piss too?

267
00:18:07,650 --> 00:18:09,320
I've had several glasses of water.

268
00:18:09,400 --> 00:18:10,380
Scott, a misunderstand--

269
00:18:10,480 --> 00:18:12,510
Happy to pull my dick out for you,

270
00:18:12,640 --> 00:18:13,710
if that's your thing,

271
00:18:13,990 --> 00:18:16,050
watching the Knowles family urinate.

272
00:18:16,650 --> 00:18:20,810
Hell, I could fly my brother in from Miami.

273
00:18:21,170 --> 00:18:23,260
He has the bladder of a small child.

274
00:18:23,610 --> 00:18:26,400
You'd probably bust a nut watching him take a leak.

275
00:18:26,990 --> 00:18:29,090
I'm not sure what she told you, but if I were you,

276
00:18:29,160 --> 00:18:31,240
I would tell her to find more appropriate ways

277
00:18:31,290 --> 00:18:33,290
of managing her imagination.

278
00:18:34,570 --> 00:18:35,580
Tyrell.

279
00:18:36,390 --> 00:18:37,930
I want you to accept a hard truth,

280
00:18:38,010 --> 00:18:40,490
right here, right now, in front of me.

281
00:18:41,690 --> 00:18:45,800
You are not going to be CTO.

282
00:18:48,410 --> 00:18:51,290
I want to see that look wash over your face.

283
00:18:52,560 --> 00:18:55,480
It's the only way I know you'll stop playing these

284
00:18:56,560 --> 00:18:58,750
silly, silly games.

285
00:19:00,720 --> 00:19:04,140
Oh, I am fully aware you're CTO, Scott.

286
00:19:04,890 --> 00:19:07,050
I'm not sure what more I can offer you.

287
00:19:10,040 --> 00:19:10,890
Wait.

288
00:19:12,620 --> 00:19:13,590
Here.

289
00:19:17,380 --> 00:19:18,100
I feel bad,

290
00:19:18,190 --> 00:19:20,470
after all, you got a child on the way.

291
00:19:20,560 --> 00:19:21,800
You need all the help you can get.

292
00:19:21,880 --> 00:19:22,720
In fact,

293
00:19:23,320 --> 00:19:26,090
this would probably pay off the rest of your mortgage.

294
00:19:27,070 --> 00:19:31,420
Aren't you still in that neat little two-bedroom in Chelsea?

295
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:36,290
There.

296
00:19:40,600 --> 00:19:42,630
That's the look I was looking for.

297
00:19:52,780 --> 00:19:55,530
I keep brute-force thinking, but it's not working.

298
00:19:57,720 --> 00:19:58,720
I need help.

299
00:20:12,700 --> 00:20:14,440
Elliot, you in there?

300
00:20:15,230 --> 00:20:16,210
Shit.

301
00:20:16,330 --> 00:20:17,460
Why is she here?

302
00:20:19,390 --> 00:20:20,650
Elliot!

303
00:20:23,200 --> 00:20:24,590
Let me in.

304
00:20:27,200 --> 00:20:28,940
Elliot, you in there?

305
00:20:31,220 --> 00:20:32,520
Little blonde bitty.

306
00:20:32,780 --> 00:20:35,470
Elliot, hit the buzzer.

307
00:20:37,660 --> 00:20:38,890
I know you're in there.

308
00:20:38,990 --> 00:20:39,930
Go.

309
00:20:40,270 --> 00:20:42,270
Shut her up, and get her the hell out of here.

310
00:20:42,380 --> 00:20:45,030
Elliot. Buzzer. Now.

311
00:20:45,780 --> 00:20:46,960
What about Darlene?

312
00:20:47,270 --> 00:20:50,160
She stays with us. And we'll be watching you,

313
00:20:50,400 --> 00:20:52,990
so don't bother trying any dumb shit, you dumb shit.

314
00:21:12,090 --> 00:21:13,800
Do you understand why you're angry?

315
00:21:15,640 --> 00:21:16,810
'Cause you know I'm right.

316
00:22:30,770 --> 00:22:33,180
I tried looking for you after Gideon's the other night.

317
00:22:33,290 --> 00:22:34,350
Where were you?

318
00:22:36,100 --> 00:22:38,510
I had to think about things, you know?

319
00:22:40,550 --> 00:22:43,840
We always knew what Evil Corp did.

320
00:22:45,030 --> 00:22:46,420
We didn't have the proof,

321
00:22:47,690 --> 00:22:48,810
but we knew.

322
00:22:50,960 --> 00:22:52,620
We were right about it all along.

323
00:22:52,620 --> 00:22:56,100
In fact, that news report wasn't a confirmation.

324
00:22:56,100 --> 00:23:00,560
It was a reminder of how angry I am.

325
00:23:04,760 --> 00:23:08,380
You remember Nayar, the lawyer on the case?

326
00:23:09,280 --> 00:23:11,470
I went to her, Elliot.

327
00:23:11,470 --> 00:23:12,580
Listen, Angela, now's not--

328
00:23:12,580 --> 00:23:14,800
I have an idea that will change the world.

329
00:23:17,830 --> 00:23:19,460
I know it sounds really stupid,

330
00:23:19,470 --> 00:23:23,990
but I know how to do it.

331
00:23:25,580 --> 00:23:27,560
I think it could actually work.

332
00:23:30,610 --> 00:23:32,140
I can't tell you what it is, because--

333
00:23:32,140 --> 00:23:33,730
Evil Corp, Angela, Vera,

334
00:23:33,730 --> 00:23:35,970
his brother, Darlene, Shayla.

335
00:23:36,060 --> 00:23:37,370
This is too much.

336
00:23:37,860 --> 00:23:39,840
I should just tell her what she wants to hear.

337
00:23:40,780 --> 00:23:41,720
Angela,

338
00:23:43,020 --> 00:23:44,410
trust yourself.

339
00:23:45,780 --> 00:23:46,970
You'll do what's right.

340
00:23:56,130 --> 00:23:57,340
That's all I needed.

341
00:23:59,300 --> 00:24:00,770
How's Shayla, by the way?

342
00:24:02,350 --> 00:24:03,390
She's...

343
00:24:05,850 --> 00:24:06,740
you know.

344
00:24:09,340 --> 00:24:10,720
Tell her I say hi.

345
00:24:22,810 --> 00:24:23,920
You have no time to pull off

346
00:24:23,920 --> 00:24:25,580
whatever it is you think you're doing.

347
00:24:25,580 --> 00:24:27,140
What are you doing here? How did you know?

348
00:24:27,140 --> 00:24:29,340
Darlene. These guys aren't playing around.

349
00:24:29,340 --> 00:24:31,860
They will fucking kill you. Now wise up, and let's go.

350
00:24:31,860 --> 00:24:34,140
Darlene's in there. We can't leave.

351
00:24:37,240 --> 00:24:39,480
Okay, then we call the cops.

352
00:24:39,480 --> 00:24:40,550
There's no other choice here.

353
00:24:40,550 --> 00:24:42,150
It's the only way out of this.

354
00:24:42,370 --> 00:24:43,500
I can't call the cops.

355
00:24:43,540 --> 00:24:44,450
Shayla will die.

356
00:24:44,450 --> 00:24:45,640
Oh, come on.

357
00:24:45,640 --> 00:24:47,460
She knew exactly what she was getting herself into.

358
00:24:47,460 --> 00:24:49,840
You think his employees have a long life expectancy?

359
00:24:49,840 --> 00:24:52,620
She was dead the minute she started working with that maniac.

360
00:24:52,680 --> 00:24:54,580
Forget it. It's not happening.

361
00:24:55,230 --> 00:24:57,000
This is a zero-sum game.

362
00:24:57,130 --> 00:24:58,800
Calculate all the outcomes.

363
00:24:59,100 --> 00:25:01,030
If you don't pull off this ridiculous miracle--

364
00:25:01,030 --> 00:25:03,420
and odds are, you won't-- you die, and so does Shayla.

365
00:25:03,420 --> 00:25:04,720
That much we know.

366
00:25:04,780 --> 00:25:05,660
But assume for a second

367
00:25:05,660 --> 00:25:08,140
that you do pull this off, bust Vera out of prison.

368
00:25:08,140 --> 00:25:10,820
Who's to say he doesn't kill you, Shayla, Darlene?

369
00:25:10,820 --> 00:25:13,160
It would be in his own best interest to do that.

370
00:25:13,250 --> 00:25:15,230
Either way, you all end up dead.

371
00:25:15,230 --> 00:25:17,050
It's the only way Vera wins.

372
00:25:17,340 --> 00:25:18,850
Zero-sum, Elliot.

373
00:25:19,030 --> 00:25:20,540
You're playing a game you already lost.

374
00:25:20,540 --> 00:25:22,000
You know I'm right.

375
00:25:22,510 --> 00:25:24,110
There's got to be a way.

376
00:25:25,120 --> 00:25:26,530
I can think of a way.

377
00:25:28,010 --> 00:25:29,170
I get it, kiddo.

378
00:25:29,740 --> 00:25:32,430
You want to help people. Watch over 'em.

379
00:25:33,200 --> 00:25:34,990
The best thing you can do for Shayla--

380
00:25:35,180 --> 00:25:37,460
allow her to become a memory.

381
00:25:38,980 --> 00:25:39,860
No.

382
00:25:42,110 --> 00:25:45,300
True courage is about being honest with yourself.

383
00:25:46,550 --> 00:25:48,360
Especially when it's difficult.

384
00:25:49,570 --> 00:25:52,880
There is no plan where both you and Shayla survive.

385
00:25:55,350 --> 00:25:56,840
I can think of a way.

386
00:25:57,380 --> 00:26:01,220
This new world that we are so close to creating will never be.

387
00:26:01,670 --> 00:26:03,240
And that new world, that is success.

388
00:26:03,240 --> 00:26:05,780
Fsociety is success.

389
00:26:05,880 --> 00:26:07,680
Look at what you accomplished at Steel Mountain.

390
00:26:07,740 --> 00:26:08,740
That got us nowhere.

391
00:26:08,780 --> 00:26:10,230
You took them down.

392
00:26:10,230 --> 00:26:12,340
You won that battle.

393
00:26:12,390 --> 00:26:14,400
This--this is failure.

394
00:26:15,850 --> 00:26:17,900
This is the old Elliot.

395
00:26:17,990 --> 00:26:21,530
The one who turns to morphine, to drugs when he feels weak.

396
00:26:21,530 --> 00:26:23,770
A coward who can't face the truth,

397
00:26:23,770 --> 00:26:26,400
even though it's staring him right in the face.

398
00:26:28,690 --> 00:26:30,540
There's that sensation again.

399
00:26:30,740 --> 00:26:31,780
Fight or flight.

400
00:26:32,470 --> 00:26:34,970
Three lives at stake, including my own.

401
00:26:35,650 --> 00:26:37,880
I, Elliot Alderson, am...

402
00:26:40,480 --> 00:26:41,340
what?

403
00:26:44,580 --> 00:26:47,860
Tom Petty, Pink Floyd, Van Halen?

404
00:26:48,130 --> 00:26:48,460
What's up, man?

405
00:26:48,460 --> 00:26:50,960
You ain't got no Drake, no Pitbull, no nothing?

406
00:26:50,960 --> 00:26:53,020
Like, what's up? What the--?

407
00:26:56,760 --> 00:26:58,140
What's up, rain man?

408
00:26:59,300 --> 00:27:00,930
I'm ready to bust Vera out.

409
00:27:01,690 --> 00:27:03,380
I can get into the network.

410
00:27:03,410 --> 00:27:04,920
We need to go to the jail.

411
00:27:05,040 --> 00:27:05,980
Now.

412
00:27:07,700 --> 00:27:09,020
She stays here.

413
00:27:09,270 --> 00:27:10,350
No, I'm not leaving you.

414
00:27:10,350 --> 00:27:11,390
Don't worry,

415
00:27:11,640 --> 00:27:14,040
He's in no position to be giving out orders.

416
00:27:16,720 --> 00:27:17,780
Let's go, girl.

417
00:27:20,460 --> 00:27:23,540
Remember when the panic would set in and we had a solution?

418
00:27:24,090 --> 00:27:25,760
To be honest, I miss that.

419
00:27:26,250 --> 00:27:28,370
Life is so much easier when you're numb.

420
00:27:31,270 --> 00:27:32,750
What's the plan, bitch boy?

421
00:27:35,600 --> 00:27:37,500
First Shayla, now Darlene.

422
00:27:38,660 --> 00:27:39,680
Yo, what the fuck?

423
00:27:39,720 --> 00:27:41,330
Elliot, what are you doing?

424
00:27:43,230 --> 00:27:45,660
Like a hard drive blasted by excessive voltage,

425
00:27:45,720 --> 00:27:46,880
my mind is frayed.

426
00:27:46,880 --> 00:27:48,180
Close to fried.

427
00:27:48,810 --> 00:27:51,280
I can feel the static running through my brain.

428
00:27:51,700 --> 00:27:54,120
Serotonin receptors working overtime.

429
00:27:54,170 --> 00:27:55,430
I need more time.

430
00:27:59,960 --> 00:28:02,540
Tonight, tonight, tonight.

431
00:28:02,540 --> 00:28:04,040
More time right now.

432
00:28:04,880 --> 00:28:06,800
I'm working on our project as we speak,

433
00:28:06,800 --> 00:28:10,010
so it's in your best interest to keep talking with me.

434
00:28:10,290 --> 00:28:11,210
At the security desk,

435
00:28:11,210 --> 00:28:12,510
my cell phone is running

436
00:28:12,510 --> 00:28:14,400
an undetectable activated signal sniffer

437
00:28:14,400 --> 00:28:17,630
that will locate any kind of wireless signal in sight.

438
00:28:18,060 --> 00:28:20,180
By the time I leave this building,

439
00:28:20,320 --> 00:28:21,960
I'll own its network.

440
00:28:23,350 --> 00:28:24,600
Good on you.

441
00:28:25,420 --> 00:28:28,480
Brave, but stupid.

442
00:28:30,750 --> 00:28:34,790
You showed your face, and then I skip out tonight.

443
00:28:34,870 --> 00:28:35,910
Who do you think they're gonna finger?

444
00:28:35,910 --> 00:28:37,750
I'm opening every cell.

445
00:28:37,920 --> 00:28:40,370
That way, they can't trace it back to you or me.

446
00:28:43,580 --> 00:28:44,750
Yeah, bro.

447
00:28:46,370 --> 00:28:48,060
That's what I'm talking about.

448
00:28:50,800 --> 00:28:52,340
I told you, didn't I?

449
00:28:52,620 --> 00:28:55,020
The universe got big plans for us, bro.

450
00:28:55,110 --> 00:28:56,840
Sit back down.

451
00:29:06,770 --> 00:29:09,290
When you get out, I realize you're gonna have to split.

452
00:29:09,290 --> 00:29:11,720
You won't be able to stay in the tri-state area.

453
00:29:12,750 --> 00:29:14,190
Oh, I love this.

454
00:29:14,200 --> 00:29:15,140
Go on.

455
00:29:15,450 --> 00:29:16,840
Wherever you go,

456
00:29:16,840 --> 00:29:18,860
you're gonna need funding to keep surviving.

457
00:29:18,870 --> 00:29:20,250
Which means your whole operation

458
00:29:20,250 --> 00:29:22,170
still needs to be making you money.

459
00:29:22,330 --> 00:29:24,300
Come on, Elliot. Give it to me.

460
00:29:24,470 --> 00:29:26,090
I hacked Isaac's phone.

461
00:29:28,970 --> 00:29:29,590
He had everything.

462
00:29:29,590 --> 00:29:32,350
Your crew, shipments, the entire operation.

463
00:29:32,350 --> 00:29:34,890
I took it all. I own your whole world.

464
00:29:41,770 --> 00:29:43,190
I need your word.

465
00:29:43,280 --> 00:29:46,170
When this goes down, Shayla and I go free.

466
00:29:46,490 --> 00:29:48,900
You leave us alone. Forever.

467
00:29:49,640 --> 00:29:51,030
If anyone tries to hurt us,

468
00:29:51,040 --> 00:29:55,520
if I even see one of your guys following me, I leak everything.

469
00:29:56,840 --> 00:29:57,760
You're saying this knowing--

470
00:29:57,760 --> 00:30:00,130
You can kill me anytime, yes.

471
00:30:01,370 --> 00:30:04,010
That's why I coded the leak to auto-send every 24 hours

472
00:30:04,010 --> 00:30:06,360
unless I continuously disable it.

473
00:30:07,040 --> 00:30:08,650
No one else has access.

474
00:30:09,000 --> 00:30:11,960
If anything happens to me or Shayla,

475
00:30:12,340 --> 00:30:14,580
your money gets deleted.

476
00:30:19,780 --> 00:30:21,170
Time's up, Vera, let's go.

477
00:30:27,870 --> 00:30:28,770
Remember.

478
00:30:30,500 --> 00:30:31,580
I'ma hug you.

479
00:30:58,050 --> 00:30:59,090
So what's your deal?

480
00:31:01,900 --> 00:31:03,570
I'm hear to see Terry Colby.

481
00:31:08,480 --> 00:31:10,370
Who is that, another damn reporter?

482
00:31:12,580 --> 00:31:14,280
No comment. Do you understand?

483
00:31:19,150 --> 00:31:20,240
Do I know you?

484
00:31:27,430 --> 00:31:28,770
Get the hell away from my home.

485
00:31:28,770 --> 00:31:30,320
Get away from my home.

486
00:31:38,080 --> 00:31:40,640
wpa2 wi-fi? Shit.

487
00:31:40,640 --> 00:31:42,310
Borderline unhackable.

488
00:31:42,570 --> 00:31:44,670
Getting that handshake could take days.

489
00:31:45,110 --> 00:31:46,560
The noose is tightening.

490
00:32:07,110 --> 00:32:09,060
The mobile feed on the cameras.

491
00:32:09,420 --> 00:32:13,000
I don't need to hack wpa2 when there's dedicated 4g.

492
00:32:26,320 --> 00:32:27,240
We're good.

493
00:32:28,110 --> 00:32:29,450
I can pull this off.

494
00:32:32,050 --> 00:32:33,140
- Get in. - Let's go, girl.

495
00:32:33,140 --> 00:32:34,360
Nah, just him.

496
00:32:36,230 --> 00:32:38,380
- Yo, Isaac, what you doing-- - Nah, bro, it's fine.

497
00:32:38,380 --> 00:32:40,380
I just want to have a private chat with him.

498
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:42,060
Come on, it's cool.

499
00:32:43,070 --> 00:32:44,250
We don't have any time, man.

500
00:32:44,260 --> 00:32:46,620
- I got to get to work. - Get the fuck in the car.

501
00:32:55,830 --> 00:32:57,110
Yo man, where you going, what you doing?

502
00:32:57,110 --> 00:32:58,750
All good, all good. Just gonna have a talk.

503
00:32:58,750 --> 00:32:59,800
Are you--?

504
00:33:13,720 --> 00:33:14,950
Why are you doing this?

505
00:33:14,950 --> 00:33:15,810
I can free your brother.

506
00:33:15,810 --> 00:33:17,020
I figured it out.

507
00:33:17,060 --> 00:33:18,760
It just wasn't your day, bruh.

508
00:33:19,060 --> 00:33:21,620
I hacked your whole operation. If you kill me--

509
00:33:21,620 --> 00:33:22,380
You don't get it.

510
00:33:22,380 --> 00:33:24,600
Like I said, it just wasn't your day.

511
00:33:28,980 --> 00:33:30,040
Stop.

512
00:33:37,000 --> 00:33:38,240
I suppose a bullet through

513
00:33:38,240 --> 00:33:40,100
the brain is peaceful in its own right.

514
00:33:47,820 --> 00:33:49,430
You don't want me to free Vera.

515
00:33:52,810 --> 00:33:54,520
That's why you don't care about the operation.

516
00:33:55,030 --> 00:33:56,340
I'd pick better last words.

517
00:33:57,330 --> 00:33:58,540
You're trying to kill him.

518
00:33:58,840 --> 00:34:00,760
That's why Vera wants to leave tonight.

519
00:34:01,780 --> 00:34:03,810
That's what's been bugging me about you.

520
00:34:04,290 --> 00:34:06,100
You never wanted me to break him out.

521
00:34:06,540 --> 00:34:08,710
Your best option for survival is to kill him in prison,

522
00:34:08,710 --> 00:34:10,020
because if you don't,

523
00:34:10,090 --> 00:34:11,150
you're dead.

524
00:34:12,780 --> 00:34:14,540
You're the reason Vera's locked up right now,

525
00:34:14,540 --> 00:34:15,660
and he knows it.

526
00:34:17,180 --> 00:34:18,360
Doesn't matter anyway.

527
00:34:19,050 --> 00:34:22,920
Vera was just gloating about how he got in with the right crew,

528
00:34:23,160 --> 00:34:25,100
how he got the jump on some men.

529
00:34:26,400 --> 00:34:27,520
He's not worried, man.

530
00:34:27,520 --> 00:34:28,980
He's protected now.

531
00:34:29,240 --> 00:34:30,390
Bullshit.

532
00:34:30,440 --> 00:34:32,690
That leaves you with a zero-sum game.

533
00:34:32,830 --> 00:34:33,960
If you don't get him out of jail,

534
00:34:34,020 --> 00:34:35,590
he'll have you killed for failing.

535
00:34:36,080 --> 00:34:37,660
Only way this works in your favor

536
00:34:37,660 --> 00:34:39,180
is for you to kill him first,

537
00:34:40,470 --> 00:34:42,560
and you can't do that with him inside anymore.

538
00:34:42,630 --> 00:34:43,930
Shut up, motherfucker.

539
00:34:43,930 --> 00:34:45,540
Shut the fuck up.

540
00:34:47,330 --> 00:34:48,420
Let me free him.

541
00:34:50,570 --> 00:34:52,420
When I break Vera out tonight,

542
00:34:53,290 --> 00:34:55,110
you do with your brother what you want.

543
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:57,400
That's the only outcome

544
00:34:57,400 --> 00:34:59,730
where you got the possibility of living.

545
00:35:02,810 --> 00:35:04,150
It's your best move.

546
00:35:05,570 --> 00:35:08,160
What makes you think I still won't kill you afterwards?

547
00:35:12,770 --> 00:35:13,850
I don't.

548
00:35:15,370 --> 00:35:17,150
I'm just playing my best move.

549
00:35:44,830 --> 00:35:46,950
I need 30 to 40 seconds with the patrol car's

550
00:35:46,950 --> 00:35:49,950
bluetooth connection to run the exploit on the plc.

551
00:35:50,760 --> 00:35:51,780
And then?

552
00:35:52,240 --> 00:35:54,440
The plan executes at 9:49.

553
00:35:56,080 --> 00:35:57,900
All the cell doors should open.

554
00:35:59,800 --> 00:36:02,320
Hey, I wanted to ask you about something.

555
00:36:03,090 --> 00:36:05,020
- Oh, yeah, what's that? - You.

556
00:36:32,810 --> 00:36:33,590
Give me a call.

557
00:36:33,600 --> 00:36:36,140
We'll grab a drink, talk, whatever.

558
00:36:36,180 --> 00:36:37,200
All right.

559
00:36:43,960 --> 00:36:45,430
The exploit's on his laptop.

560
00:36:52,570 --> 00:36:55,380
Now I need to force-feed it into the jail's network.

561
00:37:00,450 --> 00:37:01,790
I like what I hear.

562
00:37:07,190 --> 00:37:08,480
I paused the exploit.

563
00:37:08,980 --> 00:37:10,040
Drive.

564
00:37:10,680 --> 00:37:12,540
Darlene's no longer part of the plan.

565
00:37:13,280 --> 00:37:16,230
We got an alarm going off, east-side exit.

566
00:37:18,300 --> 00:37:19,660
What in the hell?

567
00:37:20,770 --> 00:37:21,870
Tell you what.

568
00:37:22,100 --> 00:37:24,430
We go out, we drink, we dance,

569
00:37:24,600 --> 00:37:25,960
see where the night takes us.

570
00:37:25,960 --> 00:37:28,090
You sure you want to make that choice right now?

571
00:37:28,610 --> 00:37:30,800
I only need to press one key to run the exploit.

572
00:37:30,800 --> 00:37:33,510
Or, I can press another and disable the entire plan.

573
00:37:33,510 --> 00:37:34,630
I made my move.

574
00:37:39,110 --> 00:37:40,240
You make yours.

575
00:37:47,920 --> 00:37:49,030
Shit.

576
00:37:49,190 --> 00:37:50,580
Please move back, miss.

577
00:37:50,710 --> 00:37:52,100
I got to get back asap.

578
00:37:52,280 --> 00:37:53,360
Whatever.

579
00:38:01,400 --> 00:38:04,050
Look, I got to come back now. My computer's on the fritz.

580
00:38:07,660 --> 00:38:09,050
Let's go to the meet, DJ.

581
00:38:09,440 --> 00:38:12,590
If I mis-typed one command, hit one wrong key,

582
00:38:12,590 --> 00:38:14,160
the cell doors won't open.

583
00:38:14,570 --> 00:38:16,520
And we both know what that means.

584
00:38:17,080 --> 00:38:18,220
Did I make a mistake?

585
00:38:18,760 --> 00:38:21,950
No, I don't make mistakes.

586
00:38:26,440 --> 00:38:28,060
One minute till Vera.

587
00:38:28,830 --> 00:38:31,480
For all his insane, inhumane ideas,

588
00:38:31,480 --> 00:38:33,520
he does understand the world.

589
00:38:34,310 --> 00:38:36,610
The wild savagery of the world.

590
00:38:44,070 --> 00:38:45,600
What you need your piece for, bro?

591
00:38:46,260 --> 00:38:48,570
Boy wonder says he's opening all the cells.

592
00:38:48,620 --> 00:38:50,110
If some fool tries to rush us,

593
00:38:52,060 --> 00:38:53,240
I want to be ready.

594
00:39:11,970 --> 00:39:13,280
Hey, what the shit?

595
00:39:13,840 --> 00:39:15,020
Power surge caused by all

596
00:39:15,020 --> 00:39:16,910
the cell doors opening at the same time.

597
00:39:16,910 --> 00:39:18,790
What about security? Sirens?

598
00:39:18,830 --> 00:39:21,550
The jail's network will show all cells locked and closed.

599
00:39:21,890 --> 00:39:23,760
Alarms are silent for two minutes.

600
00:40:02,670 --> 00:40:04,900
Yes. Yes.

601
00:40:05,010 --> 00:40:06,210
This shit right here,

602
00:40:06,840 --> 00:40:09,360
this shit tastes better than any pussy I ever had.

603
00:40:26,680 --> 00:40:28,370
DJ, shoot the cocksucker.

604
00:40:43,520 --> 00:40:44,720
My own brother.

605
00:40:46,580 --> 00:40:48,460
That's what the universe asked of me.

606
00:40:50,390 --> 00:40:51,760
To be my brother's keeper.

607
00:40:53,430 --> 00:40:55,110
Like Cain after Abel,

608
00:40:55,310 --> 00:40:57,740
I'll be a fugitive and wanderer on the earth.

609
00:40:59,360 --> 00:41:00,860
Brave fugitive.

610
00:41:03,560 --> 00:41:04,880
Brave wanderer.

611
00:41:06,570 --> 00:41:07,820
Look how you helped me.

612
00:41:09,490 --> 00:41:11,800
That's the kind of bravery I've been talking about.

613
00:41:12,420 --> 00:41:13,640
But now...

614
00:41:15,850 --> 00:41:17,720
Now I want you to look at Isaac.

615
00:41:19,880 --> 00:41:21,020
Look.

616
00:41:28,510 --> 00:41:29,570
Dead proof.

617
00:41:29,920 --> 00:41:31,710
My operation is over.

618
00:41:31,880 --> 00:41:33,570
So go on, crash it.

619
00:41:33,570 --> 00:41:34,780
Burn it to the ground.

620
00:41:35,150 --> 00:41:36,110
Doesn't matter.

621
00:41:37,720 --> 00:41:38,820
I'm gone.

622
00:41:40,910 --> 00:41:41,960
A spirit.

623
00:41:42,890 --> 00:41:44,370
One with all the heavens.

624
00:41:45,640 --> 00:41:46,740
All existence.

625
00:41:52,290 --> 00:41:53,400
Shayla.

626
00:41:55,070 --> 00:41:56,080
Where is she?

627
00:41:57,950 --> 00:41:59,030
Keys, yo.

628
00:42:00,990 --> 00:42:03,100
Told you you'd get her back, bro.

629
00:42:05,150 --> 00:42:06,550
You just didn't realize

630
00:42:07,190 --> 00:42:08,960
she was with you the whole time.

