[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 职员,MingLiU,16,&H00E8E8E8,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.5,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 标题,汉仪双线体简,40,&H001C1DB6,&H0021218D,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.1,7,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效标记,微软雅黑,13,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:01:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\an8\fad(500,500)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HE28609&\3a&HDC&\pos(189.24,0.4)}本字幕由{\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯制作，僅供學習，禁止用于任何商業盈利行為。若因私自散布傳播造成法律問題，本字幕組概不負責。更多影視請搜索并關注新浪微博{\c&H00FFFF&}@大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}。
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)}{\fsp5}{\clip(6.6,216,11.4,232.8)\t(\clip(5.4,206.4,114,232.8))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\t(2000,4000,\frx720)\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fs16\pos(42.6,225.6)}{\fsp5}{\clip(5.4,206.4,112.2,234.4)\t(\clip(104.4,210.4,112.2,234.4))\c&H00FFFF&}大家字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.50,0:00:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs40\c&H240FA0&\b1\pos(194.04,57.68)}機器人先生 前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.50,0:00:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H25119F&\b1\pos(263.28,234.686)}大家字幕組 傾情譯制
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.00,0:00:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    墳老絲  Libear
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.00,0:00:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    墳老絲  Libear
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.00,0:00:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}翻譯    子虛烏有  兔八哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.00,0:00:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}翻譯    子虛烏有  兔八哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}校對    Libear  鑫鑫美少女  Xz
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.00,0:00:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}校對    Libear  鑫鑫美少女  Xz
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.00,0:00:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}時間軸    嵬森  我在馬路邊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}時間軸    嵬森  我在馬路邊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.00,0:00:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}壓制    晟晟
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.00,0:00:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}壓制    晟晟
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.00,0:00:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,0)\move(10,11,10,8,0,300)}監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.00,0:00:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,300)\move(10,8,10,5,1700,2000)}監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森  坑坑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.20,0:06:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs80\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(197.04,48.88)}機器人先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.20,0:06:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs25\c&H0900A7&\b1\pos(202.32,203.6)}第一季  第七集
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.56,0:10:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(180.8,120.70)}禁閉時間:Kevi未經審訊就被美國政府關押了這么長時間
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.56,0:10:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(182.4,102.4)}3年，4個月，9天，10小時，42分
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(162.24,151.68)}我隆鼻了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.91,0:11:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(163.44,157.44)}我隆鼻了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.91,0:11:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(84.267,143.289)}戀足者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.83,0:11:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(298.971,191.543)}我假裝愛我丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.71,0:11:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(293.52,191.68)}我假裝愛我丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.71,0:11:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(182.88,230.08)}我暴飲暴食
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.45,0:11:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(122.64,177.28)}性恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.79,0:11:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(93.867,200.533)}性恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.71,0:11:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(50.667,203.022)}性恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.55,0:11:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(220.8,148.978)}我偷竊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.54,0:11:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(195.3,193.2)}我偷竊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.34,0:11:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(318.171,239.543)}我討厭我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.67,0:11:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(96.9,223.2)}我內心空虛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.22,0:13:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(194.7,45.6)\frz17.95}藝術家:
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.60,0:13:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\frz27.56\pos(199.2,177.6)}專輯:
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.25,0:25:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs19\pos(72,64)\frz355.3}赫斯特圖書館
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.30,0:25:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\i1\frz15.94\pos(66.24,172.8)}絕壁植入
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.54,0:31:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\c&H08ECF4&}穩住
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.31,0:00:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 有什么發現?\N{\fs14}So, what do we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.61,0:00:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰利 科爾比參與了對\N{\fs14}Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.12,0:00:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,華盛頓區有毒廢棄物丑聞的掩埋\N{\fs14}Washington Township toxic waste scandal.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.85,0:00:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要些什么證據?\N{\fs14}What do we need to prove our case?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個當時在決定制造關于\N{\fs14}Someone who was there
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.79,0:00:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化學廢棄物的假消息的時候 在現場的人\N{\fs14}when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.54,0:00:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我滾遠點\N{\fs14}Get the hell away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.92,0:00:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滾遠點\N{\fs14}Get away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.11,0:00:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特 你到底怎么了\N{\fs14}Elliot, what is going on with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.23,0:00:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不告訴我我沒辦法幫你\N{\fs14}I cannot help you if you keep me in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.88,0:00:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出問題了\N{\fs14}We got problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.31,0:00:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗軍團放鴿子了\N{\fs14}The Dark Army is bailing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.18,0:00:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事兒沒完\N{\fs14}It's not over.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.28,0:00:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚不行 我們還會找到其它辦法的\N{\fs14}We'll find a way, just not tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.38,0:00:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和這種人結婚你不覺得腦疼嗎?\N{\fs14}How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.17,0:00:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是也想看我發火(尿)?\N{\fs14}You want to watch me piss too?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯考特 這中間有誤會--\N{\fs14}Scott, a misunderstand--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.94,0:00:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了你我很樂意把我的老二掏出來\N{\fs14}Happy to pull my dick out for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.82,0:00:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特!\N{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.04,0:00:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪?\N{\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.87,0:00:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了會把她還給你的 兄弟\N{\fs14}Told you you'd get her back, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.99,0:01:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操!\N{\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.11,0:02:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臥槽!\N{\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.56,0:02:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開門!\N{\fs14}Open up!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.35,0:02:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在走廊血流成河了!\N{\fs14}I'm bleeding all over the hallway!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生死攸關!\N{\fs14}It's a life-or-death situation out here!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.42,0:02:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 我知道你在里面 我看見你剛進去\N{\fs14}Look, I know you're in there. I just saw you go in.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.45,0:02:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快開門!\N{\fs14}Open up!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找--\N{\fs14}I'm lo--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.60,0:02:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 你就傻傻地站那嗎?\N{\fs14}Well, are you just gonna stand there?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.84,0:02:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我倒杯水 傻瓜\N{\fs14}Get me a glass of water, dummy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.49,0:02:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能接點水嗎? 謝謝\N{\fs14}Can I use this? Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.31,0:02:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這條魚是我侄女給我的\N{\fs14}My niece gave him to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.14,0:02:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天 我還沒給他取名字呢\N{\fs14}I haven't even named him yet. God.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.25,0:02:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能體會到一個六歲熊孩子帶來的壓力?\N{\fs14}Do you know the pressure of an ecstatic six-year-old?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.20,0:02:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說 如果那家伙死了的話 她的整個世界都會崩潰\N{\fs14}I mean, I kill that thing, and her whole world collapses.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡你這個房間的布置\N{\fs14}I like what you did with the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.15,0:02:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 挺不錯的 不過還是更喜歡我的\N{\fs14}Yeah, nice setup. Still like mine better though.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.94,0:03:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 想要高檔貨就跟我說\N{\fs14}Yo, let me know if you want a top-shelf hookup.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.49,0:03:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 正好你在...\N{\fs14}Actually, now that I have you...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.84,0:03:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能幫我搬一下衣柜嗎...肌肉男?\N{\fs14}Will you help me move a dresser...Mr. Muscles?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.67,0:03:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 來 來吧\N{\fs14}Okay, come on. Just come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.00,0:03:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,車里男搬家公司現在太真格了\N{\fs14}Man 'n' van is getting way too legit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.27,0:03:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些家伙以前就是些 鼓手什么的\N{\fs14}They used to just be, like, drummers
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.57,0:03:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開著他們老娘的本田奧德賽面包車\N{\fs14}with their mom's Honda Odysseys.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.99,0:03:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在居然是皇后區的一家真的公司\N{\fs14}Now it's an actual company in Queens.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.52,0:03:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些人還真是面包車里的男人呀\N{\fs14}I mean, the guys are literally men in vans.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.81,0:03:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以從你那買嗎啡\N{\fs14}I'd buy morphine from you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.31,0:03:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是你要給我弄到賽寶松\N{\fs14}if you could also get me suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.64,0:03:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個 呃 要弄到賽寶松幾乎不可能\N{\fs14}Well, um, it's pretty much impossible to get suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.58,0:03:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的供貨商沒有\N{\fs14}My supplier doesn't have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.46,0:04:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看過一首歌的現場表演 簡直太激動了\N{\fs14}I saw this song live once. It was so rad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.47,0:04:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直太愛現場聽喜歡的歌\N{\fs14}Don't you just love hearing your favorite songs in person,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.93,0:04:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種 震耳欲聾\N{\fs14}like, half deaf from the speakers,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.47,0:04:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,群情鼎沸的感覺 你不喜歡嗎?\N{\fs14}everyone going nuts around you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.49,0:04:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不喜歡\N{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.27,0:04:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話很直 我敬佩這樣的人\N{\fs14}Direct. I respect that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.49,0:04:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是討厭演唱會\N{\fs14}I just hate concerts.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.94,0:04:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太多人\N{\fs14}Lots of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.35,0:04:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不喜歡別人 是吧?\N{\fs14}You don't like people, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.91,0:04:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分吧 不喜歡\N{\fs14}Not most of them, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.94,0:04:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.37,0:04:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 按這個理論\N{\fs14}Well, so by that rationale,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.38,0:04:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你真的喜歡上一個人 那就 像是\N{\fs14}if you were to really like one person, it'd be, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.54,0:04:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一種失常或者是一種異常行為\N{\fs14}considered an aberration or an abnormality
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至可以說是 腦殘了\N{\fs14}or special, even.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.55,0:04:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以這么說吧\N{\fs14}I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.68,0:04:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實 我就向往腦殘呢\N{\fs14}Well, I aim for special,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.70,0:04:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱倆比比吧\N{\fs14}so challenge accepted.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們早一點認識就好了\N{\fs14}I wish we already knew each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.59,0:05:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就不這么尷尬\N{\fs14}Would make this feel less awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.78,0:05:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在真的覺得尷尬嗎?\N{\fs14}You really feel awkward right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.64,0:05:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點\N{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.27,0:05:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 那我也希望我們早點認識呢\N{\fs14}Well, then I wish we knew each other too then.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.15,0:05:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去\N{\fs14}Oh, yikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.48,0:05:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 呃 我遲到了 約了閨蜜去喝東西\N{\fs14}I, um, I'm late. Meeting the girls for drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.31,0:05:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 對了 我叫夏拉\N{\fs14}Oh, um, I'm Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.26,0:05:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫伊利艾特\N{\fs14}Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.62,0:05:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 我倒是認識一個人有賽寶松賣\N{\fs14}You know, I do know of a guy who sells Suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.07,0:05:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據說他是個瘋子\N{\fs14}He's supposed to be a fucking psychopath,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.25,0:05:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果你需要的話 我可以給他打電話\N{\fs14}but if you want, I can call him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.28,0:05:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了你和瘋子打交道可能也是值得的\N{\fs14}You might be worth a psychopath.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.80,0:05:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道 可能吧\N{\fs14}I don't know. Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.40,0:06:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 魚就交給你了 小家伙\N{\fs14}Oh, and keep the fish, you filthy animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.44,0:06:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 一段時間沒跟你說話了\N{\fs14}Sorry I haven't talked to you in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.27,0:06:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說 才一個月\N{\fs14}I mean, it's only been a month, which I guess
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.79,0:06:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在宏偉藍圖中可能不顯得太長\N{\fs14}in the grand scheme of things isn't that long.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.85,0:06:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的生命在宇宙的歷史中\N{\fs14}Isn't our life like a blip
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.27,0:06:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就像一個光點一樣嗎?\N{\fs14}in the cosmic calender or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.45,0:06:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏拉也是\N{\fs14}So that's Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.21,0:06:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅僅是一個光點\N{\fs14}A blip.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.92,0:06:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能都算不上\N{\fs14}Not even.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.65,0:06:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一秒還在 下一秒就閃沒了\N{\fs14}Here one blip, gone the next.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.10,0:06:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我狠自己的是 我已經習慣了\N{\fs14}Makes me hate myself that I've already gotten used to
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.49,0:06:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已離去的感覺\N{\fs14}the idea of her not being here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.43,0:06:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年之后 我可能會想想她\N{\fs14}In a year, I'll maybe think about her
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.38,0:06:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是偶爾\N{\fs14}every once in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.15,0:07:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過后她就成了一件軼事 僅僅是一個談資\N{\fs14}Then she'll become an anecdote, a thing to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.85,0:07:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我認識一個已經去世的女孩"\N{\fs14}"I knew a girl that died,"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.15,0:07:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還附帶福利 "她是因我而死"\N{\fs14}with the added bonus of, "She died because of me."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.07,0:07:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我是該恨我自己\N{\fs14}Maybe I should hate myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.25,0:07:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是最后兩張表\N{\fs14}Here are the last two forms.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要趕我走了\N{\fs14}She's getting rid of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.24,0:07:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬一你還沒想到的話\N{\fs14}in case you're still trying to figure that out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.46,0:07:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 一旦我... - 在最下面簽字\N{\fs14}- Once I... - Sign on the bottom.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.13,0:07:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我把這文件送去法庭\N{\fs14}Then I'll deliver it to the court,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.13,0:07:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在兩周內 你會收到\N{\fs14}and in two weeks' time, you'll receive
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.65,0:07:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,官方的正式取消強制治療指令通知\N{\fs14}an official release from the mandate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.27,0:07:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二份表格說明我們已經在這里面談長達一年之久了\N{\fs14}That second form means that we've been sitting in this room for a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.10,0:07:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有長達52個小時的克里斯塔的嘮叨聲在這個房間里回蕩\N{\fs14}Over 52 hours of Krista's voice bouncing around this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.19,0:07:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她認為她這是在白費力氣 也許還真是\N{\fs14}She thinks she's a wasted echo. Maybe she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.03,0:07:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想 我花了多少時間\N{\fs14}I wonder how much time I've spent
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.62,0:07:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在這里 不聽她嘮叨\N{\fs14}not listening to her in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.71,0:07:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很擔心你 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}I'm worried about you, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.76,0:07:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很希望你能繼續過來\N{\fs14}I really want you to keep coming here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.17,0:07:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還有很多事要完成\N{\fs14}We've got a lot more work to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.69,0:07:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她對我還有要求\N{\fs14}She wants more from me
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.00,0:07:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她又不信任我\N{\fs14}but she doesn't believe in me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.66,0:07:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我努力嘗試是因為我相信在你心里的某一部分\N{\fs14}I tried because I believe some part inside of you
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.92,0:07:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是想好好做事的\N{\fs14}wants to do this right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.12,0:07:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢?\N{\fs14}You?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你同意她的話么?\N{\fs14}Are you on her side?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.31,0:08:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的電源插口得清理清理了\N{\fs14}You should clean your sockets.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.48,0:08:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽上去像是童話 但我還是會相信\N{\fs14}Sounds too good to be true, but I'll bite.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.06,0:08:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們想要什么?\N{\fs14}What's the ask?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.64,0:08:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我們的委托人有著\N{\fs14}Given my client has information
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.06,0:08:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能幫助你的委托人的案子的信息\N{\fs14}that could help your client's case,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.16,0:08:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要求這個會議只有她 科爾比 以及我出席\N{\fs14}we want the meeting restricted to her, Colby, and myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.44,0:08:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且是秘密會議 不得記錄\N{\fs14}And we want it conducted off-record.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.71,0:08:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安塔拉 拜托\N{\fs14}Antara, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.48,0:08:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的委托人不會同意你出席\N{\fs14}My client won't accept your presence.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.17,0:08:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的委托人花錢讓我們出席呢\N{\fs14}Our client pays for ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.70,0:08:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就有責任來代表他\N{\fs14}Then you're duty-bound to present him
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.42,0:09:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為我們的有利證據做出合法開價\N{\fs14}with any legitimate offer of beneficial evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.37,0:09:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然\N{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.88,0:09:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我們一些真正合法和有利的\N{\fs14}Give us something truly legitimate and beneficial.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.33,0:09:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你都不肯說 你的委托人手里究竟有什么證據\N{\fs14}You won't even tell us what the hell your client has.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.01,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賽斯 我們已經在談判桌上\N{\fs14}Seth, we've been sitting on opposite sides
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.98,0:09:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面對面談了二十多年了\N{\fs14}of the negotiating table for two decades.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.55,0:09:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是啥逗逼\N{\fs14}I'm not some joker come out of the woodwork
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想從科爾比那兒撈一票\N{\fs14}trying to scam Colby for millions.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.94,0:09:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在給他唯一的希望一些曙光\N{\fs14}I'm giving him the only glimmer of hope he's had.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.10,0:09:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會轉達你的提議的 謝謝\N{\fs14}We'll pass along your offer. Thanks for your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.96,0:09:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅伊德說你想見我\N{\fs14}Lloyd said you wanted to see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.33,0:09:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 我很感謝你如此敬業\N{\fs14}Look, I appreciate your commitment to this job.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:09:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的\N{\fs14}I really do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.30,0:10:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想看到你如此艱難得\N{\fs14}But I don't see how you've plowed through
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過著這幾周 所以\N{\fs14}these last few weeks, so
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.67,0:10:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想給你放幾天假\N{\fs14}I want to offer you some time off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.56,0:10:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 讓你能... - 我不需要放假\N{\fs14}- Just some time to... - I don't need time off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.11,0:10:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事\N{\fs14}I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.48,0:10:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯... 嗯 還有一件事\N{\fs14}Uh...Uh, one more thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.63,0:10:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對她的離去我很遺憾 伊利艾特\N{\fs14}I'm so sorry she was taken away, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.42,0:10:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是別因為她的離去而完全封閉起來自己\N{\fs14}but don't let her death close you off entirely.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.89,0:10:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找個能敞開心扉聊一聊的人\N{\fs14}Find someone you can be your honest self with,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.57,0:10:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎?\N{\fs14}okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.50,0:10:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得我小時候 我是因為抄襲我喜歡的網站\N{\fs14}I remember when I was a kid, I got into web design
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.77,0:10:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才喜歡上網頁設計的\N{\fs14}by ripping off sites I liked.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.16,0:10:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要在你的瀏覽器上點擊 查看源代碼\N{\fs14}All you had to do was view source on your browser
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.27,0:10:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就能看到那些代碼了\N{\fs14}and there it was, the code.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.93,0:10:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以復制粘貼一下 改點小地方\N{\fs14}You could copy-paste it, modify it a little,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.12,0:10:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寫上你的大名 就這樣 這就是你的網頁了\N{\fs14}Put your name on it, and like that, it was your site.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查看源代碼\N{\fs14}View source.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.81,0:11:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是每個人都有代碼會是怎么樣呢?\N{\fs14}What if we had that for people?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.13,0:11:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人們會不會真的想看到呢?\N{\fs14}Would people really want to see?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.99,0:11:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找個能敞開心扉聊一聊的人?\N{\fs14}Find someone to be your honest self with?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.76,0:11:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直狗屁\N{\fs14}Bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯的建議 謝啦\N{\fs14}Really good advice. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.60,0:11:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原句是 "美國黑客組織 F社會\N{\fs14}I quote, "The U.S. contingent of the hacker group fsociety
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.37,0:11:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在世界最大的跨國企業\N{\fs14}has remained quiet since the upheaval inflicted
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.09,0:11:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的動蕩之后 一直沒有動靜\N{\fs14}upon the world's largest multinational conglomerate.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.67,0:11:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國土安全部部長 杰 約翰遜\N{\fs14}Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.14,0:11:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天發表聲明說\N{\fs14}released a statement today stating that,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.15,0:11:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,'這些團體若是想發起有效攻擊\N{\fs14}'these groups lack the resources and knowledge
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.11,0:11:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還缺少很多資源和智力呢'"\N{\fs14}of the U.S. cell to successfully mount an attack.'"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.42,0:11:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引用結束\N{\fs14}End quote.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.39,0:11:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 所以呢?\N{\fs14}Yeah, so?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.80,0:11:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得把黑暗軍團找回來\N{\fs14}We gotta get the Dark Army back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.42,0:12:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 我一直都在嘗試\N{\fs14}Dude, I've been trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得要我去攻擊他多少次?\N{\fs14}How many times do you want me to hack him?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.39,0:12:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道要黑一個黑客是多難么?\N{\fs14}Do you know how hard hacking a hacker is?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.89,0:12:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思科總是換他們的操作系統啊\N{\fs14}Cisco switches OSes, like, all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.03,0:12:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴琳 我們得開個會\N{\fs14}Darlene, we need one meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.06,0:12:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我一直在用思科的口徑\N{\fs14}Yeah, well, I've been using Cisco's handle
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.48,0:12:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來發送請求 發了一個月了\N{\fs14}to send requests for the past month.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥都沒有\N{\fs14}I got nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.57,0:12:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是比我笨 但是沒笨到哪里去\N{\fs14}He's slower than me, but not by much.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.32,0:12:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們能和白玫瑰直接對話...\N{\fs14}If we can talk to WhiteRose directly...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.02,0:12:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白玫瑰? 白玫瑰?\N{\fs14}WhiteRose? WhiteRose?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說笑呢?\N{\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.48,0:12:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 假設--假設這個人真的存在\N{\fs14}Okay, if--if the guy even exists,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.22,0:12:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是個特大號的"假設"\N{\fs14}and that's a big if,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.94,0:12:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也不可能和你見面的啊\N{\fs14}no way he's meeting you face-to-face.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.94,0:12:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也可以說...\N{\fs14}For all we know...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.39,0:12:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個家伙就是白玫瑰\N{\fs14}This dude's WhiteRose.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.26,0:12:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了!\N{\fs14}Excuse me!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.35,0:12:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是白玫瑰嗎?\N{\fs14}Are you WhiteRose?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.28,0:12:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣\N{\fs14}A likely story.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.74,0:12:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何況 那些備份盤已經寄去\N{\fs14}'sides, the tape backups already shipped
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:13:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些新的鐵山設施了\N{\fs14}to all the new Steel Mountain facilities,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.74,0:13:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我們還沒找到其他方法\N{\fs14}and we still haven't found a way around that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經想好了一個計劃\N{\fs14}I got a plan in motion.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.64,0:13:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爺都笑了\N{\fs14}And god's laughing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.37,0:13:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩下這些東西是有關她的了\N{\fs14}This is all I have left of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.90,0:13:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會想念她的\N{\fs14}I will miss her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.21,0:13:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得再清理一次了\N{\fs14}I need to wipe again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.49,0:14:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你翻到下一頁\N{\fs14}So if you scroll to the next page,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.29,0:14:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能看到采購和運營的\N{\fs14}you'll see the summary of capital budgets
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.17,0:14:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,資本預算總結\N{\fs14}for purchasing and operations.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了 周一會出來一份\N{\fs14}We get it. The goddamn earning reports
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.90,0:14:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去很不錯的收益報表\N{\fs14}are gonna look good come monday.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.75,0:14:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的目標是推進賬單支付\N{\fs14}Our aim is to facilitate bill payment
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.54,0:14:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提高金融安全\N{\fs14}and heighten financial security,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.20,0:14:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有額外的2%\N{\fs14}so that's an extra 2%.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.10,0:14:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎 要是我們的收益并沒有好轉\N{\fs14}You know, if we hadn't turned our profits around,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.63,0:14:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我就走人了 - 少騙人\N{\fs14}- I was gonna leave. - No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.10,0:14:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪兒? 別跟我說去蘋果\N{\fs14}Where? Don't tell me apple.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谷歌 - 才不信\N{\fs14}- Google. - Don't buy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.18,0:14:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在谷歌總部的排球場上\N{\fs14}I got a blow job from the hiring executive
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.14,0:14:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人力資源部的主管給我來了個口活\N{\fs14}on the Googleplex volleyball court.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.50,0:14:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 她很火辣 有瑪麗莎 梅耶爾的風范\N{\fs14}Oh, she was hot. Had a Marissa Mayer thing going on, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.88,0:14:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火辣的主管都是從火辣的助理做起的\N{\fs14}Hot execs started as hot assistants
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.43,0:14:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路陪睡到頂峰\N{\fs14}who fucked their way to the top
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.17,0:14:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我們這些人 升職速度快兩倍\N{\fs14}twice as fast as the rest of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.15,0:14:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些破爛事你知道嗎?\N{\fs14}You know something screwed up?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.32,0:14:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說有些助理為了爬上去\N{\fs14}I heard that, some assistants, they're going gay
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.66,0:15:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假裝是基佬\N{\fs14}to move up the ladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.64,0:15:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告訴你件更離奇的吧\N{\fs14}I'll do you one better.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.77,0:15:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么一小撮可悲的\N{\fs14}There's a special handful
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.49,0:15:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤注一擲的主管也在做雞雞騎手\N{\fs14}of pathetically desperate execs going cock jockey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.79,0:15:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 天了嚕!\N{\fs14}No. Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.51,0:15:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 德懷特 我想問問 你的孩子怎么樣了?\N{\fs14}Hey, Dwight, I meant to ask. How are your children?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.16,0:15:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼知道 送去勞倫斯中學了\N{\fs14}Hell if I know. Sent 'em off to Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.55,0:15:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似茱莉亞喜歡藝術\N{\fs14}I think Julia likes art.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.56,0:15:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 不可能面面俱到的嘛\N{\fs14}Oh, well. Can't win 'em all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.76,0:15:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勞倫斯中學?\N{\fs14}Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.43,0:15:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你要是失業了\N{\fs14}You'll never be able
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.26,0:15:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定就付不起學費了咯\N{\fs14}to afford that tuition on unemployment.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.57,0:15:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 抱歉? - 你被炒了!\N{\fs14}- Sorry? - You're fired!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.04,0:15:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個也是\N{\fs14}You two as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.15,0:15:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會確保你們都能收到最低遣散費的\N{\fs14}I'm making sure you all receive the minimum severance packages.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.59,0:15:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威力克先生 我不明白\N{\fs14}Mr. Wellick, I-I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.49,0:15:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做錯什么了?\N{\fs14}What did we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.83,0:16:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥都沒\N{\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.40,0:16:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 之后... - 你說有新消息會告訴我\N{\fs14}- After... - You said you would update me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.31,0:16:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把我們的情況\N{\fs14}I needed to discuss our situation
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.97,0:16:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和州檢察官討論討論\N{\fs14}with the state's attorney.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.16,0:16:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你過來 羅伊\N{\fs14}Thanks for coming in, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.11,0:16:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐下吧\N{\fs14}I think you should have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.45,0:16:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科爾比的律師30分鐘前打來電話\N{\fs14}Colby's lawyers called 30 minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.53,0:16:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想要我們保證 他在開會前享有豁免權\N{\fs14}They wanted a promise of total immunity before the meeting,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從剛才你見到的這個男人那里拿到這個豁免權了\N{\fs14}which I obtained from the man you just met.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.92,0:16:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 是的 科爾比同意了...\N{\fs14}So, yes, Colby agreed...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.99,0:16:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有附加條件\N{\fs14}with a caveat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.28,0:16:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能參加會議 你要一個人進去\N{\fs14}I can't be in the room. You have to go in alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.48,0:16:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 你這么做是很有膽量\N{\fs14}Look, you made a ballsy move...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.02,0:17:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要是真那么做了\N{\fs14}But you doing what you're about to do...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.45,0:17:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進到一個非常有權力的男人的家里\N{\fs14}entering the home of a very powerful man
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.73,0:17:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒著很大的風險 還要向他索取...\N{\fs14}with a lot at stake and asking him for something...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.46,0:17:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么樣都是件危險的事\N{\fs14}That's always a dangerous proposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.39,0:17:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我再問最后一次...\N{\fs14}So one last time...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.86,0:17:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確定你想這么做嗎?\N{\fs14}Are you sure you want to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.13,0:17:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去\N{\fs14}Shit, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.67,0:17:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為你是個那些偷了\N{\fs14}Thought you was one of them high schoolers
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.18,0:17:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我媽的躺椅的高中生呢\N{\fs14}stole my mom's chaise lounge.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.64,0:17:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉告訴你\N{\fs14}As heartbreaking as it is to hear that,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得延期了\N{\fs14}you're gonna have to put that off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把大家都聚集起來\N{\fs14}Getting everybody back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 拜托 - 這次不行\N{\fs14}- Come on. - No, man, not this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.66,0:17:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不干了\N{\fs14}I'm out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.22,0:17:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能不干 我們需要你\N{\fs14}You can't be out. We need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.28,0:17:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 有一批新的人指望著我呢\N{\fs14}Look, man, I got a new set of people depending on me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.46,0:17:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成堆的客戶\N{\fs14}Clients out the wazoo.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.63,0:17:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 只能祝你好運了\N{\fs14}So, you know, I mean, good luck,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我跟其他人打聲招呼\N{\fs14}and tell the kids I said hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.54,0:18:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什么? 你在這里干嘛呢?\N{\fs14}What is this? What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.40,0:18:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞清楚了怎么把\N{\fs14}Well, I figured out how to insert
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四氫大麻酚的基因信息編碼注入酵母細胞\N{\fs14}THC's genetic information code into yeast cells.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.30,0:18:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賺錢速度翻三番\N{\fs14}Tripled my earning speed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.97,0:18:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,植物需要幾周才能長好 微生物只要幾天\N{\fs14}Plants need weeks to develop. Microbes need days.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.45,0:18:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你現在是在自家后院\N{\fs14}So, what, you got a bath and body works
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.69,0:18:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞起美體用品的裝瓶設備了?\N{\fs14}bottling facility in your backyard?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.96,0:18:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你試試\N{\fs14}Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.81,0:18:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混合物里的四氫大麻酚值靠近邊界值\N{\fs14}The THC level is borderline in that blend,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.25,0:18:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰衣草也不會影響致幻效果\N{\fs14}and the lavender doesn't mess with the high.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要涂在皮膚上\N{\fs14}You just smooth it on your skin.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.33,0:18:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是為了芳香物 放棄了一場革命?\N{\fs14}So you're rejecting a revolution in favor of aroma profiles?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.75,0:18:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是大材小用\N{\fs14}What a waste of potential.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.51,0:18:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽我說 我知道我腦子好使\N{\fs14}Look, man, I know I got a good brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.88,0:18:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且...\N{\fs14}Besides...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.83,0:18:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們這個小項目最后又是什么結果呢?\N{\fs14}What was our little project in the end, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.18,0:18:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我說的話 就是臭狗屎\N{\fs14}Wasted shit, if you ask me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.61,0:18:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 現在你基本上把我給激怒了\N{\fs14}Well, now you're borderline pissing me off.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.03,0:18:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是事實嗎?\N{\fs14}Is that a fact?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.81,0:18:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我決定把你給激怒\N{\fs14}And what exactly are you gonna do
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.39,0:18:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟會做出什么舉動?\N{\fs14}if I decide to cross that border?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.34,0:18:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅梅羅 看著我\N{\fs14}Look at my face, Romero.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.83,0:19:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都知道我是瘋子\N{\fs14}You and I both know I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.20,0:19:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且不是可愛的那種\N{\fs14}Not the cute kind either.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.87,0:19:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的是有病的瘋子!\N{\fs14}I'm talking crazy crazy!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.33,0:19:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你玩失聯\N{\fs14}You lost touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.00,0:19:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘記了為贏得戰斗\N{\fs14}You forgot the feeling of spilling blood
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.52,0:19:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在戰場上灑熱血的感覺\N{\fs14}on the battlefield by winning the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.86,0:19:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本不想傷害你的 羅梅羅\N{\fs14}I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.24,0:19:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是愛你的\N{\fs14}I love you, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.27,0:19:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想你跟我回到游樂場\N{\fs14}I just wanted you to come back to the arcade with me
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.30,0:19:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣我們就能一起改變世界\N{\fs14}so we could change the world together.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.95,0:19:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很顯然你不能對我這個瘋子說不\N{\fs14}I am clearly too crazy for you to say no to.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.42,0:19:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這表情真是千金難買!\N{\fs14}Look on your face is priceless!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.40,0:19:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你個瘋子\N{\fs14}Goddamn lunatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.10,0:19:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們開始行動的時候 你向我保證過\N{\fs14}You gave me your word when we started this thing
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.95,0:19:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會堅持到最后\N{\fs14}that you'd finish it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.06,0:19:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也向你保證 不管你做不做得到 我一定可以\N{\fs14}I gave you my word what I'd do if you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.33,0:19:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回頭游樂場見\N{\fs14}See you back at the arcade.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.88,0:20:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 姑娘把茶給你泡好了\N{\fs14}Good. I see the girl got you tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.82,0:20:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我們開始吧\N{\fs14}Well, let's get started.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要多少?\N{\fs14}How much do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.74,0:20:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,報個價\N{\fs14}Write your number.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.07,0:20:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想問我什么請隨意\N{\fs14}You can ask me anything you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.66,0:20:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我可以打包票 一切到了最后\N{\fs14}but I promise you, at the end of the day,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.82,0:20:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你要尋找什么答案 其魅力也不會超過金錢\N{\fs14}money will always be better than what you're looking for.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.51,0:20:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科爾比先生 1993年\N{\fs14}Mr. Colby, did you attend
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.86,0:20:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,董事會你出席了嗎?\N{\fs14}the executive board meetings during 1993?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.22,0:21:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會上決定 對華盛頓鎮有毒廢料的處理方案\N{\fs14}Were you in the room when the decision was made
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.09,0:21:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不給予任何處理 當時\N{\fs14}to ignore the treatment of hazardous waste
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.25,0:21:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在場嗎?\N{\fs14}in Washington Township?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.98,0:21:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一些對你有利的信息 回答我的問題\N{\fs14}I have information which can help you...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.71,0:21:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以告訴你\N{\fs14}if you answer my question.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.62,0:21:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你在說什么\N{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,針對你的指控有問題 作為證據的數據鏈有漏洞\N{\fs14}If you agree to testify against the executives
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.67,0:21:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你肯作證 指認與會的高管們\N{\fs14}who covered up the illegal dumping of expoxy resin waste,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.12,0:21:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試圖掩蓋非法傾倒環氧樹脂廢物這一事實\N{\fs14}I will testify that I broke chain of custody
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.22,0:21:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就可以幫你洗刷罪名\N{\fs14}with the dat file central to your case.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.28,0:21:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是那個一個月前\N{\fs14}You're that hot little thing
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.33,0:21:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來過的小辣妹嗎\N{\fs14}that came by here a month ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.43,0:21:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個萬安公司的姑娘\N{\fs14}The girl from Allsafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.55,0:21:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記起來了\N{\fs14}I remember, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.74,0:22:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 讓我來回答你的問題\N{\fs14}Okay...I'm gonna answer your question.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.27,0:22:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但首先 我要你做一件事\N{\fs14}But here's what I need from you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.62,0:22:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把褲子脫下來\N{\fs14}So I'm gonna pull down my pants,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.50,0:22:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把你那撅起來的小嘴湊過來\N{\fs14}and then I'm gonna need you to take that pouty mouth of yours
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.63,0:22:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吞下我的蛋蛋\N{\fs14}and swallow up my balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.88,0:22:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們又大 毛又多 尤其是左邊那顆\N{\fs14}Now, they're big and hairy, especially the left one,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.28,0:22:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你還是得想辦法\N{\fs14}so you're really gonna have to, I don't know,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.52,0:22:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它們吞下去\N{\fs14}squish 'em up to get 'em inside there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.86,0:22:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是一個腮幫子塞一個也得咽\N{\fs14}You're probably gonna have to do one cheek at a time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.66,0:22:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等它們在你嘴里含的又暖又舒服了\N{\fs14}But then, once they're all warm and snug in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.59,0:22:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再把你的問題 清清楚楚得和我\N{\fs14}I want you to repeat your question to me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.86,0:22:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,復述一遍\N{\fs14}as clearly as you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.03,0:22:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上從實招來\N{\fs14}Then, and only then, am I willing to answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.34,0:22:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看如何\N{\fs14}What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不和我合作\N{\fs14}If you don't take this deal...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.14,0:23:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也會變得和我一樣\N{\fs14}you'll become like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.92,0:23:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然 你還是有大房子住\N{\fs14}Sure, maybe you'll live in this house...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.56,0:23:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰包也大概也沒憋多少\N{\fs14}Maybe you'll have money,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.38,0:23:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就算你花重金請的律師能幫你逃脫罪名\N{\fs14}but even if your expensive lawyers find a way to get you off,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.89,0:23:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,群眾的眼睛還是雪亮的\N{\fs14}people will still think that you're guilty.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.40,0:23:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人會再尊重你\N{\fs14}Losing everyone's respect...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.31,0:23:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括你認識和不認識的\N{\fs14}the respect of people you know and the people you don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.33,0:23:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這感覺很糟糕\N{\fs14}It's a shitty feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.06,0:23:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fs14}Trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.40,0:24:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那姑娘在 不用送了\N{\fs14}I'll have "the girl" let me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.00,0:24:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鰭鰭 她身上帶微芯片嗎?\N{\fs14}Flipper. Is she microchipped?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.50,0:24:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 很好\N{\fs14}Okay, very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.35,0:24:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例行檢查做完了\N{\fs14}Housekeeping done.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.72,0:24:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在切入正題\N{\fs14}Now onto the real business.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.98,0:24:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的狗以前吃過垃圾嗎？\N{\fs14}Has your dog ever eaten trash before?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.11,0:24:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 至少我不記得她有過\N{\fs14}No. I mean, not that I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.13,0:24:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為你的銀行賬號感到慶幸的是\N{\fs14}Well, lucky for your bank account,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.77,0:24:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她吃下去的東西不大 能自己排泄出來\N{\fs14}The piece is small enough to pass on its own.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.52,0:24:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 說小也不小\N{\fs14}Unfortunately, though, it's large enough
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.27,0:24:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓她在你的公寓里到處嘔吐\N{\fs14}to send her puking all over your apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.56,0:25:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把她留在這兒 觀察幾天\N{\fs14}So I would crate her for a few days and monitor her.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.44,0:25:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你對她出于好心 她反正是不會知道的\N{\fs14}She won't know what you're doing is good for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.40,0:25:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說得對 我只不過是想證明...\N{\fs14}You were right. I was only trying to prove--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.05,0:25:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科爾比的律師剛才打來電話了 他同意開口了\N{\fs14}Colby's lawyers just called. He wants to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.91,0:25:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去趟他家\N{\fs14}Get back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.18,0:25:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大清早就出來發癡可不好\N{\fs14}It's a little early in the morning to be nerding out,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.88,0:25:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不覺得嗎\N{\fs14}don't you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.82,0:25:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多久了\N{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.04,0:25:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道如果我問你...\N{\fs14}I knew if I asked you that--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.99,0:25:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多久了\N{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.51,0:25:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾個禮拜\N{\fs14}Couple weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.67,0:26:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你膽子還真大 用我作突破口去和WhiteRose聯系?\N{\fs14}And you had the balls to ask for WhiteRose with my shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.24,0:26:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想我們兩個都被做掉嗎\N{\fs14}It's like you want to get us both killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.24,0:26:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 他回復了?\N{\fs14}What happened? He responded?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.82,0:26:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fs14}You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.26,0:26:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真不該弄得我在他們面前抬不起頭\N{\fs14}you didn't have to make me look like a shitty foot soldier.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.19,0:26:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人會問的...\N{\fs14}Nobody would ever even know--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.37,0:26:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你入侵我的電腦 找到了我們的IP地址\N{\fs14}You got root on my box and found the IP,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.58,0:26:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后通過我的資源加入他們的討論組\N{\fs14}then you joined their channel with my handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.67,0:26:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們情分已盡\N{\fs14}We're so done.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.39,0:26:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不想看到你了\N{\fs14}I don't want to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.73,0:26:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過你們這幫傻瓜心想事成了\N{\fs14}But you fools actually got your wish.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.83,0:26:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知為何\N{\fs14}I don't know why,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.34,0:26:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你們要的這次會面他居然同意了\N{\fs14}but the meeting's actually gonna be on.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.78,0:26:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告訴你 小心點\N{\fs14}I'd tell you to be careful,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.90,0:26:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道你不可能聽得進去\N{\fs14}but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.90,0:27:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的律師們正在看你帶來的文件\N{\fs14}My lawyers are looking over the paperwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.90,0:27:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你的意思是  - 就像我說過的\N{\fs14}- Does that mean that-- - exactly what I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.55,0:27:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你回來是為了確保你確實能在法庭上幫到我\N{\fs14}I asked you back here to make sure that you can pull off your testimony,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.69,0:27:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并檢驗你說的那個監管問題的消息確實屬實\N{\fs14}make sure that this chain of custody, story of yours is straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.86,0:27:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想被你陰到\N{\fs14}I can't afford any trips.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.11,0:27:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會陰你的\N{\fs14}I'm not going to trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.78,0:27:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事\N{\fs14}So, what--
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.95,0:27:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底對你有什么好處?\N{\fs14}What's in this for you, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.86,0:27:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你恨我\N{\fs14}I know you hate me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.83,0:27:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你卻打算幫我逃脫懲罰?\N{\fs14}So, what, you're gonna just let me off scot-free?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.28,0:27:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能得到什么回報?\N{\fs14}What do you get out of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.57,0:27:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前我問了你一個問題\N{\fs14}Earlier, I asked you a question.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.08,0:27:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒回答\N{\fs14}You never answered it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.27,0:27:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我同意幫你作證 那么\N{\fs14}If I'm agreeing to testify in your case, then,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.12,0:28:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我確實去過幾次會議\N{\fs14}yes, you know, I attended several meetings.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.27,0:28:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我講講他們決定忽略泄露的那次會議吧\N{\fs14}Tell me about the one when they decided to ignore the leak.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.41,0:28:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我--我不確定你想問什么\N{\fs14}I'm--I'm not sure what you're asking.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.27,0:28:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在決定的時候 是幅什么場景?\N{\fs14}What was the meeting like when you decided this?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.82,0:28:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了\N{\fs14}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.29,0:28:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道 當時是怎么樣的場景?\N{\fs14}You want to know, like, what was it like?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.29,0:28:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 我們是不是都一邊抽著雪茄 一邊瘋笑著\N{\fs14}Like, um, did we all have cigars and laugh hysterically
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.32,0:28:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簽了那個邪惡的文件?\N{\fs14}as we signed the evil documents?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.62,0:28:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你腦海里是這個畫面么?\N{\fs14}Is that what you pictured?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.39,0:28:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那抱歉你想錯了 甜心\N{\fs14}Well, I'm sorry, hon.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.49,0:28:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道 這世界不是你想的那樣\N{\fs14}See, the world doesn't work like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.31,0:28:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你告訴我 告訴我是怎么樣的\N{\fs14}Tell me. Tell me how it works.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.77,0:28:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊... 好吧 好吧\N{\fs14}Uh, Jesus, um...All right, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.38,0:28:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想 93年的一月\N{\fs14}Let's see. January, '93.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.40,0:28:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時我的秘書是伊萊恩\N{\fs14}Well, my secretary then was Elaine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.09,0:28:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時伊萊恩在晚餐上給我們點了\N{\fs14}So Elaine brought us a platter of shrimp cocktail
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.50,0:28:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一盤雞尾酒蝦 這把我們氣壞了\N{\fs14}to tide us to dinner, which pissed us off
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.72,0:29:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們剛剛在節日趴上吃了這玩意兒\N{\fs14}because we just had a platter at the holiday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.18,0:29:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆讓我們開懷暢飲\N{\fs14}Jim opened the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.46,0:29:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他現在可真是個人才\N{\fs14}Now Jim was a real piece of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.18,0:29:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說 他有時娘炮有時屌\N{\fs14}I mean, half pansy, half Mafia.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.66,0:29:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦遇到艱難抉擇的時刻 他就各種抽煙\N{\fs14}First sign of a tight decision, he'd be chain smoking
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.94,0:29:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各種喝酒\N{\fs14}down a river of Scotch.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.20,0:29:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 那天還下雨了\N{\fs14}You know, it rained.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.79,0:29:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天下雨了 我記得的 對\N{\fs14}It rained. I remember that, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.89,0:29:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...\N{\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.27,0:29:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們喝得爛醉 吃著雞尾蝦\N{\fs14}You were drunk, eating shrimp cockail,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.90,0:29:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后當時還下著雨 你們就決定讓我媽去死了么?\N{\fs14}and it was raining when you decided my mother would die?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.65,0:29:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來就是了\N{\fs14}That's why.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.86,0:29:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以像你這樣的人就不會總是在高處掌權\N{\fs14}So people like you won't keep sitting in rooms together.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.27,0:30:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在做這些個決定的時候\N{\fs14}Did any of it ever give you or anyone pause
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.94,0:30:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有過一點點的遲疑嗎?\N{\fs14}when you made those decisions?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.29,0:30:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有\N{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.48,0:30:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有 當然有\N{\fs14}Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.68,0:30:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...\N{\fs14}But, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.79,0:30:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就各回各家了 然后呢 吃個飯\N{\fs14}then you go home, and, uh, and you have dinner,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.27,0:30:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧 然后--然后第二天早上還是照樣醒來\N{\fs14}you know, and--and you wake up the next morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.61,0:30:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們敬這個有著光明前途的同事一杯\N{\fs14}Here's to a man who has a bright future at our company,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.18,0:30:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個你們都認識的人\N{\fs14}a man you all know,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.53,0:30:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個能帶我們公司走向成功的人\N{\fs14}a man who is going to change this company for the good,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.33,0:30:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個能與一位和他同樣聰明的女人結婚的人...\N{\fs14}a man smart enough to marry a woman every bit his equal...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.87,0:31:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的新任首席技術官 斯考特 諾斯\N{\fs14}Our new Chief Technology Officer, Scott Knowles.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.79,0:31:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 沒錯!\N{\fs14}Here, here!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.60,0:31:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 謝謝\N{\fs14}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.28,0:31:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 謝謝 菲利普 - 不客氣\N{\fs14}- Thank you, Phillip. - Welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.85,0:31:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 非常感謝 - 開始了\N{\fs14}- Thank you very much. - Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.02,0:31:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興能在這里 這里沒事了\N{\fs14}It's great to be here. And we're off.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.97,0:31:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 謝謝 菲利普 - 小事小事\N{\fs14}- Thanks, Phillip. - You're very welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.55,0:31:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 恭喜啊 親愛的 - 謝謝 謝謝\N{\fs14}- Congratulations, darling. - Thank you, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.72,0:31:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 喬 你好嗎?\N{\fs14}Hey, Joe, how are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.35,0:31:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝\N{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.90,0:31:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提瑞爾 很高興見到你\N{\fs14}Tyrell, nice to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.23,0:31:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?\N{\fs14}Is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.48,0:31:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說你跟你丈夫說了我們的事\N{\fs14}I hear you shared our moment with your husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.10,0:31:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 拜托 都過去一個月了\N{\fs14}Oh, come on. That was over a month ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.20,0:31:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別告訴我你現在腰還酸著呢\N{\fs14}Don't tell me you're still sore.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.18,0:32:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 我看出了一縷憂傷\N{\fs14}Hmm, I sense some defeat.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.56,0:32:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實 至少 我覺得我自己受到了譴責\N{\fs14}Well, I considered myself, at the very least, reprimanded.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.59,0:32:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真叫人失望\N{\fs14}How disappointing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.24,0:32:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點兒小挫折你就放棄了\N{\fs14}One tiny curveball and you gave up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.79,0:32:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士\N{\fs14}Miss.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.94,0:32:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝\N{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.32,0:32:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就該知道你虎頭蛇尾\N{\fs14}Should have known that you were nothing more than a bold entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.58,0:32:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說 你一點兒都不渴望那種"虎頭"的感覺嗎\N{\fs14}Are you saying you don't crave a bold entrance
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.95,0:32:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次又一次 堅持不懈么?\N{\fs14}every time, over and over, sustained?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.36,0:32:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上見一面吧\N{\fs14}Meet me tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.45,0:32:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有點忙啊\N{\fs14}I'm a little busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.16,0:32:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就去我的辦公室\N{\fs14}Come to my office now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.54,0:32:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說真的么?\N{\fs14}Are you really asking me that?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.16,0:32:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是在問你 是在命令你\N{\fs14}I don't recall phrasing it as a question, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.52,0:32:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊 那我就不出現就好了\N{\fs14}Fine, then I just won't show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.53,0:32:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去房頂\N{\fs14}Then the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.63,0:32:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從后邊的樓梯上去\N{\fs14}Take the back stairwell.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.04,0:32:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的監控三月份就壞了\N{\fs14}The cameras have been out since March.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.23,0:32:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人會知道的\N{\fs14}No one will know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.47,0:33:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把復雜的事弄得更復雜了\N{\fs14}Well, you just made a long day longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.99,0:33:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道萬安公司很快就得把我開除了\N{\fs14}I know that Allsafe will have to fire me,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.74,0:33:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是出庭作證是個正確的選擇\N{\fs14}but testifying was the right thing to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.61,0:33:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老子花了很大的力氣來照顧你\N{\fs14}I have worked my ass off to take care of you
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.48,0:33:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也照顧這個公司每一個人\N{\fs14}and of every person in this company.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.09,0:33:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道這意味著什么嗎?\N{\fs14}Do you know what that means?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.25,0:33:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直是個很棒的老板 吉迪恩--\N{\fs14}You've been a great boss, Gideon--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.61,0:33:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 一旦這份供詞被公布\N{\fs14}See, once this confession goes public,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.34,0:33:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不會有人想和我們合作了\N{\fs14}no one will want to do business with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.27,0:33:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公司就垮了\N{\fs14}The company will go under.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.93,0:33:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能讓科爾比\N{\fs14}I couldn't let Colby take the fall
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.90,0:33:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 為我的過失埋單 - 哦拜托!\N{\fs14}- for something that I did. - Oh, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.83,0:33:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都知道 你沒有在監管上做錯什么\N{\fs14}You and I both know you didn't break chain of custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.73,0:33:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有做錯 而且我感覺很糟糕--\N{\fs14}I did and I feel terrible--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.80,0:33:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉! 求你了! 別撒謊了\N{\fs14}Angela! Please! Stop lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.46,0:33:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是這么做... 這里所有的人就都完了\N{\fs14}You do this... All these people go down,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.02,0:33:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們的家庭\N{\fs14}all their families
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.20,0:33:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們需要這個公司所帶給他們的一切\N{\fs14}that rely on what this company provides for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.16,0:34:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 原來那條小樓梯能通到這兒啊?\N{\fs14}So this is where the rabbit hole leads?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.74,0:34:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說真的\N{\fs14}Got to be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.41,0:34:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你出現的可能性也就一半\N{\fs14}I half-expected you not to show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.77,0:34:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還覺得你有一半兒可能去打小報告呢\N{\fs14}And I half-expected you to be a tattletale.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.60,0:34:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你是累了\N{\fs14}So you are sore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.30,0:34:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不是吧 你迷住我了\N{\fs14}Oh, come on. You intrigued me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.01,0:34:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也得迷回來\N{\fs14}I intrigued back.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.52,0:34:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱們就不能直接一點嗎?\N{\fs14}Can't we just be more straightforward?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.65,0:34:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那可不好玩啊 但既然你堅持的話\N{\fs14}Oh, that's no fun, but if you insist,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.87,0:34:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是上樓看看看你是不是真的\N{\fs14}I just came up here to see if you were really
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.62,0:34:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像看上去那樣容易上當\N{\fs14}as gullible as you seem.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.61,0:34:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫在樓下爭取著你要的那個位置\N{\fs14}My husband's downstairs getting the job that you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.95,0:34:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你卻在想方設法勾引我\N{\fs14}and you're up here trying to fuck me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.99,0:34:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你這么做是純粹出于欲望還是在釣我上鉤\N{\fs14}Now whether that's you being straightforward or a game,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.32,0:34:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都沒能提起我的興趣\N{\fs14}either way, it's played pretty poorly, if you ask me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.61,0:34:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有問過你什么問題嗎\N{\fs14}Again, I asked no question.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.09,0:34:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這么做是因為我看出來\N{\fs14}All I can tell you is you need this
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.48,0:34:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欲求不滿 想滿足你\N{\fs14}'cause you're dissatisfied.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.26,0:35:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯考特要解雇你\N{\fs14}Scott plans on firing you,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.37,0:35:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在已經走投無路 狗急跳墻了\N{\fs14}and you are clinging on t了o any chance you can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.39,0:35:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去真絕望\N{\fs14}You seem desperate.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.39,0:36:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么 放開我\N{\fs14}What do you-- get off of me!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.78,0:36:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下\N{\fs14}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.33,0:38:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們和WhiteRose接過頭了\N{\fs14}We connected with WhiteRose.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.49,0:38:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,計劃又重回正軌\N{\fs14}The plan is back on.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.74,0:38:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以哄你 說你是F社會的核心人物\N{\fs14}I could bullshit you, tell you you're the only person
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.23,0:38:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺你不行 沒人能取代你在團隊里的位置\N{\fs14}who can fill the exact void we have at fsociety.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.80,0:38:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事實是 我需要這支團隊的每一個人都回來\N{\fs14}The truth is, I need this group back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.41,0:38:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有沒有想過 我們的計劃哪一部分最吸引你\N{\fs14}Have you ever considered which part of our scheme motivates you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.54,0:38:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當黑暗軍團發力\N{\fs14}When the Dark Army bailed,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.94,0:38:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按下一個鍵就能引發一場經濟革命\N{\fs14}you didn't care if pushing a button
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.19,0:38:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些你都不感興趣\N{\fs14}would bring an economic revolution.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.63,0:38:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要的是瞬間的無政府狀態\N{\fs14}You want momentary anarchy.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.94,0:38:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人呢\N{\fs14}The others?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.37,0:38:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫布里享受大家并肩作戰的感覺\N{\fs14}Mobley likes palling around.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.49,0:38:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅梅羅一心想要出名\N{\fs14}Romero wants a whiff of fame.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.04,0:38:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們的理由讓我厭倦\N{\fs14}Those reasons depress me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.62,0:38:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 那你是出于什么目的?  - 你不會不關心的\N{\fs14}- What's the part you want? - You don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.04,0:39:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母出生于伊朗\N{\fs14}My parents were born in Iran.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.63,0:39:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們像所有人那樣向往自由\N{\fs14}They came here like everybody else,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.41,0:39:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而來到這里\N{\fs14}for freedom,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.33,0:39:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父親每周工作60小時\N{\fs14}but my dad works 60-hour weeks
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.79,0:39:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絞盡腦汁幫一個身家百萬的藝術品經紀人設法逃稅\N{\fs14}to determine tax loopholes for a millionaire art dealer.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.83,0:39:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母親 為了一個網絡大學的文憑\N{\fs14}My mom, she ran up loans into five digits
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.67,0:39:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欠下了5位數的債\N{\fs14}to get an online degree.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.11,0:39:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,縱然如此 他們任然稱頌美國的偉大\N{\fs14}They won't shut up about how great America is.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.31,0:39:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們就將這樣 欠下一屁股債\N{\fs14}But they're gonna die in debt
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.42,0:39:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干不想干的活 了卻此生\N{\fs14}doing things they never wanted to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.18,0:39:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個世界上有多少人?\N{\fs14}There are how many billion people in this world?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.23,0:39:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,73億\N{\fs14}7.3.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.96,0:39:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命運讓我們走到一起\N{\fs14}Somehow you and I landed together...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.69,0:39:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這個特定的歷史時刻 擁有特定的條件\N{\fs14}Doing something impossible if we were alone,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.84,0:39:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去完成我們靠單打獨斗無法完成的壯舉\N{\fs14}not to mention at the right point in history with the right resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.10,0:39:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們付出那么多努力 眼看就要有所回報\N{\fs14}We have what we've worked for right there for the taking.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.60,0:39:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在只需再度攜手 就能完成它\N{\fs14}We just need each other to see this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.12,0:40:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再靠近 我就叫警察了\N{\fs14}You come any closer, I'm calling the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.91,0:40:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 接線員 我要報警\N{\fs14}Hi, operator. I'd like to report an emergency.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.95,0:40:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在家里的電腦里插入了含有惡意軟件的CD\N{\fs14}I placed a malicious cd in my work computer,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.52,0:40:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在這個給我CD的家伙就站在我面前\N{\fs14}and now this guy at the gym is saying hi to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.35,0:40:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回家了\N{\fs14}I'm going home.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.16,0:40:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你為我做件事\N{\fs14}I need you to do something for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.66,0:40:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫那些愿意來的女生 好嗎?\N{\fs14}Call the girl who wants to be involved, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.24,0:40:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫安吉拉 莫斯\N{\fs14}Her name is Angela Moss.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.60,0:40:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你她的電話吧\N{\fs14}Let me give you her phone number.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.37,0:40:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著軟蛋 如果你不按我說的做\N{\fs14}Listen, pussy. If you don't do what I say,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.85,0:40:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就會讓米田共\N{\fs14}then the giant shit storm that rains turds later
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.53,0:40:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在空中劃過一道云彩 寫著你的芳名\N{\fs14}will leave a trail of clouds in the sky spelling out your name.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.99,0:41:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊利艾特? 你怎么來了?\N{\fs14}Elliot? I wasn't expecting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.07,0:41:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來赴約看病\N{\fs14}I'm here for my appointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.49,0:41:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧　你可以在我的第一個病人來之前先看\N{\fs14}Well, you can slip in before my first patient.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.29,0:41:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說我得告訴你實情\N{\fs14}You told me I should tell you the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.56,0:41:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.61,0:41:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所說的話 你會保密嗎?\N{\fs14}Everything I say will still be protected and confidential?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.52,0:41:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前在說謊\N{\fs14}I've been lying to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.99,0:41:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒按時吃藥\N{\fs14}I don't take my pills.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.60,0:41:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也沒有\N{\fs14}But you don't either.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.90,0:41:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對安定的購買次數與\N{\fs14}Your refill frequency for ativan doesn't match
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.06,0:42:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你開藥量除以劑量不符\N{\fs14}your prescription divided by the dosage.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.45,0:42:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上...\N{\fs14}This morning...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.06,0:42:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你買了中杯的榛子拿鐵\N{\fs14}You bought a tall hazelnut latte.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.92,0:42:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的邪惡公司的卡付賬\N{\fs14}Paid for it on your evil corp card.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.87,0:42:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給你妹妹的錢多了\N{\fs14}By text, you justified the indulgence to your sister
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.51,0:42:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為邪惡公司給你的獎勵翻倍了\N{\fs14}because evil corp gives you double rewards.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.13,0:42:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你不知道這些獎勵只能用在差旅費上\N{\fs14}But those points only accumulate on travel expenses.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.70,0:42:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對錢不是很敏感啊\N{\fs14}You're not good with money.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.41,0:42:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在紙上 周四下午兩點來的那個瑪里琳 奧布賴恩\N{\fs14}On paper, your Thursday 2:00, Marilyn O'Brien,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.82,0:42:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你有著很相近的經歷\N{\fs14}is your doppelganger.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.41,0:42:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得你是在鼓勵她\N{\fs14}I think you're encouraging her
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.83,0:42:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離開她的丈夫...\N{\fs14}to leave her husband...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.94,0:42:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你知道被甩的滋味\N{\fs14}Because you're tired of being dumped.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.92,0:42:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜歡情色 尤其是走后門的\N{\fs14}You like porn, especially anal.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.83,0:42:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道是不是你自己喜歡這樣\N{\fs14}Whether you like it yourself, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.09,0:42:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我沒關系\N{\fs14}That's not relevant to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.88,0:42:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告訴你最好的朋友詹尼弗\N{\fs14}You've told your best friend Jennifer
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.75,0:42:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說你希望你媽媽早點死\N{\fs14}that you wish your mom would die.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.83,0:43:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候我會通過你的攝像頭看你\N{\fs14}I sometimes watch you on your webcam.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.29,0:43:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候你會哭...\N{\fs14}You cry sometimes...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.50,0:43:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一樣\N{\fs14}Just like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.76,0:43:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你很孤單\N{\fs14}Because you're lonely.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.48,0:43:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不只是黑你的電腦 克里斯塔\N{\fs14}I don't just hack you, Krista.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.27,0:43:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我黑所有人的\N{\fs14}I hack everyone--
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.24,0:43:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友 同事\N{\fs14}My friends, coworkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.65,0:43:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我已經幫助了很多人了\N{\fs14}But I've helped a lot of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.47,0:43:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要...\N{\fs14}I want...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.47,0:43:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個能走出孤單的方法...\N{\fs14}A way out of loneliness...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.42,0:43:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你一樣\N{\fs14}Just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.41,0:44:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你想要聽到的嗎?\N{\fs14}Is that what you wanted to hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:13.00,0:44:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,300)}\N{\fs14}{\fn微軟雅黑\fs16\b1\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&}本字幕由{\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}大家字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}原創翻譯\N{\fs14}僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為\N{\fs14}彼以國士待我 我以國士待之\N用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人\N有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們\N{\fs14\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}請聯系：dajiazimuzu@163.com
