1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,840
前情提要

2
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,840
機器人先生

4
00:05:50,940 --> 00:05:54,880
子虛烏有  Slient Bob   坑坑美少女  Rachel   | 翻譯

5
00:05:57,850 --> 00:06:01,820
時間軸&特效 |     馬路邊  拉面  柯迪夫  沒啦

6
00:06:04,020 --> 00:06:07,930
校對 |    狒狒狒狒狒

7
00:06:47,900 --> 00:06:50,830
壓制 |    宋胖子

8
00:06:52,410 --> 00:06:55,300
監制 |   狒狒 坑坑

9
00:06:07,600 --> 00:06:18,200
機器人先生

10
00:06:23,680 --> 00:06:25,580
第九集

11
00:19:16,600 --> 00:19:21,120
你是我愛的全部.

12
00:19:24,070 --> 00:19:25,590
他讓我想起了她.

13
00:19:27,660 --> 00:19:29,090
誰?

14
00:19:30,410 --> 00:19:32,510
她是個女孩, 但很文靜.

15
00:19:34,130 --> 00:19:36,220
他們長得很像.

16
00:19:41,010 --> 00:19:42,940
你說的是誰?

17
00:19:45,510 --> 00:19:47,940
我十五歲時.

18
00:19:48,890 --> 00:19:50,860
那件事兒太...

19
00:19:52,730 --> 00:19:55,870
...那過程太繁瑣.

20
00:19:57,400 --> 00:19:59,870
很多表格, 地址備案...

21
00:20:00,360 --> 00:20:02,250
...簽字.

22
00:20:04,740 --> 00:20:09,340
你會覺得我會簽署了一個手機合約計劃.

23
00:20:12,540 --> 00:20:14,470
她的父母看起來很和善.

24
00:20:16,340 --> 00:20:18,140
任何時候都是.

25
00:20:19,960 --> 00:20:22,140
我希望他們一直保持那樣.

26
00:20:24,220 --> 00:20:26,120
你為什么沒有告訴我?

27
00:20:27,260 --> 00:20:30,030
我是不會告訴不需要知道的人.

28
00:20:33,060 --> 00:20:36,410
我嘗試著忘掉那個段記憶.

29
00:20:40,820 --> 00:20:43,250
我的所作所為太殘酷了.

30
00:20:44,990 --> 00:20:47,710
我試著原諒自己. 我試著忘記.

31
00:20:48,580 --> 00:20:51,040
但不太可能.

32
00:20:56,830 --> 00:20:59,010
喬安娜 , 你該早點告訴我的.

33
00:21:00,250 --> 00:21:01,970
我是你的老公. 我愛你.

34
00:21:07,180 --> 00:21:08,610
我早已不在乎你.

35
00:21:12,180 --> 00:21:13,740
你說什么?

36
00:21:02,000 --> 00:21:03,430
別碰我.

37
00:21:14,020 --> 00:21:17,070
你再也不是我想要嫁的那個男人了.

38
00:21:18,270 --> 00:21:19,160
喬安娜.

39
00:21:19,570 --> 00:21:21,370
我知道我一直很粗心大意.

40
00:21:21,980 --> 00:21:24,870
但一定有方法.

41
00:21:25,490 --> 00:21:27,540
請理解我.

42
00:21:28,700 --> 00:21:30,920
如果你還要想呆在這個家里.

43
00:21:31,410 --> 00:21:33,420
你來補救這一切.

44
00:28:37,880 --> 00:28:39,720
Terry Colby可能面臨聯邦指控

45
00:28:42,970 --> 00:28:44,440
黑客攻擊: Colby的后果

63
00:00:00,860 --> 00:00:02,440
令人激動的時刻到了
Exciting time in the world right now.

64
00:00:02,460 --> 00:00:03,760
我的血液都在沸騰
Exciting time.

65
00:00:03,760 --> 00:00:05,490
如果你愿意指認
If you agree to testify,

66
00:00:05,490 --> 00:00:07,760
我就作證是我用數據文件
I will testify that I broke chain of custody

67
00:00:07,780 --> 00:00:08,500
破壞了監管鏈
with the .DAT file.

68
00:00:08,520 --> 00:00:11,020
我們已經設下了蜜罐 cs30
We've implemented a honey pot, CS30.

69
00:00:11,080 --> 00:00:12,690
我想看看你有什么發現
I'd like to look over your findings,

70
00:00:12,740 --> 00:00:14,690
特別是有關這個服務器的
especially this server.

71
00:00:14,750 --> 00:00:16,780
偵探來了 他們想和你聊聊
Detectives came by. They want to speak with you.

72
00:00:16,830 --> 00:00:18,520
他們在屋頂找到了具尸體
They found a body on the roof.

73
00:00:18,540 --> 00:00:20,330
而且你們都認識死者
And you both did know the deceased.

74
00:00:20,370 --> 00:00:21,900
夏倫 諾斯
Sharon Knowles.

75
00:00:21,960 --> 00:00:23,180
夏倫 諾斯？
Sharon Knowles?

76
00:00:23,240 --> 00:00:23,820
啊
Aah!

77
00:00:23,860 --> 00:00:25,120
孩子好像要出生了
I think the baby's coming.

78
00:00:25,160 --> 00:00:26,370
我們得把她送去醫院
We got to get her to the hospital.

79
00:00:26,370 --> 00:00:28,040
和我說說你的父親吧
Tell me about your father.

80
00:00:28,040 --> 00:00:30,460
我記得我曾想要抱著他 告訴他我錯了
I remember I tried to hug him, tell him I'm sorry,

81
00:00:30,510 --> 00:00:33,880
結果他猛推了我一把 直接把我推出了窗戶
and he shoved me so hard, I fell backwards out the window.

82
00:00:35,220 --> 00:00:36,680
天哪 伊利艾特！
Oh, my God, Elliot!

83
00:00:36,720 --> 00:00:39,220
你又忘了嗎？ 你又不記得我是誰了？
Did you forget again? Did you forget who I am?

84
00:00:39,220 --> 00:00:41,050
我是你的 姐姐
-I'm your... - Sister.

85
00:00:47,560 --> 00:00:49,360
我們應該談談
- I think we should talk.

86
00:00:52,330 --> 00:00:54,400
這從1904開始還從來沒發生過
- It hasn't happened since 1904

87
00:00:54,430 --> 00:00:57,000
就是約翰麥格勞退出比賽回去的那一年
the year John McGraw decided to take his bat and ball

88
00:00:57,020 --> 00:00:59,340
現在90年過去了
and go home. Here we are 90 years later,

89
00:00:59,360 --> 00:01:01,240
我想問問大家對于1994年
and I want to get your thoughts on what it was like

90
00:01:01,280 --> 00:01:04,130
世界職業棒球大賽被取消的看法
to be without the 1994 World Series.

91
00:01:04,160 --> 00:01:07,300
是的 1994年的世界職業棒球大賽被取消了
That's right, the 1994 World Series cancelled....

92
00:01:07,330 --> 00:01:08,750
如果早在八月
If you would have told me

93
00:01:08,750 --> 00:01:10,920
球員投票選擇退出時
back in August when the players voted to walk out

94
00:01:10,960 --> 00:01:12,660
你告訴我局面會變成這樣
that we would be here where we are today,

95
00:01:12,700 --> 00:01:14,340
我會說絕對不可能
I would have told you no way, no how,

96
00:01:14,380 --> 00:01:16,090
不可能會這樣
that's not gonna happen.

97
00:01:16,090 --> 00:01:17,840
就算說我搞錯了 我也會承認的
But hey, if I ever get it wrong, I admit it.

98
00:01:17,890 --> 00:01:20,430
所以 到底怎么了？ 聽聽你們怎么說
So, what happened? I want to hear from you...

99
00:01:20,720 --> 00:01:22,420
機器人先生
Mr. Robot.

100
00:01:24,100 --> 00:01:26,700
恩 我會推薦奔騰90
Um, well, I'd recommend the Pentium 90.

101
00:01:26,740 --> 00:01:29,020
它們啟動快 并且我們有現貨
They're lighting fast, and we've got some in stock now.

102
00:01:29,070 --> 00:01:32,600
配著800M的硬盤 什么都可以搞定
With an 800 megabyte hard drive, you'll be all set.

103
00:01:33,440 --> 00:01:35,020
或者我們可以給你打點折
Or we could save you a few bucks

104
00:01:35,040 --> 00:01:36,410
然后幫你升級
and upgrade what you have.

105
00:01:36,440 --> 00:01:37,910
只要換了主板和硬盤
Once we swap out that motherboard

106
00:01:37,910 --> 00:01:38,120
你會發現比新的還好用
and hard drive, you'll be better than new.
Once we swap out that motherboard

107
00:01:38,120 --> 00:01:41,080
你會發現比新的還好用
and hard drive, you'll be better than new.

108
00:01:41,110 --> 00:01:44,450
要不你有時間過來一趟吧 我幫你看看
Why don't you bring it on by, and we'll take a look.

109
00:01:44,450 --> 00:01:45,530
好的
Okay.

110
00:01:45,590 --> 00:01:46,670
謝謝
Thank you.

111
00:01:46,700 --> 00:01:47,820
回見
Bye-bye.

112
00:01:48,820 --> 00:01:51,120
怎么了 新鼠標不好用嗎
What happened? That new mouse not work out for you?

113
00:01:51,120 --> 00:01:53,460
你兒子 他偷了我的錢
Your son, he stole money from me.

114
00:01:54,290 --> 00:01:55,680
額 你說什么？
Uh, excuse me?

115
00:01:55,740 --> 00:01:58,280
你兒子偷了我的錢 我之前拿錢包的時候
Your son stole money from me. I pulled out my wallet,

116
00:01:58,320 --> 00:02:00,380
明明記得我有三張20的
and I specifically remembered I had three 20s.

117
00:02:00,430 --> 00:02:01,800
現在只有一張了
Now I only have one.

118
00:02:01,800 --> 00:02:03,440
我拿了一張來買鼠標
I used one to pay for the mouse,

119
00:02:03,470 --> 00:02:04,720
應該剩下兩張才對
and then I had two left.

120
00:02:04,770 --> 00:02:07,440
你兒子當時就站在我后面
Your son was standing right behind me

121
00:02:07,470 --> 00:02:09,470
就剛才我在柜臺這把錢拿出來的時候
when I had my money out on the counter.

122
00:02:09,530 --> 00:02:11,060
我 先冷靜點好嗎
 I--just calm down.

123
00:02:11,110 --> 00:02:12,500
這其中肯定有什么誤會
I'm sure there's an explanation for this.

124
00:02:12,540 --> 00:02:14,140
沒什么誤會
-I don't want an explanation.

125
00:02:14,160 --> 00:02:16,040
我只想要回我的錢
The only thing I want from you is my money

126
00:02:16,080 --> 00:02:17,820
還有他媽的給我道歉
and a f---ing apology.

127
00:02:18,290 --> 00:02:19,480
您不用這樣
There's no need for that.

128
00:02:19,540 --> 00:02:20,760
我只是想把事情搞清楚
I'm just trying to figure it out.

129
00:02:20,800 --> 00:02:23,910
你覺得我在乎嗎？
Can you tell how much of a shit I give about that?

130
00:02:23,960 --> 00:02:26,410
我沒時間在這扯
Ugh. I don't have time for this.

131
00:02:26,460 --> 00:02:28,780
你到底給不給我錢？
Are you giving me my money or not?

132
00:02:29,550 --> 00:02:32,380
好了你知道怎么做是對的 快點吧
Look, do the right thing here guy.

133
00:02:36,840 --> 00:02:38,420
我不
Then, no.

134
00:02:39,170 --> 00:02:40,670
你說什么？
 Excuse me?

135
00:02:40,720 --> 00:02:42,040
我不給
 The answer's no.

136
00:02:47,810 --> 00:02:50,400
你—你別瞎扯了好嗎
 Are you-- you being serious right now?

137
00:02:50,430 --> 00:02:52,440
我沒什么能幫到你的現在
I can't help you.

138
00:02:53,840 --> 00:02:58,240
你就準備坐那兒然后隨便撒謊？
You--you're really just
gonna sit there and lie?

139
00:02:58,690 --> 00:03:00,500
我要叫警察了
I should call the cops!

140
00:03:03,280 --> 00:03:05,280
上梁不正下梁歪你知道么
What an example you're setting.

141
00:03:05,330 --> 00:03:06,700
我幸幸苦苦掙錢
I--I earn my money,

142
00:03:06,750 --> 00:03:10,000
你就教你兒子怎么偷竊
and you're just teaching him how to steal.

143
00:03:10,040 --> 00:03:11,720
你真是的極品老爸
You're a terrible father.

144
00:03:11,740 --> 00:03:13,040
請你離開好么
- I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.

145
00:03:13,090 --> 00:03:14,620
你算老幾
You're a nobody.

146
00:03:14,680 --> 00:03:16,630
人到中年
You're a middle-aged man doing

147
00:03:16,680 --> 00:03:20,160
還在做我智障的侄子都能做的事
what my retarded nephew could do.

148
00:03:20,680 --> 00:03:22,080
這就是你的生活
That's your life.

149
00:03:24,270 --> 00:03:27,300
好吧 留著你的20刀吧
You know what? Keep your 20.

150
00:03:27,350 --> 00:03:29,690
以后我就改去好樂買
I'll just go to Best Buy from now on.

151
00:03:29,980 --> 00:03:31,520
天吶
God...

152
00:03:48,410 --> 00:03:49,980
出來吧
Come on out.

153
00:04:02,760 --> 00:04:05,760
爸 這不是我做的
Dad, I didn't do it.

154
00:04:13,930 --> 00:04:15,570
給我
Let me see it.

155
00:04:40,460 --> 00:04:42,460
看時空特警還是星際之門？
"Timecop" or "Stargate"?

156
00:04:47,130 --> 00:04:49,630
怎么了？ 那20刀應該可以夠買我們倆的票了
What? 20 bucks ought to cover the both of us.

157
00:04:55,360 --> 00:04:58,140
低俗小說？ 從來沒聽說過
"Pulp Fiction"? Never heard of it.

158
00:04:58,200 --> 00:05:00,280
要我帶你看這個嗎
Sure I can take you to that?

159
00:05:00,310 --> 00:05:01,980
好吧 去拿你的夾克吧
All right, get your jacket.

160
00:05:26,720 --> 00:05:27,890
怎么了？
What?

161
00:05:30,230 --> 00:05:33,010
你不找我麻煩？
How come I'm not in trouble?

162
00:05:37,570 --> 00:05:40,270
雖然你做的不對
Even though what you did was wrong,

163
00:05:40,320 --> 00:05:41,900
但你是個好孩子
you're still a good kid,

164
00:05:44,490 --> 00:05:46,360
而且那個男的就是個無賴
and that guy was a prick.

165
00:05:46,360 --> 00:05:48,720
有的時候這更重要
Sometimes that matters more.

166
00:05:51,000 --> 00:05:52,830
走吧 15分鐘后就開始了
Come on, let's go. It starts in 15 minutes.

167
00:05:52,870 --> 00:05:54,750
我還想買點爆米花 走吧走吧
I want to get some popcorn. Come on.

168
00:06:42,750 --> 00:06:45,420
真的是他
It's really him.

169
00:06:52,430 --> 00:06:54,980
真的是你
It's really you.

170
00:07:00,770 --> 00:07:04,400
我還從沒來過你的公寓
Never been to your apartment before.

171
00:07:04,440 --> 00:07:06,690
看起來不錯
It's nice.

172
00:07:06,740 --> 00:07:11,940
有點亂 不過這也不稀奇
A little messy, but that's not Earth-shattering news.

173
00:07:11,950 --> 00:07:14,780
你從來就不喜歡整理房間
You never really did like cleaning your room.

174
00:07:19,840 --> 00:07:22,790
我就草了
Jesus f---ing Christ.

175
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:27,120
怎么可能是你呢
I can't believe it's really you.

176
00:07:28,090 --> 00:07:29,540
我之前都開始想了
I was beginning to wonder how long

177
00:07:29,600 --> 00:07:32,380
你要多久才能認出我
it was gonna take before you recognized me.

178
00:07:32,430 --> 00:07:37,380
而且你也沒認出戴琳
The fact that you stopped recognizing Darlene too, well...

179
00:07:38,190 --> 00:07:41,690
老實說 因為這個我有點不爽
I got to be honest, that's a little disconcerting.

180
00:07:44,610 --> 00:07:46,780
你為什么不說？
Why didn't you say anything?

181
00:07:46,810 --> 00:07:48,780
為什么不告訴我？ - 伊利艾特
Why didn't you tell me? - Okay, Elliot--

182
00:07:48,820 --> 00:07:49,780
- 都過了這么久了
- This whole time?

183
00:07:49,820 --> 00:07:51,920
- 伊利艾特 冷靜點
- Elliot, you are not well.

184
00:07:52,370 --> 00:07:57,160
我只想一步步來
I was trying to handle it gently.

185
00:07:57,160 --> 00:07:59,120
一步步來？
Gently?

186
00:07:59,300 --> 00:08:01,020
一步步來
Gently?

187
00:08:01,460 --> 00:08:03,020
一步步來
Gently?

188
00:08:04,160 --> 00:08:07,000
這就是這三個月我們就是這樣慢慢來的嗎?
Is that what the last three months have been?

189
00:08:07,050 --> 00:08:12,500
不 這三個月我們在做重要的事情
No. It's been about us doing something important,

190
00:08:12,560 --> 00:08:16,310
而且我們還得繼續做下去
and that's what it still needs to be about.

191
00:08:16,340 --> 00:08:18,390
你應該死了
You died.

192
00:08:18,430 --> 00:08:19,540
你死了
You died.

193
00:08:21,350 --> 00:08:23,150
你明明死了！
You're dead!

194
00:08:25,190 --> 00:08:28,150
你最好小點聲
I suggest you lower your voice.

195
00:08:32,240 --> 00:08:33,760
小點聲？
Lower my voice?

196
00:08:33,990 --> 00:08:37,500
你在你應該死了20年后突然出現在我門后
You want me to lower my voice after appearing at my door

197
00:08:37,530 --> 00:08:41,700
然后要我小點聲？
20 years after your supposed death?

198
00:08:43,840 --> 00:08:49,710
我覺得我就該這么大聲!
I think this is a perfect f---ing volume!

199
00:08:54,550 --> 00:08:56,700
伊利艾特 你不會想讓別人聽到吧
Elliot, you don't want them to hear us.

200
00:08:57,720 --> 00:09:00,240
特別是昨晚提瑞爾 威力克
Especially after my impromptu visit from

201
00:09:00,260 --> 00:09:02,050
突然提到了我
Tyrell Wellick last night.

202
00:09:06,110 --> 00:09:08,860
伊利艾特 有些人
Elliot, there are people out there

203
00:09:08,900 --> 00:09:10,780
不想讓我們做成這件事
who do not want us to work together.

204
00:09:14,730 --> 00:09:16,820
這就是那些人跟蹤我的原因？
Is that why they've been following me?

205
00:09:18,540 --> 00:09:21,640
因為你？
Is that why, because of you?

206
00:09:22,740 --> 00:09:25,830
冷靜想想吧 你不記得我了
Think about it. You don't remember me.

207
00:09:25,880 --> 00:09:27,910
你也不記得你的姐姐
You don't remember your own God damn sister.

208
00:09:28,000 --> 00:09:31,380
你去看心理醫生 吃她開的藥
You see that shrink, pop their pills.

209
00:09:31,470 --> 00:09:33,840
他們是故意想要混淆你的視聽的
They intentionally put you in this haze, fog,

210
00:09:33,880 --> 00:09:35,670
讓你大腦混亂
or whatever brain matter you have left in there,

211
00:09:35,720 --> 00:09:38,720
所以你忘了他們想要你忘記的
so you forget what they want you to forget.

212
00:09:38,760 --> 00:09:40,840
他們想要控制你 伊利艾特
They're trying to control you, Elliot.

213
00:09:40,890 --> 00:09:43,730
他們一直想要控制你
They've been trying to control you all along.

214
00:09:43,760 --> 00:09:46,930
這太不可思議了 我要瘋了
This is crazy. I'm crazy.

215
00:09:46,980 --> 00:09:48,360
我要瘋了 你瘋了
I'm crazy. You're crazy.

216
00:09:48,420 --> 00:09:49,430
這怎么可能
This is crazy.

217
00:09:49,440 --> 00:09:51,350
你在嘀咕什么
What are you talking about?

218
00:09:51,400 --> 00:09:53,350
誰想要控制我？
Who's trying to control me?

219
00:09:53,410 --> 00:09:56,610
外面那些想要我死的人
The people out there who don't want me alive.

220
00:09:56,660 --> 00:09:58,940
那些害怕我們的人
The people who are afraid of us.

221
00:09:59,780 --> 00:10:03,250
我們得比以往更加小心
We have to be more careful, now more than ever.

222
00:10:03,280 --> 00:10:06,900
那戴琳呢 她知道嗎
And Darlene, she knew about this?

223
00:10:08,510 --> 00:10:11,460
伊利艾特 我會給你解釋的
Elliot, I will explain everything,

224
00:10:11,460 --> 00:10:15,020
但現在 我們要執行計劃了
but right now, tonight, we have to stick to the plan.

225
00:10:16,180 --> 00:10:17,960
你在開玩笑嗎？
Are you kidding me?

226
00:10:17,960 --> 00:10:20,470
你想讓我把這事先擱一邊？
You want me to put this on hold?

227
00:10:20,520 --> 00:10:22,800
你他媽到底吃錯了什么藥?
Are you out of your God damn mind?

228
00:10:22,800 --> 00:10:25,050
現在說這事不安全
It's not safe to discuss this here.

229
00:10:25,110 --> 00:10:27,400
關我蛋事
I don't give a shit!

230
00:10:29,190 --> 00:10:31,640
告訴我這是怎么回事
Tell me what the f--- is going on.

231
00:10:34,980 --> 00:10:38,180
好吧 跟我走吧
All right. Come on, let's go.

232
00:10:38,540 --> 00:10:39,820
去哪？
Where?

233
00:10:42,870 --> 00:10:44,910
你想知道這是怎么回事？
You want answers?

234
00:10:44,960 --> 00:10:47,460
別再問了 跟我走
Stop asking questions and follow me.

235
00:10:59,620 --> 00:11:01,540
哦 真是貼心啊 我不能--
Oh, that's sweet. I--I can't.

236
00:11:01,580 --> 00:11:02,840
你做的太快了
You're going too fast.

237
00:11:02,880 --> 00:11:05,130
相信我 那個不是最重要的問題
Trust me, don't think that's the problem.

238
00:11:05,170 --> 00:11:07,000
嘿
Hey.

239
00:11:07,330 --> 00:11:09,970
我知道你昨晚不想說
I know you didn't want to talk last night.

240
00:11:10,000 --> 00:11:12,120
不行 哈利 我現在不行
No, Harry, I can't right now.

241
00:11:12,140 --> 00:11:13,590
我要- 深呼吸
I have to-- - Breathe...

242
00:11:13,640 --> 00:11:15,500
和我一塊吃點床上早餐吧
and have some breakfast in bed with me.

243
00:11:30,490 --> 00:11:32,940
你還能吃得這么香的秘訣是什么?
How are you enjoying anything like that?

244
00:11:35,250 --> 00:11:36,360
嗯
Mm.

245
00:11:36,680 --> 00:11:38,040
親愛的 謝謝你這么用心
Honey, I appreciate it.

246
00:11:38,120 --> 00:11:41,030
我...天哪 要是你知道就不知么說了
I...God, if you only knew.

247
00:11:41,080 --> 00:11:42,670
告訴我 我很樂意知道
Tell me. I would love to know.

248
00:11:42,700 --> 00:11:43,870
他們黑了我們
They hacked us.

249
00:11:43,870 --> 00:11:46,370
你知道的 新聞都在播
You know that. It's all over the news.

250
00:11:46,420 --> 00:11:48,400
如今 一個普通的公司應對這種事兒是沒問題的
Now, normally a company can get through this,

251
00:11:48,440 --> 00:11:50,710
可我們是網絡安全公司
but we're a cyber security company.

252
00:11:50,760 --> 00:11:54,630
你知道這意味著多大的問題嗎?
Can you appreciate how bad that is?

253
00:11:54,680 --> 00:11:58,020
我們這下真的是走投無路了
We're hanging on by our fingernails.

254
00:11:58,940 --> 00:12:01,970
呃 誰知道呢?
Ugh, who knows?

255
00:12:02,320 --> 00:12:04,800
或許我們已經一落千丈
Maybe we've already fallen off a cliff,

256
00:12:04,840 --> 00:12:07,180
但我任然嘗試著抓根救命稻草
and I'm still trying to grasp on to something.

257
00:12:12,780 --> 00:12:14,900
我是個失敗者
I'm a failure.

258
00:12:16,200 --> 00:12:18,040
看著我
Look at me.

259
00:12:22,410 --> 00:12:25,800
看著這個深愛著你的人
Look at this person who loves you so much

260
00:12:25,860 --> 00:12:27,720
他現在都快要高興死了 就因為
he would die a happy man right now just 'cause

261
00:12:27,780 --> 00:12:33,590
他可以坐在兒 我兩一起坐在這兒吃早餐
he had this, us, sitting down and having breakfast.

262
00:12:33,590 --> 00:12:37,590
失敗在我的眼里可不是這樣的
I don't think failing looks like this.

263
00:12:50,400 --> 00:12:52,240
再一次確認你看過的那些郵件
Make sure you go through all those emails again,

264
00:12:52,280 --> 00:12:53,860
從91年到95年 一個都不能放過
everything from '91 to '95,

265
00:12:53,920 --> 00:12:55,240
我們建一個表格
and let's start building a table

266
00:12:55,300 --> 00:12:57,180
和日歷對照起來
that cross-references our calendar.

267
00:12:57,400 --> 00:13:00,530
- 好的 女士 - 嘿 見到你很高興
- Yes, ma'am. - Hey, good to see you.

268
00:13:00,800 --> 00:13:02,520
哦 你應該感到自豪
Oh, you should be proud.

269
00:13:02,540 --> 00:13:04,620
科爾比認罪的新聞今天到處都是
News of Colby's confession is breaking today.

270
00:13:04,670 --> 00:13:09,090
我們可是火力全開了 你來是有事嗎
So far we are firing on all cylinders, so what's up?

271
00:13:09,120 --> 00:13:11,790
我是來幫忙的
I came to help out.

272
00:13:16,300 --> 00:13:19,520
好啊 你能再掃描一遍這些 然后把PDF文件用郵件傳我
Yeah, can you rescan these and email the .PDFs to me

273
00:13:19,540 --> 00:13:20,560
然后復制粘貼一下?
and copy Ry on them?

274
00:13:20,620 --> 00:13:22,130
你不去工作嗎?
Shouldn't you be at work?

275
00:13:22,140 --> 00:13:23,970
我辭職了
I quit.

276
00:13:29,140 --> 00:13:33,230
安吉拉 你不能在這兒工作
Angela, you can't work here.

277
00:13:33,280 --> 00:13:36,300
為什么不行? 我為了這個案子放棄了一切
Why not? I gave up everything for this case.

278
00:13:36,360 --> 00:13:38,620
我并不希望你干涉此案
I don't want you to.

279
00:13:38,650 --> 00:13:42,060
我這兒不是為了幫助你尋求人生目標而來的
I am not here to help you find purpose in your life.

280
00:13:42,140 --> 00:13:44,580
如果你想干點什么事兒 去上個珠寶課吧
If you need something to do, take a jewelry class,

281
00:13:44,660 --> 00:13:46,840
但你不能在這兒工作
but you can't work here.

282
00:13:47,880 --> 00:13:50,160
我干了這些事兒
After what I did,

283
00:13:50,210 --> 00:13:53,160
我在技術員領域是找不到工作了
I won't be able to find another job in tech.

284
00:13:53,220 --> 00:13:54,670
我破產了
I'm broke.

285
00:13:54,670 --> 00:13:56,740
這筆錢少說也要在幾年之后才能到賬
The lawsuit money won't come in for years.

286
00:13:56,780 --> 00:13:59,670
這就是你為什么要去找點別的事兒做
Which is why you need to find something you can get.

287
00:13:59,670 --> 00:14:01,310
但這個不是
But this is not it,

288
00:14:01,340 --> 00:14:04,180
不是這個節骨眼上我們所做的事兒
not at this level for what we're trying to do.

289
00:14:06,180 --> 00:14:07,180
你好?
Hello?

290
00:14:07,180 --> 00:14:08,600
約翰 是 是 是
John. Yeah, yeah, yeah.

291
00:14:08,680 --> 00:14:09,850
不 說吧
No, tell me.

292
00:14:09,850 --> 00:14:12,980
呃...四個?
Um...four?

293
00:14:13,020 --> 00:14:14,860
不 不 不 我們不去那條街
No, no, no, we're not going down that road.

294
00:14:14,940 --> 00:14:16,490
當然不
Absolutely not.

295
00:14:16,520 --> 00:14:18,490
不可能
It's not happening.

296
00:14:18,530 --> 00:14:20,740
不 要么就是六 要么就沒有
No, it's gonna be six or nothing.

297
00:14:27,530 --> 00:14:29,220
- 誰啊? - 是我
- Who is this? - It's me.

298
00:14:29,240 --> 00:14:31,700
我在找伊利艾特 他不在工作崗位
I'm looking for Elliot He's not at work.

299
00:14:31,760 --> 00:14:34,860
- 我說他肯定又翹班了 - 什么意思?
- I think he's flipping out again.- What do you mean?

300
00:14:34,960 --> 00:14:38,710
他昨天晚上要親我
He tried to kiss me last night.

301
00:14:38,760 --> 00:14:41,380
你是昨天發現他那樣行為的人
You're the one that found him last time he was like this.

302
00:14:41,380 --> 00:14:43,720
我真的需要你幫忙
I really need your help.

303
00:14:46,390 --> 00:14:48,220
好 你在哪兒?
Okay, where are you?

304
00:15:06,240 --> 00:15:08,490
他不在
He's not here.

305
00:15:08,540 --> 00:15:10,540
再好好兒想想
Let's keep thinking then.

306
00:15:10,580 --> 00:15:12,540
我在想
I have been.

307
00:15:12,580 --> 00:15:14,500
這是我們的秘密隱匿點
This was our runaway hideout.

308
00:15:14,560 --> 00:15:16,580
他總來這兒
He always came here.

309
00:15:17,220 --> 00:15:20,420
好 我們一起想想那里比較有可能
Okay, let's spitball together.

310
00:15:20,470 --> 00:15:22,500
我幫不了你
I can't help you.

311
00:15:23,760 --> 00:15:25,590
什么意思?
What does that mean?

312
00:15:25,640 --> 00:15:30,120
意思是...我真的不懂伊利艾特了
- It means...I don't really know Elliot any more.

313
00:15:30,600 --> 00:15:33,480
安吉拉 他這次是真正地瘋了
He has gone psycho legit this time, Angela.

314
00:15:33,520 --> 00:15:34,980
我們現在可是十萬火急的狀態
We are in a state of 911.

315
00:15:35,020 --> 00:15:36,620
我們得跟他談談
We just need to talk to him.

316
00:15:36,660 --> 00:15:38,440
是啊 哎 他根本不想和我溝通
Yeah, well, he doesn't want to talk back.

317
00:15:38,440 --> 00:15:41,360
就算他說話了 通常都是謊話連篇
And if he does, it's usually with a bunch of lies.

318
00:15:41,410 --> 00:15:44,440
我們無法繼續保護他不受自己的傷害了 達琳
We can't keep protecting him from himself, Darlene.

319
00:15:44,440 --> 00:15:46,900
他拯救了我們好幾次
He has saved our asses multiple times,

320
00:15:46,940 --> 00:15:48,750
而你就打算這么對待他嗎?
and you're just gonna do him like this?

321
00:15:48,980 --> 00:15:51,040
你怎么這么關心?
Why do you even care?

322
00:15:51,920 --> 00:15:53,450
這是什么意思?
What is that supposed to mean?

323
00:15:53,500 --> 00:15:56,290
我的意思是你兩關系從來沒有這么好過
It means you guys were never that close.

324
00:15:56,340 --> 00:15:58,120
說實話
In fact,

325
00:15:58,170 --> 00:16:01,600
在你回到這座城市之前 他都表現得很好
he's been doing just fine until you moved back to the city.

326
00:16:03,300 --> 00:16:05,800
你來這兒是干嘛?
Why are you even here?

327
00:16:05,850 --> 00:16:08,920
為什么你和伊利艾特呆在一起這么久?
Why have you and Elliot been spending so much time together?

328
00:16:09,120 --> 00:16:11,140
好 你冷靜點 親愛的
Okay, you need to back off, babe.

329
00:16:11,140 --> 00:16:13,390
他是我弟弟 我只是要幫助他
He is my brother, and I'm just trying to help.

330
00:16:13,440 --> 00:16:15,310
這需要什么理由嗎
That requires no explanation.

331
00:16:15,310 --> 00:16:17,580
你并不想告訴我發生了什么
You don't want to tell me what's really going on here,

332
00:16:17,640 --> 00:16:20,810
很好 那就不要求我來幫忙
that's fine, but then stop asking me for my help.

333
00:16:44,360 --> 00:16:46,000
還好嗎
I think we're good.

334
00:16:49,510 --> 00:16:51,680
記得這個嗎?
Remember this?

335
00:16:51,680 --> 00:16:53,660
當然記得
Of course I do.

336
00:16:53,720 --> 00:16:56,020
我覺得吧 現在是一個合理的時機來確認--
I think it's reasonable for me to confirm given your--

337
00:16:56,040 --> 00:16:59,100
我甚至記得我的游戲
I even remember my game.

338
00:16:59,150 --> 00:17:01,600
我會計算統計概率
I'd calculate the statistical probability

339
00:17:01,650 --> 00:17:04,190
算算火車每節車廂的安全概率
of safety for each car on the train

340
00:17:04,190 --> 00:17:07,190
基于它們出軌的頻率
based on how often they would derail.

341
00:17:07,190 --> 00:17:09,560
去的時候 我會選擇最安全的車廂上去
On the way there, I'd always pick the safest car

342
00:17:09,600 --> 00:17:13,700
因為我很期待我們去那座城市的旅程
'cause I looked forward to our trips to the city so much.

343
00:17:13,750 --> 00:17:17,360
而回來的時候 我會選擇最危險的那一節
Then on the way back, I'd pick the most dangerous ones...

344
00:17:18,870 --> 00:17:21,370
因為我討厭回家
'cause I hated going home.

345
00:17:24,040 --> 00:17:27,210
她不在了 伊利艾特
She's not there any more, Elliot.

346
00:17:27,210 --> 00:17:28,880
聽著 我不知道我們要去向何方
- Look, I don't know where we're going,

347
00:17:28,930 --> 00:17:30,380
但我們得找到戴琳
but we need to find Darlene.

348
00:17:30,430 --> 00:17:32,100
他們可能在跟蹤她- 噓
They may be after her-  Shh.

349
00:17:39,390 --> 00:17:41,530
我就以為是你
I thought that was you.

350
00:17:45,060 --> 00:17:48,730
哦 上帝啊 好久沒見你了
Oh, my God. I haven't seen you in forever.

351
00:17:53,040 --> 00:17:55,040
我們現在不能見戴琳
We can't see Darlene right now.

352
00:17:55,080 --> 00:17:57,280
太冒險了
It's too risky.

353
00:17:58,630 --> 00:18:01,260
我知道你很困惑 伊利艾特 但我會讓你知道的
I know you're confused, Elliot, but I'm gonna show you.

354
00:18:01,360 --> 00:18:06,080
我會讓你知道這些日子我都去了什么地方
I'm gonna show you exactly where I've been this whole time.

355
00:18:19,730 --> 00:18:21,430
聽著 冷靜點
Look, calm down.

356
00:18:21,430 --> 00:18:23,570
我會弄明白的
I'll figure this out.

357
00:18:23,600 --> 00:18:25,270
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.

358
00:18:25,320 --> 00:18:27,190
要是我也不會 但我會告訴你
I wouldn't either, but I'm telling you,

359
00:18:27,240 --> 00:18:29,940
隨著時間流逝 我記得越來越多的東西
I'm remembering more and more now as time goes on.

360
00:18:29,990 --> 00:18:31,780
這是種累積
That's a plus.

361
00:18:31,830 --> 00:18:34,450
記憶都漸漸地回來了
It's all starting to come back,

362
00:18:34,450 --> 00:18:36,560
一旦我們得到了所有答案
and once we get all the answers,

363
00:18:36,660 --> 00:18:39,420
我又回歸平凡了
I'll be back to normal,

364
00:18:39,450 --> 00:18:41,760
除了我那已經死去的老爹
except for the fact that my dead father

365
00:18:41,780 --> 00:18:45,120
并沒有死 而是坐在我的對面
isn't really dead and is sitting across from me.

366
00:19:00,680 --> 00:19:04,040
我出去下 給你們一些私人空間
I'm gonna step outside and give you guys a moment to yourselves.

367
00:19:04,040 --> 00:19:06,560
我們等下再喂他好嗎?
We'll try feeding him again later, okay?

368
00:19:06,720 --> 00:19:08,120
好的
Okay

369
00:21:47,080 --> 00:21:50,280
不 我認識主人 弗雷迪
No, I know the owner. Freddy

370
00:21:50,960 --> 00:21:53,880
你還好嗎? 大家還好嗎? 這他媽的是怎么回事?
Are you okay? Is everyone okay? What the hell happened?

371
00:21:53,880 --> 00:21:55,400
我自己也搞不清楚
I'm still trying to figure that one out myself.

372
00:21:55,400 --> 00:21:57,200
我去北邊呆了一天
I was gone one day upstate.

373
00:21:57,200 --> 00:21:58,560
他們說是電子炸彈 誰知道呢?
They're saying it was electrical, but who knows?

374
00:21:58,560 --> 00:22:00,000
我在和保險公司談
On hold with the insurance.

375
00:22:00,040 --> 00:22:02,200
這群王八蛋又在玩老把戲
Cocksuckers are doing their typical dance.

376
00:22:02,200 --> 00:22:04,120
是的 我可以接聽了?
Yeah, I was on hold?

377
00:22:04,400 --> 00:22:07,760
不 等等 又來
No, wait, not again.

378
00:22:07,760 --> 00:22:10,680
我是來取硬盤的
Well, I just came by to pick up some drives

379
00:22:10,680 --> 00:22:12,320
我的一個同事昨天掉在這里的
one of my employees dropped off yesterday.

380
00:22:12,560 --> 00:22:14,560
抱歉你白來一趟了
I'm sorry you wasted the trip.

381
00:22:14,560 --> 00:22:14,600
所有東西都被毀了 抱歉你白來一趟了
Everything's gone. I'm sorry you wasted the trip.

382
00:22:14,600 --> 00:22:16,840
所有東西都被毀了
Everything's gone.

383
00:22:30,960 --> 00:22:33,520
提利爾
Tyrell.

384
00:22:33,720 --> 00:22:34,880
男孩還是女孩?
What was it?

385
00:22:34,880 --> 00:22:36,200
男孩?
Boy?

386
00:22:36,960 --> 00:22:38,680
是的
Yeah.

387
00:22:38,960 --> 00:22:40,280
很好
Good.

388
00:22:40,400 --> 00:22:42,080
謝謝你的花 先生
Thank you for the flowers, sir.

389
00:22:42,160 --> 00:22:44,120
說實話  花是
If I'm being honest,it was Anwar

390
00:22:44,120 --> 00:22:46,120
安華送的
who sent the flowers.

391
00:22:46,680 --> 00:22:49,240
他擅長處理這些事
He has a way with them.

392
00:22:52,080 --> 00:22:56,920
提瑞爾  我不兜圈子了
Tyrell, you don't know me to beat around the bush,

393
00:22:57,040 --> 00:22:59,200
我就直說吧
so I'll get right to it.

394
00:22:59,280 --> 00:23:01,320
坐吧
Have a seat.

395
00:23:01,380 --> 00:23:07,360
你應該明白這些天我們公司的處境比較微妙
You understand the delicate state we're in these days.

396
00:23:07,400 --> 00:23:09,840
我相信你已經意識到
As I'm sure you're aware,this situation

397
00:23:09,880 --> 00:23:13,200
夏倫·諾斯的事是...是很可怕的
with Sharon Knowles is...it's horrific.

398
00:23:13,440 --> 00:23:16,640
對斯科特來說是很大的打擊
Scott is understandably devastated by it.

399
00:23:16,920 --> 00:23:19,160
是的 我很同情他
Yeah, my heart goes out to him.

400
00:23:19,160 --> 00:23:20,440
我不知道我可以做什么 如果...
I don't know what I'd do if--

401
00:23:20,440 --> 00:23:22,680
好 好 我知道 我知道 但是...
Yeah, yeah,I know, I know, but...

402
00:23:22,720 --> 00:23:25,480
問題是 現在警方
The thing is that the police

403
00:23:25,850 --> 00:23:29,850
已經盯上我和斯科特了
have indicated to Scott and to me

404
00:23:30,160 --> 00:23:34,480
而你 也是懷疑的對象
that you are a person of interest.

405
00:23:34,840 --> 00:23:38,120
我不知道他們的懷疑是不是因為斯科特告訴他們
They're suspicions are based on information Scott

406
00:23:38,120 --> 00:23:43,370
你曾經對夏倫有過一些表示?
gave them about advances you made on Sharon?

407
00:23:43,680 --> 00:23:46,680
聽著 安華 我對這件事并不感興趣
Look, Tyrell,it was not lost on me

408
00:23:46,720 --> 00:23:50,360
你和斯科特之間的競爭是你們的事
that you and Scott had your own competitive frictions.

409
00:23:50,520 --> 00:23:54,440
當然了 他從你的手里搶奪了首席技術官的位置
Hell, the man nabbed CTO right out from under you.

410
00:23:54,640 --> 00:23:58,000
我相信他遭遇不幸會讓他想要發泄
I'm sure his distress is just causing him to lash out,

411
00:23:58,000 --> 00:23:59,840
而且你對他而言是個輕松的目標
and you're an easy target for him,

412
00:23:59,880 --> 00:24:03,680
我估計你和這場慘劇沒什么關系
and of course I doubt you're involvement in this mishap,

413
00:24:03,680 --> 00:24:06,110
但是 但是
but...but...

414
00:24:08,730 --> 00:24:12,560
問題還沒有解決
The problem remains.

415
00:24:15,320 --> 00:24:18,200
斯科特將留在公司
Scott will continue here,

416
00:24:18,240 --> 00:24:21,400
但是你 恐怕不行了
but you, I'm afraid, can not.

417
00:24:37,080 --> 00:24:40,680
我不太懂你的意思 菲利普
I'm not sure what you're saying, Phillip.

418
00:24:45,100 --> 00:24:48,600
你當然知道我在說什么
You know exactly what I'm saying.

419
00:24:50,760 --> 00:24:55,070
菲利普 你不能這樣做
Phillip, you can't do this.

420
00:24:55,110 --> 00:24:57,440
你不能這樣做
You can't do this.

421
00:24:57,490 --> 00:24:59,110
你不可以!
You can't!

422
00:24:59,110 --> 00:25:01,720
我為這家公司傾盡心血!
I've killed myself for this company!

423
00:25:01,720 --> 00:25:05,280
我比所有其他人升職的都快!
I've been promoted faster than anyone else!

424
00:25:07,000 --> 00:25:11,200
實話告訴你 我試圖想象過你的反應
I can't deny I tried picturing your reaction.

425
00:25:12,120 --> 00:25:15,260
我通常是不會花時間在這上面的
I seldom have time for such imaginings.

426
00:25:15,290 --> 00:25:17,320
對于你 我很好奇
For you, I was curious.

427
00:25:17,360 --> 00:25:19,160
有多種可能性
It could've gone any number of ways,

428
00:25:19,160 --> 00:25:22,240
我承認每種可能性都很有趣
and I found all the different versions quite interesting,

429
00:25:22,280 --> 00:25:24,630
但是 現在...
I admit, but now...

430
00:25:25,000 --> 00:25:28,160
面對現實...
confronted with the reality...

431
00:25:28,970 --> 00:25:32,000
我只能說我很失望
I have to say I'm disappointed.

432
00:25:32,980 --> 00:25:37,000
菲利普 請不要這樣做
Phillip, please don't do this.

433
00:25:37,000 --> 00:25:39,240
我才剛步入正軌
I was on a track.

434
00:25:49,440 --> 00:25:52,320
曾經有那么一瞬間 提瑞爾
There was a moment, Tyrell,

435
00:25:52,320 --> 00:25:55,830
就在最近的一個關鍵時間點
a point in your recent past,

436
00:25:56,320 --> 00:25:57,720
可能是一個錯誤
a mistake,

437
00:25:57,800 --> 00:25:59,640
一個沖動的決定
a compulsion, decision,

438
00:25:59,680 --> 00:26:04,670
或者別的什么東西讓你變成了今天這個樣子
something, that led you to this point right now.

439
00:26:05,240 --> 00:26:07,280
我對你只有一個建議 就是...
My only advice to you is...

440
00:26:07,680 --> 00:26:10,360
去找到那個瞬間
find that moment,

441
00:26:10,720 --> 00:26:13,080
好好理解它
understand it.

442
00:26:15,490 --> 00:26:18,120
這也是唯一的方法來挽救你自己
It's the only way to reconcile this...

443
00:26:18,160 --> 00:26:20,720
以及你的失敗
this failure with yourself.

444
00:26:22,360 --> 00:26:26,610
拜托了 先生 不要這樣做
Please, sir, don't do this.

445
00:26:27,160 --> 00:26:29,600
我求你了
I'm begging you.

446
00:26:30,500 --> 00:26:36,040
我...我愛這家公司
I...I love this company.

447
00:27:00,900 --> 00:27:04,360
威力克先生 你不能一直這樣不搭理我們
Mr. Wellick,you can't keep ignoring us.

448
00:27:04,360 --> 00:27:06,440
如果你們有任何問題 請去聯系我的律師
If you have any questions,contact my lawyer.

449
00:27:06,440 --> 00:27:08,900
如果你們有足夠的證據 就去告我
If you have evidence against me, charge me.

450
00:27:18,440 --> 00:27:20,800
我知道是我帶你回這個鎮上的
I know I brought you back to township,

451
00:27:20,800 --> 00:27:24,440
但是來拜訪我們的舊宅并不是我們的計劃之一
but stopping by our old house is not part of the plan.

452
00:27:24,440 --> 00:27:26,480
走吧 他們馬上就要回來了
Come on, these people are gonna be home soon.

453
00:27:26,480 --> 00:27:27,800
現在不是私闖民宅的時候
Not the best time for a B and E.

454
00:27:27,800 --> 00:27:29,200
事情就是在這里發生的 對吧?
This is where it happened,isn't it?

455
00:27:29,200 --> 00:27:32,430
什么?在這里發生什么了?
What? Where what happened?

456
00:27:32,760 --> 00:27:35,560
你對那個窗戶有印象嗎?
You remember anything about that window?

457
00:27:35,600 --> 00:27:37,180
快走吧 伊利艾特
Come on, Elliot.

458
00:27:37,240 --> 00:27:38,930
我說過了 我們得趕緊走
Like I said, we should go.

459
00:27:38,940 --> 00:27:42,120
伊利艾特 你在做什么?冷靜一下
Elliot, what are you doing?Calm down.

460
00:27:42,640 --> 00:27:44,000
啊!嗷!
Aah!Ugh!

461
00:27:44,040 --> 00:27:45,480
-你把我從這個窗戶推了出去 -伊利艾特...
-You pushed me out this window.- Elliot...

462
00:27:45,480 --> 00:27:47,400
-你把我推下了木板橋 -嘿 別這樣
-You pushed me off the boardwalk.- Hey, come on.

463
00:27:47,400 --> 00:27:49,560
不 也許現在你也該嘗嘗被推下去的滋味
No. Maybe you're the one who needs some pushing now.

464
00:27:49,600 --> 00:27:51,080
冷靜一下 那是一次事故
Calm down.It was an accident.

465
00:27:51,080 --> 00:27:53,160
放屁! 那時我只有八歲!
Bullshit! I was eight years old.

466
00:27:53,160 --> 00:27:54,360
你覺得我活該
You thought I deserved it.

467
00:27:54,360 --> 00:27:55,760
-你就知這么說的 對吧? -不 不是
-That's what you said, isn't it? -No, no.

468
00:27:55,760 --> 00:27:57,320
-是的!就在你把我推下去之前  -不不不 伊利艾特
-Yeah, right before you pushed me again! -No, no, no, Elliot,

469
00:27:57,360 --> 00:28:00,040
那是你自己覺得你活該
you thought you deserved it.

470
00:28:00,040 --> 00:28:02,000
你對你自己的人生感到罪惡
You felt guilty about this your whole life,

471
00:28:02,040 --> 00:28:03,640
因為你告訴了別人我的秘密
about telling people my secret.

472
00:28:03,680 --> 00:28:05,200
這些憤怒不是來源于我
This anger was never at me.

473
00:28:05,240 --> 00:28:06,640
是來源于你
It was at you.

474
00:28:06,640 --> 00:28:08,040
拜托了 伊利艾特
Please, Elliot,

475
00:28:08,080 --> 00:28:10,480
你不必再仇恨你自己了
you don't have to be angry at yourself any more.

476
00:28:10,480 --> 00:28:11,720
讓一切都過去吧
Just let it go.

477
00:28:11,760 --> 00:28:13,160
求你了 該放下了
Please let it go.

478
00:28:13,240 --> 00:28:15,640
你說的對 我很憤怒
You're right.I was angry.

479
00:28:15,680 --> 00:28:16,840
我恨我自己
I was angry at myself.

480
00:28:16,880 --> 00:28:20,400
我恨我那樣對你
I hated myself for doing what I did to you.

481
00:28:21,810 --> 00:28:23,610
我準備好放手了
I'm ready to let go.

482
00:28:23,650 --> 00:28:24,810
啊!
Aah!

483
00:29:03,080 --> 00:29:06,360
我打算去花園里干會活
Gonna work in the garden a little.

484
00:29:06,400 --> 00:29:08,350
如果你能來幫我一下那更好
It'd be nice if you wanted to help.

485
00:29:11,520 --> 00:29:14,840
噢 對了你怎么沒告訴我戴琳回來了
Oh, by the way, you didn't tell me Darlene was back in town.

486
00:29:14,840 --> 00:29:17,200
我已經好久沒看見她回來過了
I haven't seen her back here in a while.

487
00:29:17,200 --> 00:29:18,610
你說什么?
What did you say?

488
00:29:18,650 --> 00:29:21,980
戴琳 至少 我覺得那是她
Darlene. At least, I think it was her.

489
00:29:22,030 --> 00:29:26,240
你看到她了?在哪?
You saw her? Where?

490
00:29:26,290 --> 00:29:29,960
我告訴你 我沒有收到申請通知
I'm telling you,I did not get notification of the request.

491
00:29:29,960 --> 00:29:32,760
那個服務器還需要保留一個離線的蜜罐程序
That server needs to remain a honey pot, off the network.

492
00:29:32,800 --> 00:29:34,280
先生 我這里明明收到一個昨天的申請
Sir, I have the request right here from yesterday.

493
00:29:34,320 --> 00:29:35,800
我想告訴你的是 吉姆
I'm trying to tell you, Jim,

494
00:29:35,800 --> 00:29:37,840
我們的網絡昨天被盜用了
our network was compromised yesterday.

495
00:29:37,880 --> 00:29:39,160
那個請求不是我發出的
I did not make the request.

496
00:29:39,200 --> 00:29:40,520
明顯是其他人發的
Someone else obviously did,

497
00:29:40,560 --> 00:29:42,520
所以你現在趕緊將服務器斷網
so you need to take the server off the network,

498
00:29:42,520 --> 00:29:43,840
否則肯定要出事
or something's gonna happen.

499
00:29:43,880 --> 00:29:44,960
我不能這樣做 先生
I just can't do that, sir.

500
00:29:44,970 --> 00:29:46,670
我們從提瑞爾·威力克那里收到了特別指令
We have specific orders from Tyrell Wellick

501
00:29:46,680 --> 00:29:48,520
要按照這個申請來做
to keep the request as is.

502
00:29:48,520 --> 00:29:50,520
這根本說不通
That just doesn't make any sense.

503
00:29:50,560 --> 00:29:53,840
聽著 我現在需要跟你們主管談
Look, I need to speak to your supervisor.

504
00:30:01,690 --> 00:30:03,400
有人嗎?
Hello?

505
00:30:05,360 --> 00:30:07,480
有人在嗎?
Is anyone here?

506
00:30:21,430 --> 00:30:23,160
有人嗎?
Hello?

507
00:30:24,320 --> 00:30:26,800
喔!天哪!
Oh, Jesus.

508
00:30:27,680 --> 00:30:30,000
我已經找遍了所有地方
I ran out of places to look,

509
00:30:30,000 --> 00:30:32,640
我以為我可以來最后一個他可能去的地方試試
so I figured I'd try the last place he'd ever be.

510
00:30:32,960 --> 00:30:35,120
又一次落空了
Struck out again.

511
00:30:35,280 --> 00:30:37,040
噢 天哪
Oh, God.

512
00:30:37,390 --> 00:30:40,640
我已經好幾年沒來過這里了
I haven't been here in years.

513
00:30:41,230 --> 00:30:45,080
新搬過來的一家人太奇怪了
The new family that just moved in is so weird,

514
00:30:45,160 --> 00:30:47,450
尤其是他們的爸爸
especially the dad.

515
00:30:50,370 --> 00:30:53,040
確實變化了很多
They really change much.

516
00:30:54,380 --> 00:30:56,400
你還好嗎?
You okay?

517
00:30:56,920 --> 00:30:58,250
嗯
Yeah.

518
00:30:59,300 --> 00:31:00,410
我靠
Shit.

519
00:31:00,420 --> 00:31:02,250
怪爸爸回來了
Weird new dad's back.

520
00:31:19,400 --> 00:31:22,270
對了 我很抱歉
I'm sorry, by the way.

521
00:31:22,320 --> 00:31:24,160
為什么?
For what?

522
00:31:25,240 --> 00:31:29,990
我應該對你和你的家人更誠實點
I should be more open with you, your family.

523
00:31:33,950 --> 00:31:35,640
好了 好了
Okay, okay.

524
00:31:35,640 --> 00:31:38,160
別跟我矯情了
Don't get all mushy on me now.

525
00:31:43,920 --> 00:31:46,160
你看到那個了嗎?
Do you see that?

526
00:31:47,510 --> 00:31:49,720
那不是伊利艾特的房間嗎?
Wasn't that Elliot's room?

527
00:31:57,120 --> 00:32:01,400
我們快要到了 快要到了
We're almost there.Almost there.

528
00:32:01,440 --> 00:32:03,280
為什么 我們來這里做什么?
Why?Why are we here?

529
00:32:03,310 --> 00:32:05,720
我以為我們要去安全點的地方
I thought you said we were going somewhere safe.

530
00:32:05,760 --> 00:32:07,000
啊!
Aah!

531
00:32:07,370 --> 00:32:09,480
伊利艾特!
Elliot!

532
00:32:09,540 --> 00:32:11,320
伊利艾特!
Elliot!

533
00:32:11,320 --> 00:32:13,070
糟了
Shit.

534
00:32:13,120 --> 00:32:15,820
她們倆怎么在這?
What the hell are they doing here?

535
00:32:15,820 --> 00:32:17,960
她們不會待很久的
Won't be long now.

536
00:32:17,990 --> 00:32:19,760
我努力的在保護你 孩子
I tried to protect you, son,

537
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:21,400
但是他們已經追過來了
but they caught up to us.

538
00:32:21,400 --> 00:32:23,660
-伊利艾特! -你在說什么?
-Elliot!- What are you talking about?

539
00:32:23,670 --> 00:32:26,360
那是戴琳和安吉拉
That's Darlene and Angela.

540
00:32:26,400 --> 00:32:29,280
相信我吧 孩子 我也想早點告訴你的
Trust me, son,I wanted to tell you sooner.

541
00:32:29,360 --> 00:32:31,340
但是事情到最后發展得太快了
Things got too accelerated at the end there.

542
00:32:31,390 --> 00:32:33,340
你必須相信
You have to believe that.

543
00:32:33,340 --> 00:32:36,880
不管別人怎么做 我永遠都不會離開你的
No matter what anyone tries to do, I will never leave you.

544
00:32:36,920 --> 00:32:38,720
我永遠都在這 在你身邊
I will always be right here.

545
00:32:38,800 --> 00:32:41,040
你明白嗎?他們不能再一次把我們父子倆分開
Do you understand that? They are not going to break us apart again.

546
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:41,960
究竟發生什么事了?
What's going on?

547
00:32:41,960 --> 00:32:43,400
-聽我說 -告訴我到底怎么回事!
- Listen to me. - Tell me right now!

548
00:32:43,400 --> 00:32:44,840
你聽我說 我們時間不多了
Listen to me because we don't have much time.

549
00:32:44,840 --> 00:32:46,160
她們又要試圖甩掉我了
They're gonna try and get rid of me again,

550
00:32:46,820 --> 00:32:47,820
我需要你阻止他們!
and I need you to not let them!

551
00:32:47,880 --> 00:32:49,000
他們為什么要擺脫你?
Why would they get rid of you?

552
00:32:49,040 --> 00:32:49,880
伊利艾特 聽我說
Please, Elliot, listen to me.

553
00:32:50,240 --> 00:32:51,740
我永遠不會離開你的
I will never leave you.

554
00:32:53,260 --> 00:32:56,320
我再也不會讓你孤身一人了
I will never leave you alone again.

555
00:32:58,200 --> 00:33:00,240
兒子啊 爸爸愛你
I love you, son.

556
00:33:11,980 --> 00:33:13,940
他在說什么呢?
What's he talking about?

557
00:33:14,160 --> 00:33:16,140
他在說什么啊?
What's he talking about?

558
00:33:16,650 --> 00:33:18,850
我想知道他在說什么
Hey, I want to know.

559
00:33:18,900 --> 00:33:21,100
我想知道
I want to know.

560
00:33:21,160 --> 00:33:23,440
我想知道!
I want to know!

561
00:33:23,490 --> 00:33:27,080
伊利艾特 你在和誰說話?
Elliot, who are you talking to?

562
00:33:29,530 --> 00:33:32,080
什么意思? 我在和...
What do you mean? I'm talking to

563
00:33:40,130 --> 00:33:45,380
離我遠點 離我遠點
Stay back. Stay back.

564
00:33:45,380 --> 00:33:47,210
伊利艾特 你流血了
Elliot, you're bleeding.

565
00:33:49,550 --> 00:33:52,890
啊
Aah.

566
00:33:52,890 --> 00:33:54,720
伊利艾特...
Elliot...

567
00:33:55,770 --> 00:33:57,220
啊
Aah.

568
00:34:02,110 --> 00:34:06,070
伊利艾特 你在這兒干什么?
Elliot, what are you doing here?

569
00:34:06,070 --> 00:34:10,070
你沒看到他嗎?
You didn't see him?

570
00:34:10,070 --> 00:34:13,240
看到誰?
Who?

571
00:34:13,240 --> 00:34:15,710
啊!
Aah!

572
00:34:15,740 --> 00:34:18,580
這不是真的
This can't be happening.

573
00:34:18,580 --> 00:34:20,960
-這不是真的 -不...
-This can't be happening. -No...

574
00:34:29,060 --> 00:34:31,760
這是真的 是不是?
This is happening, isn't it?

575
00:34:36,730 --> 00:34:40,270
你一直都知道 對不對?
You knew all along, didn't you?

576
00:34:47,740 --> 00:34:53,500
伊利艾特 你剛在和誰說話?
Elliot, who do you think you've been talking to?

577
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:58,840
你想逼我說出來 對吧?
You're gonnamake me say it, aren't you?

578
00:35:03,090 --> 00:35:05,120
我就是機器人先生
I'm Mr. Robot.

579
00:35:20,370 --> 00:35:25,490
你會沒事的
You're gonna be okay.

580
00:35:25,540 --> 00:35:28,750
我他媽離沒事差了十萬八千里
I think I'm pretty f---ing far from okay.

581
00:35:31,750 --> 00:35:35,250
我這么說你可別誤會
Don't take this the wrong way,

582
00:35:35,250 --> 00:35:37,050
但是我好羨慕你
but I envy you.

583
00:35:40,480 --> 00:35:44,340
我也好想再和我媽媽說幾句話
I wish I could talk to my mom again,

584
00:35:44,400 --> 00:35:46,730
就算她不是真實存在的
even if she isn't real.

585
00:36:09,120 --> 00:36:12,620
照顧好自己 好嗎?
Take care of yourself, okay?

586
00:36:27,140 --> 00:36:29,720
我知道你不想聊這個
I know you don't feel like talking about it...

587
00:36:29,770 --> 00:36:32,390
是不想
You're right, I don't.

588
00:36:32,440 --> 00:36:35,810
但鑒于我們一直在做的這些事 伊利艾特
Unfortunately I need to know, Elliot,

589
00:36:35,810 --> 00:36:39,780
我必須得知道
given what we've been doing.

590
00:36:39,820 --> 00:36:42,450
必須
I just need to know.

591
00:36:44,620 --> 00:36:46,790
你能記得多少?
Do you remember any of it?

592
00:36:50,160 --> 00:36:53,000
記得什么?
Remember what?

593
00:36:53,050 --> 00:36:55,670
我們剛成立F社會的時候
When we first started fsociety.

594
00:37:04,140 --> 00:37:06,590
威力克先生在嗎?
Is Mr. Wellick in?

595
00:37:06,640 --> 00:37:09,150
哦 你好 戈達德先生
Oh, hi, Mr. Goddard.

596
00:37:09,180 --> 00:37:10,350
威力克先生離開了
No, he's gone.

597
00:37:10,350 --> 00:37:12,150
他...
He was, um...

598
00:37:12,180 --> 00:37:13,600
他今天被開除了
He was let go today.

599
00:37:13,650 --> 00:37:18,020
啥? 為什么?
What? Why?

600
00:37:18,020 --> 00:37:20,270
我不清楚
I don't know.

601
00:37:20,330 --> 00:37:22,610
他不是那么好相處的
He wasn't always the easiest person to deal with.

602
00:37:22,660 --> 00:37:24,360
這我知道
I--I'm sure.

603
00:37:24,360 --> 00:37:29,330
你能安排我見一下斯考特 諾斯嗎?
Uh, do you think you can get me in to see Scott Knowles?

604
00:37:29,370 --> 00:37:33,840
-我有急事 -哦 不行 現在肯定不行
-It's urgent. - Oh, no, definitely not now.

605
00:37:33,870 --> 00:37:35,710
你沒聽說嗎?
You haven't heard?

606
00:38:05,870 --> 00:38:08,240
爸 這是什么情況?
Dad, what's going on?

607
00:38:08,240 --> 00:38:11,070
你們兩個聊吧
I'll let you two talk.

608
00:38:16,460 --> 00:38:19,050
好啦 好啦 但是這么不請自來 可是你做的初一
I know, I know, but hey, you popped in over at my home.

609
00:38:19,460 --> 00:38:23,090
我想我也差不多該做十五了
I figured I'd return the favor.

610
00:38:23,090 --> 00:38:24,920
你想怎么樣?
What do you want?

611
00:38:24,970 --> 00:38:27,670
給你一樣你可能想要的東西
To offer you something you may want.

612
00:38:27,730 --> 00:38:30,680
過來啊
Come on in.

613
00:38:30,730 --> 00:38:32,180
如果是和案子有關的...
If this is about the case--

614
00:38:32,230 --> 00:38:33,600
拜托 案子什么的我根本不關心
Please. I don't care about the case.

615
00:38:33,600 --> 00:38:34,760
這個案子我都沒能理解
I don't even understand the case.

616
00:38:34,820 --> 00:38:36,770
所以我有律師
I have lawyers for that.

617
00:38:36,820 --> 00:38:39,070
那?
Then what?

618
00:38:41,160 --> 00:38:43,940
你們去外面等吧
You boys can wait outside.

619
00:38:48,450 --> 00:38:52,110
說真的 你讓我刮目相看
So I got to be honest, I was impressed by you.

620
00:38:52,170 --> 00:38:54,030
沒錯 你的事業是完蛋了
Sure, your career's finished,

621
00:38:54,090 --> 00:38:56,290
但你這個短線玩的很不錯
but you played a great short game.

622
00:38:56,290 --> 00:38:58,920
賭得很大 而且得到了你想要的
You took a big gamble, and you got what you wanted.

623
00:38:58,960 --> 00:39:02,170
但你要錯了東西
It was just, you know, the wrong thing to want.

624
00:39:09,430 --> 00:39:11,300
關你什么事?
What do you care?

625
00:39:11,350 --> 00:39:14,270
你在萬安公司的時候 我觀察過你
You know, I looked into you over there at Allsafe.

626
00:39:14,310 --> 00:39:15,890
這么說吧 很多人
I mean, lots of people

627
00:39:15,940 --> 00:39:17,720
要是經歷了你經歷的那些破事
would've settled into middle management bliss

628
00:39:17,780 --> 00:39:19,140
能坐到中層的位置就滿足了
after all the shit you've taken,

629
00:39:19,140 --> 00:39:20,810
但你沒有
but you didn't.

630
00:39:20,810 --> 00:39:22,450
你冷酷無情 機智過人 這兩點結合起來
You're relentless and smart, and that combination

631
00:39:22,480 --> 00:39:26,320
對很多大人物 是很有價值的
is very valuable to a lot of important people,

632
00:39:26,320 --> 00:39:28,820
比如一些我認識的人
people I know.

633
00:39:28,820 --> 00:39:32,320
你說了這么多 到底想干嘛?
Where are you going with all of this?

634
00:39:32,320 --> 00:39:36,880
我想我可以幫你搞到一份非常有利可圖的工作
I think I can land you a pretty lucrative gig.

635
00:39:39,830 --> 00:39:43,500
什么工作? 哪家公司?
A gig? Where?

636
00:39:43,550 --> 00:39:46,670
當然是你最喜歡的公司咯
Your favorite place, where else?

637
00:39:50,140 --> 00:39:53,840
你大老遠親自趕到澤西來
You slummed it all the way down to Jersey in person

638
00:39:53,900 --> 00:39:58,180
就為了讓我給我正在起訴的公司打工?
to offer me a job at the company I'm currently suing?

639
00:39:58,180 --> 00:40:00,350
你到底想干什么?
What's the real ask here?

640
00:40:00,400 --> 00:40:02,520
我認為你會成為一位成功的女實業家
I think you'd make a great business woman.

641
00:40:02,520 --> 00:40:05,440
恐怕也僅此而已
I'm afraid it's nothing more than that.

642
00:40:05,490 --> 00:40:07,020
- 是在開玩笑嗎? - 不是玩笑
- Is this a joke? - It's no joke.

643
00:40:07,030 --> 00:40:08,940
我的朋友們覺得你能幫我們干成大事
My pals think you can bring a lot to the table.

644
00:40:08,990 --> 00:40:11,190
你不能給我這么一份工作
You can't be offering me a job there.

645
00:40:11,200 --> 00:40:13,200
你是我的控方證人
You're testifying against them.

646
00:40:13,250 --> 00:40:15,030
你很快就會明白的
So, you'll find this out fairly soon,

647
00:40:15,080 --> 00:40:18,200
但做生意的 哪有什么積怨啊
but in business, grudges aren't really a thing.

648
00:40:18,250 --> 00:40:19,620
那是意氣用事
It's too emotional.

649
00:40:19,670 --> 00:40:21,340
因為你做成了這件事
It's because you pulled off

650
00:40:21,370 --> 00:40:23,210
他們才打電話給我的
what you pulled off that they called me.

651
00:40:23,260 --> 00:40:26,340
這可是一樁大型集體訴訟
This is a huge class action lawsuit.

652
00:40:26,380 --> 00:40:28,380
賠償金就會有好幾百萬
They are going to pay millions.

653
00:40:28,380 --> 00:40:31,050
大概7500萬到1億吧
Roughly 75 to 100 million.

654
00:40:31,050 --> 00:40:33,300
但這是他們的律師會接受的數字
I mean, that's what their lawyers will settle for

655
00:40:33,350 --> 00:40:35,550
在將來七年里 你的律師團所有的資金
after they exhaust most of your legal team's funds

656
00:40:35,600 --> 00:40:37,640
都被他們在消耗殆盡后
for the next seven years.

657
00:40:37,690 --> 00:40:39,390
沒錯 的確是一大筆錢
And sure, that is-- that's a lot of money,

658
00:40:39,440 --> 00:40:41,560
但對他們來說算不上大數目
but not to them, not really.

659
00:40:41,560 --> 00:40:43,230
我們早就啟動了一項應急基金
We started a rainy-day fund

660
00:40:43,280 --> 00:40:45,730
來應對泄密 也就是現在這種情況
when the leak happened just for this occasion.

661
00:40:45,780 --> 00:40:48,900
基金本身就已經賺了賠償金的五倍那么多了
The fund itself has already made five times that amount.

662
00:40:57,630 --> 00:40:59,710
我要請你離開
I'd like to ask you to leave.

663
00:40:59,740 --> 00:41:00,990
需要我把你的名字報上去嗎?
Shall I pass your name along then?

664
00:41:01,050 --> 00:41:02,830
我不會去那里工作的
I'm not working there.

665
00:41:02,880 --> 00:41:04,410
他們殺了我的母親
They killed my mother.

666
00:41:04,470 --> 00:41:06,250
街角的每一家快餐連鎖
And every fast food joint around the corner

667
00:41:06,300 --> 00:41:08,920
都是數以萬計的糖尿病病情的元兇
delivers diabetes to millions of people.

668
00:41:08,970 --> 00:41:11,550
菲利普 莫里斯煙草公司更是對世界肺癌做出了不朽的貢獻
Phillip Morris hands out lung cancer on the hour, every hour.

669
00:41:11,590 --> 00:41:12,960
這么跟你說吧
I mean, hell,

670
00:41:13,120 --> 00:41:16,560
每個人都在破壞地球 大家都沒回頭路好走
everyone's destroying the planet beyond the point of no return.

671
00:41:16,590 --> 00:41:18,930
難道對所有這些事
Are you really gonna start taking all of these things

672
00:41:18,980 --> 00:41:20,100
你都要這么感情用事?
so personally?

673
00:41:20,150 --> 00:41:21,680
或許吧
Maybe I will.

674
00:41:21,730 --> 00:41:23,270
或許必須有個人這么做
Maybe someone has to.

675
00:41:23,320 --> 00:41:24,430
給你個建議:
A suggestion:

676
00:41:24,490 --> 00:41:26,240
如果你想改變什么
If you want to change things,

677
00:41:26,270 --> 00:41:30,940
或許你該從它的內部開始
perhaps you should try from within,

678
00:41:30,990 --> 00:41:36,250
因為現在這些都是發生在外部的
because this is what happens from the outside.

679
00:41:36,280 --> 00:41:37,950
那些人不等人的
These guys don't wait on anyone,

680
00:41:38,000 --> 00:41:40,450
你最晚明天給他們答復
so you'll have to let them know by tomorrow.

681
00:41:42,000 --> 00:41:44,250
我自己出去
I'll show myself out.

682
00:42:08,570 --> 00:42:11,130
這些都是空的
These are all empty.

683
00:42:11,170 --> 00:42:16,670
你是不是裝滿了就扔?
Are you just filling them and dumping them?

684
00:42:16,730 --> 00:42:19,680
新的處方在哪里?
Where are your new 'scrips?

685
00:42:19,680 --> 00:42:22,350
吃不吃藥有什么關系?
What does it matter?

686
00:42:22,400 --> 00:42:27,980
我都分不清真假了
I don't even know what's real any more.

687
00:42:28,020 --> 00:42:31,020
聽著 我知道你現在感覺很糟
Look, I know you feel shitty right now,

688
00:42:31,070 --> 00:42:32,520
但吃了藥...
but once you take your meds--

689
00:42:32,520 --> 00:42:35,780
或許我們該停下來 戴琳
Maybe we should stop it, Darlene.

690
00:42:35,830 --> 00:42:38,030
停下什么?
Stop what?

691
00:42:38,030 --> 00:42:39,860
計劃
The plan.

692
00:42:39,920 --> 00:42:41,450
黑客 一切的一切
The hack. Everything.

693
00:42:41,500 --> 00:42:43,700
我們或許不該執行的
Maybe we shouldn't execute it.

694
00:42:43,750 --> 00:42:46,040
什么? 為什么?
What? Why?

695
00:42:46,040 --> 00:42:48,710
我們被感染的服務器一旦回到主網絡
The minute our infected server gets back on the main network,

696
00:42:48,710 --> 00:42:51,880
- 就萬事大吉了 - 當時那個人不是我
- we're set. - It wasn't me.

697
00:42:51,930 --> 00:42:57,510
整件事情 一直以來 都不是我在做
The whole time, it wasn't really me doing all of that.

698
00:42:57,550 --> 00:43:02,690
伊利艾特 我們做這件事的理由
Elliot, the reasons we wanted to do this,

699
00:43:02,720 --> 00:43:05,020
我們所有人做這件事的理由
the reasons why we all wanted to do this,

700
00:43:05,060 --> 00:43:08,060
是真實的
are real.

701
00:43:08,060 --> 00:43:12,560
可能你沒意識到吧 但這的確是你的點子
Maybe you don't realize this, but this was your idea.

702
00:43:12,560 --> 00:43:16,230
是你想到的
You came up with this.

703
00:43:16,240 --> 00:43:19,240
在你內心深處 有一部分
There is a part of you. somewhere deep down inside,

704
00:43:19,290 --> 00:43:22,620
知道這么做是對的
that knows this is the right thing to do.

705
00:43:26,750 --> 00:43:28,410
我去取你的藥
I'm gonna get your meds.

706
00:43:28,410 --> 00:43:30,580
回來了我們再聊 好嗎?
We'll talk more when I get back, okay?

707
00:43:35,550 --> 00:43:36,890
來吧
Come on.

708
00:43:46,270 --> 00:43:49,680
你要是我 會怎么做?
What would you do if you were in my shoes?

709
00:43:49,740 --> 00:43:52,770
我知道 我知道 我是真的瘋了
I know. I know, I'm officially crazy,

710
00:43:52,770 --> 00:43:56,410
但這個計劃并不瘋狂 對嗎?
but the plan isn't, is it?

711
00:44:05,280 --> 00:44:06,250
你他媽在...
What the hell are you--

712
00:44:06,290 --> 00:44:07,670
噓
Shh.

713
00:44:23,970 --> 00:44:27,440
我一直等在你房子外面 一直等到她離開
I've been waiting outside your apartment until she left.

714
00:44:27,470 --> 00:44:30,640
不想讓任何人知道我在這兒
Didn't want anyone to know I'm here.

715
00:44:30,690 --> 00:44:32,640
我知道你是幕后主使
I know you're behind it,

716
00:44:32,640 --> 00:44:36,480
所有的事 F社會 服務器
all of it, F society, the server,

717
00:44:36,530 --> 00:44:38,980
科爾比 萬安
Colby, Allsafe.

718
00:44:39,030 --> 00:44:42,490
你是變量海洋中的一粟常量
You're the one constant in a sea of variables.

719
00:44:50,500 --> 00:44:54,410
伊利艾特...
Elliot...

720
00:44:54,470 --> 00:44:58,500
我不知道你的宏大計劃是什么
now, I don't know what your grand plan is,

721
00:44:58,550 --> 00:45:00,840
但我得知道 你得告訴我
but I need to, and you're going to tell me.

722
00:45:11,980 --> 00:45:17,820
兩天前我徒手掐死了一個女人
Two days ago I strangled a woman to death just with my hands.

723
00:45:17,860 --> 00:45:20,820
我感到了一種異樣的感覺
That's a strange sensation.

724
00:45:25,450 --> 00:45:27,360
生死攸關的事
Something so tremendous done

725
00:45:27,370 --> 00:45:30,370
做起來卻輕而易舉
by something so simple.

726
00:45:33,170 --> 00:45:38,210
前十秒鐘是不太舒服
The first ten seconds were...uncomfortable,

727
00:45:38,210 --> 00:45:40,840
有點像在地獄邊境
a feeling of limbo,

728
00:45:40,880 --> 00:45:42,550
接著你的肌肉緊繃
but then your muscles tense,

729
00:45:42,600 --> 00:45:46,220
她又在那里掙扎反抗
and she struggles and fights,

730
00:45:46,270 --> 00:45:48,220
但這卻又幾乎和世界上的其他一切
but it almost disappears in the background

731
00:45:48,270 --> 00:45:52,860
一起消失在背景之中
along with everything else in the world.

732
00:45:52,890 --> 00:45:58,560
在那一刻 就只有你和絕對的權力
At that moment it's just you and absolute power,

733
00:45:58,560 --> 00:46:03,480
此外無他
nothing else.

734
00:46:03,540 --> 00:46:05,900
那一刻永駐我心
That moment stayed with me.

735
00:46:11,080 --> 00:46:14,910
原以為成了殺人犯 我會有罪惡感
I thought I'd feel guilty for being a murderer,

736
00:46:14,960 --> 00:46:19,580
然而我并沒有
but...I don't.

737
00:46:19,640 --> 00:46:21,970
我只感到了奇妙
I feel wonder.

738
00:46:43,590 --> 00:46:45,560
你搞了多久了？
How long has this been going on?

739
00:46:48,000 --> 00:46:48,720
我不知道
I don't know.

740
00:46:56,340 --> 00:46:58,240
那你干的到底是什么？
And what is it that you're doing exactly?

741
00:46:59,020 --> 00:47:00,480
給所有文件加密
Encrypting all the files.

742
00:47:03,040 --> 00:47:05,150
邪惡公司所有的財政記錄
All of Evil Corp's financial records

743
00:47:05,200 --> 00:47:07,000
是碰都碰不著的
will be impossible to access.

744
00:47:07,740 --> 00:47:09,400
加密鑰匙在程序完成后
The encryption key will self-delete

745
00:47:09,410 --> 00:47:11,120
會自動銷毀
after the process completes.

746
00:47:11,400 --> 00:47:12,320
備份呢？
What about the backups?

747
00:47:12,330 --> 00:47:13,420
我關心的是這個
I took care of that too.

748
00:47:14,640 --> 00:47:15,760
中國那邊...鐵山...
China. Steel Mountain.

749
00:47:17,340 --> 00:47:19,520
當然了 就算我們用了冗余數據
Of course, even when we went redundant.

750
00:47:19,530 --> 00:47:21,160
我黑掉了整個云上夢幻網絡
I hacked the Air Dream network.

751
00:47:22,120 --> 00:47:23,300
我無所不在
I was in all of them.

752
00:47:24,620 --> 00:47:26,060
你真是考慮周全啊
You really thought of everything.

753
00:47:28,560 --> 00:47:29,740
你還有什么同伙嗎?
Who else was involved?

754
00:47:32,880 --> 00:47:34,000
只有我
Just me.

755
00:47:38,300 --> 00:47:40,280
好 現在還有我了
Well, now it's you and me.

756
00:47:41,720 --> 00:47:44,130
伊利艾特 我早就說過 有一天我們會合作的
I've always told you we'd end up working together, Elliot.

757
00:47:48,250 --> 00:47:51,770
但我還是要知道
But still, I have to know.

758
00:47:52,850 --> 00:47:54,360
你為什么這么做?
Why did you do it?

759
00:47:58,540 --> 00:48:01,470
你做這些 歸根結底是為了什么?
What did you hope to accomplish by doing all of this?

760
00:48:07,240 --> 00:48:07,860
我不知道
I don't know.

761
00:48:17,000 --> 00:48:18,480
我想拯救世界
I wanted to save the world.

