[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 职员,MingLiU,16,&H00E8E8E8,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.5,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 标题,汉仪双线体简,40,&H001C1DB6,&H0021218D,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0.1,7,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 特效标记,微软雅黑,13,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fscx60\fscy70\\pos(40.2,257.6)}{\fad(0,2000)\an7\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(56.4,257.6)}{\p1\bord0\shad0\pos(192,148)}m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,2000)\an5\fscy0\t(0,300,\fscy100)\pos(43,270.8)}{\fs9}EVERYONE
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.31,0:00:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what do we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.61,0:00:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.12,0:00:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Washington Township toxic waste scandal.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.85,0:00:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do we need to prove our case?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Someone who was there
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.79,0:00:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.54,0:00:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Get the hell away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.92,0:00:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Get away from my home.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.11,0:00:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot, what is going on with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.23,0:00:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I cannot help you if you keep me in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.88,0:00:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We got problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.31,0:00:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The Dark Army is bailing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.18,0:00:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's not over.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.28,0:00:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll find a way, just not tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.38,0:00:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.17,0:00:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want to watch me piss too?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Scott, a misunderstand--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.94,0:00:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Happy to pull my dick out for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.82,0:00:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.04,0:00:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.87,0:00:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Told you you'd get her back, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.99,0:01:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.11,0:02:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.56,0:02:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Open up!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.35,0:02:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm bleeding all over the hallway!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's a life-or-death situation out here!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.42,0:02:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, I know you're in there. I just saw you go in.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.45,0:02:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Open up!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm lo--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.60,0:02:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, are you just gonna stand there?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.84,0:02:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Get me a glass of water, dummy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.49,0:02:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can I use this? Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.31,0:02:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My niece gave him to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.14,0:02:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I haven't even named him yet. God.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.25,0:02:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you know the pressure of an ecstatic six-year-old?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.20,0:02:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, I kill that thing, and her whole world collapses.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.24,0:02:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I like what you did with the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.15,0:02:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, nice setup. Still like mine better though.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.94,0:03:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yo, let me know if you want a top-shelf hookup.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.49,0:03:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Actually, now that I have you...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.84,0:03:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Will you help me move a dresser...Mr. Muscles?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.67,0:03:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, come on. Just come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.00,0:03:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Man 'n' van is getting way too legit.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.27,0:03:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They used to just be, like, drummers
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.57,0:03:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with their mom's Honda Odysseys.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.99,0:03:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now it's an actual company in Queens.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.52,0:03:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, the guys are literally men in vans.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.81,0:03:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd buy morphine from you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.31,0:03:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}if you could also get me suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.64,0:03:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, um, it's pretty much impossible to get suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.58,0:03:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My supplier doesn't have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.46,0:04:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I saw this song live once. It was so rad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.47,0:04:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't you just love hearing your favorite songs in person,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.93,0:04:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}like, half deaf from the speakers,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.47,0:04:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}everyone going nuts around you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.49,0:04:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.27,0:04:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Direct. I respect that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.49,0:04:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I just hate concerts.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.94,0:04:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Lots of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.35,0:04:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You don't like people, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.91,0:04:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not most of them, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.94,0:04:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.37,0:04:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, so by that rationale,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.38,0:04:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}if you were to really like one person, it'd be, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.54,0:04:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}considered an aberration or an abnormality
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}or special, even.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.55,0:04:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.68,0:04:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, I aim for special,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.70,0:04:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so challenge accepted.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wish we already knew each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.59,0:05:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Would make this feel less awkward.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.78,0:05:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You really feel awkward right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.64,0:05:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.27,0:05:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, then I wish we knew each other too then.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.15,0:05:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, yikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.48,0:05:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I, um, I'm late. Meeting the girls for drinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.31,0:05:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, um, I'm Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.26,0:05:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.62,0:05:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, I do know of a guy who sells Suboxone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.07,0:05:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's supposed to be a fucking psychopath,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.25,0:05:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but if you want, I can call him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.28,0:05:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You might be worth a psychopath.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.80,0:05:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know. Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.40,0:06:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, and keep the fish, you filthy animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.44,0:06:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sorry I haven't talked to you in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.27,0:06:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, it's only been a month, which I guess
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.79,0:06:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in the grand scheme of things isn't that long.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.85,0:06:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Isn't our life like a blip
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.27,0:06:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in the cosmic calender or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.45,0:06:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So that's Shayla.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.21,0:06:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A blip.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.92,0:06:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not even.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.65,0:06:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here one blip, gone the next.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.10,0:06:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Makes me hate myself that I've already gotten used to
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.49,0:06:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the idea of her not being here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.43,0:06:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}In a year, I'll maybe think about her
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.38,0:06:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}every once in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.15,0:07:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then she'll become an anecdote, a thing to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.85,0:07:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}"I knew a girl that died,"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.15,0:07:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with the added bonus of, "She died because of me."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.07,0:07:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe I should hate myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.25,0:07:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here are the last two forms.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She's getting rid of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.24,0:07:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in case you're still trying to figure that out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.46,0:07:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Once I... - Sign on the bottom.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.13,0:07:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then I'll deliver it to the court,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.13,0:07:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and in two weeks' time, you'll receive
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.65,0:07:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}an official release from the mandate.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.27,0:07:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That second form means that we've been sitting in this room for a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.10,0:07:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Over 52 hours of Krista's voice bouncing around this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.19,0:07:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She thinks she's a wasted echo. Maybe she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.03,0:07:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wonder how much time I've spent
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.62,0:07:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}not listening to her in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.71,0:07:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm worried about you, Elliot.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.76,0:07:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I really want you to keep coming here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.17,0:07:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We've got a lot more work to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.69,0:07:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She wants more from me
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.00,0:07:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but she doesn't believe in me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.66,0:07:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I tried because I believe some part inside of you
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.92,0:07:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}wants to do this right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.12,0:07:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.56,0:07:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you on her side?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.31,0:08:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You should clean your sockets.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.48,0:08:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sounds too good to be true, but I'll bite.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.06,0:08:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's the ask?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.64,0:08:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Given my client has information
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.06,0:08:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that could help your client's case,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.16,0:08:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}we want the meeting restricted to her, Colby, and myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.44,0:08:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And we want it conducted off-record.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.71,0:08:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Antara, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.48,0:08:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My client won't accept your presence.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.17,0:08:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Our client pays for ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.70,0:08:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then you're duty-bound to present him
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.42,0:09:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with any legitimate offer of beneficial evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.37,0:09:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.88,0:09:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Give us something truly legitimate and beneficial.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.33,0:09:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You won't even tell us what the hell your client has.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.01,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Seth, we've been sitting on opposite sides
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.98,0:09:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of the negotiating table for two decades.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.55,0:09:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm not some joker come out of the woodwork
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}trying to scam Colby for millions.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.94,0:09:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm giving him the only glimmer of hope he's had.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.10,0:09:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll pass along your offer. Thanks for your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.96,0:09:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Lloyd said you wanted to see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.33,0:09:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, I appreciate your commitment to this job.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:09:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I really do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.30,0:10:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But I don't see how you've plowed through
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}these last few weeks, so
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.67,0:10:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want to offer you some time off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.56,0:10:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Just some time to... - I don't need time off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.11,0:10:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm good.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.48,0:10:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Uh...Uh, one more thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.63,0:10:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm so sorry she was taken away, Elliot,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.42,0:10:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but don't let her death close you off entirely.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.89,0:10:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Find someone you can be your honest self with,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.57,0:10:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.50,0:10:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I remember when I was a kid, I got into web design
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.77,0:10:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}by ripping off sites I liked.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.16,0:10:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All you had to do was view source on your browser
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.27,0:10:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and there it was, the code.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.93,0:10:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You could copy-paste it, modify it a little,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.12,0:10:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Put your name on it, and like that, it was your site.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}View source.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.81,0:11:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What if we had that for people?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.13,0:11:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Would people really want to see?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.99,0:11:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Find someone to be your honest self with?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.76,0:11:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.92,0:11:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Really good advice. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.60,0:11:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I quote, "The U.S. contingent of the hacker group fsociety
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.37,0:11:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}has remained quiet since the upheaval inflicted
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.09,0:11:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}upon the world's largest multinational conglomerate.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.67,0:11:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.14,0:11:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}released a statement today stating that,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.15,0:11:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}'these groups lack the resources and knowledge
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.11,0:11:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of the U.S. cell to successfully mount an attack.'"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.42,0:11:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}End quote.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.39,0:11:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, so?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.80,0:11:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We gotta get the Dark Army back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.42,0:12:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Dude, I've been trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.79,0:12:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How many times do you want me to hack him?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.39,0:12:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you know how hard hacking a hacker is?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.89,0:12:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Cisco switches OSes, like, all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.03,0:12:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Darlene, we need one meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.06,0:12:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, well, I've been using Cisco's handle
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.48,0:12:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to send requests for the past month.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.57,0:12:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's slower than me, but not by much.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.32,0:12:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If we can talk to WhiteRose directly...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.02,0:12:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}WhiteRose? WhiteRose?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.48,0:12:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, if--if the guy even exists,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.22,0:12:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and that's a big if,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.94,0:12:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}no way he's meeting you face-to-face.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.94,0:12:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}For all we know...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.39,0:12:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This dude's WhiteRose.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.26,0:12:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Excuse me!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.35,0:12:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you WhiteRose?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.28,0:12:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A likely story.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.74,0:12:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}'sides, the tape backups already shipped
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.67,0:13:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to all the new Steel Mountain facilities,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.74,0:13:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and we still haven't found a way around that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got a plan in motion.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.64,0:13:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And god's laughing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.37,0:13:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is all I have left of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.90,0:13:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will miss her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.21,0:13:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I need to wipe again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.49,0:14:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So if you scroll to the next page,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.29,0:14:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you'll see the summary of capital budgets
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.17,0:14:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}for purchasing and operations.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We get it. The goddamn earning reports
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.90,0:14:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}are gonna look good come monday.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.75,0:14:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Our aim is to facilitate bill payment
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.54,0:14:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and heighten financial security,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.20,0:14:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so that's an extra 2%.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.10,0:14:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, if we hadn't turned our profits around,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.63,0:14:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- I was gonna leave. - No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.10,0:14:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where? Don't tell me apple.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.12,0:14:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Google. - Don't buy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.18,0:14:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got a blow job from the hiring executive
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.14,0:14:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}on the Googleplex volleyball court.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.50,0:14:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, she was hot. Had a Marissa Mayer thing going on, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.88,0:14:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hot execs started as hot assistants
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.43,0:14:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}who fucked their way to the top
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.17,0:14:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}twice as fast as the rest of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.15,0:14:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know something screwed up?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.32,0:14:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I heard that, some assistants, they're going gay
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.66,0:15:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to move up the ladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.64,0:15:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll do you one better.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.77,0:15:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There's a special handful
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.49,0:15:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of pathetically desperate execs going cock jockey.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.79,0:15:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No. Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.51,0:15:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, Dwight, I meant to ask. How are your children?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.16,0:15:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hell if I know. Sent 'em off to Lawrence.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.55,0:15:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think Julia likes art.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.56,0:15:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, well. Can't win 'em all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.76,0:15:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Lawrence?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.43,0:15:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You'll never be able
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.26,0:15:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to afford that tuition on unemployment.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.57,0:15:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Sorry? - You're fired!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.04,0:15:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You two as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.15,0:15:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm making sure you all receive the minimum severance packages.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.59,0:15:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mr. Wellick, I-I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.49,0:15:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What did we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.83,0:16:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.40,0:16:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- After... - You said you would update me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.31,0:16:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I needed to discuss our situation
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.97,0:16:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with the state's attorney.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.16,0:16:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thanks for coming in, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.11,0:16:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think you should have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.45,0:16:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Colby's lawyers called 30 minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.53,0:16:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They wanted a promise of total immunity before the meeting,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.24,0:16:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}which I obtained from the man you just met.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.92,0:16:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, yes, Colby agreed...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.99,0:16:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with a caveat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.28,0:16:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't be in the room. You have to go in alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.48,0:16:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, you made a ballsy move...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.02,0:17:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But you doing what you're about to do...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.45,0:17:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}entering the home of a very powerful man
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.73,0:17:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with a lot at stake and asking him for something...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.46,0:17:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's always a dangerous proposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.39,0:17:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So one last time...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.86,0:17:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you sure you want to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.13,0:17:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shit, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.67,0:17:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thought you was one of them high schoolers
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.18,0:17:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}stole my mom's chaise lounge.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.64,0:17:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}As heartbreaking as it is to hear that,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you're gonna have to put that off.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Getting everybody back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.03,0:17:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Come on. - No, man, not this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.66,0:17:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.22,0:17:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't be out. We need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.28,0:17:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, man, I got a new set of people depending on me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.46,0:17:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Clients out the wazoo.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.63,0:17:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, you know, I mean, good luck,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and tell the kids I said hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.54,0:18:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What is this? What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.40,0:18:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, I figured out how to insert
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.65,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}THC's genetic information code into yeast cells.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.30,0:18:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tripled my earning speed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.97,0:18:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Plants need weeks to develop. Microbes need days.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.45,0:18:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what, you got a bath and body works
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.69,0:18:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}bottling facility in your backyard?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.96,0:18:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.81,0:18:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The THC level is borderline in that blend,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.25,0:18:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and the lavender doesn't mess with the high.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You just smooth it on your skin.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.33,0:18:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So you're rejecting a revolution in favor of aroma profiles?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.75,0:18:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What a waste of potential.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.51,0:18:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, man, I know I got a good brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.88,0:18:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Besides...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.83,0:18:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What was our little project in the end, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.18,0:18:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Wasted shit, if you ask me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.61,0:18:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, now you're borderline pissing me off.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.03,0:18:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that a fact?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.81,0:18:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And what exactly are you gonna do
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.39,0:18:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}if I decide to cross that border?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.34,0:18:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look at my face, Romero.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.83,0:19:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You and I both know I'm crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.20,0:19:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not the cute kind either.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.87,0:19:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm talking crazy crazy!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.33,0:19:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You lost touch.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.00,0:19:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You forgot the feeling of spilling blood
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.52,0:19:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}on the battlefield by winning the fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.86,0:19:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.24,0:19:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I love you, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.27,0:19:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I just wanted you to come back to the arcade with me
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.30,0:19:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so we could change the world together.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.95,0:19:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I am clearly too crazy for you to say no to.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.42,0:19:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look on your face is priceless!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.40,0:19:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Goddamn lunatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.10,0:19:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You gave me your word when we started this thing
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.95,0:19:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that you'd finish it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.06,0:19:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I gave you my word what I'd do if you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.33,0:19:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}See you back at the arcade.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.88,0:20:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Good. I see the girl got you tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.82,0:20:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, let's get started.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How much do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.74,0:20:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Write your number.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.07,0:20:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can ask me anything you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.66,0:20:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but I promise you, at the end of the day,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.82,0:20:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}money will always be better than what you're looking for.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.51,0:20:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mr. Colby, did you attend
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.86,0:20:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the executive board meetings during 1993?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.22,0:21:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Were you in the room when the decision was made
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.09,0:21:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to ignore the treatment of hazardous waste
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.25,0:21:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in Washington Township?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.98,0:21:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have information which can help you...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.71,0:21:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}if you answer my question.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.62,0:21:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.81,0:21:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you agree to testify against the executives
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.67,0:21:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}who covered up the illegal dumping of expoxy resin waste,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.12,0:21:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will testify that I broke chain of custody
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.22,0:21:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with the dat file central to your case.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.28,0:21:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're that hot little thing
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.33,0:21:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that came by here a month ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.43,0:21:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The girl from Allsafe.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.55,0:21:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I remember, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.74,0:22:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay...I'm gonna answer your question.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.27,0:22:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But here's what I need from you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.62,0:22:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So I'm gonna pull down my pants,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.50,0:22:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and then I'm gonna need you to take that pouty mouth of yours
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.63,0:22:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and swallow up my balls.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.88,0:22:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now, they're big and hairy, especially the left one,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.28,0:22:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so you're really gonna have to, I don't know,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.52,0:22:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}squish 'em up to get 'em inside there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.86,0:22:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're probably gonna have to do one cheek at a time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.66,0:22:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But then, once they're all warm and snug in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.59,0:22:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want you to repeat your question to me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.86,0:22:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}as clearly as you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.03,0:22:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then, and only then, am I willing to answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.34,0:22:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you don't take this deal...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.14,0:23:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you'll become like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.92,0:23:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sure, maybe you'll live in this house...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.56,0:23:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe you'll have money,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.38,0:23:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but even if your expensive lawyers find a way to get you off,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.89,0:23:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}people will still think that you're guilty.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.40,0:23:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Losing everyone's respect...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.31,0:23:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the respect of people you know and the people you don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.33,0:23:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's a shitty feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.06,0:23:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.40,0:24:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll have "the girl" let me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.00,0:24:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Flipper. Is she microchipped?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.50,0:24:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, very good.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.35,0:24:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Housekeeping done.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.72,0:24:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now onto the real business.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.98,0:24:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Has your dog ever eaten trash before?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.11,0:24:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No. I mean, not that I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.13,0:24:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, lucky for your bank account,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.77,0:24:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The piece is small enough to pass on its own.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.52,0:24:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Unfortunately, though, it's large enough
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.27,0:24:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to send her puking all over your apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.56,0:25:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So I would crate her for a few days and monitor her.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.44,0:25:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She won't know what you're doing is good for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.40,0:25:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You were right. I was only trying to prove--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.05,0:25:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Colby's lawyers just called. He wants to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.91,0:25:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Get back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.18,0:25:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's a little early in the morning to be nerding out,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.88,0:25:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}don't you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.82,0:25:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.04,0:25:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I knew if I asked you that--
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.99,0:25:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.51,0:25:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Couple weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.67,0:26:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And you had the balls to ask for WhiteRose with my shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.24,0:26:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's like you want to get us both killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.24,0:26:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What happened? He responded?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.82,0:26:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.26,0:26:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you didn't have to make me look like a shitty foot soldier.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.19,0:26:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Nobody would ever even know--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.37,0:26:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You got root on my box and found the IP,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.58,0:26:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}then you joined their channel with my handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.67,0:26:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We're so done.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.39,0:26:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't want to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.73,0:26:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But you fools actually got your wish.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.83,0:26:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know why,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.34,0:26:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but the meeting's actually gonna be on.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.78,0:26:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd tell you to be careful,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.90,0:26:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but I know that's the last thing you're gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.90,0:27:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My lawyers are looking over the paperwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.90,0:27:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Does that mean that-- - exactly what I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.55,0:27:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I asked you back here to make sure that you can pull off your testimony,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.69,0:27:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}make sure that this chain of custody, story of yours is straight.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.86,0:27:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't afford any trips.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.11,0:27:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm not going to trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.78,0:27:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what--
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.95,0:27:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's in this for you, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.86,0:27:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know you hate me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.83,0:27:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what, you're gonna just let me off scot-free?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.28,0:27:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you get out of this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.57,0:27:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Earlier, I asked you a question.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.08,0:27:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You never answered it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.27,0:27:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If I'm agreeing to testify in your case, then,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.12,0:28:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}yes, you know, I attended several meetings.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.27,0:28:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tell me about the one when they decided to ignore the leak.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.41,0:28:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm--I'm not sure what you're asking.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.27,0:28:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What was the meeting like when you decided this?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.82,0:28:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.29,0:28:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want to know, like, what was it like?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.29,0:28:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Like, um, did we all have cigars and laugh hysterically
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.32,0:28:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}as we signed the evil documents?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.62,0:28:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that what you pictured?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.39,0:28:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, I'm sorry, hon.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.49,0:28:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}See, the world doesn't work like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.31,0:28:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tell me. Tell me how it works.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.77,0:28:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Uh, Jesus, um...All right, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.38,0:28:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Let's see. January, '93.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.40,0:28:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, my secretary then was Elaine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.09,0:28:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So Elaine brought us a platter of shrimp cocktail
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.50,0:28:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to tide us to dinner, which pissed us off
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.72,0:29:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}because we just had a platter at the holiday party.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.18,0:29:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jim opened the bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.46,0:29:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now Jim was a real piece of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.18,0:29:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, half pansy, half Mafia.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.66,0:29:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}First sign of a tight decision, he'd be chain smoking
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.94,0:29:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}down a river of Scotch.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.20,0:29:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, it rained.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.79,0:29:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It rained. I remember that, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.89,0:29:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.27,0:29:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You were drunk, eating shrimp cockail,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.90,0:29:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and it was raining when you decided my mother would die?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.65,0:29:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's why.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.86,0:29:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So people like you won't keep sitting in rooms together.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.27,0:30:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Did any of it ever give you or anyone pause
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.94,0:30:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}when you made those decisions?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.29,0:30:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.48,0:30:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.68,0:30:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.79,0:30:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}then you go home, and, uh, and you have dinner,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.27,0:30:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you know, and--and you wake up the next morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.61,0:30:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here's to a man who has a bright future at our company,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.18,0:30:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a man you all know,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.53,0:30:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a man who is going to change this company for the good,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.33,0:30:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a man smart enough to marry a woman every bit his equal...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.87,0:31:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Our new Chief Technology Officer, Scott Knowles.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.79,0:31:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here, here!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.60,0:31:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.28,0:31:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Thank you, Phillip. - Welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.85,0:31:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Thank you very much. - Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.02,0:31:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's great to be here. And we're off.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.97,0:31:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Thanks, Phillip. - You're very welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.55,0:31:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Congratulations, darling. - Thank you, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.72,0:31:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, Joe, how are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.35,0:31:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.90,0:31:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tyrell, nice to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.23,0:31:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.48,0:31:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I hear you shared our moment with your husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.10,0:31:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, come on. That was over a month ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.20,0:31:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't tell me you're still sore.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.18,0:32:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hmm, I sense some defeat.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.56,0:32:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, I considered myself, at the very least, reprimanded.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.59,0:32:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How disappointing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.24,0:32:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}One tiny curveball and you gave up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.79,0:32:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Miss.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.94,0:32:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.32,0:32:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Should have known that you were nothing more than a bold entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.58,0:32:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you saying you don't crave a bold entrance
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.95,0:32:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}every time, over and over, sustained?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.36,0:32:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Meet me tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.45,0:32:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm a little busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.16,0:32:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come to my office now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.54,0:32:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Are you really asking me that?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.16,0:32:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't recall phrasing it as a question, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.52,0:32:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Fine, then I just won't show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.53,0:32:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Then the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.63,0:32:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Take the back stairwell.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.04,0:32:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The cameras have been out since March.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.23,0:32:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No one will know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.47,0:33:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, you just made a long day longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.99,0:33:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I know that Allsafe will have to fire me,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.74,0:33:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but testifying was the right thing to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.61,0:33:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have worked my ass off to take care of you
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.48,0:33:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and of every person in this company.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.09,0:33:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you know what that means?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.25,0:33:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You've been a great boss, Gideon--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.61,0:33:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}See, once this confession goes public,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.34,0:33:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}no one will want to do business with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.27,0:33:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The company will go under.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.93,0:33:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I couldn't let Colby take the fall
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.90,0:33:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- for something that I did. - Oh, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.83,0:33:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You and I both know you didn't break chain of custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.73,0:33:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I did and I feel terrible--
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.80,0:33:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Angela! Please! Stop lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.46,0:33:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You do this... All these people go down,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.02,0:33:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}all their families
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.20,0:33:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that rely on what this company provides for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.16,0:34:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So this is where the rabbit hole leads?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.74,0:34:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Got to be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.41,0:34:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I half-expected you not to show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.77,0:34:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And I half-expected you to be a tattletale.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.60,0:34:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So you are sore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.30,0:34:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, come on. You intrigued me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.01,0:34:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I intrigued back.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.52,0:34:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can't we just be more straightforward?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.65,0:34:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, that's no fun, but if you insist,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.87,0:34:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I just came up here to see if you were really
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.62,0:34:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}as gullible as you seem.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.61,0:34:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My husband's downstairs getting the job that you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.95,0:34:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and you're up here trying to fuck me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.99,0:34:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now whether that's you being straightforward or a game,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.32,0:34:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}either way, it's played pretty poorly, if you ask me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.61,0:34:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Again, I asked no question.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.09,0:34:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All I can tell you is you need this
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.48,0:34:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}'cause you're dissatisfied.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.26,0:35:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Scott plans on firing you,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.39,0:35:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You seem desperate.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.39,0:36:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you-- get off of me!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.78,0:36:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.33,0:38:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We connected with WhiteRose.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.49,0:38:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The plan is back on.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.74,0:38:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I could bullshit you, tell you you're the only person
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.23,0:38:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}who can fill the exact void we have at fsociety.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.80,0:38:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The truth is, I need this group back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.41,0:38:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Have you ever considered which part of our scheme motivates you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.54,0:38:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}When the Dark Army bailed,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.94,0:38:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you didn't care if pushing a button
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.19,0:38:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}would bring an economic revolution.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.63,0:38:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want momentary anarchy.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.94,0:38:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The others?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.37,0:38:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mobley likes palling around.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.49,0:38:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Romero wants a whiff of fame.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.04,0:38:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Those reasons depress me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.62,0:38:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- What's the part you want? - You don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.04,0:39:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My parents were born in Iran.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.63,0:39:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They came here like everybody else,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.41,0:39:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}for freedom,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.33,0:39:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but my dad works 60-hour weeks
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.79,0:39:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to determine tax loopholes for a millionaire art dealer.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.83,0:39:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My mom, she ran up loans into five digits
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.67,0:39:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to get an online degree.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.11,0:39:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They won't shut up about how great America is.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.31,0:39:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But they're gonna die in debt
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.42,0:39:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}doing things they never wanted to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.18,0:39:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There are how many billion people in this world?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.23,0:39:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}7.3.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.96,0:39:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Somehow you and I landed together...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.69,0:39:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Doing something impossible if we were alone,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.84,0:39:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}not to mention at the right point in history with the right resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.10,0:39:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We have what we've worked for right there for the taking.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.60,0:39:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We just need each other to see this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.12,0:40:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You come any closer, I'm calling the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.91,0:40:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hi, operator. I'd like to report an emergency.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.95,0:40:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I placed a malicious cd in my work computer,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.52,0:40:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and now this guy at the gym is saying hi to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.35,0:40:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm going home.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.16,0:40:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I need you to do something for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.66,0:40:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Call the girl who wants to be involved, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.24,0:40:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Her name is Angela Moss.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.60,0:40:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Let me give you her phone number.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.37,0:40:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen, pussy. If you don't do what I say,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.85,0:40:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}then the giant shit storm that rains turds later
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.53,0:40:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}will leave a trail of clouds in the sky spelling out your name.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.99,0:41:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Elliot? I wasn't expecting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.07,0:41:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm here for my appointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.49,0:41:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Well, you can slip in before my first patient.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.29,0:41:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You told me I should tell you the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.56,0:41:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.61,0:41:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Everything I say will still be protected and confidential?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.52,0:41:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've been lying to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.99,0:41:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't take my pills.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.60,0:41:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But you don't either.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.90,0:41:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your refill frequency for ativan doesn't match
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.06,0:42:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}your prescription divided by the dosage.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.45,0:42:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This morning...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.06,0:42:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You bought a tall hazelnut latte.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.92,0:42:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Paid for it on your evil corp card.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.87,0:42:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}By text, you justified the indulgence to your sister
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.51,0:42:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}because evil corp gives you double rewards.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.13,0:42:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But those points only accumulate on travel expenses.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.70,0:42:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're not good with money.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.41,0:42:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}On paper, your Thursday 2:00, Marilyn O'Brien,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.82,0:42:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}is your doppelganger.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.41,0:42:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think you're encouraging her
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.83,0:42:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to leave her husband...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.94,0:42:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Because you're tired of being dumped.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.92,0:42:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You like porn, especially anal.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.83,0:42:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Whether you like it yourself, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.09,0:42:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's not relevant to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.88,0:42:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You've told your best friend Jennifer
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.75,0:42:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that you wish your mom would die.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.83,0:43:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I sometimes watch you on your webcam.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.29,0:43:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You cry sometimes...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.50,0:43:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Just like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.76,0:43:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Because you're lonely.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.48,0:43:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't just hack you, Krista.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.27,0:43:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I hack everyone--
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.24,0:43:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My friends, coworkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.65,0:43:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But I've helped a lot of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.47,0:43:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.47,0:43:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A way out of loneliness...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.42,0:43:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.41,0:44:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is that what you wanted to hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:13.00,0:44:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(100,300)}
