1
00:07:16,490 --> 00:07:18,500
艾薩克的三星S5

2
00:07:23,000 --> 00:07:24,340
華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞:科爾比是否牽連其中?

3
00:07:28,170 --> 00:07:30,090
在地下水和飲用水中發現污染物

4
00:07:28,460 --> 00:07:30,090
對健康造成一定的不利影響

5
00:07:39,520 --> 00:07:39,930
第7條 環境保護
第26章 固體廢料
第1分章 總則

6
00:07:42,480 --> 00:07:44,900
有證據表明 我們的員工的健康受到了不利影響

7
00:07:47,860 --> 00:07:49,030
貝克特律師

8
00:11:39,010 --> 00:11:40,630
點擊此處 免費獲取價值100美元
eTunes禮品卡

9
00:11:42,510 --> 00:11:45,800
問題1 你目前更喜歡哪一類音樂   搖滾  饒舌

10
00:11:42,510 --> 00:11:45,800
搖滾

11
00:11:42,510 --> 00:11:45,800
饒舌

12
00:11:45,800 --> 00:11:46,760
問題2 你更喜歡哪一流派的饒舌音樂

13
00:11:45,800 --> 00:11:46,760
硬核

14
00:11:45,800 --> 00:11:46,760
嘻哈

15
00:11:51,890 --> 00:11:53,310
問題3 最喜歡Wu-Tang Clan組合中的哪一位成員

16
00:11:58,230 --> 00:11:59,780
惡意軟件 被攔截

17
00:11:58,230 --> 00:11:59,780
avast!文件系統防護 已攔截一個威脅

18
00:11:58,230 --> 00:11:59,780
無需進一步操作

35
00:43:41,900 --> 00:44:07,000
本字幕由大家字幕組原創翻譯
僅供學習使用 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
彼以國士待我 我以國士待之
用過免費優質字幕服務 而又有能力的人
有義務將這個免費服務做下去 若有心加入我們
請聯系QQ群：428872140

36
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:02,140
機器人先生 前情提要

37
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:02,140
大家字幕組 傾情譯制

38
00:01:23,670 --> 00:01:32,800
機器人先生

39
00:01:23,670 --> 00:01:32,590
第一季  第六集

40
00:00:27,000 --> 00:00:29,000
翻譯    顧顧  子虛烏有  墳老絲

41
00:00:29,000 --> 00:00:31,000
翻譯    顧顧  子虛烏有  墳老絲

42
00:00:31,000 --> 00:00:33,000
翻譯    兔八哥  零零七  薇薇

43
00:00:33,000 --> 00:00:35,000
翻譯    兔八哥  零零七  薇薇

44
00:00:35,000 --> 00:00:37,000
校對    Libear  寶馬蹄前大命狒

45
00:00:37,000 --> 00:00:39,000
校對    Libear  寶馬蹄前大命狒

46
00:00:39,000 --> 00:00:41,000
時間軸    嵬森  拉面

47
00:00:41,000 --> 00:00:43,000
時間軸    嵬森  拉面

48
00:00:43,000 --> 00:00:45,000
壓制    JEV

49
00:00:45,000 --> 00:00:47,000
壓制    JEV

50
00:00:47,000 --> 00:00:49,000
監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森

51
00:00:49,000 --> 00:00:51,000
監制    LilBear  寶馬蹄前大命狒  嵬森

52
00:21:17,790 --> 00:21:19,210
他什么都知道

53
00:21:20,340 --> 00:21:22,260
我跟你說了他很危險

54
00:21:23,090 --> 00:21:26,340
我差點就搞定她了!她腿都張開了!

55
00:21:28,970 --> 00:21:31,640
很明顯不夠開

56
00:21:38,480 --> 00:21:41,110
這下我-我們-冒了太大的風險

57
00:21:41,820 --> 00:21:43,780
這事躲不掉了

58
00:21:44,360 --> 00:21:46,530
我越界了 我需要退一步緩一緩

59
00:21:47,030 --> 00:21:47,780
保持耐心

60
00:21:53,660 --> 00:21:58,040
你都快失去控制了

61
00:21:59,290 --> 00:22:02,590
要耐心 是的 但是不能膽怯

62
00:22:02,920 --> 00:22:05,380
實際上 她的行為可能對我們有所幫助

63
00:22:06,470 --> 00:22:07,970
幫了我們什么

64
00:22:09,050 --> 00:22:10,640
現在我們知道了她的需求

65
00:22:12,560 --> 00:22:13,600
什么需求

66
00:22:15,810 --> 00:22:18,060
被需求的需求

67
00:00:02,220 --> 00:00:04,140
你跟維拉被逮捕這件事可有關聯?
Did you have something to do with Vera getting busted?

68
00:00:04,140 --> 00:00:05,400
誰讓你把你的生意
Who told you to put your business

69
00:00:05,400 --> 00:00:07,150
放到社交網絡上去的?
anywhere near social media?

70
00:00:07,210 --> 00:00:09,550
我那上進的弟弟
My aspirational little brother.

71
00:00:10,110 --> 00:00:11,880
看來有人要因此受些皮肉之苦了
Someone's gonna get hurt for this.

72
00:00:12,030 --> 00:00:13,000
安吉拉怎么了?
What happened to Angela?

73
00:00:13,000 --> 00:00:15,660
在這個層面上 她對我們毫無用武之地
She's not going to work out for us, not on this level.

74
00:00:15,820 --> 00:00:17,480
你當時并不用站出來幫我的
You didn't have to stick up for me in there.

75
00:00:17,560 --> 00:00:18,540
別再這么做了
Don't do it again.

76
00:00:18,600 --> 00:00:21,530
邪惡公司想挖你去當首席技術官 對嗎?
Evil corp tapped you for CTO, yes?

77
00:00:22,760 --> 00:00:23,550
你這是在毀了自己的生活
You're ruining your life.

78
00:00:23,550 --> 00:00:25,220
我也一起毀了你的
I also ruined yours.

79
00:00:25,390 --> 00:00:28,120
泰利 科爾比參與包庇
Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up of

80
00:00:28,200 --> 00:00:31,290
華盛頓鎮有毒廢料丑聞
The Washington Township toxic waste scandal.

81
00:00:31,370 --> 00:00:31,950
夏倫?
Sharon?

82
00:00:32,010 --> 00:00:34,970
嫁給這種人 你竟然沒有開槍自殺?
How do you not blow your brains out being married to him?

83
00:00:35,050 --> 00:00:36,220
我在這里
I'm in here.

84
00:00:38,860 --> 00:00:40,670
你介意今晚睡這里嗎?
Would you mind sleeping here tonight?

85
00:00:40,870 --> 00:00:42,600
那邊那個女孩是我的
That girl in there is mine.

86
00:00:42,650 --> 00:00:43,630
今晚你要是在附近的話
If you're around tonight,

87
00:00:43,680 --> 00:00:45,260
就過來親自告訴我吧
come over and tell me about it.

88
00:00:49,160 --> 00:00:50,020
夏拉?
Shayla?

89
00:00:50,590 --> 00:00:53,630
有時候 宇宙的排列組合真是奇妙無比
Sometimes the universe aligns perfectly.

90
00:00:53,870 --> 00:00:55,520
現在 我被關起來了
Here I am, locked away.

91
00:00:55,680 --> 00:00:58,060
但是 手機能讓我找到你
Still, it brings you right to me.

92
00:01:07,380 --> 00:01:08,810
我有一種感覺
I feel the sensation.

93
00:01:09,020 --> 00:01:10,190
戰斗還是逃跑
Fight or flight.

94
00:01:10,490 --> 00:01:11,710
持續不斷地出現
It's constant.

95
00:01:12,890 --> 00:01:14,110
我應該從中選擇其一
I should just pick one.

96
00:01:15,310 --> 00:01:18,490
我 伊利艾特 奧爾德森 選擇戰斗
I, Elliot Alderson, am flight.

97
00:01:19,200 --> 00:01:20,120
我就是恐懼
I am fear.

98
00:01:20,520 --> 00:01:23,720
也是焦慮 可怕 恐慌
I am anxiety, terror, panic.

99
00:01:41,480 --> 00:01:42,880
我覺得這好不真實
Doesn't feel real.

100
00:01:48,190 --> 00:01:49,040
你應該吃點東西
You should eat.

101
00:01:51,290 --> 00:01:52,330
我不餓
Not hungry.

102
00:01:52,430 --> 00:01:54,250
我都不知道我點了些什么
I don't know what I ordered.

103
00:01:57,640 --> 00:01:59,180
抱歉
I'm sorry.

104
00:02:09,070 --> 00:02:10,600
你不喜歡墨西哥燉肉嗎?
You don't like the guisado?

105
00:02:11,130 --> 00:02:13,320
不 它 它很好吃
No, it's--it's good.

106
00:02:13,370 --> 00:02:14,440
謝謝
Thank you.

107
00:02:27,110 --> 00:02:28,440
你在想什么?
What are you thinking about?

108
00:02:31,500 --> 00:02:32,810
我們的初遇
First time we met.

109
00:02:35,440 --> 00:02:37,080
倒也不覺得是很久之前
Doesn't feel that long ago.

110
00:02:40,040 --> 00:02:41,600
看看我們現在
Now look at us.

111
00:02:42,600 --> 00:02:43,840
誰又能想到呢?
Who would have thought?

112
00:02:47,630 --> 00:02:49,790
如果我能回去并還原一切——
If I could go back and undo this--

113
00:02:49,840 --> 00:02:50,820
你不能
You can't.

114
00:02:53,980 --> 00:02:55,470
你答應我了
You promised me.

115
00:02:56,280 --> 00:02:58,240
我會讓你擺脫困境的 知道嗎?
I'm gonna get you out of this, okay?

116
00:02:58,300 --> 00:02:59,310
時間到了
Time's up.

117
00:03:00,370 --> 00:03:01,210
我們走
Let's go.

118
00:03:01,260 --> 00:03:02,240
伊利艾特!
Elliot!

119
00:03:02,510 --> 00:03:04,520
坐下 給我坐下
Sit down. Sit down.

120
00:03:12,480 --> 00:03:13,320
跟我走
Come with me.

121
00:03:15,370 --> 00:03:16,260
走吧
Let's go.

122
00:03:47,980 --> 00:03:49,890
- 你好? -  你名字的來源
- Hello? - The origin of your name.

123
00:03:49,980 --> 00:03:51,490
我特意為你去查了資料 老兄
I looked it up for you, bruh.

124
00:03:51,550 --> 00:03:52,870
你把她帶去哪里了?
Where are you taking her?

125
00:03:53,640 --> 00:03:54,640
伊利艾特
Elliot.

126
00:03:55,040 --> 00:03:57,480
"勇敢與真實"
"Brave and true."

127
00:03:58,170 --> 00:04:01,750
你知道"勇敢"是由"野蠻"進化來的嗎?
Did you know the origin of "Brave" Evolved from "Savage"?

128
00:04:01,820 --> 00:04:03,900
我不知道你是怎樣看待這一切的
I don't know what you think this is about,

129
00:04:04,370 --> 00:04:05,960
但你必須放她走
but you need to let her go.

130
00:04:06,040 --> 00:04:07,310
說件有意思的事給你聽
You know, funny thing.

131
00:04:07,570 --> 00:04:09,510
我的名字也有著跟你差不多的意思
My name means something similar.

132
00:04:09,570 --> 00:04:11,280
勇敢的旅人
Brave traveler.

133
00:04:11,650 --> 00:04:12,830
冒險家
Adventurer.

134
00:04:12,970 --> 00:04:16,470
野蠻的旅人成為了勇敢的旅行者
Savage traveler becomes brave traveler.

135
00:04:16,700 --> 00:04:20,540
我們究竟是野蠻呢 還是勇敢呢?
Are we savages, or are we brave?

136
00:04:21,280 --> 00:04:22,510
我也不知道 兄弟
Don't know, bro.

137
00:04:22,590 --> 00:04:24,210
聽我說 哥們
Listen to me, man.

138
00:04:26,380 --> 00:04:29,990
當我發現是你做了這一切時 我沒有生氣
When I found out you did this, I didn't get angry.

139
00:04:30,150 --> 00:04:32,700
你倒是給我留下了深刻印象
I got impressed.

140
00:04:32,920 --> 00:04:33,930
你的力量
Your power.

141
00:04:34,640 --> 00:04:36,100
我想要它 伊利艾特
I want it, Elliot.

142
00:04:36,200 --> 00:04:38,480
我太想要它了 想得我吊都硬了
And I want it so bad it makes my dick hard.

143
00:04:38,580 --> 00:04:39,930
我今天就要擁有它
And I want it today.

144
00:04:41,070 --> 00:04:42,250
我不知道你認為我能做什么
I don't know what you think I can do.

145
00:04:42,400 --> 00:04:44,380
我并不能用我的黑客技能直接帶你出獄
I can't just hack you out of prison.

146
00:04:45,140 --> 00:04:48,090
不是所有的監獄都有聯網 即便你的監獄有網絡
Not all prisons are networked, and even if yours is,

147
00:04:48,160 --> 00:04:50,800
找到安全漏洞也要花上好幾周
it would take weeks to find security holes.

148
00:04:50,890 --> 00:04:51,970
必須是今夜
Has to be tonight.

149
00:04:52,590 --> 00:04:54,480
我已經被狙擊槍的十字射線瞄準了心臟
I got crosshairs on my heart.

150
00:04:54,630 --> 00:04:55,710
出不去
I don't make it out,

151
00:04:55,910 --> 00:04:58,420
我就會死 但我的大限還沒到呢
I'm dead, and that ain't meant to be just yet.

152
00:04:59,440 --> 00:05:00,820
你做你的 兄弟
You do your thing, bro.

153
00:05:01,240 --> 00:05:03,060
你這是在強求我去做不可能完成的事
You're asking the impossible.

154
00:05:03,610 --> 00:05:07,380
我們今晚相見的時候 伊利艾特 我會擁抱你的
When we cross paths tonight, Elliot, I'ma hug you.

155
00:05:08,390 --> 00:05:09,920
聽我說 哥們
Please listen, man.

156
00:05:10,430 --> 00:05:13,070
夏拉——一切都是我的錯
Shayla--this is on me.

157
00:05:13,240 --> 00:05:14,130
知道嗎?
Okay?

158
00:05:14,230 --> 00:05:15,650
你必須放她走
You got to let her go.

159
00:05:16,120 --> 00:05:17,060
喔 就這事?
Oh, that?

160
00:05:17,400 --> 00:05:18,620
她很好 兄弟
She cool, bro.

161
00:05:19,010 --> 00:05:20,540
相信我 她好得很
Trust me, she cool.

162
00:05:20,910 --> 00:05:22,510
今晚她也會去的
She'll be there tonight too.

163
00:05:23,020 --> 00:05:24,940
這會是個大團圓結局的
It'll be one big happy happy.

164
00:05:28,430 --> 00:05:29,350
嘿 伊利艾特
Hey, Elliot.

165
00:05:30,550 --> 00:05:31,650
我愛你 兄弟
I love you, bro.

166
00:05:52,790 --> 00:05:53,780
夏拉在哪里?
Where's Shayla?

167
00:05:53,970 --> 00:05:55,100
老兄 最后警告你一次
Man, I'm not gonna tell you again.

168
00:05:55,200 --> 00:05:57,140
別再問這么多問題了
Stop asking so many questions.

169
00:05:58,930 --> 00:05:59,770
跟上
Come on.

170
00:06:04,990 --> 00:06:06,840
維拉也許是瘋了沒錯
Vera may be out of his mind,

171
00:06:07,150 --> 00:06:10,440
但是 黑進監獄網絡還是有可能的
but yes, it is possible to hack into a prison's network.

172
00:06:10,810 --> 00:06:13,770
大多數監獄使用常規的工業控制系統
Most of them use regular industrial control systems.

173
00:06:17,230 --> 00:06:19,640
我真不知道維拉看中這小子哪點了
I'm a blind man to what Vera sees in this dude.

174
00:06:19,710 --> 00:06:23,880
可不是 啥天才黑客 有我的多明尼加吊吊么
Amen. Techie computer hacker genius, my thick Dominican dick.

175
00:06:25,990 --> 00:06:27,340
你要是能掌控住工業控制系統
When you have control of that,

176
00:06:28,000 --> 00:06:30,360
基本上就掌控了監獄的各扇門
you basically have control of the cell doors.

177
00:06:33,150 --> 00:06:35,550
但這些白癡不知道的是
But what these morons don't know is,

178
00:06:35,930 --> 00:06:38,990
不事先做研究 根本不可能掌控住
it's almost impossible without any research.

179
00:06:39,520 --> 00:06:41,560
趕緊麻利地干活
Time to shine your cojones and get to work.

180
00:06:42,840 --> 00:06:44,030
俺們就一條規矩:
Our only rule:

181
00:06:44,400 --> 00:06:46,340
照我們說的去做
do what we say.

182
00:06:46,430 --> 00:06:49,440
你要是違反了這條規矩 俺們就讓你的妞去見閻王爺
You violate that dictate, we kill your sweetheart.

183
00:06:50,070 --> 00:06:51,310
喲 艾薩克
Yo, Isaac.

184
00:06:51,450 --> 00:06:52,770
我的龜-距怎么樣?
How my dic-tate?

185
00:06:53,530 --> 00:06:54,650
閉嘴 傻吊
Shut up, bitch.

186
00:06:56,160 --> 00:06:57,420
規矩
Dictate.

187
00:07:04,360 --> 00:07:05,920
維拉的兄弟 艾薩克
Vera's bro, Isaac.

188
00:07:06,530 --> 00:07:08,220
關于他 總有點什么讓我心煩
Something about him bugs me,

189
00:07:08,770 --> 00:07:11,090
你知道我喜歡怎樣應對這種情況嗎?
and you know what I like to do when that happens?

190
00:07:48,480 --> 00:07:51,000
你好 請幫我接貝克特先生
Hi, I'm trying to reach Mr. Beckett.

191
00:07:52,620 --> 00:07:54,720
拉蒂默先生什么時候有空呢?
When would Mr. Lattimer be available?

192
00:07:54,780 --> 00:07:56,010
我今天可以過來的
I can come in today.

193
00:07:56,160 --> 00:07:58,530
我已經告訴過你 是關于什么事情的了
I already told you what it's in reference to.

194
00:07:59,590 --> 00:08:01,570
我還是找納亞爾夫人
I'm trying again for Mrs. Nayar.

195
00:08:02,670 --> 00:08:05,200
關于華盛頓鎮丑聞的事情
Regarding the Washington Township Scandal.

196
00:08:05,290 --> 00:08:07,130
我可能發現了一些信息
I may have found some information.

197
00:08:07,160 --> 00:08:08,750
別又讓我等候接聽了
Please don't put me on hold again.

198
00:08:23,260 --> 00:08:24,770
周一愉快 安吉拉
Happy Monday, Angela.

199
00:08:26,710 --> 00:08:27,970
真是愉快
How fun.

200
00:08:30,060 --> 00:08:31,220
謝了
Thanks.

201
00:09:13,520 --> 00:09:15,420
我是艾蜜莉 莫斯的女兒
I'm Emily Moss's daughter.

202
00:09:16,320 --> 00:09:18,250
我叫安吉拉 莫斯 我打了
Angela Moss. I called--

203
00:09:18,320 --> 00:09:19,550
六次
Six times.

204
00:09:20,190 --> 00:09:21,120
是的
Yes.

205
00:09:21,220 --> 00:09:24,120
我是來討論華盛頓鎮一案的
I'm here to discuss the Washington Township case.

206
00:09:27,880 --> 00:09:28,880
我聽著呢
I'm listening.

207
00:09:31,270 --> 00:09:33,260
您當時代表受害人家屬
You represented the victim's families.

208
00:09:33,290 --> 00:09:35,390
26個家庭 包括我們一家
26 families, mine included.

209
00:09:35,780 --> 00:09:38,000
我是想 隨著近期數據轉儲引發的新聞
I thought with the latest news in the data dumps--

210
00:09:38,090 --> 00:09:39,640
泰利 科爾比的丑聞曝光
the Terry Colby scandal,

211
00:09:39,740 --> 00:09:41,570
他在掩蓋化學廢料泄露一事
his covering up the chemical waste spill.

212
00:09:41,680 --> 00:09:42,560
尚未證實
Alleged.

213
00:09:43,460 --> 00:09:45,430
好吧 但還有文件資料
Well, and documents.

214
00:09:45,500 --> 00:09:46,840
微不足道
Superficial.

215
00:09:47,210 --> 00:09:50,840
但是若是我們拿這個更加有力 強硬的案例
But if we bring this stronger, more concrete case--

216
00:09:51,760 --> 00:09:54,170
你就會知道我從這些數據里找到了證據
You'll see that I have the evidence from the data dumps.

217
00:09:54,640 --> 00:09:56,240
其他的是深入研究
Along with further research.

218
00:09:56,320 --> 00:09:57,520
還貼紙了
Stickies.

219
00:09:57,660 --> 00:10:00,080
哦 你還做了劃了重點啊
Oh, and you've highlighted and underlined.

220
00:10:00,720 --> 00:10:02,120
很認真嘛
This is serious.

221
00:10:06,220 --> 00:10:10,300
所以 你想把網絡流言呈上聯邦法院
So, you want to take internet gossip to federal court

222
00:10:10,380 --> 00:10:12,610
和人類文明史上最強大的綜合企業
and throw it at the strongest conglomerate

223
00:10:12,700 --> 00:10:14,430
對簿公堂?
in the history of civilization?

224
00:10:27,390 --> 00:10:28,620
西裝革履的男人
Guy in the suit.

225
00:10:30,070 --> 00:10:32,250
兩次因性侵犯被判有罪
Twice convicted of sexual assault,

226
00:10:32,400 --> 00:10:34,170
上周末又被控告
charged again this past weekend.

227
00:10:34,350 --> 00:10:35,830
強奸了他有孕在身的女朋友
Raped his pregnant girlfriend.

228
00:10:35,900 --> 00:10:37,980
用xBox把她的頭砸了個洞
Bashed her head in with an xbox.

229
00:10:38,060 --> 00:10:39,960
理由是她在打"光暈"(射擊游戲)的時候作弊了
Claims she cheated during Halo.

230
00:10:40,720 --> 00:10:43,340
然而我為他辯護 勝訴的幾率還要比你的高一些
Yet I have a better chance of defending him.

231
00:10:56,460 --> 00:10:57,480
但你回我電話了
You called back.

232
00:10:59,230 --> 00:11:01,240
我給本案相關的所有律師都打了電話
I called every lawyer from this case,

233
00:11:01,340 --> 00:11:03,650
只有你給我回了電話
and you're the only one that called me back.

234
00:12:00,730 --> 00:12:02,630
糟了 糟了 糟了
Shit. Shit, shit.

235
00:12:08,390 --> 00:12:10,620
遠程主機斷開連接
Connection closed by remote host.

236
00:12:10,680 --> 00:12:12,670
但魚兒已經上鉤了 我已經進入過系統
But we had a fish. I was in.

237
00:12:13,400 --> 00:12:16,970
程序跑了一半就停下了 是因為代碼寫錯了嗎?
The exploit started to run, and then--was it the code?

238
00:12:17,040 --> 00:12:18,330
小子 它要干嘛?
Brah, what's the deal?

239
00:12:26,090 --> 00:12:27,520
我得帶她出去溜達一下
I got to take her for a walk.

240
00:12:27,750 --> 00:12:28,460
為什么?
Why?

241
00:12:29,500 --> 00:12:30,930
要是不溜她 她就會尿在地板上
'Cause she'll piss on the floor if I don't.

242
00:12:30,930 --> 00:12:33,240
你的地板他媽的與我何干?
You think I give a shit about your goddamn floor?

243
00:12:41,820 --> 00:12:43,120
逗你玩呢 小子
I'm just playing, brah.

244
00:12:43,530 --> 00:12:44,780
去溜她吧
Yeah, you can take her.

245
00:12:48,130 --> 00:12:49,240
聽見我說了什么嗎?
You hear what I said?

246
00:12:49,550 --> 00:12:50,800
我說你可以帶她出去
I said you can take her.

247
00:13:02,050 --> 00:13:02,820
來吧
Come on.

248
00:13:15,640 --> 00:13:16,380
煙滅了
It's out.

249
00:13:16,380 --> 00:13:17,540
知道了
Okay, got you.

250
00:13:39,010 --> 00:13:40,640
她喜歡我送的小玩具嗎?
Did she like my little toy?

251
00:13:42,110 --> 00:13:44,140
那個釣魚程序是你一個人寫的?
Did you write that exploit yourself?

252
00:13:45,560 --> 00:13:46,670
就一個小時的時間
I had an hour.

253
00:13:46,940 --> 00:13:49,270
所以你的代碼都是東拼西湊出來的?
So what, you just pulled code from rapid nine or some shit?

254
00:13:49,360 --> 00:13:51,590
你怎么也開始亂來了?
Since when did you become a script kiddie?

255
00:13:52,230 --> 00:13:54,320
我再說一遍 我只有一個小時
I repeat, I had an hour.

256
00:13:55,130 --> 00:13:57,090
一定是被反惡意程序軟件滅了
Malware detection must have caught it.

257
00:13:58,150 --> 00:13:59,340
你把我害慘了
You fucked me.

258
00:13:59,420 --> 00:14:00,800
嘿 這事不賴我 成嗎?
Hey, don't put this on me, okay?

259
00:14:00,860 --> 00:14:02,180
這本來就是個爛活兒
This is a shit show

260
00:14:02,240 --> 00:14:04,310
而且你都沒給夠我時間來好好完成
and you gave me no time to do it right.

261
00:14:04,400 --> 00:14:07,230
要是給我正確的白皮書和足夠的時間
I can run circles around an ics given the proper whitepapers and time.

262
00:14:10,220 --> 00:14:11,580
你丫想去哪兒呢?
Where the hell are you going?

263
00:14:11,990 --> 00:14:14,120
我完全可以跟那兩個混球說
I have no problem telling these two douchetools

264
00:14:14,170 --> 00:14:15,140
在我們找到更好的解決方案前
they're gonna have to sit on their pricks

265
00:14:15,230 --> 00:14:16,930
你們還是乖乖坐等吧
till we can find a better solution.

266
00:14:17,000 --> 00:14:18,710
你不明白 這些人是
You don't understand. These guys are--

267
00:14:18,810 --> 00:14:21,370
混蛋? 沒錯 我要告訴他們實情
Assholes? Yeah, I'm gonna tell them what's up.

268
00:14:24,920 --> 00:14:26,080
實情就是這個 小妞
That's what's up, girl.

269
00:14:27,970 --> 00:14:28,930
好了 我們走吧
Now, let's go.

270
00:14:39,470 --> 00:14:42,550
所以那些人都沒給你回電話 拉蒂默也沒有?
So none of those guys called you back, not even lattimer?

271
00:14:43,010 --> 00:14:44,030
膽小鬼
Pussies.

272
00:14:44,100 --> 00:14:46,440
我猜他們都不高興去看那些數據轉儲
I bet they didn't even bother to read the data dumps.

273
00:14:46,590 --> 00:14:47,610
但你看了
But you read them.

274
00:14:49,160 --> 00:14:51,040
你知道嗎 在我們的案子被駁回后
You know it took me eight years

275
00:14:51,130 --> 00:14:54,160
我花了八年時間來重建我的事業?
to rebuild my career after our case was dismissed?

276
00:14:54,720 --> 00:15:00,390
雖然我認為這公司就是邪惡的化身
So, as much as I think this company is evil incarnate--

277
00:15:00,570 --> 00:15:01,980
相信我 他們肯定是
and trust me, they are--

278
00:15:02,640 --> 00:15:04,400
但這么做不值得
you know, it's not worth it.

279
00:15:09,500 --> 00:15:10,940
我們到底要怎樣
What would it take,

280
00:15:12,350 --> 00:15:13,980
假設的話...
hypothetically...

281
00:15:15,050 --> 00:15:17,280
我們需要些什么證據?
what do we need to prove our case?

282
00:15:17,340 --> 00:15:19,720
假設的話 我們需要一個可靠的證人
Hypothetically, a reliable eye witness.

283
00:15:20,040 --> 00:15:21,850
比如 如果你能奇跡般地找到一個人
You know, if you miraculously find someone

284
00:15:21,920 --> 00:15:23,420
一個愿意作證的內部人員
on the inside to flip.

285
00:15:23,760 --> 00:15:25,480
一個當時在決定制造關于
Someone who was there

286
00:15:25,560 --> 00:15:30,540
化學廢棄物的假消息的時候 在現場的人
when the decision was made to falsify chemical waste intel.

287
00:15:30,800 --> 00:15:31,930
所以說
So,

288
00:15:32,030 --> 00:15:36,060
除非你和他們其中的哪個人渣是社交網絡上的小伙伴
unless you're facebook friends with one of those assholes,

289
00:15:36,470 --> 00:15:39,210
這個假設也就只能假設假設
this hypothetical is just that.

290
00:15:42,320 --> 00:15:43,710
我們還是往前看吧
Let's move on.

291
00:15:44,320 --> 00:15:46,110
你最近在哪上班?
Where are you working these days?

292
00:15:47,000 --> 00:15:48,240
有男朋友嗎?
You have a boyfriend?

293
00:15:48,640 --> 00:15:49,840
你爸還好嗎?
How's your dad?

294
00:15:51,530 --> 00:15:54,690
我工作的公司不尊重我
I work for a company that doesn't respect me,

295
00:15:55,050 --> 00:15:57,560
我男朋友最近出軌了
my boyfriend recently cheated on me,

296
00:15:57,760 --> 00:16:02,020
我爸欠了一屁股債
and my father is drowning in debt.

297
00:16:09,130 --> 00:16:10,810
- 我們下次見 - 好的
- I'll see you next time. - Okay.

298
00:16:18,320 --> 00:16:20,300
熒光燈真讓人難受 是吧?
Fluorescent lights are hell, no?

299
00:16:23,690 --> 00:16:25,240
日程表臨時改了嗎?
Was there a change in schedule?

300
00:16:25,440 --> 00:16:27,260
我以為我下一個要見的是斯潘塞
I thought I had Spencer next.

301
00:16:28,470 --> 00:16:32,010
這些面試 簡直就是浪費時間
These interviews, they're just a waste of your time.

302
00:16:32,110 --> 00:16:35,690
我是說 你對監管和IP問題的情況了若指掌
I mean, you know our regulatory and IP issues inside out.

303
00:16:36,300 --> 00:16:38,180
要不我們今天就翹了吧
I was thinking we play hooky the rest of the day,

304
00:16:38,240 --> 00:16:39,510
去玩玩高爾夫
hit the back nine.

305
00:16:44,000 --> 00:16:45,400
你那是支江詩丹頓表嗎?
Is that a vacheron?

306
00:16:46,540 --> 00:16:47,940
是百達翡麗
Patek Philippe tourbillon.

307
00:16:48,030 --> 00:16:52,410
是一個王子送給我的 他是...
A gift from the prince of, uh...

308
00:16:55,530 --> 00:16:57,020
是誰有所謂嗎?
Oh, does it even matter?

309
00:17:03,370 --> 00:17:05,670
我不會取消剩下的面試的
But I'm not blowing off my remaining interviews.

310
00:17:06,830 --> 00:17:07,790
聽著
Look.

311
00:17:09,770 --> 00:17:13,040
我知道你以為你當定CTO了
I know you think you were a shoo-in for CTO,

312
00:17:13,860 --> 00:17:15,310
我知道你現在不爽了
And you're pissed.

313
00:17:16,710 --> 00:17:19,240
你說不定甚至希望我摔下地鐵軌道
Probably wishing I'd fall into the subway tracks.

314
00:17:20,890 --> 00:17:23,150
所以廢話少說
So how about you cut the bullshit?

315
00:17:25,500 --> 00:17:28,410
我想你是太多疑了吧 不過
I'm afraid your paranoia has gotten the best of you, but,

316
00:17:28,810 --> 00:17:30,590
盡管如此 失陪了
nevertheless, please excuse me.

317
00:17:30,670 --> 00:17:32,090
我就不打擾你回顧你的筆記了
I'll leave you to review your notes

318
00:17:32,200 --> 00:17:33,740
待會兒斯潘塞就來了
before Spencer arrives.

319
00:17:33,840 --> 00:17:36,110
對了 謝謝你邀請我參加晚宴
Oh, and thank you for dinner.

320
00:17:38,690 --> 00:17:39,890
我度過了一個美好的夜晚
The entire evening was enchanting.

321
00:17:39,980 --> 00:17:42,840
美食 美酒 美麗的夏倫
The food, the wine, the lovely Sharon.

322
00:17:45,100 --> 00:17:46,700
麻煩你代問她好
Please tell her I say hello.

323
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:51,410
你看得爽嗎?
Did you enjoy the view?

324
00:17:56,130 --> 00:18:00,380
怎么 你以為她不會跟我說嗎
What, do you think she wouldn't tell me?

325
00:18:03,960 --> 00:18:05,690
我不確定你到底想表達什么...
I'm not sure what you're trying...

326
00:18:05,770 --> 00:18:07,390
你是不是也想看我尿?
You want to watch me piss too?

327
00:18:07,650 --> 00:18:09,320
我可喝了好幾杯水了
I've had several glasses of water.

328
00:18:09,400 --> 00:18:10,380
斯考特 這中間有誤會--
Scott, a misunderstand--

329
00:18:10,480 --> 00:18:12,510
為了你我很樂意把我的老二掏出來
Happy to pull my dick out for you,

330
00:18:12,640 --> 00:18:13,710
如果你喜歡
if that's your thing,

331
00:18:13,990 --> 00:18:16,050
看諾斯一家小便
watching the Knowles family urinate.

332
00:18:16,650 --> 00:18:20,810
我甚至可以讓我兄弟從邁阿密飛過來
Hell, I could fly my brother in from Miami.

333
00:18:21,170 --> 00:18:23,260
他膀胱就像小屁孩兒一樣 尿個不停
He has the bladder of a small child.

334
00:18:23,610 --> 00:18:26,400
你看他尿一泡是不是直接就射了?
You'd probably bust a nut watching him take a leak.

335
00:18:26,990 --> 00:18:29,090
我不知道她跟你說了啥 我是你的話
I'm not sure what she told you, but if I were you,

336
00:18:29,160 --> 00:18:31,240
我會讓她好好地
I would tell her to find more appropriate ways

337
00:18:31,290 --> 00:18:33,290
控制一下她的想象力
of managing her imagination.

338
00:18:34,570 --> 00:18:35,580
提瑞爾
Tyrell.

339
00:18:36,390 --> 00:18:37,930
我希望你能接受殘酷的現實
I want you to accept a hard truth,

340
00:18:38,010 --> 00:18:40,490
就在這里 就現在 在我面前
right here, right now, in front of me.

341
00:18:41,690 --> 00:18:45,800
你當不成CTO
You are not going to be CTO.

342
00:18:48,410 --> 00:18:51,290
我就想在你臉上看到這樣的表情
I want to see that look wash over your face.

343
00:18:52,560 --> 00:18:55,480
只有這樣我才確定你會停止這些
It's the only way I know you'll stop playing these

344
00:18:56,560 --> 00:18:58,750
無比可笑的游戲
silly, silly games.

345
00:19:00,720 --> 00:19:04,140
哦 我非常明白你是CTO 斯考特
Oh, I am fully aware you're CTO, Scott.

346
00:19:04,890 --> 00:19:07,050
我不知道還能為你做些什么了
I'm not sure what more I can offer you.

347
00:19:10,040 --> 00:19:10,890
等等
Wait.

348
00:19:12,620 --> 00:19:13,590
來
Here.

349
00:19:17,380 --> 00:19:18,100
我很愧疚
I feel bad,

350
00:19:18,190 --> 00:19:20,470
畢竟 你是要當爸爸的人了
after all, you got a child on the way.

351
00:19:20,560 --> 00:19:21,800
你急需幫助
You need all the help you can get.

352
00:19:21,880 --> 00:19:22,720
實際上
In fact,

353
00:19:23,320 --> 00:19:26,090
這個可能會幫你把剩下的債都抵了吧
this would probably pay off the rest of your mortgage.

354
00:19:27,070 --> 00:19:31,420
你不是還住在切爾西區那個小巧玲瓏的兩室一廳嗎?
Aren't you still in that neat little two-bedroom in Chelsea?

355
00:19:35,310 --> 00:19:36,290
看
There.

356
00:19:40,600 --> 00:19:42,630
我要的就是這個表情
That's the look I was looking for.

357
00:19:52,780 --> 00:19:55,530
我頭都要想爆了 然而并沒有什么卵用
I keep brute-force thinking, but it's not working.

358
00:19:57,720 --> 00:19:58,720
我需要幫助
I need help.

359
00:20:12,700 --> 00:20:14,440
伊利艾特 你在嗎?
Elliot, you in there?

360
00:20:15,230 --> 00:20:16,210
操蛋
Shit.

361
00:20:16,330 --> 00:20:17,460
她來干嘛?
Why is she here?

362
00:20:19,390 --> 00:20:20,650
伊利艾特!
Elliot!

363
00:20:23,200 --> 00:20:24,590
讓我進來
Let me in.

364
00:20:27,200 --> 00:20:28,940
伊利艾特 你到底在不在?
Elliot, you in there?

365
00:20:31,220 --> 00:20:32,520
是個金發小美女
Little blonde bitty.

366
00:20:32,780 --> 00:20:35,470
伊利艾特 幫我開門
Elliot, hit the buzzer.

367
00:20:37,660 --> 00:20:38,890
我知道你在
I know you're in there.

368
00:20:38,990 --> 00:20:39,930
快去
Go.

369
00:20:40,270 --> 00:20:42,270
讓她閉嘴 把她給我趕走
Shut her up, and get her the hell out of here.

370
00:20:42,380 --> 00:20:45,030
伊利艾特 開門 現在
Elliot. Buzzer. Now.

371
00:20:45,780 --> 00:20:46,960
戴琳怎么辦?
What about Darlene?

372
00:20:47,270 --> 00:20:50,160
她留在這里 我們會盯著你的
She stays with us. And we'll be watching you,

373
00:20:50,400 --> 00:20:52,990
所以別他媽給老子耍花樣 你個臭傻逼
so don't bother trying any dumb shit, you dumb shit.

374
00:21:12,090 --> 00:21:13,800
你知不知道你為什么生氣?
Do you understand why you're angry?

375
00:21:15,640 --> 00:21:16,810
因為你知道我是對的
'Cause you know I'm right.

376
00:22:30,770 --> 00:22:33,180
那天晚上從吉迪恩那走后我到處找你
I tried looking for you after Gideon's the other night.

377
00:22:33,290 --> 00:22:34,350
你跑哪去了?
Where were you?

378
00:22:36,100 --> 00:22:38,510
我有些事情要想清楚
I had to think about things, you know?

379
00:22:40,550 --> 00:22:43,840
我們一直以來都清楚邪惡公司做了些什么
We always knew what Evil Corp did.

380
00:22:45,030 --> 00:22:46,420
只是我們沒有證據
We didn't have the proof,

381
00:22:47,690 --> 00:22:48,810
但我們知道
but we knew.

382
00:22:50,960 --> 00:22:52,620
我們一直是對的
We were right about it all along.

383
00:22:52,620 --> 00:22:56,100
那則新聞的內容對我們來說沒什么新鮮的
In fact, that news report wasn't a confirmation.

384
00:22:56,100 --> 00:23:00,560
但卻讓我怒火中燒
It was a reminder of how angry I am.

385
00:23:04,760 --> 00:23:08,380
你還記得負責那個案子的律師嗎 納亞爾？
You remember Nayar, the lawyer on the case?

386
00:23:09,280 --> 00:23:11,470
我去找過她了 伊利艾特
I went to her, Elliot.

387
00:23:11,470 --> 00:23:12,580
聽著 安吉拉 現在不是
Listen, Angela, now's not--

388
00:23:12,580 --> 00:23:14,800
我有一個討回公道的辦法
I have an idea that will change the world.

389
00:23:17,830 --> 00:23:19,460
我知道可能貌似行不通
I know it sounds really stupid,

390
00:23:19,470 --> 00:23:23,990
但我知道怎么去做
but I know how to do it.

391
00:23:25,580 --> 00:23:27,560
而且我覺得會有用
I think it could actually work.

392
00:23:30,610 --> 00:23:32,140
具體我現在不能告訴你 因為
I can't tell you what it is, because--

393
00:23:32,140 --> 00:23:33,730
邪惡公司 安吉拉 維拉
Evil Corp, Angela, Vera,

394
00:23:33,730 --> 00:23:35,970
他的兄弟 戴琳 夏拉
his brother, Darlene, Shayla.

395
00:23:36,060 --> 00:23:37,370
所有的事都撞一起了
This is too much.

396
00:23:37,860 --> 00:23:39,840
就說她想聽的給她聽吧
I should just tell her what she wants to hear.

397
00:23:40,780 --> 00:23:41,720
安吉拉
Angela,

398
00:23:43,020 --> 00:23:44,410
相信你自己
trust yourself.

399
00:23:45,780 --> 00:23:46,970
你的判斷是正確的
You'll do what's right.

400
00:23:56,130 --> 00:23:57,340
有你這句話就夠了
That's all I needed.

401
00:23:59,300 --> 00:24:00,770
順便問下 夏拉好嗎？
How's Shayla, by the way?

402
00:24:02,350 --> 00:24:03,390
她...
She's...

403
00:24:05,850 --> 00:24:06,740
你懂的
you know.

404
00:24:09,340 --> 00:24:10,720
替我向她問聲好
Tell her I say hi.

405
00:24:22,810 --> 00:24:23,920
你現在沒時間
You have no time to pull off

406
00:24:23,920 --> 00:24:25,580
來管你正關的這檔子事
whatever it is you think you're doing.

407
00:24:25,580 --> 00:24:27,140
你在這里干嘛？ 你怎么知道這事的？
What are you doing here? How did you know?

408
00:24:27,140 --> 00:24:29,340
戴琳聯系的我 這些家伙可不是鬧著玩的
Darlene. These guys aren't playing around.

409
00:24:29,340 --> 00:24:31,860
他們會殺了你 放聰明點 跟我走吧
They will fucking kill you. Now wise up, and let's go.

410
00:24:31,860 --> 00:24:34,140
我們不能走 戴琳還在上面
Darlene's in there. We can't leave.

411
00:24:37,240 --> 00:24:39,480
那好 我們叫條子來
Okay, then we call the cops.

412
00:24:39,480 --> 00:24:40,550
沒有其他的選擇
There's no other choice here.

413
00:24:40,550 --> 00:24:42,150
只能這么辦
It's the only way out of this.

414
00:24:42,370 --> 00:24:43,500
我不能報警
I can't call the cops.

415
00:24:43,540 --> 00:24:44,450
他們會殺了夏拉的
Shayla will die.

416
00:24:44,450 --> 00:24:45,640
偶 拜托
Oh, come on.

417
00:24:45,640 --> 00:24:47,460
她很清楚自己的處境
She knew exactly what she was getting herself into.

418
00:24:47,460 --> 00:24:49,840
你指望幫這種人干活還能長命百歲？
You think his employees have a long life expectancy?

419
00:24:49,840 --> 00:24:52,620
她和這瘋子沾上關系的那一刻 就半只腳進棺材了
She was dead the minute she started working with that maniac.

420
00:24:52,680 --> 00:24:54,580
別勸我了 我已經決定了
Forget it. It's not happening.

421
00:24:55,230 --> 00:24:57,000
這是一個零和游戲
This is a zero-sum game.

422
00:24:57,130 --> 00:24:58,800
你想想所有可能的結果
Calculate all the outcomes.

423
00:24:59,100 --> 00:25:01,030
如果你搞砸了他荒唐的要求 他會殺了你和夏拉
If you don't pull off this ridiculous miracle--

424
00:25:01,030 --> 00:25:03,420
而且你很有可能會搞砸 然后你就掛了 夏拉也是
and odds are, you won't-- you die, and so does Shayla.

425
00:25:03,420 --> 00:25:04,720
這我們都知道了
That much we know.

426
00:25:04,780 --> 00:25:05,660
假設另一種可能性
But assume for a second

427
00:25:05,660 --> 00:25:08,140
你成功把維拉救出監獄
that you do pull this off, bust Vera out of prison.

428
00:25:08,140 --> 00:25:10,820
誰又能保證他不會照樣殺了你和夏拉呢？
Who's to say he doesn't kill you, Shayla, Darlene?

429
00:25:10,820 --> 00:25:13,160
留著你們倆的小命對他半點好處沒有
It would be in his own best interest to do that.

430
00:25:13,250 --> 00:25:15,230
不管哪種情況 你都得死
Either way, you all end up dead.

431
00:25:15,230 --> 00:25:17,050
殺了你 維拉才會放心
It's the only way Vera wins.

432
00:25:17,340 --> 00:25:18,850
零和游戲  伊利艾特
Zero-sum, Elliot.

433
00:25:19,030 --> 00:25:20,540
你輸了是輸 贏了還是輸
You're playing a game you already lost.

434
00:25:20,540 --> 00:25:22,000
你知道我是對的
You know I'm right.

435
00:25:22,510 --> 00:25:24,110
肯定有辦法的
There's got to be a way.

436
00:25:25,120 --> 00:25:26,530
我能想出來
I can think of a way.

437
00:25:28,010 --> 00:25:29,170
我懂的 小伙計
I get it, kiddo.

438
00:25:29,740 --> 00:25:32,430
你想幫助別人  守護他們
You want to help people. Watch over 'em.

439
00:25:33,200 --> 00:25:34,990
但你能為夏拉做的
The best thing you can do for Shayla--

440
00:25:35,180 --> 00:25:37,460
就只有放手
allow her to become a memory.

441
00:25:38,980 --> 00:25:39,860
不
No.

442
00:25:42,110 --> 00:25:45,300
不自欺欺人是真正的勇敢
True courage is about being honest with yourself.

443
00:25:46,550 --> 00:25:48,360
尤其是面對艱難抉擇的時候
Especially when it's difficult.

444
00:25:49,570 --> 00:25:52,880
你和夏拉都能全身而退是不可能的
There is no plan where both you and Shayla survive.

445
00:25:55,350 --> 00:25:56,840
我能想出辦法的
I can think of a way.

446
00:25:57,380 --> 00:26:01,220
我們離創造一個新世界已經很近了 你死了就一切泡湯了
This new world that we are so close to creating will never be.

447
00:26:01,670 --> 00:26:03,240
那個新世界將代表你的成功
And that new world, that is success.

448
00:26:03,240 --> 00:26:05,780
F社會就是你的成功
Fsociety is success.

449
00:26:05,880 --> 00:26:07,680
想象你在鐵山取得的成功
Look at what you accomplished at Steel Mountain.

450
00:26:07,740 --> 00:26:08,740
那種爛尾算什么成功
That got us nowhere.

451
00:26:08,780 --> 00:26:10,230
你滲透成功
You took them down.

452
00:26:10,230 --> 00:26:12,340
贏得漂亮
You won that battle.

453
00:26:12,390 --> 00:26:14,400
但你現在這樣 只能算是失敗
This--this is failure.

454
00:26:15,850 --> 00:26:17,900
又變回以前的你了
This is the old Elliot.

455
00:26:17,990 --> 00:26:21,530
那個靠嗎啡和毒品來緩解內心無力感的伊利艾特
The one who turns to morphine, to drugs when he feels weak.

456
00:26:21,530 --> 00:26:23,770
一個懦夫 因為事實就在眼前
A coward who can't face the truth,

457
00:26:23,770 --> 00:26:26,400
你卻連看一眼的勇氣都沒有
even though it's staring him right in the face.

458
00:26:28,690 --> 00:26:30,540
那種感覺又來了
There's that sensation again.

459
00:26:30,740 --> 00:26:31,780
逃避或是抗爭
Fight or flight.

460
00:26:32,470 --> 00:26:34,970
連我在內 三條命有危險
Three lives at stake, including my own.

461
00:26:35,650 --> 00:26:37,880
我   伊利艾特·奧爾德森是
I, Elliot Alderson, am...

462
00:26:40,480 --> 00:26:41,340
什么？
what?

463
00:26:44,580 --> 00:26:47,860
湯姆拍迪 粉紅弗洛伊德 范海倫？
Tom Petty, Pink Floyd, Van Halen?

464
00:26:48,130 --> 00:26:48,460
你這人怎么回事
What's up, man?

465
00:26:48,460 --> 00:26:50,960
不聽德雷克 不聽皮普保羅? 那不就是什么都沒聽過嗎?
You ain't got no Drake, no Pitbull, no nothing?

466
00:26:50,960 --> 00:26:53,020
比如 怎么了？干什么
Like, what's up? What the--?

467
00:26:56,760 --> 00:26:58,140
雨人 出什么事了？
What's up, rain man?

468
00:26:59,300 --> 00:27:00,930
我準備去把維拉救出來
I'm ready to bust Vera out.

469
00:27:01,690 --> 00:27:03,380
我有辦法黑進監獄的網絡
I can get into the network.

470
00:27:03,410 --> 00:27:04,920
我們需要親自去一趟監獄
We need to go to the jail.

471
00:27:05,040 --> 00:27:05,980
現在就去
Now.

472
00:27:07,700 --> 00:27:09,020
她留在這兒
She stays here.

473
00:27:09,270 --> 00:27:10,350
不 我不會離開你的
No, I'm not leaving you.

474
00:27:10,350 --> 00:27:11,390
別擔心
Don't worry,

475
00:27:11,640 --> 00:27:14,040
沒人會聽他的
He's in no position to be giving out orders.

476
00:27:16,720 --> 00:27:17,780
我們走 小妞
Let's go, girl.

477
00:27:20,460 --> 00:27:23,540
你有過那種急中生智的經歷嗎？
Remember when the panic would set in and we had a solution?

478
00:27:24,090 --> 00:27:25,760
說實話 我懷念那種感覺
To be honest, I miss that.

479
00:27:26,250 --> 00:27:28,370
有時候麻木一點 生活反而簡單
Life is so much easier when you're numb.

480
00:27:31,270 --> 00:27:32,750
接下來怎么做 小屁精？
What's the plan, bitch boy?

481
00:27:35,600 --> 00:27:37,500
夏拉被抓 戴琳又被抓
First Shayla, now Darlene.

482
00:27:38,660 --> 00:27:39,680
嘿 什么鬼?
Yo, what the fuck?

483
00:27:39,720 --> 00:27:41,330
伊利艾特 你要干什么？
Elliot, what are you doing?

484
00:27:43,230 --> 00:27:45,660
就像一個被過高的電壓弄爆的硬盤
Like a hard drive blasted by excessive voltage,

485
00:27:45,720 --> 00:27:46,880
我內心煩操不堪
my mind is frayed.

486
00:27:46,880 --> 00:27:48,180
幾近崩潰
Close to fried.

487
00:27:48,810 --> 00:27:51,280
我能感受到數據在我的大腦中運行
I can feel the static running through my brain.

488
00:27:51,700 --> 00:27:54,120
血清素受體超時工作
Serotonin receptors working overtime.

489
00:27:54,170 --> 00:27:55,430
我需要更多時間
I need more time.

490
00:27:59,960 --> 00:28:02,540
今晚 今晚 今晚
Tonight, tonight, tonight.

491
00:28:02,540 --> 00:28:04,040
現在需要更多時間
More time right now.

492
00:28:04,880 --> 00:28:06,800
我們說話的當口我就在弄這事
I'm working on our project as we speak,

493
00:28:06,800 --> 00:28:10,010
所以 你最好保持給我的對話
so it's in your best interest to keep talking with me.

494
00:28:10,290 --> 00:28:11,210
在安保的桌子那邊
At the security desk,

495
00:28:11,210 --> 00:28:12,510
我的手機在運行一個
my cell phone is running

496
00:28:12,510 --> 00:28:14,400
他們無法察覺的活動信號嗅探器
an undetectable activated signal sniffer

497
00:28:14,400 --> 00:28:17,630
能夠定位這里所有無線信
that will locate any kind of wireless signal in sight.

498
00:28:18,060 --> 00:28:20,180
我離開這棟大樓的時候
By the time I leave this building,

499
00:28:20,320 --> 00:28:21,960
它的網絡就是我的了
I'll own its network.

500
00:28:23,350 --> 00:28:24,600
不錯啊
Good on you.

501
00:28:25,420 --> 00:28:28,480
很勇敢 但夠蠢
Brave, but stupid.

502
00:28:30,750 --> 00:28:34,790
你露了臉 然后今晚我逃走了
You showed your face, and then I skip out tonight.

503
00:28:34,870 --> 00:28:35,910
你知道他們會懷疑到誰頭上吧?
Who do you think they're gonna finger?

504
00:28:35,910 --> 00:28:37,750
我會打開所有牢門
I'm opening every cell.

505
00:28:37,920 --> 00:28:40,370
那樣 他們就不會找上你和我了
That way, they can't trace it back to you or me.

506
00:28:43,580 --> 00:28:44,750
是啊 兄弟
Yeah, bro.

507
00:28:46,370 --> 00:28:48,060
我就說了
That's what I'm talking about.

508
00:28:50,800 --> 00:28:52,340
我跟你說過 對吧?
I told you, didn't I?

509
00:28:52,620 --> 00:28:55,020
宇宙已經給我們哥倆計劃好了 要我們做點大事
The universe got big plans for us, bro.

510
00:28:55,110 --> 00:28:56,840
給我坐下來
Sit back down.

511
00:29:06,770 --> 00:29:09,290
我看等你出去 你要換個地方做你的生意
When you get out, I realize you're gonna have to split.

512
00:29:09,290 --> 00:29:11,720
你們不能再在三州地區活動
You won't be able to stay in the tri-state area.

513
00:29:12,750 --> 00:29:14,190
哦 那也很好啊
Oh, I love this.

514
00:29:14,200 --> 00:29:15,140
然后呢
Go on.

515
00:29:15,450 --> 00:29:16,840
不論你去哪兒
Wherever you go,

516
00:29:16,840 --> 00:29:18,860
你都要找到賺錢的營生
you're gonna need funding to keep surviving.

517
00:29:18,870 --> 00:29:20,250
這意味著你的所有運作
Which means your whole operation

518
00:29:20,250 --> 00:29:22,170
還是要能獲利
still needs to be making you money.

519
00:29:22,330 --> 00:29:24,300
直說吧 伊利亞特 你想說什么
Come on, Elliot. Give it to me.

520
00:29:24,470 --> 00:29:26,090
我黑了艾薩克的手機
I hacked Isaac's phone.

521
00:29:28,970 --> 00:29:29,590
那里面什么都有
He had everything.

522
00:29:29,590 --> 00:29:32,350
你的團隊 貨物 所有業務
Your crew, shipments, the entire operation.

523
00:29:32,350 --> 00:29:34,890
我都拿到了 我現在擁有你的真個世界
I took it all. I own your whole world.

524
00:29:41,770 --> 00:29:43,190
我需要你一句話
I need your word.

525
00:29:43,280 --> 00:29:46,170
等這事兒搞定 夏拉和我可以全身而退
When this goes down, Shayla and I go free.

526
00:29:46,490 --> 00:29:48,900
你永遠都不會再找我們
You leave us alone. Forever.

527
00:29:49,640 --> 00:29:51,030
如果有任何人企圖傷害我們
If anyone tries to hurt us,

528
00:29:51,040 --> 00:29:55,520
即使我看到你們有人跟蹤我 我也會把所有信息透露出去
if I even see one of your guys following me, I leak everything.

529
00:29:56,840 --> 00:29:57,760
你說這些話知道--
You're saying this knowing--

530
00:29:57,760 --> 00:30:00,130
你可能隨時會來殺我 我知道
You can kill me anytime, yes.

531
00:30:01,370 --> 00:30:04,010
所以我把信息透露設成了每天自動發送
That's why I coded the leak to auto-send every 24 hours

532
00:30:04,010 --> 00:30:06,360
除非我本人不斷中止它
unless I continuously disable it.

533
00:30:07,040 --> 00:30:08,650
除了我誰也沒有權限
No one else has access.

534
00:30:09,000 --> 00:30:11,960
如果我或者夏拉發生什么意外
If anything happens to me or Shayla,

535
00:30:12,340 --> 00:30:14,580
你的錢就全沒了喲
your money gets deleted.

536
00:30:19,780 --> 00:30:21,170
時間到 維拉 走了
Time's up, Vera, let's go.

537
00:30:27,870 --> 00:30:28,770
記住
Remember.

538
00:30:30,500 --> 00:30:31,580
我會擁抱你的
I'ma hug you.

539
00:30:58,050 --> 00:30:59,090
你有什么事?
So what's your deal?

540
00:31:01,900 --> 00:31:03,570
我是來見泰利 科爾比的
I'm hear to see Terry Colby.

541
00:31:08,480 --> 00:31:10,370
誰啊 又是個該死的記者?
Who is that, another damn reporter?

542
00:31:12,580 --> 00:31:14,280
我不發表任何評論 明白嗎?
No comment. Do you understand?

543
00:31:19,150 --> 00:31:20,240
我認識你嗎?
Do I know you?

544
00:31:27,430 --> 00:31:28,770
他媽的給我滾出去
Get the hell away from my home.

545
00:31:28,770 --> 00:31:30,320
從我家滾出去
Get away from my home.

546
00:31:38,080 --> 00:31:40,640
無線網絡安全防護? 我日
wpa2 wi-fi? Shit.

547
00:31:40,640 --> 00:31:42,310
邊界無法侵入
Borderline unhackable.

548
00:31:42,570 --> 00:31:44,670
想要連上可能需要好幾天
Getting that handshake could take days.

549
00:31:45,110 --> 00:31:46,560
這可怎么辦呢
The noose is tightening.

550
00:32:07,110 --> 00:32:09,060
警車上的攝像頭也是聯網的
The mobile feed on the cameras.

551
00:32:09,420 --> 00:32:13,000
對啊 如果有4g 就不用去黑無線網絡安全防護了
I don't need to hack wpa2 when there's dedicated 4g.

552
00:32:26,320 --> 00:32:27,240
問題解決了
We're good.

553
00:32:28,110 --> 00:32:29,450
我能把這個打開
I can pull this off.

554
00:32:32,050 --> 00:32:33,140
- 上車 - 我們走吧 姑娘
- Get in. - Let's go, girl.

555
00:32:33,140 --> 00:32:34,360
不 就他一個人
Nah, just him.

556
00:32:36,230 --> 00:32:38,380
- 呦 艾薩克 你是要做什么-- - 沒什么 兄弟 沒事
- Yo, Isaac, what you doing-- - Nah, bro, it's fine.

557
00:32:38,380 --> 00:32:40,380
我只是想和他單獨聊聊
I just want to have a private chat with him.

558
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:42,060
來吧 很有勁的
Come on, it's cool.

559
00:32:43,070 --> 00:32:44,250
我們沒時間了 伙計
We don't have any time, man.

560
00:32:44,260 --> 00:32:46,620
- 我也有事要做 - 趕緊他媽的滾上車
- I got to get to work. - Get the fuck in the car.

561
00:32:55,830 --> 00:32:57,110
嘿 你 要去那兒 要干什么?
Yo man, where you going, what you doing?

562
00:32:57,110 --> 00:32:58,750
沒事 沒事 就是說說話
All good, all good. Just gonna have a talk.

563
00:32:58,750 --> 00:32:59,800
你--?
Are you--?

564
00:33:13,720 --> 00:33:14,950
你為什么要這么干?
Why are you doing this?

565
00:33:14,950 --> 00:33:15,810
我可以讓你大哥重獲自由
I can free your brother.

566
00:33:15,810 --> 00:33:17,020
我已經搞出眉目了
I figured it out.

567
00:33:17,060 --> 00:33:18,760
是你今天運氣不好 兄弟
It just wasn't your day, bruh.

568
00:33:19,060 --> 00:33:21,620
我已經黑了你所有的生意 如果你殺了我--
I hacked your whole operation. If you kill me--

569
00:33:21,620 --> 00:33:22,380
你的所有生意也就抖沒了
You don't get it.

570
00:33:22,380 --> 00:33:24,600
我說過了 今兒是你運氣不好
Like I said, it just wasn't your day.

571
00:33:28,980 --> 00:33:30,040
停下
Stop.

572
00:33:37,000 --> 00:33:38,240
我猜有一顆子彈正平靜地等著
I suppose a bullet through

573
00:33:38,240 --> 00:33:40,100
穿過我的大腦
the brain is peaceful in its own right.

574
00:33:47,820 --> 00:33:49,430
你不想讓我救維拉
You don't want me to free Vera.

575
00:33:52,810 --> 00:33:54,520
這就是為什么你并不關心事情進展
That's why you don't care about the operation.

576
00:33:55,030 --> 00:33:56,340
臨終遺言還是說點別的吧
I'd pick better last words.

577
00:33:57,330 --> 00:33:58,540
你只想置他于死地
You're trying to kill him.

578
00:33:58,840 --> 00:34:00,760
維拉想要今晚行動也是因為這個
That's why Vera wants to leave tonight.

579
00:34:01,780 --> 00:34:03,810
這也是你一直以來讓我覺得心煩意亂的地方
That's what's been bugging me about you.

580
00:34:04,290 --> 00:34:06,100
你壓根就不想讓我把他弄出來
You never wanted me to break him out.

581
00:34:06,540 --> 00:34:08,710
為了自保你最好的選擇就是讓他死在監獄里
Your best option for survival is to kill him in prison,

582
00:34:08,710 --> 00:34:10,020
因為如果他不死
because if you don't,

583
00:34:10,090 --> 00:34:11,150
你也就活不了了
you're dead.

584
00:34:12,780 --> 00:34:14,540
是你讓維拉身陷囹圄
You're the reason Vera's locked up right now,

585
00:34:14,540 --> 00:34:15,660
而且他都知道
and he knows it.

586
00:34:17,180 --> 00:34:18,360
不管怎樣這些都不重要了
Doesn't matter anyway.

587
00:34:19,050 --> 00:34:22,920
維拉剛還洋洋得意的想著他的團隊如何如何
Vera was just gloating about how he got in with the right crew,

588
00:34:23,160 --> 00:34:25,100
想著他如何能騎在別人頭上為所欲為
how he got the jump on some men.

589
00:34:26,400 --> 00:34:27,520
他一點兒都不擔心 伙計
He's not worried, man.

590
00:34:27,520 --> 00:34:28,980
他現在是受保護的
He's protected now.

591
00:34:29,240 --> 00:34:30,390
放屁
Bullshit.

592
00:34:30,440 --> 00:34:32,690
這就導致你只有一個 一方收益另一方就損失 和為零的情況
That leaves you with a zero-sum game.

593
00:34:32,830 --> 00:34:33,960
如果你不把他弄出監獄
If you don't get him out of jail,

594
00:34:34,020 --> 00:34:35,590
他會殺了你 因為你失敗了
he'll have you killed for failing.

595
00:34:36,080 --> 00:34:37,660
這件事只有在一種情況下發生才對你有利
Only way this works in your favor

596
00:34:37,660 --> 00:34:39,180
就是你先把他殺了
is for you to kill him first,

597
00:34:40,470 --> 00:34:42,560
但是他在里面 你不能殺了他
and you can't do that with him inside anymore.

598
00:34:42,630 --> 00:34:43,930
閉你媽的嘴
Shut up, motherfucker.

599
00:34:43,930 --> 00:34:45,540
閉嘴
Shut the fuck up.

600
00:34:47,330 --> 00:34:48,420
讓我放他出來
Let me free him.

601
00:34:50,570 --> 00:34:52,420
當我今晚把維拉弄出去的時候
When I break Vera out tonight,

602
00:34:53,290 --> 00:34:55,110
你怎么處理他是你的事
you do with your brother what you want.

603
00:34:56,120 --> 00:34:57,400
這是唯一一種
That's the only outcome

604
00:34:57,400 --> 00:34:59,730
你還能繼續活著的結果
where you got the possibility of living.

605
00:35:02,810 --> 00:35:04,150
這是你最好的方法
It's your best move.

606
00:35:05,570 --> 00:35:08,160
你怎么知道事后我不會殺了你?
What makes you think I still won't kill you afterwards?

607
00:35:12,770 --> 00:35:13,850
我不知道
I don't.

608
00:35:15,370 --> 00:35:17,150
但這是我最佳的選擇
I'm just playing my best move.

609
00:35:44,830 --> 00:35:46,950
我需要大概30-40秒
I need 30 to 40 seconds with the patrol car's

610
00:35:46,950 --> 00:35:49,950
來和巡邏車藍牙連接上 運行黑客軟件
bluetooth connection to run the exploit on the plc.

611
00:35:50,760 --> 00:35:51,780
然后呢?
And then?

612
00:35:52,240 --> 00:35:54,440
9點49分計劃開始
The plan executes at 9:49.

613
00:35:56,080 --> 00:35:57,900
所有牢房的門都會打開
All the cell doors should open.

614
00:35:59,800 --> 00:36:02,320
嘿 我想跟你說件事
Hey, I wanted to ask you about something.

615
00:36:03,090 --> 00:36:05,020
- 是嗎 你想說啥? - 你
- Oh, yeah, what's that? - You.

616
00:36:32,810 --> 00:36:33,590
記得給我打電話哦
Give me a call.

617
00:36:33,600 --> 00:36:36,140
咱們可以一起喝點東西 聊聊天 隨便什么
We'll grab a drink, talk, whatever.

618
00:36:36,180 --> 00:36:37,200
好的
All right.

619
00:36:43,960 --> 00:36:45,430
軟件現在在他的電腦上運行了
The exploit's on his laptop.

620
00:36:52,570 --> 00:36:55,380
現在我需要逼它進入監獄網絡
Now I need to force-feed it into the jail's network.

621
00:37:00,450 --> 00:37:01,790
這些我喜歡
I like what I hear.

622
00:37:07,190 --> 00:37:08,480
我暫停了軟件的運行
I paused the exploit.

623
00:37:08,980 --> 00:37:10,040
開車吧
Drive.

624
00:37:10,680 --> 00:37:12,540
戴琳不再是計劃的一部分了
Darlene's no longer part of the plan.

625
00:37:13,280 --> 00:37:16,230
我們有一個警鈴被觸發了 東邊出口那里的
We got an alarm going off, east-side exit.

626
00:37:18,300 --> 00:37:19,660
臥槽這是啥
What in the hell?

627
00:37:20,770 --> 00:37:21,870
跟你說
Tell you what.

628
00:37:22,100 --> 00:37:24,430
咱們出去玩 喝喝小酒 跳跳舞
We go out, we drink, we dance,

629
00:37:24,600 --> 00:37:25,960
晚上看看優衣庫試衣間的風景
see where the night takes us.

630
00:37:25,960 --> 00:37:28,090
你確定你現在要做出這個選擇嗎?
You sure you want to make that choice right now?

631
00:37:28,610 --> 00:37:30,800
我只需要按一個按鈕來繼續運行黑客軟件
I only need to press one key to run the exploit.

632
00:37:30,800 --> 00:37:33,510
或者 我可以按另一個按鈕 撤銷整個計劃
Or, I can press another and disable the entire plan.

633
00:37:33,510 --> 00:37:34,630
我出了我的招
I made my move.

634
00:37:39,110 --> 00:37:40,240
你做你的選擇
You make yours.

635
00:37:47,920 --> 00:37:49,030
肏
Shit.

636
00:37:49,190 --> 00:37:50,580
小姐 請你往邊站點
Please move back, miss.

637
00:37:50,710 --> 00:37:52,100
我必須馬上回去
I got to get back asap.

638
00:37:52,280 --> 00:37:53,360
隨便你
Whatever.

639
00:38:01,400 --> 00:38:04,050
聽著 我得馬上回去了 我的電腦不運行了
Look, I got to come back now. My computer's on the fritz.

640
00:38:07,660 --> 00:38:09,050
咱們走吧 DJ
Let's go to the meet, DJ.

641
00:38:09,440 --> 00:38:12,590
如果我打錯一個指令 點錯一個鍵
If I mis-typed one command, hit one wrong key,

642
00:38:12,590 --> 00:38:14,160
監獄門就不會打開
the cell doors won't open.

643
00:38:14,570 --> 00:38:16,520
咱們倆都知道那樣會發生什么
And we both know what that means.

644
00:38:17,080 --> 00:38:18,220
我犯了一個錯誤嗎?
Did I make a mistake?

645
00:38:18,760 --> 00:38:21,950
不 我從不犯錯
No, I don't make mistakes.

646
00:38:26,440 --> 00:38:28,060
維拉還有一分鐘
One minute till Vera.

647
00:38:28,830 --> 00:38:31,480
無論他有多少瘋狂 多少沒人性的想法
For all his insane, inhumane ideas,

648
00:38:31,480 --> 00:38:33,520
他確實理解這個世界
he does understand the world.

649
00:38:34,310 --> 00:38:36,610
世界的殘酷
The wild savagery of the world.

650
00:38:44,070 --> 00:38:45,600
你用那個干干嗎 兄弟?
What you need your piece for, bro?

651
00:38:46,260 --> 00:38:48,570
奇妙男孩說他把所有監獄門都能打開
Boy wonder says he's opening all the cells.

652
00:38:48,620 --> 00:38:50,110
如果什么煞筆 朝咱們沖過來
If some fool tries to rush us,

653
00:38:52,060 --> 00:38:53,240
我想做好準備
I want to be ready.

654
00:39:11,970 --> 00:39:13,280
咋回事
Hey, what the shit?

655
00:39:13,840 --> 00:39:15,020
所有的牢房門同時打開
Power surge caused by all

656
00:39:15,020 --> 00:39:16,910
造成了對電力的需求激增
the cell doors opening at the same time.

657
00:39:16,910 --> 00:39:18,790
保安和警報怎么辦?
What about security? Sirens?

658
00:39:18,830 --> 00:39:21,550
監獄的網絡會顯示所有的老房門都是鎖好的 關住的
The jail's network will show all cells locked and closed.

659
00:39:21,890 --> 00:39:23,760
警報兩分鐘內是沒聲音的
Alarms are silent for two minutes.

660
00:40:02,670 --> 00:40:04,900
哈哈哈
Yes. Yes.

661
00:40:05,010 --> 00:40:06,210
這個
This shit right here,

662
00:40:06,840 --> 00:40:09,360
這比我草過的任何一個人都感覺好
this shit tastes better than any pussy I ever had.

663
00:40:26,680 --> 00:40:28,370
DJ 殺死這個屌絲
DJ, shoot the cocksucker.

664
00:40:43,520 --> 00:40:44,720
我的親兄弟
My own brother.

665
00:40:46,580 --> 00:40:48,460
這就是宇宙要求我做的
That's what the universe asked of me.

666
00:40:50,390 --> 00:40:51,760
做他監護人
To be my brother's keeper.

667
00:40:53,430 --> 00:40:55,110
像該隱殺死亞伯(創世紀中哥哥因嫉妒殺死弟弟的故事)
Like Cain after Abel,

668
00:40:55,310 --> 00:40:57,740
我會成為地球上的 一個逃犯 一個漂泊者
I'll be a fugitive and wanderer on the earth.

669
00:40:59,360 --> 00:41:00,860
勇敢的逃犯
Brave fugitive.

670
00:41:03,560 --> 00:41:04,880
勇敢的漂泊者
Brave wanderer.

671
00:41:06,570 --> 00:41:07,820
看看你怎么幫了我
Look how you helped me.

672
00:41:09,490 --> 00:41:11,800
這就是我欣賞的那種勇敢
That's the kind of bravery I've been talking about.

673
00:41:12,420 --> 00:41:13,640
但是現在
But now...

674
00:41:15,850 --> 00:41:17,720
現在我想讓你好好看俺艾薩克
Now I want you to look at Isaac.

675
00:41:19,880 --> 00:41:21,020
你看
Look.

676
00:41:28,510 --> 00:41:29,570
死證
Dead proof.

677
00:41:29,920 --> 00:41:31,710
我的行動結束了
My operation is over.

678
00:41:31,880 --> 00:41:33,570
所以現在上去  碾碎它
So go on, crash it.

679
00:41:33,570 --> 00:41:34,780
燒毀它
Burn it to the ground.

680
00:41:35,150 --> 00:41:36,110
都不重要
Doesn't matter.

681
00:41:37,720 --> 00:41:38,820
我走了
I'm gone.

682
00:41:40,910 --> 00:41:41,960
一個靈魂
A spirit.

683
00:41:42,890 --> 00:41:44,370
一個和所有天堂
One with all the heavens.

684
00:41:45,640 --> 00:41:46,740
所有的存在一起的
All existence.

685
00:41:52,290 --> 00:41:53,400
夏拉
Shayla.

686
00:41:55,070 --> 00:41:56,080
她在哪?
Where is she?

687
00:41:57,950 --> 00:41:59,030
鑰匙給我
Keys, yo.

688
00:42:00,990 --> 00:42:03,100
早跟你說了她會回到你身邊的 兄弟
Told you you'd get her back, bro.

689
00:42:05,150 --> 00:42:06,550
你就是沒有意識到
You just didn't realize

690
00:42:07,190 --> 00:42:08,960
全程她都跟你在一起
she was with you the whole time.

